<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Alphabet's third-quarter profit beats estimates: Alphabet Inc beat Wall Street estimates for third-quarter profit on Thursday, as the search engine giant's revenue from online advertisements soared. https://t.co/4vuKMoKqIU https://t.co/W9lSFOMvD0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mexico central bank says client resources not affected by insurer AXA cyberattack: Mexican central bank governor Alejandro Diaz de Leon said on Thursday that there is no indication that client resources in the financial system were affected by a recent… https://t.co/ddu5O8daUF https://t.co/HRr99vAl74]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elon Musk's SpaceX seeks $500 million loan via Goldman: Bloomberg: Elon Musk's rocket company SpaceX is looking to borrow $500 million in the leveraged loan market through Goldman Sachs, which is leading talks with potential investors this week,… https://t.co/fPC1ffzIBn https://t.co/rpqL3BwoEX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump signs order to set U.S. spectrum strategy as 5G race looms: U.S. President Donald Trump on Thursday signed a presidential memorandum directing the Commerce Department to develop a long-term comprehensive national spectrum strategy to prepare for… https://t.co/3lWsGIxcTx https://t.co/19MOXHEYgs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nokia kicks off new cost cuts, counts on 5G for profit boost: Telecom network equipment maker Nokia kicked off a new cost-cutting program on Thursday and repeated an ambitious profit forecast, saying operators' demand for next-generation 5G networks… https://t.co/FoQXr1KYAf https://t.co/M3A7q5rPGB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canon cuts full-year outlook on lean demand for cameras, chip equipment: Japan's Canon Inc on Thursday lowered its full-year earnings outlook for the second time this year, citing lower sales of single-lens reflex (SLR) cameras and lean demand for… https://t.co/6msN5BR5fE https://t.co/AgT8y2gkgU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China's Wingtech to gain control of Dutch chipmaker Nexperia for $3.6 billion: China's Wingtech Technology Co Ltd, the world's largest smartphone contract manufacturer, is acquiring Dutch semiconductor firm Nexperia Holding by buying a majority stake… https://t.co/hc1Phl913i https://t.co/qMHjaRTROM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South Korea's LG Electronics posts higher quarterly profit as mobile losses narrow: South Korea's LG Electronics Inc said on Thursday third-quarter operating profit jumped 45 percent as its mobile phone division narrowed losses. https://t.co/BuyBVmS9D3 https://t.co/FlNfXmrVkj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Telecoms group Orange says competition dented sales growth, confirms targets: Orange, France's biggest telecoms operator, strengthened profits in the third quarter despite heavy competition in its home country and Spain that dented sales growth. https://t.co/BKVHrFBtDN https://t.co/CyL26HDr6N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embattled BT names Worldpay's Philip Jansen CEO: BT Group Plc named Philip Jansen as its new Chief Executive on Thursday, ending months of speculation on who it would task with tackling a host of problems at Britain's biggest broadband and mobile provider. https://t.co/9CWzYGVlKk https://t.co/Bn5xxv14mW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LG Electronics' third-quarter profit rises 45 percent as mobile losses narrow: South Korea's LG Electronics Inc said on Thursday third-quarter operating profit jumped 45 percent to 749 billion won ($657.83 million) as its mobile phone division narrowed… https://t.co/l8ujQRVnxF https://t.co/z3WBTyYybJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canon's third-quarter profit drops, cuts full-year outlook: Japan's Canon Inc reported a 12.4 percent drop in third-quarter operating profit on Thursday, dented by lean demand for high-end cameras, and lowered its full-year earnings outlook for the… https://t.co/McUrvVDXRp https://t.co/LAoiQo6gX1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BT names Worldpay's Philip Jansen CEO: BT Group Plc named Philip Jansen as Chief Executive Officer on Thursday to replace Gavin Patterson after its chairman said in June a new leader was needed to restructure Britain's biggest broadband and mobile… https://t.co/7DLEz0S7Xz https://t.co/uXGn78bUfM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Learning Management System Analyst: Job Description Carpenter Technology Corporation is a leading producer and distributor of premium specialty alloys, including titanium alloys, nickel and cobalt based superalloys, stainless steels, alloy steels… https://t.co/boDQxUSyV5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China's Wingtech to acquire Dutch semiconductor firm Nexperia for $3.6 billion: China's Wingtech Technology Co Ltd, the world's largest smartphone contract manufacturer, plans to acquire control of Dutch semiconductor firm Nexperia Holding for 25.2… https://t.co/pZnwbgtdmR https://t.co/8zn7pDaRSn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla's Musk says Model 3 to be available in Australia around mid 2019: Tesla Inc Chief Executive Officer Elon Musk said on Thursday the electric carmaker's new Model 3 will be available in Australia around the middle of next year. https://t.co/t1athfAgJH https://t.co/BnHc908m2L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Telecoms group Orange's third-quarter core operating profit rises 3 percent: Orange, France's number one telecoms operator, reported on Thursday a 3 percent increase in its third quarter core operating profit, driven by continued growth in its home… https://t.co/0SMPvLdBAU https://t.co/4OkYR1XjBO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nokia kicks off cost-cutting plan after third-quarter profit drops 27 percent year-on-year: Telecom network equipment maker Nokia on Thursday announced a new cost-cutting program after reporting quarterly profits down 27 percent from a year ago. https://t.co/xwkgfaWhJK https://t.co/4aNi4f7ZC7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SK Hynix warns of more chip price falls, capex cut as trade tensions bite: SK Hynix offered a downbeat outlook for semiconductors on Thursday, warning prices of flash memory chips will fall further until early next year from over two-year lows, hit by… https://t.co/uMD9VGkI48 https://t.co/z05O4uEXqT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chinese EV startup WM Motor raising at least $288 million from Baidu, others: sources: Chinese electric vehicle (EV) startup WM Motor Technology Co Ltd aims to raise at least 2 billion yuan ($288.33 million) in its latest funding round to finance growth,… https://t.co/dV27dJAAkG https://t.co/qm8Zvffh05]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Specialist Developer ALM: Sr. Specialist Developer ‘ ALM (Asset and Liability Management) The desired candidate will work as a developer on our Asset and Liability Management (ALM) applications for the Treasury and Finance Group’s enhancements. The… https://t.co/xuamkLbWqS https://t.co/uhl1piKpnZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SW QA Engineer: Job Description SW QA Engineer Location: US-PA-Malvern Job ID: ****** Company: : ********** Services, Inc. Position Category: Systems, Quality, &amp; Security Engineering Company/Location (search) : Country (Full Name): : United States Job… https://t.co/gACi97K8Br https://t.co/XykuCoH0JV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smartphones emerge as bright spot for Indian manufacturing: Smartphone-maker Lava is a small player in India's booming mobile communications industry, but it has become a poster child for Prime Minister Narendra Modi's ambitious effort to make India a… https://t.co/xUswjkziwk https://t.co/0tZjahsqqu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South Korea's SK Hynix posts record third-quarter profit as chip outlook dims: South Korea's SK Hynix Inc posted record third-quarter operating profit on Thursday despite softer chip prices, beating expectations thanks to a seasonal sales boost for… https://t.co/5fhhvCGT6V https://t.co/8MHnBIh4CV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Broadcom facing EU antitrust scrutiny over market dominance: Bloomberg: Broadcom Inc is facing antitrust scrutiny from the European Union over the possible use of its market dominance to pressure customers to buy its semiconductors, Bloomberg reported on… https://t.co/Y6Ew48CDWg https://t.co/0fFbuQzanM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chipmaker SK Hynix posts record third-quarter profit: South Korea's SK Hynix Inc posted record third-quarter operating profit on Thursday, beating expectations thanks to a seasonal sales boost for mobile devices and strong server demand. https://t.co/JTMQevNdFC https://t.co/6szWfDmWEE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AMD revenue forecast disappoints as crypto demand subsides, shares plummet: Advanced Micro Devices Inc on Wednesday forecast fourth-quarter revenue below estimates as the chipmaker faces dwindling demand from cryptocurrency miners for its high-margin… https://t.co/hojWkQshNB https://t.co/EjRcW8T5zO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google, Facebook executives meet with UK government over no-deal Brexit: Telegraph: The UK chiefs of Microsoft Corp , Facebook and Alphabet Inc's Google met with British government ministers in London on Wednesday to seek assurances over the impact of a… https://t.co/yLIt3G46Bx https://t.co/LiXTExjCrF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google, Facebook executives meet UK government ministers over no-deal Bexit: Telegraph: The UK chiefs of Microsoft Corp , Facebook and Alphabet Inc's Google met with British government ministers in London on Wednesday to seek assurances over the impact… https://t.co/tkMIdsCN6f https://t.co/TL3BEz0B4f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Support Analyst: The Support Analyst provides support and maintenance to the users within the Company’s desktop computing environment. Responsibilities include the following: Installs, diagnoses, repairs, maintains and upgrades all PC hardware and… https://t.co/FzGgIqN0MY https://t.co/gvcUt6sceq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AMD revenue forecast disappoints as crypto demand wanes: Advanced Micro Devices Inc on Wednesday forecast fourth-quarter revenue below estimates as the chipmaker wrestled with waning demand from cryptocurrency miners for its high-margin graphic… https://t.co/EqKrhKLwof https://t.co/8iyjqbhxKd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The cloud floats Microsoft earnings again: Microsoft Corp beat Wall Street estimates for revenue and profit in its first quarter on Wednesday, as more businesses signed up for its Azure cloud computing services and Office 365 software. https://t.co/SDKfT4mfyH https://t.co/ZzwtuA4OCj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exclusive: Information technology company ConvergeOne explores sale - sources: Information technology services provider ConvergeOne Holdings Inc is exploring a sale after it attracted takeover interest from private equity firms, people familiar with the… https://t.co/kqytJX8Tl9 https://t.co/hNKMbrBZvM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla's Musk says Model 3 to be available in Australia, UK around mid-2019: Tesla Inc Chief Executive Officer Elon Musk said on Thursday the electric carmaker's new Model 3 will be available in Australia and the UK around the middle of next year. https://t.co/CNJxclLSZ0 https://t.co/ZWMVE7MbN6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla shares jump as Musk delivers quarterly profit, cash: Tesla Inc reported a net profit, positive cash flow and fatter-than-expected margins for the latest quarter on Wednesday, delivering on Chief Executive Elon Musk's promise to turn the electric… https://t.co/ZO6JvAPALM https://t.co/1K3yNuNYAw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AMD revenue forecast falls short of estimates, shares sink: Advanced Micro Devices Inc on Wednesday forecast fourth-quarter revenue below estimates as the chipmaker wrestled with waning demand from cryptocurrency miners for its high-margin graphic… https://t.co/K5nwCSCnFs https://t.co/nin8djx7st]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FCC to vote to allow U.S. devices to use European navigation system: The U.S. Federal Communications Commission said on Wednesday it will vote in November to allow U.S. devices to access the European global navigation satellite system known as Galileo, a… https://t.co/0CPhsqwyhB https://t.co/blGybDAeU9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Preferred Success Functional Specialist HANA and HANA: Preferred Success Functional Specialist – C4 HANA and S4 HANA Job Close By continuing to use and navigate this website, you are agreeing to the use of cookies. Accept – SAP Careers home – SAP… https://t.co/GcOtEe0QDQ https://t.co/uNCU3BFUKC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chipmaker AMD's third-quarter revenue rises 4 percent: Chipmaker Advanced Micro Devices Inc's quarterly revenue rose 4 percent, helped by higher sales of its processors and graphics chips used in computers and data centers. https://t.co/ODIRDo7zkG https://t.co/5UAgVPWT9v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla posts profit with Model 3 surge, shares jump: Tesla Inc made good on Chief Executive Officer Elon Musk's promise that it would turn a profit in the third quarter as it ramps up production of its Model 3 sedan, sending its shares up 7 percent in… https://t.co/C8fANt16By https://t.co/SikkHBqVbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla posts quarterly profit: Tesla Inc made good on Chief Executive Officer Elon Musk's promise that it would turn a profit in the third quarter. https://t.co/7Tw6SuVMgy https://t.co/OeGOsruba4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft results beat estimates on strong cloud growth: Microsoft Corp beat Wall Street estimates for revenue and profit in its first quarter on Wednesday, as more businesses signed up for its Azure cloud computing services and Office 365 software. https://t.co/ZYg0Rz9fLr https://t.co/1ItCvmJd7o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft quarterly revenue beats estimates: Microsoft Corp beat Wall Street estimates for revenue in its first quarter on Wednesday, as more businesses signed up for its Azure cloud computing services and Office 365 software. https://t.co/VcDPJWayFn https://t.co/8ZvI7dsmBq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook removes 8.7 million sexual photos of kids in last three months: Facebook Inc said on Wednesday that company moderators during the last quarter removed 8.7 million user images of child nudity with the help of previously undisclosed software that… https://t.co/a51ttGVlbU https://t.co/GCMGi8WRxU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snap hires Amazon, HuffPost executives to fill big roles: Snap Inc said on Wednesday it had hired https://t.co/XCGE1TBbK6 Inc's head of advertising Jeremi Gorman as its chief business officer and HuffPost media company Chief Executive Jared Grusd as… https://t.co/HZhak3u9DA https://t.co/cQWeCIyWui]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Autodesk, Flex veterans raise $179 mln for manufacturing startup: (This version of the Oct. 23 story corrects paragraph 4 to say McNamara is current Flex CEO rather than former Flex CEO) https://t.co/dkzZ79jAIe https://t.co/EC64RU96wq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla may post profit with Model 3 surge, investors look for more: Chief Executive Elon Musk may post a long-promised profit when Tesla Inc reports third-quarter results later on Wednesday, as production of the Model 3 electric sedan takes off, but… https://t.co/YRTDMatLJV https://t.co/J851PccvJj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pay-TV, Video-on-Demand outgrowing ad-funded TV in Germany: Pay-TV and Paid Video-on-Demand are expected to rapidly outgrow advertising funded TV in Germany this year, an industry association said, as commercial broadcasters struggle to compete with… https://t.co/Pny1tZm3Uo https://t.co/NJc2eKwnPE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senators question Google's tardy disclosure of user data exposure: Two U.S. senators said Alphabet Inc's disclosure of user data vulnerabilities at Google+ raised "serious questions" over whether it violated a 2011 consent decree with the Federal Trade… https://t.co/bxLx2A7jID https://t.co/DwyaKzTk3Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Point profit tops estimates, buys cloud security firm: Network security provider Check Point Software Technologies reported quarterly net profit that beat expectations and said it has acquired Israel's Dome9 to strengthen its position in cloud… https://t.co/mN1oFDwFXG https://t.co/I7YYJL64DQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AT&amp;T satellite TV numbers disappoint, shares fall: AT&amp;T Inc's quarterly profit for the latest quarter rose less than expected, held back by its declining satellite TV business, sending the company's shares down more than 6 percent. https://t.co/mMhltWELjI https://t.co/2u8WI3mUaI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Citron's Tesla U-turn dealt short sellers a $1.11 billion loss: The sharp surge in Tesla Inc's share price on Tuesday slammed short sellers of the stock with $1.11 billion in losses for the day on paper, pushing their performance for the year into the… https://t.co/WbTceLahL0 https://t.co/0I2qRKNuP6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two Democrats say Google+ data exposure may violate FTC consent decree: Two U.S. senators said Alphabet Inc's disclosure that private profile data of at least 500,000 users of Google+ may have been exposed to hundreds of external developers raises… https://t.co/htGgxrkFQZ https://t.co/LwFyezKv0b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla's Shanghai factory to produce two models for first phase project: filing: Tesla Inc's Shanghai Gigafactory is planning to produce two models in its first phase project, a Shanghai government filing showed on Wednesday. https://t.co/eOfqoL60OU https://t.co/2VSlRlx150]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Point profit tops estimates, buys cloud security firm: Network security provider Check Point Software Technologies reported quarterly net profit that beat expectations and said it has acquired Israel's Dome9 to strengthen its position in cloud… https://t.co/kcETIzBy6P https://t.co/k1uC6epNMB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Volvo Cars invests in BP-backed charging firm to lure electric buyers: Volvo is investing in a startup called FreeWire whose rapid charging systems for electric cars are being installed across BP gasoline stations in Europe this year. https://t.co/kJmSbD9Xpc https://t.co/rjrMDqPENW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GM's driverless car bet faces long road ahead: It’s one of the biggest bets going in the world of cars. https://t.co/Ukphv9nvnX https://t.co/TEwSghJs63]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chip stocks fall after Texas Instruments, STMicro warn on slowing demand: Semiconductor stocks slumped on Wednesday after Texas Instruments Inc and Franco-Italian chipmaker STMicroelectronics warned of slowing demand. https://t.co/LeWYZHaUJN https://t.co/gSxRZmHeBs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook unveils systems for catching child nudity, grooming of children: Facebook Inc said on Wednesday that company moderators during the last quarter removed 8.7 million user images of child nudity with the help of previously undisclosed software that… https://t.co/msC4Ole1yl https://t.co/WWWOSnWS6V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exclusive: Russia opposes U.S. OneWeb satellite service, cites security concerns: Russia's state security agency is opposing a high-level deal for the U.S. OneWeb satellite startup to bring Internet access to remote parts of the country because it says… https://t.co/KIm8nQs0cJ https://t.co/owfY5Dzitz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toshiba Memory to go public as soon as next autumn: Kyodo: Toshiba Memory Corp, the world's No. 2 producer of NAND flash memory chips, will go public as soon as the autumn of next year, Kyodo News reported on Wednesday. https://t.co/LV9zGNSpVm https://t.co/VfOXG0Rx5y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AT&amp;T misses profit estimates, shares fall: AT&amp;T Inc's quarterly profit missed analysts' estimates on Wednesday, sending its shares down 2 percent before the bell, even as it posted a surprise gain in U.S. wireless postpaid subscribers. https://t.co/VMaXHe726b https://t.co/SlZmA5jCdr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AT&amp;T posts a surprise gain in U.S. phone subscribers: AT&amp;T Inc on Wednesday reported a surprise gain in U.S. net wireless subscribers who pay a monthly bill, as it began to bundle media content from Time Warner into new wireless plans. https://t.co/l9WyNmvjTN https://t.co/trBp6wBsbj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why did Dyson pick Singapore to build its electric car?: When James Dyson, the billionaire British inventor of the bagless vacuum cleaner, unveiled a plan to build an electric car plant in Singapore, it raised a few eyebrows. https://t.co/GR4ZgRsckO https://t.co/EAeAPqn8Xu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla may post profit with Model 3 surge, but is it repeatable?: When Tesla Inc posts third-quarter results on Wednesday, Chief Executive Elon Musk may show off a long-promised quarterly profit, as production of his Model 3 electric sedan takes off. But… https://t.co/rDfyifKw4D https://t.co/lEIG4SjZ7d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple boss takes aim at 'weaponization' of customer data: Apple Chief Executive Tim Cook said on Wednesday customer data was being "weaponized with military efficiency" by companies to increase profit. https://t.co/P6fMt0Cjwt https://t.co/yNpr7LNONC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Italian watchdog fines Apple, Samsung over software updates: Italy's anti-trust watchdog said on Wednesday it was fining Apple Inc. and Samsung Electronics Co Ltd 5 million euros ($5.7 million) each following complaints they used software updates to slow… https://t.co/LDInIKX2wF https://t.co/9nf3zJZHUd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla hikes new Model 3 price by $1,000: Tesla Inc has increased the price for its new Model 3 sedan launched last week by $1,000 to $46,000, according to the company's website. https://t.co/EtuyfaO42F https://t.co/3KWDs5IREl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Point Software third quarter profit up, acquires cloud security firm: Network security provider Check Point Software Technologies reported third quarter net profit that beat expectations and said it has acquired Israel's Dome9 to strengthen its… https://t.co/lV8aeVaVbQ https://t.co/2znILOLD0c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Product Manager, SAP Ariba Connect the Help Center Job: Requisition ID: ****** Work Area: Customer Service and Support Expected Travel: 0 – 10% Career Status: Professional Employment Type: Regular Full Time COMPANY DESCRIPTION SAP started in 1972 as a… https://t.co/F2l3UsvbCx https://t.co/i0Z3m8rhYM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Japan grants cryptocurrency industry self-regulatory status: Japan's Financial Services Agency (FSA) on Wednesday gave the cryptocurrency industry self-regulatory status, permitting the , Japan Virtual Currency Exchange Association to police and sanction… https://t.co/r34zIYSPlA https://t.co/nCdM1u1ePU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. firm to start building hyperloop track in Abu Dhabi next year: A U.S. company plans to start building an ultra-fast hyperloop track for Abu Dhabi's transport system in the third quarter of 2019, it said on Wednesday. https://t.co/du88qOE1PX https://t.co/z7S20pDqGD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worries on demand, profit outlook and trade dent global tech shares: Global tech stocks have lost about $1 trillion or 9 percent of market value this month, Refinitiv data showed, hurt by worries over slowing global demand, valuations and trade tensions… https://t.co/zgQ3bpgHfg https://t.co/XGgnsqLL0V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Optimization Developer (Mobile Hardware): Company Description Bosch Security Systems in Pittsburgh (in trendy ‘strip’ area) is focused on the research and development of cutting-edge technologies that will shape the future of the company’s… https://t.co/Oqgkp4J5Cg https://t.co/1bTsFmEaUc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[STMicro upholds bullish 2018 growth target on strong automotive, imaging sales: Franco-Italian chipmaker STMicroelectronics upheld its bullish growth target for 2018 on Wednesday, bolstered by strong demand from the car and smartphone industries for its… https://t.co/tjpm3iW9fa https://t.co/GYC6Zavvef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[STMicro third-quarter profits rise on strong automotive, imaging sales: Franco-Italian chipmaker STMicroelectronics reported a jump in third-quarter sales and profits, driven by a strong performance of its automotive and imaging businesses. https://t.co/1xDOVutHQh https://t.co/0HEbvzgsZA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst IT Intern: Job/Internship Description COMPANY PROFILE The Access segment consists of the JLG and Jerr-Dan business units. At JLG, we are committed to being the provider of choice worldwide for access equipment. The Company’s diverse… https://t.co/QLqLcLzt9a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CityFibre to invest 2.5 billion pounds in full-fiber for UK homes: CityFibre, a British broadband operator backed by Goldman Sachs, said it would spend 2.5 billion pounds ($3.25 billion) on rolling out fiber networks in 37 towns and cities, offering… https://t.co/cvS3FbfSPG https://t.co/UXMNPHNeXL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cathay Pacific flags data breach affecting 9.4 million passengers: Cathay Pacific Airways Ltd said on Wednesday that data of about 9.4 million passengers of Cathay and its unit Hong Kong Dragon Airlines Limited had been accessed without authorisation. https://t.co/yZspglpTjR https://t.co/g3qqslIvMG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Analyst: The Systems Analyst will be responsible for participating in all phases of the System Development Life Cycle (Planning, Analysis, Design, Build, Test, Deployment, and Maintenance). This is a ‘hands-on’ position requiring technical skills… https://t.co/Gfq3Lp4x0m https://t.co/AmNTbvBqrf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Target expands delivery, pickup options ahead of U.S. holiday season: Target Corp, aiming to one-up retail rivals during the upcoming U.S. holiday shopping season, said on Tuesday it was adding more delivery and pickup options for online shoppers to have… https://t.co/AWU6nSQ9JR https://t.co/jtFt0L2iA3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Despite Brazil election turmoil, Facebook stands by WhatsApp limits: Facebook Inc's messaging service WhatsApp has no plans to change its group messaging limits in Brazil, an executive said on Tuesday, resisting calls from the leading presidential… https://t.co/jObaB8tsjb https://t.co/zIkJ22GkeO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FCC moves to open more spectrum to connected devices: The U.S. Federal Communications Commission voted unanimously on Tuesday to open additional spectrum to the growing number of connected devices as it studies whether to tap another largely unused block. https://t.co/U5hMgcqAAG https://t.co/VLfpjyjQrD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SoftBank's Son cancels Saudi conference speech: sources: SoftBank Group Corp Chief Executive Masayoshi Son, whose $93 billion Vision Fund drew nearly half its money from Saudi Arabia, canceled a speaking engagement at the kingdom's investment conference… https://t.co/5IlJFTYxS8 https://t.co/9OfSYhphBU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web performance software company Cloudflare readies IPO: sources: Cloudflare Inc, a U.S. startup whose software makes websites load faster and with greater security, is preparing for an initial public offering (IPO) that could value it at more than $3.5… https://t.co/OjIxmTUXeN https://t.co/nvcE2vKIq0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook launches searchable database for U.S. political ad spending: Facebook Inc on Tuesday unveiled a searchable database that will provide information on spending by advertisers for political ads and issues of national importance in the run-up to the… https://t.co/yHzRjMRKKv https://t.co/JMWSsqud25]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple's Cook set to back strong privacy laws in Europe, U.S. at Brussels event: Apple Chief Executive Tim Cook is expected to praise new European privacy rules and to voice the company's support for strong laws in Europe and the United States to protect… https://t.co/7QQmCaLjmF https://t.co/eJdCm73Hzx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook's WhatsApp says no plan to lift forwarding limit in Brazil: Facebook Inc's popular messaging service WhatsApp has no plan to lift its limit on the number of people who can receive a forwarded message in Brazil, an executive for the company told… https://t.co/USNHf9If9P https://t.co/WJRs1y2T04]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dyson chooses Singapore over Britain to build electric car: James Dyson, the billionaire British inventor of the bagless vacuum cleaner, has chosen to build his electric car in Singapore to be close to Asian customers, supply chains and a highly skilled… https://t.co/pefJbgtbf3 https://t.co/DjKw5XI5wi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[London's popularity as tech hub slumps ahead of Brexit: London's popularity among Europe's tech startup hubs has slumped as Brexit approaches and the city only kept its top spot in an European industry survey published on Tuesday by a narrow margin. https://t.co/NNOICUIKMC https://t.co/JXizMpXlIp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Verizon beats Wall Street estimates, shares hit 18-year high: Verizon Communications Inc reported quarterly profit and net new phone subscribers well ahead of Wall Street estimates on Tuesday, as customers took advantage of its subsidies for Apple Inc's… https://t.co/NbFRpXBDPM https://t.co/1aam6uFwhb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Autodesk, Flex veterans raise $179 million for manufacturing startup: A group of former executives from Autodesk Inc and Flex Ltd has raised $179 million in venture capital for a manufacturing startup that aims to use a combination of robots and new… https://t.co/9BNqcPWpFG https://t.co/DDa38fw339]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nissan Leaf gets approval for vehicle-to-grid use in Germany: Nissan's Leaf became the first electric vehicle (EV) to secure regulatory approval as an energy backstop for Germany's electricity grid, the Japanese carmaker said on Tuesday, something it… https://t.co/lpeocDRB19 https://t.co/W9T7qAH116]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple supplier AMS hit by forecast doubts amid chip slowdown: Apple chip supplier AMS AG disappointed investors with its fourth quarter forecast, knocking 25 percent off the value of its shares despite the Austrian firm winning deals with other… https://t.co/endhDArjXX https://t.co/rWFMgxPRVz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exclusive: China's Huawei opens up to German scrutiny ahead of 5G auctions: Chinese's Huawei Technologies Co Ltd [HWT.UL] will open a new information security lab in Germany next month that will enable source code reviews, in a step aimed at winning… https://t.co/hHeHr8PpWw https://t.co/fY2fZ7amOK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber to go all-electric in London, awaits Khashoggi murder facts: Uber aims for London to be the first city where all of its taxis will be electric in 2025, with a clean air fee added to rides to help drivers go green, a part of efforts to cut pollution… https://t.co/iPSfusuQjf https://t.co/MYGKY3gr2M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Xerox beats on profit, misses on revenue under Icahn appointees: Xerox Corp fell short on revenue but beat estimates for profit on the back of cost-cutting in its first full quarter under new management backed by activist investors Carl Icahn and Darwin… https://t.co/F0Irg7pN7S https://t.co/g6Fuy3v4cB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[iPhone promotional offers help Verizon beat phone subscriber estimates: Verizon Communications Inc on Tuesday beat Wall Street estimates for net new phone subscribers who pay a monthly bill, helped by promotional offers for Apple Inc's new iPhones. https://t.co/G1396cJPFU https://t.co/13K5jfL2dQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Verizon beats phone subscriber estimates: Verizon Communications Inc on Tuesday beat Wall Street estimates for net new phone subscribers who pay a monthly bill, helped by promotions for Apple Inc's new iPhone. https://t.co/rh5HD4Riiw https://t.co/qSSM0YIskc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israel's Team8 launches $85 million cybersecurity and data fund: Team8, which creates cybersecurity firms, launched on Tuesday a second fund of $85 million to build about eight cybersecurity and data companies over the next five years. https://t.co/RXLQTRjVAs https://t.co/nFmyoS6wt7]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>