<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence is no match for Natural Stupidity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're listening to a rock star in order to get your information on who to vote for, you're a bigger moron than they are. - Alice Cooper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is not the most important thing in the world. Love is. Fortunately, I love money. - Jackie Mason]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is the key to unlock the golden door of freedom. - George Washington Carver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest lie you can make is to lie to yourself. - Matt Zotti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hokey religions and ancient weapons are no substitute for a good blaster at your side, kid. - Han Solo, Star Wars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yum Yum Canned Unicorn Meat - great gag gift :&gt;)  http://t.co/Ig1eiJEep0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding good players is easy. Getting them to play as a team is another story. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every instructor assumes that you have nothing else to do except study for that instructor's course.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About eCommerce E-Tips  http://t.co/d13iwWZc0Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Choose a job you love, and you will never have to work a day in your life. - Confucius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Amazing Big Bag Of Science! http://t.co/sjJeBWJn7h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of The Ruins of Gorlan by John Flanagan  http://t.co/cPLRzbsTkN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Small Dogs Can Make Great Pets - Picking the Right Breed  http://t.co/SeWPwk4EZW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the goodness of a good egg cannot make up for the badness of a bad egg...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have ways of making money that you know nothing of.   John D. Rockefeller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 4 - Supplements and Herbs  http://t.co/0P0V2bEKAj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Favorite Things for Kids to Review  http://t.co/DxpZcIYt0J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The dog was created especially for children. He is the God of frolic. - Henry Ward Beecher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the darkness of the world cannot put out the light on one small candle. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Robin Trower  http://t.co/62dQPvc7Oj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Love Unlimited  http://t.co/sMMhbRKyh6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future belongs to those who believe in the beauty of their dreams. - Eleanor Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Beautiful Canadian Rockies Tour  http://t.co/7Wm0auAZP0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always wear expensive shoes. People notice. - Brian Koslow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Daddy: Mommy just backed the car over my bicycle! "I told you not to leave it in the living room!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Uriah Heep  http://t.co/mU709nS25E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I play with my cat, who knows whether she is not amusing herself with me more than I with her. - Montaigne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Help with Picking Garage Cabinets  http://t.co/WCLbU8URL7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hold fast to dreams, for if dreams die, life is a broken winged bird that cannot fly. - Langston Hughes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The right shoe can make everything different. - Jimmy Choo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you are thin, don't eat fast. If you are fat, don't eat fast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Foreigner  http://t.co/j1dvRqYcDy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very cool 23 mile range walkie talkies!  Stay connected!  http://t.co/828Q8Ctbg5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Creedance Clearwater Revival  http://t.co/HVyws91mnm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Pet Insurance  http://t.co/qHe1uyGdRB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Buying Gardening Supplies and Plants  http://t.co/Ca0Hgv6Vwj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Don Henley  http://t.co/xVpfihzejL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Commodores  http://t.co/8Q2trI4lsJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Adorable Fleece Baby Carrier Cover!  http://t.co/E0x6Szz8XN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You gotta love that - an aquarium coffee table!  Drink with the fishes! http://t.co/0MrzbW4KI9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep your face to the sunshine and you cannot see the shadows. - Helen Keller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science fiction writers foresee the inevitable, and although problems and catastrophes may be inevitable, solutions are not. - Isaac Asimov]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Heineken Phone Case --&gt; http://t.co/mqeKjZsUpv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Overview of the X-Files  http://t.co/oq3L29rYDq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who are the Three Degrees oldies group?  http://t.co/SPJDnW0Rwx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business has only two functions - marketing and innovation. - Milan Kundera]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picking Earphones for Fitness Activities  http://t.co/tuzuKhgRcO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Champions keep playing until they get it right. - Billie Jean King]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The dog represents all that is best in man. - Etienne Charlet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd just as soon kiss a wookiee! - Princess Leia, The Empire Strikes Back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Star Trek Enterprise Pizza Cutter! http://t.co/3EXhgAJ0WT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of a sudden, you're like the Bin Laden of America. Osama Bin Laden is the only one who knows exactly what I'm going through.  R. Kelly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Pink Floyd  http://t.co/5d9qZf8anc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes are just made from leather, rubber and cloth - read about exotic shoes... http://t.co/PlrFo4tc5i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't drown by falling in the water. You drown by staying there. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Five card stud, nothing wild. And the sky's the limit - Captain Jean Luc Picard - Last Line of Star Trek the Next Generation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't fix stupid - Larry Morgan, NHRA Pro Stock driver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To confine our attention to terrestrial matters would be to limit the human spirit. - Stephen Hawking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must begin to think of yourself as becoming the person you want to be. - David Viscott]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fitness - If it came in a bottle, everybody would have a great body. - Cher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plano Texas is an up and coming area of Dallas - read more here!  http://t.co/HvCYf6X0m9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winning is everything. The only ones who remember you when you come second are your wife and your dog. - Damon Hill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Keys to Good Marketing for Your Business  http://t.co/8sQZZBUxqR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winners take time to relish their work, knowing that scaling the mountain is what makes the view from the top so exhilarating. Denis Waitley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very cool Star Wars windshield sun reflector - may the force be with you!   http://t.co/SZ8nX7T2fS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Commodores  http://t.co/xUenyrmN8k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The easiest way to stay out of hot water is to keep a cool head]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sex and the City changed New York - New York's become a big shoe store now, unfortunately. -  Chris Noth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn Baseball Lingo  http://t.co/RjpYgPayMy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A classic TV sit-com - the fascinating history of Andy Griffith - they didn’t get along with sweet Aunt Bee?  http://t.co/4QTh5AqSFr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Learning Tool for Kids - Snap Circuits Jr - Hands On Learning All About Circuits http://t.co/Qw4voN2lVs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If people don't want to come out to the ball park, nobody's gonna stop 'em. - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am the legal guardian over a massive shoe collection. - Linda Dominique Grosvenor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel like punching the boss' jaw again  "Did you say again?" "Yes, I felt like doing it once before today!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion is not necessarily about labels. It's not about brands. It's about something else that comes from within you. - Ralph Lauren]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the History of the Nautilus Fitness Equipment  http://t.co/dfnLaMhViF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Peter Cetera  http://t.co/w4eedkxwmo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Interesting History of Dos XX Beer  http://t.co/NP91G31VFr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pessimist: A man who thinks that all woman are bad Optimist: A man who hopes so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I live in heels. Give me a pair of flip-flops and I'll trip all over myself. - Brenda Song]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good teaching is one-fourth preparation and three-fourths pure theatre. - Gail Godwin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oooh right, it's actually quite a funny story once you get past all the tragic elements and the over-riding sense of doom. - Duckman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome marriage t-shirts &amp; gear - give the gift of marriage!  http://t.co/AhDU9uUc6r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of David Gates  http://t.co/fzcLVj6Qmc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Marvin Gaye  http://t.co/JJ6HBSy2ka]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He who laughs last, didn't get it!!  :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the The History of the Chambers Brothers  http://t.co/qFEKX5lJDQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Delfonics  http://t.co/jBL4jYs3Z9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like flying jet fighters in a gymnasium - Dick Trickle was asked what racing at Winchester Speedway was like.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Until one has loved an animal,  a part of one's soul remains unawakened. - Anatole France]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God gives us the ability, but rock 'n' roll was created by men.  - Little Richard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Men who talk like big wheels usually are mere spokesmen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I consider exercise vulgar. It makes people smell. - Alec Yuill Thornton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Heineken International  http://t.co/g4R0oHOhyO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Customer:  "Could I try on that suit in the window?"  Clerk:  "We'd rather you do that in the dressing room."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Barbara Acklin a Great Singer http://t.co/i1b5omLO3M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do something for somebody every day for which you do not get paid. - Albert Schweitzer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about the Bay Area city of Danville, California http://t.co/Bxefeyov4g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Barbara Acklin – “Love Makes a Woman”  http://t.co/eFqwIanFTW]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>