<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[You may lose the people you love, You may lose the things you have. But no matter what happens, Never lose yourself!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live every day like it's your last, because one day it will be, and you'll look back on all the things you wish you had done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just because you can't see the air doesn't mean you stop breathing. And just because you can't see God doesn't mean you stop believing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is too short to worry about haters. They don't deserve to be an issue in your life. Think about the people who love and support you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When something bad happens, you have 3 choices: You can either let it define you, destroy you, or let it strengthen you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never give up, not because you still have tomorrow to try, but because you may not have tomorrow to try.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just because a person smiles all the time doesn't mean their life is perfect. That smile is a symbol of hope &amp; strength.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Believe in yourself and create your own destiny. Don't fear failure!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spend life with the people who make you happy, not the people who you have to impress.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Believe in yourself, push your limits, and do whatever it takes to conquer your goals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grudges are a waste of perfect happiness. Laugh when you can, apologize when you should, and let go of what you can't change.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Use your smile to change this world. Don't let this world change your smile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life doesn't let you to go back and change things. All you can do is learn from the past, and prepare for what the future may bring.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What hurts you today makes you stronger tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't give up just because things are hard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every struggle in your past has shaped you into the person you are today. Take God's hand and step into your future without fear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It does not matter how many times you get knocked down, but how many times you get up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone can make you smile, many people can make you cry, but it takes someone special to make you smile with tears in your eyes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God gave you this life because he knew you were strong enough to live it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Success isn't something given, it's something earned. So go out there, work hard, and make your dreams come true!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you focus on problems, you'll have more problems. When you focus on possibilities, you'll have more opportunities.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Respect isn't something that's given. It's earned.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything has beauty, but not everyone sees it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A few tears won't kill you, only heal you. A little pain won't destroy you, only strengthen you. So cry, forgive, and move on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Success is a journey, not a destination. The process is often more important than the outcome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find a heart that will love you at your worst, and arms that will hold you at your weakest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Start each day with a new hope, leave bad memories behind and have faith for a better tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your past is done, so forget it, your future is yet to come, so dream it, but your present is now, so live it with no regrets!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge nothing, you will be happy. Forgive everything, you will be happier. Love everything, you will be happiest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today is the oldest you've ever been, and the youngest you'll ever be again. So live life to the fullest today, and have no regrets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God has perfect timing; never early, never late. It takes a little patience and it takes a lot of faith but it's worth the wait.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nobody can go back and start a new beginning, but anyone can start today and make a new ending.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smile for what you have, rather than cry for what you don't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A positive attitude gives you power over your circumstances instead of your circumstances having power over you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes silence is the best answer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't be afraid of change. You may end up losing something good, but you will probably end up gaining something better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good things come to those who believe, Better things come to those who wait and the Best things come to those who don't give up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God, please give us the courage to accept things for what they are, but to never lose hope that things will always get better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't get stuck on the one thing that ruins your day. Smile and be happy. Life is too short to waste on negativity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A good life is when you smile often, dream big, laugh a lot and realize how blessed you are for what you have.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes you have to stop worrying &amp; doubting. Have faith that things will work out. Maybe not how you planned but the way it's meant to be]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Knowing when to walk away, is wisdom. Being able to, is courage. Walking away with your head held high, is dignity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over-thinking ruins you. Ruins the situation, twists things around, makes you worry and just makes everything much worse than it actually is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People will hate you, rate you, shake you, and break you. But how strong you stand is what makes you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/lqEiehGLE4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you stop chasing the wrong things, you give the right things a chance to catch you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's easier to go down a hill than up it but the view is much better at the top.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is too short to worry about what others say or think about you. So have fun and give them something to talk about.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop running away from your problems because that only increases the distance from the solution. Make it right today, tomorrow is too late.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret of success: stop wishing, start doing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes you need patience in order to find true happiness. It won't come fast and it won't come easy, but it will be worth it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We can smile even though we are hurting and we can feel happy even though we are unhappy. It's called strength.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God, please give us the courage to accept things for what they are, but to never lose hope that things will always get better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only time you should ever look back, is to see how far you've come.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A clever person solves a problem. A wise person avoids it. A stupid person makes it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smile. Let everyone know that today you're a lot stronger than you were yesterday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best revenge is to move on and get over it. Don't give someone the satisfaction of watching you suffer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep smiling and enjoy the journey even when it's like there's no hope at all. Everything will be alright.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes you face difficulties not because you're doing something wrong, But because you're doing something right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Appreciate those who love you. Help those who need you. Forgive those who hurt you. Forget those who leave you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is full of fake people. Before you decide to judge them, make sure you're not one of them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes it takes the worst pain to bring about the best change.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is too short to worry about what others say or think about you. So have fun and give them something to talk about.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Respect people's feelings. Even if it doesn't mean anything to you, it could mean everything to them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The life you have left is a gift. Cherish it. Enjoy it now, to the fullest. Do what you want most.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't change the Past, but you can do something to change the Present &amp; Future. Live the way you want, and have no regrets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You were born to be real, not to be perfect. You are here to be you, not to live someone else's life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have to hurt in order to know. Fall in order to grow. Lose in order to gain. Because many of life's lessons are learned in pain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In life, many things don't go according to plan. If you fall, get back up. If you stumble, re-gain your balance. Never give up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live as if you were to die tomorrow. Learn as if you were to live forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1) Work your hardest 2) Dream your biggest 3) Be your greatest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As we grow up, we realize it becomes less important to have a ton of friends, and more important to have real ones.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never let your memories be greater than your dreams.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To everyone going through any struggle or pain right now, keep your head up, and keep on smiling, you'll get through it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop beating yourself up. You are a work in progress; which means you get there a little at a time, not all at once.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes silence is the best answer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God knew you were going to be special to someone..that's why he created you. Be happy with yourself, and know you are loved.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not cry for the past is gone, do not stress about the future has not arrived, live in the present and make it awesome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before you talk, listen. Before you react, think. Before you criticize, wait. Before you pray, forgive. Before you quit, try.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A negative mind will never give you a positive life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't start your day with the broken pieces of yesterday. Every morning we wake up is the first day of the rest of our life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Successful people are always looking for opportunities to help others. Unsuccessful people are always asking, 'What's in it for me?']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't be good enough for everybody, but you'll always be the best for the one who deserves you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is too precious to stress yourself out by worrying about everything. Relax, have fun, and enjoy the learning process.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Challenges are what makes life interesting, overcoming them is what makes life meaningful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you stop chasing the wrong things, you give the right things a chance to catch you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be strong now, because it will get better. It may be stormy now, but it can't rain forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The hard work you're putting in now will be worth it in the long run.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Head up, stay strong. Fake a smile, move on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disappointments are just God's way of saying: "I've got something better"' Be patient, live life, have faith.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In this world, there's always going to be people who are better then you. So stop comparing yourself to others, and just be the best you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always remember: you're braver than you believe, stronger than you seem, and smarter than you think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Choose your friends with caution, plan your future with purpose, and frame your life with faith.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd rather live my life knowing that I'm not perfect, than spending my whole life pretending to be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy are they who take life day by day, complain very little, and are thankful for the little things in life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone can give up, it's the easiest thing ever. But to hold it together when everyone else thinks you'd fall apart is true strength.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pain makes you stronger, tears make you braver, and heartbreaks make you wiser, so thank the past for a better future.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Use your smile to change this world. Don't let this world change your smile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Concentrate on your strengths instead of your weaknesses, on your powers instead of your problems.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Try not to become a man of success, but rather a man of value.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>