<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SRAF: We're opening in half an hour with 5,500 pints of 129 different beers pouring. #camra #realale #beer #edinburgh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @millarmind: I'm so fucking excited. I love the Tour de France.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AdamRichman: Twitter bullies are such pussies. You respond directly to insults &amp; they post screen shots claiming how hurt they a ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BBCBreaking: The US astronaut Neil Armstrong, the first man to walk on the Moon, has died aged 82, US media reports
http://t.co/n7AfiIuT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @skierfrank: @MillerBode They should make all pro athletes eat cheese burgers and drink Coke.  No Starbucks or Ibuprofen, just cheese ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mcintoshpaul: @iainmacintosh If it turns out he used drugs to beat cancer too I dread to think what the lads at USADA will do when t ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BBCBreaking: Seven-time Tour de France winner Lance Armstrong says he is giving up his fight against doping accusations http://t.co/ ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mymodernmet: Funny meme! It's gold medalist Mo Farah hilariously running away from things. http://t.co/obB5bYv6--- AMAZING!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't fucking roll on shabbas! #lebowski]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BBCAnnaT: BREAKING: Tour de France winner @bradwiggins to ride Tour of Britain starting 9 September]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GrahamSpiers: I’m re-reading ‘Sunset Song’ here. I’d forgotten how beautiful and absorbing this story is. #grassicgibbon #arbuthnott]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @matvenn: "Just think: two weeks ago the world thought we were rubbish at sport and great at music" - Guardian live blog”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Matt bellamy's suit is the balls #closingceremony #London2012]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rory mcillroy is about to win another major by the way...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ed Sheehan doing pink floyd. I could accept arctics doing come together, kaisers were bad, but this is is unacceptable. #London2012]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bit weird the whole 'fleet street' theme as well, considering... y'know... #London2012]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now a really bizarre Bowie montage. Think this is all a bit crap really. #London2012]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kaiser chiefs playing the who. Oh dear #London2012. Still at least George
Michael has been removed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CraigLevein: Ian Black. Levein is finally beyond parody.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Beathhigh: Not many films get me welling up, but those last few minutes of Toy Story 3, man...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Kenny_Millar: Great review of the book. RT @STVSport: Exploring the charm behind the game: Football Manager Stole My Life http://t.c ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow. 13,000 for a derby....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HibernianFCClub: The crowd at this afternoon's Edinburgh Derby was 12, 887 - thanks for your support. A step in the right direction. ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alan maybury. Who could have anticipated that being a shit hibs signing? #sarcasm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#mo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back up on The Wire. #shiiiiit #awwwjimmeehhh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @frankieboyle: Brilliant Jade Jones.Brilliant Katie Taylor. Brilliant Nicola Adams. Can one of you start dating Chris Brown?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[well not in. but finished anyway!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[dissertation in! i'm freeee!!! Get the beers in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@MikeDski: Holy Crap! This #Paralympics vid is all-time awesome. Must watch http://t.co/jQgmVLEx” ---British telly ads reaching Canada eh!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @henrywinter: Unprecedented scenes at V &amp; A Museum. A bagpiper has just greeted the arrival of Pele who is receiving an honorary  ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kajackson6: This is brilliant - piers Morgan is such a numpty!!! #norespect #Olympics2012 http://t.co/9XloA1vZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @robertflorence: And James Kelman can't afford to write full-time. RT @RandomHouseUK FIFTY SHADES OF GREY becomes bestselling British ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@gregjmchugh: Off to see 'trainspotting' at the CINEMA!!! YAAAAAAAAAAAAAAS! AND WHY WOULD I WANT TO SELL MY PASSPORT?” @ThisisMannah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Scotlandteam: Another Scot wins Olympic gold . . . Two in two days . . . And Reporting Scotland chooses to lead on Rangers FC . . . ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Doctor_Hutch: UCI must be pleased at how the rule changes have opened up the competition and stopped one nation from dominating.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FRabbits: Morrissey on Richard Madeley: “He referred to me as a 'puffed-up prat'. This is a bit rich coming from a man who married h ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CraigLevein: Dobbie and McCormack haven't featured for their team for the last two months. They have to be playing regularly to be s ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BrewDogJames: With only £20k &amp; a big dream in 2007 we now have 125 staff, sales in 29 countries, £12m turnover &amp; a new £8m e ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @wilw: http://t.co/YU0hfgin You're welcome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good start to the season hibs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThisisMannah re our conversation last night, I got an email today from football manager wishing me a happy birthday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bbc sport comparing Olympic success to 1966 and wilkinson drop goal. Bunch of ballbags #britishnotenglish]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Scott Pilgrim VS The World soundtrack is immense. #wearesexbobomb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unbelievable scenes men's canoe! #London2012]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @henrywinter: Sad to hear of Roberto Carlos' retirement. I'll never forget #eng players trying to copy his fk at Tournoi. They pepper ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Beathhigh: My abiding memory of Gore Vidal is missing seeing him at a festival in Italy because I was busy being arrested for trespa ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @akselsvindal: I do hope sideburns will take over for shaved legs as the biggest trend in cycling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give that man a knighthood #SirWiggo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cancellara in absolute pieces. Heroic effort! #London2012]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @millarmind: 52km/h average. Fucking hell. And he gave 100% to the team in the road race on Saturday. Inspiring.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The average speed of these guys over that distance is frankly sickening #TT #London2012]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Rondebike: Come support @chrishoy &amp; the rest of team #GB at the shop from 4-7pm. SKY, ITV &amp; BBC radio here at the shop too,  ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The lack of graphics and information for the  #London2012 road racing has been fucking annoying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uh-oh. Spartacus looking strong. #London2012 #TT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taking diss break for the TT. #allezwiggo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First draft is when you write words. Second draft is when you make those words not shit. #dissertationmantra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All I want to do today is watch #London2012. Fudging dissertation. #losing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @millarmind: Good luck @bradwiggins although I don't think he needs luck, this is just a Wednesday West London TT for him. Apples.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @brewdog: Scottish Brewery Gets into Olympic Spirit by Launching 'Performance Enhancing' Beer http://t.co/cbckyItF via @IBTimes @Brew ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Phelps is a hero, but there are so many gold medals available in swimming. Admire C Lewis more for winning 100 meters &amp; Long jump medals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HansOlssons: Swimming is cool, but 34 different events I would say is overkill! Where is skate board vert ramp? BMX big air? Downhil ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quite fancy LL Sanchez for the TT tomorrow #London2012]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gymnastastic #London2012]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andyknoxmusic well said knoxy! Couple of southern fairies!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FRabbits: Heading down south today to put the (almost) final piece of the puzzle that is album #4 into place. #nearlythere #light #e ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think that's it. #London2012]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even if team GB get Cav to front, how much will they have for lead out? #Olympic2012]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Froome gone. Not good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come on Germany, you've got as much to lose here! Put in some work #2012LondonOlympics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't think this looks good for Cav and co at all... #2012LondonOlympics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rory_g_macrae Think im going to miss it tonight mate; staying at Mum and Dads and sessioning dissertation. Have a good yin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Team GB need the likes of the German team, Gilbert and Fabian 'Spartacus' Cancellara to help them bridge the gap here.  #2012LondonOlympics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @iainmacintosh: If both of Poulter's testicles had been in that Mayan temple, I'm afraid that Ark would have stayed lost.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @iainmacintosh: You know the rolling rock that almost wipes out Indiana Jones in Raiders of the Lost Ark? That's the size of just one ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @akselsvindal: Reading about Maria Riesch´s new book. The truth is less exciting and a lot more normal. But that wouldn´t sell any bo ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GSElevator: #1: When life gives you lemons, order the lobster tail.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MikeDski: Eric Hjorleifson is safe at home in Whistler.  He was not on Manaslu when the accident happened. Please share &amp; stop b ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SteepSkiing: Skiing loses another legend. RIP Remy Lecluse. Manaslu Avalanche.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @iainmacintosh: Look at them. Just look at them. Mancini looks a 1940s movie star and Platt looks like a fucking painted egg.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @iainmacintosh: Poor old David Platt. I know that pretty much *anybody* would be classed as Roberto Mancini's ugly mate, but he's got ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @slukenelson: Sad news from #Manaslu- Avalanche on Manaslu: Glen Plake Alive, Rémy Lécluse &amp; Greg Costa Missing http://t.co/w8eZB ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @alexbe11: I hear congratulations are in order for Raheem Sterling (17), who apparently yesterday became a father for the 3rd time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @iainmacintosh: Pirlo looks like Aragorn, son of Arathorn. This pleases me. "If by my life or death I can play a decent through-ball  ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @henrywinter: #cfc will want the Uefa award for Goal of the Round to be called an Oscar. (Just getting that one out the way)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LASTEXITshirts: #FilmPosterOfTheDay. Hungarian Star Wars poster (1977) http://t.co/s3mPkJfD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another season, another shocker of a haircut for Gael #Clichy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @stevenfletch10: “@vhonest_lad: @stevenfletch10 would you pull on your Scotland jersey next month if Craig levein asked you to come b ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JojoRobertson1: #ballin' in first class...some benefits of a fractured neck. Aaaaand my nurse even let me have a sip of champagne #b ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chrishoy: Just for clarification, my Evening news front page photo pose was in reference to 6 golds and nothing else! ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @iainmacintosh: Do you remember that moment when you almost cracked and went to bed? Well done, you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How will I sleep after this? Another break please Andrew.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Muuuuuuuurrrraaaaaaayyyyy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @iainmacintosh: Fergie keeps looking at his watch, but I'm not sure what can be gained by that in this sport. Still, it's nice that h ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @iainmacintosh: Did Twitter search for 'British Scottish'. It's like the bit in 'I Am Legend' when Will Smith walks into a whole fuck ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Believe!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HibernianFCClub: Club can confirm that 'Boozy' Beuzelin has rejoined Hibernian as an Academy coach #welcomebackboozy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Kenny_Millar: Just left Hampden. So deflating. No lack of effort but think the players could be let off the leash. Amy Macdonald was ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JamesWoodsy: Thank thank you SO much everyone for all your support!! Really happy, today I won the World Cup in Argentina! :D http:/ ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @arobertwebb: As a former columnist for the Telegraph, I know their newsroom is going berserk. "Ooh, the reshuffle, ooh." Like shuffl ...]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>