<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[come to this and absolutely nothing else https://t.co/XtXwz2ckOt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @daytimesnaps: https://t.co/GHVI5IHIwP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving that just sounds like the worst clickbait]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving oh  god, not them too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving BEZOS SHILL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving tbh i see this as playing into Kindle's hands as publishers refuse to publish books with huge segments of blank pages]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving so would an ellipsis be         ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @hollymorgan97: Lee’s maw n dad haven’t been in the same house together in about 4 years, wake up n he’s sent me this fuck sake hahahah…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving Calm your spam ts Elliott]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving Yep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hollysses They're still all so partridge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hollysses Two racist stereotypes for the price of one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hollysses Holy shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Steve_THFC: Why does Messi look like Mark Corrigan https://t.co/SyNCpASfLm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adfinnes @Dashmundo  https://t.co/UXry1efx3G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adfinnes @Dashmundo You're so wrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jtlovell1979 maybe Lawrenson just makes everyone look good in comparison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dashmundo anyone can win at maths]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jtlovell1979 his commentary has made me absolutely fine with Panama's constant shithousing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[scotland can still win this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MrTomYoull: Not to put to much of a fine a point on it @Edinburgh_CC really don’t give a shit about anything that happens outside of Au…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HealthUntoDeath: Give Simpsons Shitposting a permanent seat on the ITV punditry couch. https://t.co/bAzpxcYIgV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ByLeavesWeLive: Edinburgh poets are threatened by whispers of 'the Fringe is coming!' In order to survive, they must slam. If they lose…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['It's the heel' says Danny Murphy, desperate to show that he understood Series 1 of GLOW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarianneMacRae he is bringing the game into disrepute. it is footBALL not handWANG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ScarredForLife2: Get yer irony overloads here, two for the price of one https://t.co/XTybP8a3BK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GlenTChapman either way it haunts me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GlenTChapman or their child]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GlenTChapman krang.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@literature_wine @strongmisgiving Sometimes u just kno]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving @literature_wine Aye it's time to move on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @strongmisgiving: Hey I just met you 
During thirty years of hurt 
So here's my number 
Three Lions on a shirt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @riffraffhands: Just received a customer satisfaction questionnaire from the crematorium! Tempted to write “Well, she’s still dead, and…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @bornmiserable: [hospital]
SURGEON: [lowers mask] I'm sorry, we were unable to separate the art from the artist
ME: is he
S: yes, he's s…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @afrendlypingu: Google predicts my biggest fear https://t.co/BCWWKmwk5U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robertjbennett Lord of the Rings is literally this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Jickle: https://t.co/P6I5Q0vBSE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ByLeavesWeLive: Edinburgh poets are threatened by whispers of 'the Fringe is coming!' In order to survive, they must slam. If they lose…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[dgaf abt ozymandias tbh #MakePoetryBoring]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @erikgregersen: If I had $200 mil to remake Last Jedi, I’d hire Rian Johnson to redo it under absurd constraints like The Five Obstructi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving idea for poetry show https://t.co/4bX9RHaIlV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Josherick3: man's got a point https://t.co/2wIJJWcLLO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @periwinklewine: Emoshed many emotions seeing @IdlewildtheBand at @Summerhallery this evening, dedicating their #RipItUp set to Scott Hu…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bob Fairfoul then.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving @TyroneLewis22 I forgot you lived in the future but were forbidden from directly interfering]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TyroneLewis22 It'll make Attack of the Clones look like Infinity War]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving Iambic pentametwat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dashmundo It's the law.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rob_Motto @eclaire082 @mattzollerseitz You're not, you're saying daft things on Twitter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rob_Motto @eclaire082 @mattzollerseitz So we shouldn't take you seriously because you're not currently writing about film?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @demarionunn: starting to think wes streeting is dril https://t.co/26FVIn5CXu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @warkslibraries: Latest poem composed by our RFID machines #StratfordLibrary https://t.co/Uk8C2dwMGo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dashmundo Don't be fooled by his sly winking facade]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dashmundo When Ramos is dead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I mean, far be it for me to question the integrity of the Daily Telegraph, but Scottish football's done alright tonight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rakelrank @Josherick3 @kerperplexed @poetryasfuck @smaychel have you not seen Animals of Farthing Wood?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sebpatrick *googles*
*reads "narrated by Clive Owen"*
how did i not know about this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sebpatrick how would you feel if Liverpool released a retrospective of last season produced in the style of Arrested Development?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dashmundo we need a bolton fan to solve this mystery]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sebpatrick however I'm feeling a lot more confident about playing hibs first game of the season now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sebpatrick not actually related to scansion but the goalie they already had was pretty good and I have no idea why they signed Bogdan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sebpatrick and it still scans *italian chef kissing fingers emoji*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sebpatrick: @freelance_liar I can understand why Stranraer lie so lowly
They could save a lot of points by signing Hibs’ goalie
Except…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[can anyone confirm whether Adam Bogdan was ever good at football? is his confidence just totally shot?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @classiclib3ral: https://t.co/mi6QP7chkX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come for the name, stay for the fury 
https://t.co/bpyD5vM56A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheSpoilist Added to the list]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheSpoilist yeah, i remember when they announced it and someone praised it as a sign of big finish's innovation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheSpoilist *holds two fingers to ear* I'm just getting news that Big Finish have already commissioned this as a boxset]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheSpoilist I can do 800 words by monday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheSpoilist as long as I can write the occasional fluff piece about why cybermen are a bit shit, fine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheSpoilist is this why everyone is leaving Den of Geek?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CrimsonEbolg i don't think we even need to enter any sort of agreement, people can just do their's whenever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sianbevan @msjlindsay sure, in relative terms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimultimate @triplebozzmun they played an excerpt at the 50th anniversary prom, have you seen that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CrimsonEbolg i mean, if you're not in edinburgh around christmas then absolutely set one up where you are]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@msjlindsay i'll put you down for five minutes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving idea for a twitter bot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving that line got me too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i love scottish football https://t.co/sMjbiJUPqz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simonbrew Do you think it'd survive Miriam Margolyes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimultimate @triplebozzmun next he'll be saying he sees nothing wrong with tomb of the cybermen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KildayAngela i really want to sell out a poetry gig with no actual poetry on at it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lloydpoetrock It's been a while since we came up with a show deliberately]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@triplebozzmun @jimultimate You can keep it.

I have a further copy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimultimate @triplebozzmun I think I gave him an old copy. It is, I think, good and overrated and racist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[so, uh, this might actually happen https://t.co/A7bK1WOfMd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeatherParryUK @strongmisgiving @InkyFingersEdin magnifcunder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving @HeatherParryUK @InkyFingersEdin tbh it's free to get in, so...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimultimate I forget - did I lend you Talons of Weng Chieng?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["adequate food"

*gestures at foodbanks*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes yes I know the line up's great and everything but I want you to prioritise the one I'm on at. https://t.co/CqEGEP5gLf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CWilsonPoet ...brb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CWilsonPoet i wasn't expecting to have to actually put this show on but as soon as I find a venue I'll let you know]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @heyworstartist: Yeah as someone who worked for nearly eight years in retaile, the corporate elite don't give a fuck about this or the o…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeatherParryUK he read a lot of teen horror, famously]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeatherParryUK I agree, but also: https://t.co/DQ8gsrRtyG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ByLeavesWeLive: In The Slaminals of Farthing Wood, Edinburgh poets are an endangered species  who must slam to survive the oncoming Ed…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lloydpoetrock @strongmisgiving And 99% of poems go unread]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dashmundo We have a special bond]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>