<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA["All God does is watch and change channels when He gets bored."
- Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Everything you ever love will reject you or die. Everything you're proud of will end up as trash. "
- Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When she's in love, nothing can make her sad; however when she's not in love, nothing can make her happy."
- Tell-All]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You save people by letting them save you."
- Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The only reason why we ask other people how their weekend was is so we can tell them about our own weekend."
- Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fight Club... http://t.co/u5mRcz8sJr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“I wanted to destroy everything beautiful I'd never have.”
- Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["People fall so in love with their pain, they can’t leave it behind. The same as the stories they tell. We trap ourselves."
- Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Anything you can acquire is only another thing you'll lose."
- Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's my petty fear of personal rejection that allows so many true evils to exist. My cowardice enables atrocities."
- Damned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ProbablyAlice: @PalahniukQuote I drew this with a quote from Invisible monsters http://t.co/Zawekna7Bk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Maybe humans are just the pet alligators that God flushed down the toilet."
- Lullaby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Everything before now, before now, before now, is just a story I carry around. I guess that would apply to anybody in the world."
- I.M.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The moment you make yourself available to any man, he starts to take you for granted."
- Snuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Nothing happened, and nothing kept happening."
- Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“It's funny how the beauty of art has so much more to do with the frame than the artwork itself.”
- Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MsWildeChild: ‘Snuff’ by Chuck Palahniuk – Caustically Lucid Verisimilitude @PalahniukQuote  http://t.co/2xCohzBzf5 via @Jack_Marshall94]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["As far as regret, I think that's the sign of a well lived life. If I grew old without having regrets, I'd regret my caution."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Everybody looks a little crazy if you're looking close enough. And if you can't look that close, then you don't really love them."
-Romance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Your birth is a mistake you'll spend your whole life trying to correct."
- Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Everyone crowds the same sidewalks, scattered with garbage, and sees the same sunrise bleary and red behind smog."
- Diary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even the best part of any city is just a deluxe luxury suite in hell. The stars and moon erased by the lights from a million used car lots.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If enough folks believe a lie, it ain't a lie no more."
- Rant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I suppose it’s comfort, perhaps a sense of self-control, doing worse things to yourself than the world will ever dare inflict."
- Tell-All]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A girl calls and asks, "Does it hurt very much to die?" "Well, sweetheart," I tell her, "yes, but it hurts a lot more to keep living."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["On a long enough timeline, the survival rate for everyone drops to zero."
- Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The one you love and the one who loves you are never, ever the same person."
- Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @xDisappearHerex: Chuck Palahniuk's "Obsolete".
One of my favorite stories from 'Haunted'.
http://t.co/mGFZjLs5BQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's so hard to forget pain, but it's even harder to remember sweetness. We have no scar to show for happiness."
- Diary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Most times, it's just a lot easier not to let the world know what's wrong."
- Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you can watch much television, then being dead will be a cinch."
- Damned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Someday, I'd like to live a life based on doing good stuff instead of just not doing bad stuff."
- Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["She figured a brush with death would make her really enjoy her life. Like she would feel more alive."
- Rant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To some of us, the nights are too long. To some, the days."
- Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I need to rebel against myself. I need to do what I most fear."
- Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The first time you meet that someone special, you can count on them one day being dead and in the ground."
- Survivor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Advertising has us chasing cars and clothes. Working jobs we hate, so we can buy shit we dont need."
- Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["By the time you read this, you'll be older than you remember."
- Rant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“You can only hold a smile for so long, after that it's just teeth.”
- Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The world is a battle for attention, a war to be heard."
- Damned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You not talk about Fight Club... http://t.co/wp5hrjRyFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Your being born makes your parents God. You owe them your life, and they can control you. Then puberty makes you Satan."
Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RomanceFilm: What a great new interview with "Fight Club" author Chuck Palahniuk about the brutal negotiations undertook to... http://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chuck Palahniuk announces new short story 'Zombies' for the October Playboy. Also, if you haven't already, read 'Cannibal' in the May issue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["She's bored to death of dying."
- Diary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The only difference between a suicide and a martyrdom really is the amount of press coverage."
- Survivor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["With everyone's imagination atrophied, no one will ever be a threat to the world."
- Lullaby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fight Club... http://t.co/1HU7fwBt7e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["For this moment, nothing matters. Look up into the stars and you’re gone."
- Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["They say the smart dog obeys, but the smarter dog knows when to disobey."
- Amy Hempel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Sometimes your best way to deal with shit, is to not hold yourself as such a precious little prize."
- Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What makes earth feel like hell is our expectation that it should feel like heaven."
- Damned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Life's greatest comfort is being able to look over your shoulder and see people worse off, waiting in line behind you."
- Rant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You realize that our mistrust of the future makes it hard to give up the past."
- Survivor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That’s pretty much how we get through our own lives, watching television. Smoking crap. Self medicating. Redirecting our attention. Denial.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Marla's philosophy of life, she told me, is that she can die at any moment. The tragedy of her life is that she doesn't."
- Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Find what you're afraid of most and go live there."
- Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We’d turn our lives into a terrible adventure. A true-life horror story with a happy ending. A trial we’d survive to talk about."
- Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/8G7EJeOpB0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To hell with housework, our top priority has always been between our legs."
- Snuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Torture is torture and humiliation is humiliation only when you choose to suffer."
- Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Maybe you don't go to hell for the things you do. Maybe you go to hell for the things you don't do. The things you don't finish."
- Lullaby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's another longest day of the year. Again."
- Diary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You have a choice. Live or die. Every breath is a choice. Every minute is a choice. To be or not to be."
- Survivor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In truth, the degree of anyone's success depends on how often they can say the word yes and hear the word no."
- Tell-All]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The whole world is a disaster waiting to happen."
- Survivor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["For both genders, adolescence occurs as a kind of Ice Age of dumbness."
- Damned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["This is your life and it's ending one minute at a time."
- Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We'll never be as young as we are tonight."
- Rant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @xDisappearHerex: "32 Books That Will Actually Change Your Life" via @buzzfeed
'Invisible Monsters' made #6! @chuckpalahniuk 
http://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You are permanent, but this life is not."
- Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's only after you've lost everything that you're free to do anything."
- Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Nothing of me is original. I am the combined effort of everyone I've ever known."
- Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We're all of us haunted and haunting."
- Lullaby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Invisible Monsters... http://t.co/Rfeiv8Vori]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You have endless ways you can commit suicide without 'dying' dying."
- Diary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The lower you fall, the higher you'll fly."
- Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Diary http://t.co/CWff4UofRm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Some people are just born human, the rest of us, we take a lifetime to get there."
- Rant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Did you ever think about life as a metaphor for television?"
- InvIsible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The things you used to own, now they own you."
- Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I need to rebel against myself. It's the opposite of following your bliss. I need to do what I most fear."
- Lullaby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A book is as private and consensual as sex."
- Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chuck Palahniuk discusses 'The Cacophony Society' and more in this new interview via @SFWeekly 
http://t.co/M85I6pll8G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["People used what they called a telephone because they hated being close together and they were too scared of being alone."
- Survivor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you could be either God’s worst enemy or nothing, which would you choose?"
- Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Not everyone enjoys baseball or even fishing, but every person is obsessed with himself. You're your own favorite hobby."
- Rant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Everything is funnier in retrospect, funnier and prettier and cooler. You can laugh at anything from far enough away."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["How do you cope when your whole life story turns out to be wrong?"
- Snuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Anymore , no one's mind is their own."
- Lullaby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's all mirror, mirror on the wall because beauty is power, the same way money is power, the same way a gun is power."
-Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love is bullshit. Emotion is bullshit. I am a rock. A jerk. I'm an uncaring asshole and proud of it."
- Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We have to show these men and women freedom by enslaving them, and show them courage by frightening them."
- Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @xDisappearHerex: QUIZ: Can you tell the difference between Taylor Swift lyrics &amp; Chuck Palahniuk quotes? 
via @cbcbooks 
http://t.co/Vq…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In truth, the degree of anyone's success depends on how often they can say the word yes and hear the word no."
- Tell-All]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Almost all the time, you tell yourself you're loving somebody when you're just using them. This only looks like love."
-Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["All the effort in the world won't matter if you're not inspired."
- Diary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It just seems natural. You and me against the world."
- Lullaby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you haven’t already noticed, all my books are about a lonely person looking for some way to connect with other people."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You do the little job you're trained to do.
Pull a lever. 
Push a button. 
You don't understand any of it, and then you just die."]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>