<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The Battle for Title IX and The Opportunities It Created: 
	When my six-year-old daughter Nina is a bit older I ... http://t.co/FEN19eFt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celebrating Success: 40 Years of Pell Grants: 
	Chances are you know someone who wouldn’t have gone to college w... http://t.co/xFpMqGfi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Address: Congress Must Act on Transportation Bill and Student Loans: 
	President Obama discusses the urge... http://t.co/XqE5VwGv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Wrap Up: Don't Double My Rate: 

  Click here to see the video. 

	Here's a quick glimpse at what ha... http://t.co/SbFTFzJy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celebrating Olmstead and our Commitment to Community Living: 
	As I travel the country and visit people in their... http://t.co/MnxSAcK8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Wing Week: 06/22/12 or "Dreamers": 
	This week, the President talks about an important policy change on imm... http://t.co/K3M50c7u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[40th Anniversary of Title IX: 

	Yesterday, June 20th, the White House Council on Women and Girls hosted a gre... http://t.co/WTkoP17D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Again Pushes Congress to Act on Student Loans: 

    President Barack Obama, with Education... http://t.co/RjHazw8u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Community Colleges Are Changing the Way We Think About Workforce Development: 

    Dr. Biden meets Jackie ... http://t.co/TzDSBBZ8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1 is 2 Many Launches Dating Violence Public Service Announcement: 

	Last year, Vice President Biden launched ... http://t.co/TvsS3JM1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tune In to Hear the President on Student Loans: 

	In a little more than a week, the interest rates on federal... http://t.co/GvKLZdft]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Board with Jay Carney: 
	We caught Jay Carney -- the White House press secretary -- on the flight back from M... http://t.co/hkJqY0tx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Issue Beyond Debate: Congress Should Act Now to Protect Women: 
	Ed. Note: This op-ed was first published by ... http://t.co/HXcODikS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Giving Women Control Over Their Health Care: 
	Ed. Note: This article is a cross post from http://t.co/RQpGmff2

... http://t.co/lCryhl7X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First Lady Michelle Obama Leads Presidential Delegation to the Olympics: 

    First Lady Michelle Obama hu... http://t.co/2priNkaW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strengthening Tribal Communities Through the HEARTH Act: 

    President Barack Obama signs H.R. 205, the H... http://t.co/vcDd9OZF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the Archives: The Medicare Bill of 1965: 
	On July 30, 1965, President Lyndon B. Johnson signed into law th... http://t.co/5fMW3G4b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Address: The House of Representatives Must Act on Middle Class Tax Cut Extension: 
	President Obama urges... http://t.co/C5yttiSm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join the Conversation: Discussion on the Obama Administration’s Strategy towards sub-Saharan Africa: 
	Note: Pla... http://t.co/NYMKlRAg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First Lady Michelle Obama Hosts Let's Move! London: 
	Today, First Lady Michelle Obama joined 2,000 American mil... http://t.co/EOwjDyfA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More Than 2.4 Million Records Released: 
	In September 2009, the President announced that—for the first time in ... http://t.co/I2mWX9w1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Signs the United States-Israel Enhanced Security Cooperation Act: 

    President Barack Ob... http://t.co/kHi6Vf4H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Long-Term Game Plan for Solar Energy Development on our Public Lands: 
	Secretary Salazar’s Interior Departmen... http://t.co/8aKehKPM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fact Check: The Bust of Winston Churchill: 
	Lately, there’s been a rumor swirling around about the current loca... http://t.co/fdOB6rFa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David Plouffe: "The Reason Why I'm Hopeful": 
	Yesterday, David Plouffe, Senior Advisor to President Obama, sent... http://t.co/KBLK5ANE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow First Lady Michelle Obama at the 2012 Olympic Games in London on Twitter @LetsMove: 
	First Lady Michelle... http://t.co/rEuNDv4S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advance Estimate of GDP for the Second Quarter of 2012 and Annual Revision: 
	Today’s report shows that the econ... http://t.co/IiraJniC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Wing Week 07/27/12 “A Brighter Day Is Going To Come”: 
	This week, the President addressed the nation on th... http://t.co/fdNrNbcE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Pushes the House of Representatives on Middle Class Tax Cuts: 
	Kicking off a Cabinet meeting th... http://t.co/RIT2wqic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My First Job: Alonzo Mourning: 
	Summer Jobs+ is a call to action for businesses, non-profits, and government to... http://t.co/YO9gBynJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marking the 22nd Anniversary of the ADA: 
	Today, I had the pleasure of delivering remarks at the White House ob... http://t.co/JUB6nLIC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. Public Lands Continue to Create Jobs and Boost Local Economies Through Tourism, Restoration Efforts, and En... http://t.co/91SzWYuy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dr. Jill Biden Views the AIDS Memorial Quilt: 

    Dr. Jill Biden views sections of the AIDS Memorial Quil... http://t.co/dfzE9hUR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Far We've Come on AIDS: 
	This week, Washington, DC is hosting the International AIDS Conference. To mark th... http://t.co/NToijOvl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Speaks to the National Urban League: 

    President Barack Obama delivers remarks at the U... http://t.co/cIXCXp4N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the Archives: A Landmark Moment for Americans with Disabilities: 

    Photo of President George Bush ... http://t.co/ZtUYY2g4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Transitioning Our Service Members: 
	In August 2011, President Obama visited the Washington Navy Yard to discuss... http://t.co/SbGcOMax]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CBO Confirms: The Health Care Law Reduces the Deficit: 
	This afternoon, the Congressional Budget Office (CBO) r... http://t.co/xmmtAWcU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New “Shopping Sheet” Will Make It Easier for Students to “Know Before They Owe”: 
	Editor’s Note: You can read m... http://t.co/5YLnrHqs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Speaks to the Veterans of Foreign Wars: 
	Today, President Obama spoke to the Veterans of Foreig... http://t.co/Q441A21A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remembering Sally Ride: President Obama Salutes an American Hero: 

    President Obama greets former astro... http://t.co/Anlgob3F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By the Numbers: $140 Million: 

	Last week, the Consumer Financial Protection Bureau announced its first publi... http://t.co/DIb5yfOW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Offers Comfort to Aurora: 

    President Barack Obama hugs Stephanie Davies, who helped ke... http://t.co/MVa5jAdt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama welcomes 2012 International AIDS Conference Attendees: 

	 This week, the 19th International A... http://t.co/FmP0o3XF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wall Street Reform Two-Years Later: Reforming the System and Protecting American Consumers: 
	It’s now been almo... http://t.co/NVh6v8Ub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Address: Remembering the Victims of the Aurora, Colorado Shooting: 
	President Obama honors the victims o... http://t.co/ALX6m3O0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Tragedy in Colorado: 
	Just after midnight, a gunman walked into a busy movie theater in Aurora, Colorado an... http://t.co/BrnADSxd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Wing Week 07/20/12 "The Biennial Bring Back the Gold Edition": 
	This week, the President attended the Team... http://t.co/SzTrKCs5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reforming Wall Street, Protecting Main Street: An Update on Wall Street Reform: 
	Ed. note: This is cross-posted... http://t.co/rvtbMRNa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Photo Gallery: Behind the Scenes in June 2012: 
	The White House Photo Office just released their latest batch o... http://t.co/ZY33mmek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celebrating Perfection with the Baylor Lady Bears: 

    President Barack Obama welcomes Coach Kim Mulkey a... http://t.co/CsolGsXe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House Office Hours: #STEM Master Teacher Corps: 
	This morning, the Obama Administration announced the Pre... http://t.co/MOAlgJq4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By the Numbers: 10,000: 

	Today, the Obama Administration announced a plan to create a national STEM Master T... http://t.co/KqDGwMkA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helping Local Officials Achieve Healthier Communities with Let's Move! Cities, Towns and Counties: 

    Lo... http://t.co/bzzpoQSH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women in the Financial Sector: A White House Forum on Economic Growth: 
	Ed. Note: This piece is cross-posted fr... http://t.co/srIyGaT5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boosting Advanced Manufacturing and Driving Innovation: 
	President Obama has made revitalizing manufacturing a ... http://t.co/CuixHpVA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The President and First Lady Honor Nelson Mandela International Day: 

    First Lady Michelle Obama talks ... http://t.co/YMJbfAoW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advise the Advisor: Streamlining Improving, and Simplifying Rules and Regulations: 

	How can we continue to s... http://t.co/mgRPTD5m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Responsibly Expanding America’s Offshore Energy Development: 
	In recent weeks, the Department of the Interior a... http://t.co/obBhsMEp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So How Many Consumer Reporting Companies Are There?: 
	Ed note: The Consumer Financial Protection Bureau (CFPB) ... http://t.co/Cx58odLQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Know Your Farmer, Know Your Food - Across the United States: 
	Today, I hosted a Google+ Hangout with Agricultur... http://t.co/Q7RrOm66]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vice President Biden Speaks To Seniors About Retirement Security: 

    Vice President Joe Biden delivers r... http://t.co/qEDdCWUI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's Time to Keep the Conversation Going": 
	Last week, we organized a Google+ Hangout with Secretary of Housin... http://t.co/wLCEthYF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Missouri National Guard Joining Forces with Faith Community: 

    Dr. Biden meets with Missouri National G... http://t.co/a7Wtfa9r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First Lady Michelle Obama Honors Design Innovators at the White House: 
	First Lady Michelle Obama paid tribute ... http://t.co/Mi8mItpT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the Archives: Ruby Bridges Visits the White House: 
	One year ago today, President Obama got a visit from a... http://t.co/RzY6X9Pp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Address: It’s Time for Congress to Pass the Middle Class Tax Cut Extension: 
	President Obama calls on Co... http://t.co/GGTeQYve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Community College to Career: Preparing Workers for the Jobs of the Future: 
	Earlier this week, I had the opport... http://t.co/rpjnDD8P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[International Visitors to the U.S. Spent Record $13.9 billion in May, Helping Support U.S. Jobs: 
	Ed. Note: Thi... http://t.co/OnkOiQGJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Resurgence of Manufacturing: 
	The President knows that America’s middle class was built on the strength of ... http://t.co/ClCTGItU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join a White House Hangout on Local Foods: div.bio
  {
height: 150px;
}
div.imgleft
  {
  padding-bottom: 3px;
 ... http://t.co/7TBeCyGk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Wing Week: 7-13-12 or "Lets Agree To Do What We Agree On": 
	This week the President signed the MAP-21 Act ... http://t.co/ffm050Kf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hanging Out and Talking Mortgage Refinance with HUD Secretary Donovan and Zillow: 

	Earlier today, Secretary ... http://t.co/xizbgvmX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still Time for Summer Jobs: 

    Secretary Solis suits up to help local Job Corps students make smoothies ... http://t.co/IGKFXcPm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Assisting Iranians in Need: 
	On August 11, strong earthquakes in northwest Iran destroyed and damaged hundreds ... http://t.co/0WSUhLT7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s Go Time for the Presidential Innovation Fellows: 
	Excitement is building as we prepare for Thursday’s laun... http://t.co/cdARXozF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First Lady Michelle Obama Hosts First-Ever Kids' State Dinner: 

	Today, First Lady Michelle Obama hosted the ... http://t.co/ZQnfKSwh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Holds a Press Conference: 
	In an unscheduled visit to the White House briefing room this aftern... http://t.co/gGjkd33r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Behind the Scenes: White House Chefs Prep the Kids' State Dinner: 
	You can watch the Kids' State Dinner live to... http://t.co/B052z8t4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Address: Congress Should Back Plan to Hire Teachers: 
	With students starting to head back to school, Pre... http://t.co/FyL6e7S7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Wrap Up: Dream Day: 

	Here's a quick glimpse at what happened this week on http://t.co/4TLOL8vz:

	NASA... http://t.co/pWduevxb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Using Idle Earmarks to Improve Transportation and Put People to Work: 
	Ed. Note: This is cross-posted from The ... http://t.co/wWlAt2LM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Wing Week 08/17/12 or, "Dream Day": 

	Welcome to the West Wing Week, your guide to everything that's ha... http://t.co/Yk6rOwYT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boosting Innovation in the Rust Belt: 
	Soon, Youngstown, Ohio will be the home to a new public-private institut... http://t.co/meA045dH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Redoubling Efforts to Support American Manufacturing: 
	I just returned from the White House Business Council Am... http://t.co/pMs6ov1b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the Archives: President Obama's 2011 Rural Tour: 

	A year ago today, President Obama kicked off a bus to... http://t.co/lZpzUUiw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday to Julia Child from the White House: 
	Ed note: PBS invited White House Executive Pastry Chef Bil... http://t.co/wksTgVqe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[11 Facts About the Tax Debate: 
	Unless the House of Representatives takes action before January 1, 2013, taxes ... http://t.co/huCRIrkQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deferred Action for Childhood Arrivals: Who Can Be Considered?: 
	Ed. note: This post was originally published o... http://t.co/EdDVvtbv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jill-Care: Pre-Existing Condition Insurance Plan Keeps Her Running: 

	Ed. note: This is cross-posted from hea... http://t.co/KFu2mrsA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Banner Year for the U.S. Wind Industry: 
	
Click here to see the photo gallery. 

	Ed. note: This is cross-p... http://t.co/AdwGsJvR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More Help for Those Coping with the Drought: 
	Farmers in Iowa are among those struggling with the fallout from ... http://t.co/tiNLEWpp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celebrating the Soldier Athletes on Team USA: 

		As President Obama said in a recent Weekly Address, Americans ... http://t.co/5qlFh489]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Congratulates the Curiosity Team: 

    President Barack Obama talks on the phone with ... http://t.co/RmjDrUK0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Whitehouse Celebrates the 2012 Olympic Games in London: 
	Like people all over the world, the White House has b... http://t.co/0d4OogHz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welfare, Work and America’s Governors: 
	This morning, former Minnesota Governor Tim Pawlenty appeared on ABC an... http://t.co/cYinmm2g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Hosts Fourth Annual Iftar Dinner at the White House: 

	Last night, President Obama hosted his... http://t.co/IfPC51RG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Address All-Hands-On-Deck Response to the Drought: 
	President Obama discusses the Administration’s all-h... http://t.co/PyeuMJOJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Progress Toward a World Without Violence Against Women and Girls: 
	Eqlima is a young girl from Afghanistan. She... http://t.co/kMw8QhB8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Photo Gallery: Behind the Scenes of July 2012: 
	The White House Photo Office just released their latest batch o... http://t.co/ewK0cODu]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>