<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the largest life insurance companies in the US!  http://t.co/8kUvPea99O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just in time for winter - Touch Screen Texting Gloves  - http://t.co/z65cB0ZIHn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometime the best thing to get off your chest is your chin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't do any vulgar movements.  -  Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the History of the Hamburger  http://t.co/8nAj6fy4c9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't do fashion. I am fashion. - Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the first place, God made idiots. That was for practice. Then he made school boards. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NERD POWER Pin Button - Must Wear! http://t.co/AmveVYDuPp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adversity causes some men to break; others to break records. - William A. Ward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To make a rock'n'roll record, technology is the least important thing.  -  Keith Richards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Fun - Bumper Water Boats with Water Cannons! http://t.co/8TUD0UbobS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it's too close to bother to buckle your seat belt it's close enough to walk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gold Glitter Lips - Cool Look!  http://t.co/tKrIUZQ9Pq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He didn't believe in flying saucers until he tickled the waitress]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't accept your dog's admiration as conclusive evidence that you are wonderful. - Ann Landers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good-bye, Broadcast.  Hello, Conversation.  Shel Israel - Co-Author Naked Conversations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Style is knowing who you are, what you want to say, and not giving a damn --&gt; Orson Welles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't care half so much about making money as I do about making my point, and coming out ahead. Cornelius Vanderbilt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think the last 4 words of the national anthem are gentlemen, start your engines, you might be a redneck. - Jeff Foxworthy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't pay good wages because I have a lot of money; I have a lot of money because I pay good wages. - Robert Bosch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Planning Beach Camping Tips  http://t.co/9bGNS7vpvi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only those who risk going too far can possibly find out how far one can go. - T.S. Eliot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Celiac Disease And Gluten Free Foods  http://t.co/ITPx135uBW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Successful Alternatives For Link Building  http://t.co/4FIPwnQbvD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dog is the only thing on earth that will love you more than you love yourself. - Josh Billings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Early History of Hamburgers  http://t.co/uorfzfIWwD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to John D. Loudermilk  http://t.co/F53pmKtP6j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go Big, or Go Home - Eliza Dushku]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Face it tiger, you just hit the jackpot! - Mary Jane, Spider-Man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science fiction writers foresee the inevitable, and although problems and catastrophes may be inevitable, solutions are not. - Isaac Asimov]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We never repent of having eaten too little. - Thomas Jefferson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trust people and they will be true to you; Treat them greatly, and they will show themselves great. - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stumbling is not falling. - Portuguese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drill sarge to recruit:  "wipe that opinion off your face!”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes are just made from leather, rubber and cloth - read about exotic shoes... http://t.co/sga4qerUG5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The box said 'Requires Windows 95 or better'. So I installed LINUX.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Corona Beer  http://t.co/D7TPSN8NVX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The History of Lyme Disease  http://t.co/0nKdjIMoZj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the shoe fits, it's too expensive. - Adrienne Gusoff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't go into details, I've already told you  more than I overheard myself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first one gets the oyster the second gets the shell. - Andrew Carnegie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is Ununpentium?  http://t.co/Yjkh8jhEhw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peter Townshend shows us it's all right to grow up. There is dignity after rock'n'roll. - Sting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Isaac Asimov  http://t.co/4d2xa71Cgb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellence is to do a common thing in an uncommon way. - Booker T. Washington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once you've raced, you never forget it -- and you never get over it. - Richard Childress]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you think, your mouth is closed, but your mind keeps on talking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool Garages and Flooring Types  http://t.co/PMULv1G2uD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We (San Francisco) have football weather during baseball season, and baseball weather during football season. - Herb Caen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn the Keys to Using LinkedIn for Your Company  http://t.co/gXKai8b6Uz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having Fine Wine with Dinner - learn more! http://t.co/kl6mMbOH1F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have never let my schooling interfere with my education. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pair off in threes. - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good pitching will beat good hitting any time, and vice versa. - Bob Veale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great History of Johnny Ace: A ‘One of his Kind’ Musical Legend  http://t.co/I60XmFgV71]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft: "You've got questions. We've got dancing paperclips."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a moral imperative. - Chris Knight, Real Genius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thousands of years ago, cats were worshipped as gods. Cats have never forgotten this. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rock n' roll is dream soup, what's your brand? - Patti Smith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love This Nerds Candy Juniors Tunic Tank Dress with Nerd Glasses - Dig It! http://t.co/mW8WZxxFlU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A philosopher is someone who knows what to do until it happens to him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live daringly, boldly, fearlessly. Taste the relish to be found in competition - in having put forth the best within you. - Henry J. Kaiser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never look back unless you are planning to go that way. - Henry David Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Pink Floyd  http://t.co/CzNKuGNhKy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, where's the Cannes Film Festival being held this year?  Christina Aguilera]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And now, I'm just trying to change the world, one sequin at a time. Lady Gaga]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually, I majored in marketing and I have a bachelor of science. - Wanda Sykes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is what survives when what has been learned has been forgotten. - B. F. Skinner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Mars Rover Curiosity  http://t.co/euTLdYUfW0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion is a form of ugliness so intolerable that we have to alter it every six months. --&gt; Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is like a poker game, nobody wants to quit when he's losing: nobody wants you to quit when you're ahead. - Jackie Robinson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone who lives within their means suffers from a lack of imagination. - Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boys are Whatever, Shoes are Forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Invest in Penny Stocks And Earn Huge Profits  http://t.co/jPwqbeTM8G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rock n' roll is dream soup, what's your brand? - Patti Smith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the The Early History of Beer  http://t.co/mfZRX15ZMl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Neil Young  http://t.co/Lk2ZT2JMQM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Animals are such agreeable friends - they ask no questions, they pass no criticisms. - George Elliot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After the third flip, I lost control - Don Roberts after crashing in the Jade Grenade at New England Dragway in 1975.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Car sickness is the feeling you get when the monthly payment is due. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Different Types of Ashes Scattering Services  http://t.co/8Lxyja8TDo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Paul McCartney and Wings  http://t.co/GsMxe1fo9c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Hamstring Rehab  http://t.co/06NKg1DbUX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if you want to save face --  keep the lower half shut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I prefer the company of peasants because they have not been educated sufficiently to reason incorrectly. - Michel de Montaigne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Pet Insurance  http://t.co/VJFl8VvoDm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the history of the Modern Tennis Shoe  http://t.co/PCsmvijQYC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whether you think you can or whether you think you can't, you're right! - Henry Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most games are lost, not won! - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Paul Davis  http://t.co/C5prbGBhpj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Hallmarks of a Quality Insurance Company  http://t.co/PHb7ibIQZi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL A Toilet Mug for your Coffee!  http://t.co/dOcZCEw4Hi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If at first you don't succeed; call it version 1.0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Facebook-Top Tips for Business Success  http://t.co/hiU0x3wzgm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very "COOL" Titanic Ice Cube mold - http://t.co/VHdlbgV81y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I care not for a man's religion whose dog and cat are not the better for it. - Abraham Lincoln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Home is where -- . You hang your head]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating History of American Idol   http://t.co/WIYXpjCVzr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Setup an iPad Speaker System  http://t.co/R2eVDnwX4C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A toupee is ear to ear carpeting!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>