<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Dreams are like stars. You can't touch them,  but if you follow them, they will lead you to your destiny. –Spudnick  (Space Buddies)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/hwODqIJKjV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you leave, I just, I remember things better with you. –Dory (Finding Nemo)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friends stick to you like honey. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Telling stories and laughing with friends: precious moments you'll never forget. –Brother Bear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you ever wished for something so much you could feel it in your heart? –Ariel (Little Mermaid Series)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow! Retweet if you love these Disney Drawings!&gt;&gt; http://t.co/uS6Zh1sfNX - sp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'll be in my heart, no matter what they say. You'll be here in my heart, always. –Kala (Tarzan)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have got to get out of the past and look to the future. –Mildred (Meet the Robinsons)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can’t just wish on a star and expect things. –Tiana (Princess and the Frog)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listen to me. The human world is a mess. –Sebastian (Little Mermaid)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you had the chance to change your fate, would you? –Merida (Brave)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only way to fix a friendship is to try. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My world has changed, and so have I. I have learned to choose and I have learned to say goodbye. –Pocahontas (Pocahontas II)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You and me together, that's how it always should be. One without the other don't mean nothing to me. –Monster, Inc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For every problem, there's a solution. –Mrs.Potts (Belle's Magical World)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My love is higher than the sky, deeper than the  ocean, warmer than the sun shining down on me, quiet as a prayer.  –Ariel’s Beginning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It would be so nice if something would make sense for a change. –Alice (Alice in Wonderland)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We tried, and if we failed, we failed together. And to me, that’s not failing at all. –Kermit (The Muppets)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happiness is contentment, but it doesn’t mean you have to have wealth. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you follow your heart, there's no heart you can't win. –Cinderella II]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do or die, you gotta try. –A Bug’s Life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My heart has wings and I can fly. I'll touch  every star in the sky. So this is the miracle that I've been dreaming  of. –Cinderella]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think it's best to leave the past in the past. Do not look back. Only ahead. –Great Prince (Bambi II)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're braver than you believe, stronger than you seem, and smarter than you think. –Christopher Robin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be strong, be true, be forever ‘who you are’. –Kala (Tarzan II)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I do love you, but I've got to stop pretending to be something I'm not. –Aladdin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dreams do come true, and maybe something wonderful will happen. –Giselle (Enchanted)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone needs a family. No one should be alone. –Ariel (Little Mermaid Series)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can be happy or you can be unhappy. It's just according to the way you look at things. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marlin: “I promised him I’d never let anything happen to him.” | Dory: “That’s a funny thing to promise.” –Finding Nemo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Piglet: “How do you spell love?” | Pooh: “You don’t spell it. You feel it.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know what else to do except to try to dream of you and wonder if you are dreaming too, wherever you are. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My one true love. I'll find him someday. He's out there. I just know it. –Minnie Mouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I do marry, I want it to be for love. –Jasmine (Aladdin)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is taking a few steps backward, maybe even more, to give way to the happiness of the person you love. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Prince Charming didn't come along, Cinderella went over to the palace and got him. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Retweet if you love these Disney Movies!&gt;&gt; http://t.co/jAhgptXZ - sp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd get over losing anything, but I'll never get over losing you. –Toy Story]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you keep dreaming, I just know that someday you can make your wishes come true. –Cinderella (Princess Stories)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not fear death, but rather the unlived life. You don't have to live forever. You just have to live. –Tuck (Tuck Everlasting)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes the smallest things take up the most room in your heart. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walt Disney once said.. http://t.co/CYaFEaL2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can I go back? I'm not who I used to be. –Simba (The Lion King)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Retweet if you love these Disney Couples!&gt;&gt; http://t.co/xxNQSBFg - sp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The truth sounds insane sometimes, but that doesn't mean it's not the truth. –Linguini (Ratatouille)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My treasures were only things. You are my true treasures. –Ariel (Little Mermaid Series)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you keep saying no, it just makes me so, sometimes you make me so angry. –Giselle (Enchanted)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now statistics prove that you have one birthday, but there are 364 unbirthdays. –Mad Hatter (Alice in Wonderland)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always standing right beside you, one true friend is there to guide you, to believe in who you are. –Disney Fairies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have given so much happiness to others, that you deserve to have your wish come true. –The Blue Fairy (Pinocchio)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The more you like yourself, the less you are like anyone else, which makes you unique. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes the smallest thing can make the biggest changes of all. –Plio (Dinosaur)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You’re never alone, you know. Just think of your friends, the ones who care. –The Tigger Movie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep your chin up, someday there will be happiness again. –Robin Hood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I liked you. My mistake. –Colette (Ratatouille)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just don't see how a world that makes such wonderful things could be bad. –Ariel (Little Mermaid)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Close your eyes and pretend it’s all a bad dream. That’s how I get by. –Jack Sparrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love begins with trust, with mutual respect. All relationships must be firmly based on that. –Cogsworth (Belle's Magical World)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You've got a friend in me. If you got troubles, then I got them too. There isn't anything I wouldn't do for you. –Toy Story]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m a realist, and I’m not gonna go chasing after some fantasy. I’m going beyond what I see. –Timon (Lion King 1½)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I bet you didn't know this about Alice in Wonderland&gt;&gt; http://t.co/sYr1pYOy - sp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman appreciates a man who can make her laugh. –Genie (Aladdin)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’ve got no strings, so I have fun. I’m not tied up to anyone. –Pinocchio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is my family. I found it, all on my own. It’s little, and broken, but still good. Yeah, still good. –Stitch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Start at the beginning, and when you come to the end, stop. –Mad Hatter (Alice in Wonderland)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One thing it takes to accomplish something is courage. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need you to come here and find me ‘cause without you I'm totally lost. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, you should learn to control your temper. –Belle (Beauty and the Beast)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just because you can't see something, doesn't mean it doesn't exist. –Charlie (The Santa Clause)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You want love? Buy a dog. –Daisy Duck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can’t lose you again. I can’t. Not again. I’m not strong enough. –Mr. Incredible (The Incredibles)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're my ohana, and I'll always love you. –Lilo (Lilo &amp; Stitch 2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Retweet if you want a Disney tattoo like this&gt;&gt; http://t.co/mzWHMF7i - sp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They say if you dream a thing more than once, it's sure to come true. –Aurora (Sleeping Beauty)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He doesn’t understand me, but I can be myself around him. –Remy (Ratatouille)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't think, and don't worry. If the time comes, you'll know what to do. - Mrs. Incredible]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm like a shooting star, I've come so far. I can't go back to where I used to be. - Jasmine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dig a little deeper. Think of something that we've never thought of before. - Winnie the Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was heartbroken. It just didn't seem fair. –Cinderella (Princess Stories)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think of the happiest things. It's the same as having wings. –Peter Pan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are many voices around you, but you must listen to your own voice. –Pocahontas (Pocahontas II)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love can make miracles, change everything, lift you from the darkness and make your heart sing. –Cinderella 3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even a good decision, if made for the wrong reasons, can be a wrong decision. –Governor Swann (Pirates of the Caribbean)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What if it’s not everything I dreamed it would be? And what if it is? What do I do then? –Rapunzel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wasn’t worried at all, except for the part where I was worried, of course. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LOL look at these celebs that look like Disney Characters &gt;&gt; http://t.co/xT0ryJ6hUJ #sp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love can calm your fears, turning all your tears into smiles. –Cinderella 3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just a little love. That's how you begin, showing him you care. –Ariel (Little Mermaid Series)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I did know once, only I've sort of forgotten. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is me. I think it's apparent I need to rethink my life a little bit. What's my problem? –Remy (Ratatouille)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dream is a wish your heart makes when you're fast asleep. –Cinderella]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you could please donate to Relay for Life (Donators will be given a shoutout!) http://t.co/9Ida6YP5sO :) thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do you do when things go wrong? Oh, you sing a song. –Snow White]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do you know you don't like it if you won't try it? –Elinor (Brave)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friends are wonderful, don't you think? They're always there to lend a helping hand. –Jasmine (Aladdin Series)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s easy to feel like you don’t need help, but it’s harder to walk on your own. –Disney Fairies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You need to love yourself before someone can love you. I love myself, well, ladies come running. –Ken (Toy Story Campaign)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haven’t you ever had a dream? Something you wanted so bad you’d do anything? –Hercules]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder why each little bird has someone to sing. –Aurora (Sleeping Beauty)]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>