<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I love my crazy girlfriend - hilarious t-shirt - http://t.co/OKSQoTt1ff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Using Tumblr for Business  http://t.co/PaHASb7BdL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of In-N-Out Burger  http://t.co/qRDUMjwJID]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Jay Ferguson  http://t.co/87R4cFBjaB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't win unless you learn how to lose. - Kareem Abdul-Jabbar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Invest in Penny Stocks And Earn Huge Profits  http://t.co/fz14wiIWDM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marriage lets you annoy and aggravate one special person for the rest of your life.  What a joy LOL!!  :&gt;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Courage is not the absence of fear, but rather the judgment that something else is more important than fear - Ambrose Redmoon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome climbing t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the climbing lovers in your life!  http://t.co/Xj5JjIrNg8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Guide – Business to Business Internet Marketing Tips  http://t.co/IFBqikNbCK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mick Jagger can't even make a successful solo album, and the Stones are the biggest rock group that ever was.  - Don Henley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The time has come the Walrus said, To talk of many thing’s Of shoes and ships and sealing-wax of cabbages and kings - Lewis Carroll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I actually don't understand a word Paula's saying anymore. It's like a new language.  Simon Cowell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Renowned Tuba  http://t.co/MCSvS46DVS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Big-Dog Pet Fountain - Keeps Fresh and Tasty Water for Your Big Dog! http://t.co/B7flbKQw49]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Stylistics  http://t.co/aEmV4s1StU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not wait to strike until the iron is hot; but make it hot by striking - William B. Sprague]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wait a minute, Doc. Ah --  Are you telling me you built a time machine --  out of a DeLorean? - Marty McFly, Back to the Future]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The person who doesn't know where his next dollar is coming from usually doesn't know where his last dollar went.  Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never hit a man with glasses. Hit him with a baseball bat. - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bring the best of your authentic self to every opportunity.  John Jantsch - Author of Duct Tape Marketing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Condolence:  something that aches when everything else feels so good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter Can be an Invaluable Business Tool  http://t.co/YSUSKdf49Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of the Inheritance Series Third Volume – Brisingr  http://t.co/0lSAU1slGL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An ounce of prevention is worth a pound of cure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Health and Mana Video Game Inspired Earrings with Key Charms!  Cool! http://t.co/LDhN4Hiz8U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10-Light Star Wars Plastic Yoda Light Set - may the force be with you! http://t.co/oBn2Hn8GiR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Institutions that once had to go through media to deliver information are now themselves media - Andrew Nachison - Founder We Media]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge : " Your wife charges that you haven't spoken to her in  5 years. Why is that?" Defendant: "I didn't dare interrupt."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The man who can drive himself further once the effort gets painful is the man who will win. - Roger Bannister]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[History of Blogging  http://t.co/CsyQABk4KZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Snow Beer  http://t.co/TSqISwsfvm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So now I'm left with cigarettes, and I'm trying to scrape that off my shoe and then I'll be done. - Diane Lane]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is nothing so stupid as the educated man if you get him off the thing he was educated in.  - Will Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Magic texting glove with conductive yarn finger tips for iPhone, iPad and all touch screen devices - 4 colors  --&gt; http://t.co/vXEzaOnt7P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the dressing room, I always put on my right shoe first. Same thing for my right wristband. -  Mary Lou Retton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ELVIS - The King - One Person's Thoughts  http://t.co/zoJTQo2M9V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Confucius say it is better to be looked over than overlooked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jazz up  your pool or patio with these trendy light cubes - cool!  http://t.co/EayU7YaJWv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to John D. Loudermilk  http://t.co/HDAHVfAzlD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In order to break the ice --  crack a smile]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The Official How I Met Your Mother Premium Grey Silk Suit Jammies http://t.co/9RRoXbxDqE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the great department store of life, baseball is the toy department. - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sorry. You are right. Those pants don't make you look fat. - Jin-Soo Kwon  The only three things a woman needs to hear! - Sawyer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd like to compliment you on your work -- When will you start?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are seven winners of the Monaco Grand Prix on the starting line today, and four of them are Michael Schumacher. - Murray Walker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's always itching for money, but he never scratches for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Girls are like internet domain names, the ones I like are already taken.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Barbara Acklin a Great Singer http://t.co/mbwWR6lcZQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When money talks these days, it's probably asking what happened]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Use SEO on Multiple Websites to Drive Traffic in Your Direction  http://t.co/SnOvarghJJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome gardening t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the gardening lovers in your life!   http://t.co/oiBfg0vLqk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How tall am I? Honey, with hair, heels and attitude I'm through this damned roof! - Rupaul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blogging Lost – Season 1  http://t.co/CCZX47KdXD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You will never change your life until you change something you do daily. - Mike Murdock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Breaking News” Michael Jackson Song Stirs Controversy  http://t.co/hBIjS3iQ0w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Facebook-Top Tips for Business Success  http://t.co/z7pDzhD1eZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Ways to Use Website Builders for Links to Your Website  http://t.co/D0gI0dAc2Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one gets very far unless he accomplishes the impossible at least once a day. - Elbert Hubbard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If opportunity doesn't knock, build a door. - Milton Berle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two big firms are fighting for his services, the loser gets him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business has only two functions - marketing and innovation. - Milan Kundera]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is where you &amp; I are different. Because this is all I want to talk about. Letterman to Paris when she didn’t want to talk about jail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Michael Jordan Shoes  http://t.co/hqBenxCjaM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome - The World's Smallest Solar Powered Car! http://t.co/ccXwcaU3go]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I went to college for four years. - Kim Kardashian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I didn't have a big fat Greek wedding, but I have a lot of fat Greek friends. Pete Sampras]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Marie Antoinette's Watch  http://t.co/l1fyIchYKv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the Icebound Land by John Flanagan  http://t.co/CgqON5LEYB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Classic Cassette Silicone Case for Your iPhone! http://t.co/QriIbbhQS6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the first place, God made idiots. That was for practice. Then he made school boards. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[End Of Line - The MCP, TRON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm on a 90-day wonder diet. Thus far, I've lost 45 days. - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fascinating history of solar power - read on!  http://t.co/LqNe9QwDrX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the parents of a Little Leaguer, a baseball game is simply a nervous breakdown into innings. - Earl Wilson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Different Types of Major League Pitches  http://t.co/IKqXrdl31z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we can't live together, then we're going to die alone. - Jack Shephard, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Marketing Experts Reveal Tips to Success  http://t.co/CxMpbgSXS6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our work is the presentation of our capabilities. - Johann Wolfgang Von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If man is a little lower than angels, then angels should reform.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Empty pockets never held anyone back. Only empty heads and empty hearts can do that.  Norman Vincent Peale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fish Hotel Aquarium - Jazz Up Your Office! http://t.co/3qXtLR26UC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How to Select the Right Technology for Seniors  http://t.co/zJSRaLQsgw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep you can keep your devices charged via solar power - find out here - http://t.co/OZb0xoKDXr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't read other science fiction. I don't read any at all. - Jack Vance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL - Cool - A Computer Mouse with a Spider in it!   http://t.co/mPoJevKl7K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious T-Shirt - “I Got Your Back” http://t.co/biF2HsZ90m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Evolution of the Wooden Clog  http://t.co/kc1kuZz2sx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The quickest way to get a doctor today is to turn on your television set. . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The attention economy is not growing, which means we have to grab the attention that someone else has today.  Brent Leary - CRM Essentials]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Isley Brothers  http://t.co/5yA6jByGUt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Product Reviews Through the Eyes of a Child  http://t.co/1kZyUnwTVF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The earth? Oh the earth will be gone in a few seconds...I'm going to blow it up. It's obstructing my view of Venus. - Marvin the Martian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whether you think you can or whether you think you can't, you're right! - Henry Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some of the greatest Hollywood actors are not the award winners, but those congratulating them on their triumph]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no black magic to successfully attracting customers via the web.  Rand Fishkin, Founder SEOMoz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How To Find The Right Gluten Free Foods  http://t.co/cZYaDoQ0yx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The roots of education are bitter, but the fruit is sweet. - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doctor, giving prescription to a patient "Let me know if this stuff works. I'm having the same trouble myself."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Twilight Zone is a scifi TV classic - read its fascinating history here - http://t.co/arG0Ah5a67]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>