<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[After 20 Years of Silence, Strangers in Ethiopia and Eritrea Call to Say Hello https://t.co/joq1znN1X8 https://t.co/6InVJ3Ytpx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The dream of an African wide free-trade zone is still alive, as Nigeria says it will sign up 'soon'
 https://t.co/JH4WkyWTKL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the Ethiopia-Eritrea peace process could reunite one family https://t.co/3XY0jXub9T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BluntSpeaking: More extraordinary scenes in Ethiopia... https://t.co/VMwZHkF34s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This massacre in Cameroon. One of the most sickening videos I have ever seen https://t.co/FpwulyU7JV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @geoffreyyork: Kevin Anderson wins!  Amazing victory for the South African at Wimbledon. He battles back from a deep deficit, defeats Ro…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who cares what the stars earn? I care far more about the poor pay for BBC staff at the bottom of the pay scale - men and women! https://t.co/m4JqwhBIsi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @hawelti: #Eritrea; #Ethiopia: Driving on a fast lane for peace and cooperation: telephone links already restored; inaugural flight of E…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @campbellclaret: Spot on Jeremy https://t.co/H6qBYHih82]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South Africa: Who's behind the five bombs found in n Durban in the last week?
 https://t.co/CI4N4nfIeL via @dailymaverick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Barack Obama will give his most important speech since leaving office next week - in Johannesburg
https://t.co/Dh8lrmsz1n via @qzafrica]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Selkid: To my Ethiopian friends... you can't celebrate reform in #Ethiopia and celebrate a tyrant in #Eritrea Issias Afworki continues…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In case you missed it: Eritrea and Ethiopia have made peace. How it happened and what happens next https://t.co/EqWS7ocRU5 via @TC_Africa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UAE’s role in Ethiopia-Eritrea rapprochement draws praise https://t.co/bZ5s7D0EN9 https://t.co/FZx4SrjSPE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somalia: fighting fear with fun https://t.co/SPxsmHrEnS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HarunMaruf: BREAKING: Ethiopia Somali regional leader Abdi Mohamud Omar releases prisoners from Jail Ogaden today following the scathin…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The South African who formed  Britain’s Royal Air Force https://t.co/gAl9Gs81AS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[S Sudan: UN report describes campaign of gang-rape, killing and torture, with three commanders identified as bearing greatest responsibility https://t.co/NY1bsTVPbK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vanessa is absolutely right. Time for freedom and democracy in Eritrea - and the release of all political prisoners! https://t.co/QU2eSBGygC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ReutersAfrica: South Sudan government forces, allies killed, raped hundreds of civilians - U.N. https://t.co/6ro0MTHC92]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HurstPublishers: As Eritrea and Ethiopia reach a peace accord after years of conflict, @martinplaut ’s ‘Understanding Eritrea’ offers u…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prime Minister Abiy’s thank you letter to President Isaias https://t.co/K3Z2UqwYqR https://t.co/Er2otjsHSO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The smouldering resentment between Eritrea and Tigray explained https://t.co/yH1yRzVXZh https://t.co/C1QN3td9Ka]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @markc_anderson: #Ethiopia Airlines will next week launch two flights a day to #Eritrea, marking the first flights between the two count…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eritrea and Ethiopia have made peace. How it happened and what happens next https://t.co/7gMCJWeLnM https://t.co/sA45986e8Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eritrea and Ethiopia have made peace. How it happened and what next https://t.co/EqWS7ocRU5 via @TC_Africa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is shocking. Why turn your back on the UN if you have nothing to hide? https://t.co/27GNB4lI4F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israeli trade unions change policy, and admit refugees https://t.co/Vj44PW5wOR https://t.co/MIn6t4Idux]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MaggieFick: Ethiopians &amp; Eritreans currently in your respective countries: are you able to reach each other by phone? In Addis our repo…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ethiopia and Eritrea say war over, UN Secretary General hails "wind of hope" in Africa 
https://t.co/asETOvheaZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remind me how often Corbyn voted against Labour ? https://t.co/vkoDJJi5FV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Keir_Starmer: Theresa May’s Brexit strategy has failed. Parliament must take the lead.  https://t.co/2q3DJyhCCU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.N. chief says sanctions on Eritrea likely to become obsolete | Article [AMP] | Reuters https://t.co/d5t0Obn52s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ReutersAfrica: Ethiopian Airlines to resume flights to Eritrea's Asmara next week -Ethiopian media https://t.co/97UIHa9ND2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boris Johnson quits to add to pressure on May over Brexit https://t.co/DCe18KluGR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheNamibian: Air Namibia is expected to generate N$140 million in revenue from the West Africa route as part of the implementation of c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @hawelti: Wheels Up! Prime Minister Abiy Ahmed and his delegation head home after a historic and successful Summit in a two-day official…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[War ends between Eritrea and Ethiopia https://t.co/at1XPZCC9y https://t.co/mVcty3S1j1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @hawelti: Eritrea and Ethiopia have signed a Joint Declaration of Peace and Friendship today.  The Agreement, which specifies five pilla…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fantastic news! https://t.co/NyI38gUlJF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am pleased it is being read! Hope you enjoy it. https://t.co/fpAbObIWsx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ReutersAfrica: South Africa releases Zuma's son on bail after corruption charges https://t.co/kFjnguw4Qk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UN issues official list of those accused of human trafficking in Libya https://t.co/uk4MDNl3sz https://t.co/NArpxiQrdi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UN chief to meet Ethiopia's PM in Addis Ababa on Monday after peace breakthrough with Eritrea. Excellent. UN acting to cement reconcilliation 
https://t.co/ZncfkySWQd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @hawelti: President Isaias: "the tumultuous welcome accorded to Prime Minister Abiy underscores how much the people of Eritrea cherish p…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From Special Relationship to Special War: Can Eritrea and Ethiopia make a Special Peace? https://t.co/uHRovoXuG9 https://t.co/NZI4lgLEvr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MaggieFick: Another pretty surprising development from the weekend here in East Africa:
JUBA, July 8 (Reuters) - South Sudan’s former v…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @bbclaurak: Sources close to Johnson say no statement planned for tomorrow - he is helpfully however expeted to be doing a press confere…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Natberh: Breaking News :- #Eritrea is invited to rejoin #IGAD after over a decade absence. It's to be recalled that IGAD was instrument…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @bbclaurak: Things VERY febrile in Tory party - not so long ago that some pointed to DD as replacement for May - after conference last y…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @bbclaurak: Hear minister is Steve Baker who is said to be about to resign or to have just done so]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or even a summer election? https://t.co/GZjUxBRQmF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PA: #Breaking Brexit Secretary David Davis has resigned from the Government, the Press Association understands https://t.co/dKCkiqFk82]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @britainelects: David Davis MP (Con, Haltemprice and Howden) has resigned as Brexit Secretary.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Labour must change anti-Semitism code of conduct 'sharpish' - Sir Keir Starmer - Sky News https://t.co/XcdD0DoDGu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@elaichimhamed I have direct messaged you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['These changes are unprecedented': how Abiy is upending Ethiopian politics https://t.co/YFZW5ST4xM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Sarah_Hayward: Good for Keir. A number of local members had expressed deep concern about this. https://t.co/Sj5bPd0XdY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HarunMaruf: BREAKING: Ethiopia and Eritrea to normalise relations, open embassies in each other’s capital; direct phone connections res…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ethiopian Prime Minister Abiy in Asmara on historic visit – in pictures https://t.co/VEWy3qOKEj https://t.co/7oY3BHdvsa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I agree up to a point. Some negotiations need to be Confidentail until agreements can be found https://t.co/zWmyp1qjuy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An excellent beginning. So much to do. https://t.co/ueatGY9W8R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With hugs, leaders of rivals Ethiopia, Eritrea finally meet https://t.co/eQo5FGLkCe https://t.co/zyNjCBAneD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prime Minister Abiy of Ethioia arrives in Eritrea. Unthinkable only months ago https://t.co/TKUGTKOxJV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mvreisen: Thousands cheer Ethiopian leader’s visit to former enemy Eritrea for unprecedented summit https://t.co/RgAVQ7ZgL4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Natberh: @martinplaut The confirmation also seems well coordinated...Fitsum Arega (Chief of staff for the PM) and Yemane G/Meskel (Spok…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ethioia confirms Prime Minister Abiy visiting Eritrea today. An opportunity for peace and reconciliation https://t.co/J5R0Hh663i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mogadishu car bomb attack claimed by al-Shabab https://t.co/3tHzESF3YY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @edrisu2: #Eritrea|ns are celebrating in #Asmara with the #Ethiopia|n flag https://t.co/xJHBDTTuwu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ethiopian Prime Minister Abiy Ahmed will conduct a two-day state visit to the U.S. from July 28-29 https://t.co/fVxGjUw4Ck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @edwardcropley: "The people of Bulawayo, they love me," says #Zimbabwe's Mnangagwa. Let's wait and see... What goes around, comes around…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eritrea plans to welcome Ethiopian Prime Minister Abiy. Unthinkable before his premiership. Many issues to overcome but with goodwill anything is possible https://t.co/PN7UjBDo6T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Allehone: Eritrea preparing to welcome Ethiopian PM. What a wonderful development....blesssed are the peacemakers....Photos shared by E…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Natberh: Some reports say @Dr_Abiy_Ahmed to arrive #Asmara #Eritrea on Sunday &amp; people are ordered 2 come out 2 streets &amp; welcome him.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @burke_jason: In the Cape Town enclave that survived apartheid, the new enemy is gentrification. My  despatch from one of the loveliest…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why U.K Should Not Recognise Zimbabwe Election Result – Kate Hoey, British MP.  https://t.co/Ojbi831swo via @Allnet Africa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The biography of Mugabe by Sue Onslow and I now prominently on sale in Cape Town International Airport https://t.co/tvYDJ21gmp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @john_pether: Wonderful story of the Indian island of Janjira - which had an African Muslim nawab and a Jewish prime minister
https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @hawelti: The President of z Republic of South Sudan, General Salva Kiir Mayardit, arrived in Asmara today for official visit to z count…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GhideonMusa: #Ethiopia denies news reports of withdrawing its troops from the highly militarized areas along the #Eritrea n boarder.
 h…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TomGardner18: My @MonocleMag story about peace between #Eritrea and #Ethiopia, on board the first flight in 20 years. With @luistatopho…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to make a stand https://t.co/h4rvqB9BJ4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South African Graft Probe Hearing on Zuma begins Monday  https://t.co/9b8ImvSI1D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kofi Annan, former UN chief, dies at 80. A Secretary General who had many fine attributes but also failed on Rwanda  https://t.co/2LCMA66A6R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @asmarinoen: Swiss Court Rules that #Eritrea’s never-ending compulsory military service is not adequate grounds for granting... https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KjetilTronvoll: Concern among #Eritrean refugees in #Ethiopia of possible (forced?) return to #Eritrea. Reforms in Eritrea needed to mi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @willintune: US embassy in Uganda calls on the government to show the world that Uganda respects its constitution and the human rights o…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @UCTLibrary_SC: The 1968 University of Cape Town "Mafeje Affair" and student protest sit-in for academic freedom: 50th anniversary. See…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @davidpilling: #Africa cannot count on a demographic dividend https://t.co/CN0DfGC9OQ via @financialtimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sudanese Westminster terror suspect had received British passport two weeks ago, friends say
https://t.co/eyN7XvBxjH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“This excellent short biography of former Zimbabwean President Robert Mugabe covers his life from Zimbabwe’s independence, in 1980, to his ouster last year in a military coup. “ https://t.co/QjtvVYpEmp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @adrianblomfield: Shocking that no sitting British PM has visited Kenya for 30 years. Last was Thatcher in '98, though Cameron was due t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JacquesMaree73: Unbelievable. A whole big Gauteng municipality has all its vehicles repossessed due to non-payment. That's traffic, wat…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TomGardner18: And in some circles Teddy Afro is still the most popular man in the country. *Maybe*. ENDS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @UmaruFofana: Breaking News: The #SierraLeone Navy has just seized a Chinese boat illegally fishing in the country’s waters. It’s being…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will Ross should know:  he has reported on Uganda for years https://t.co/72LKZAeYuF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reporting from a country that feels like a prison https://t.co/yYAZNvb6XB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Doylebytes: Yes, radio matters enormously in poorer countries. I’m sure the BBC’s West Africa Ebola health messages in 2014/15, plus br…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KjetilTronvoll: Former PM Hailemariam unveils the internal #EPRDF power struggle in #Ethiopia : « Whenever I brought new reforms before…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Selkid: Eritrea: Hundreds of water-tanker owners under arrest: https://t.co/rCJR8vWzic]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>