<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaogungbesan If things are bad, they will get better. You will make it through.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaogungbesan You are fantastic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaogungbesan What you make and give and create is valuable and worthy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaogungbesan Life is a process. It never ends, but it does improve.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaogungbesan This world would be a different and worse place without you. Thanks for being here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaogungbesan The impact you leave on the universe can never be erased.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaogungbesan You are enough as you are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaogungbesan You are on your way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaogungbesan Hi! I like you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaogungbesan You're my favorite you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaogungbesan Everything will be all right. You'll see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ElizabethKGreen You are enough as you are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaggieDuke15 You deserve a better life than the one you have now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things may be hard right now, but they'll get better. I promise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you find yourself skipping breakfast, try buying a big box of granola bars!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning everyone!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaogungbesan Some days are just the worst. But you can handle them. You can.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@enistoja I think you're doing a great job today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beuktv Hee, thank you for the attention!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaogungbesan Thank you for listening to me! It makes me happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaogungbesan Your wishes are not too grand. They're yours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaogungbesan You got this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaogungbesan Life is a process. It never ends, but it does improve.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaogungbesan You are a luminous being.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KDBryan This world would be a different and worse place without you. Thanks for being here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaogungbesan You deserve everything that you hope for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaogungbesan You are worthy of the good things in your life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaogungbesan You are deserving of happiness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaogungbesan It's really tough to be kind to yourself, but please keep trying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pasparaki5 You are just so great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justinyourmind You deserve everything that you hope for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In hard times, some people become warriors, some become diplomats, and some become healers. They're all needed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichelleBocklag Thank you for listening to me! It makes me happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lrogers66821 You're my favorite you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even introverts need people sometimes. Say hello to your friends!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alteregobae Everything is gonna be okay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marilopxz You are worthy of the good things in your life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JuryisStillOuch You are just so great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaniPhantom__ It's so great to have you here today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alteregobae Hugs if you want them!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@not_theimp The universe is better for having you in it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drawpetrichor You've accomplished more than you think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coffeespoonie Thank you for reaching out to me. I know it's not always easy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hez_1979 Being friends with you is great! People should tell you that more often.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Starteddy Hi! I like you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leezy206_ Some days are just the worst. But you can handle them. You can.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alteregobae You are worthy of the good things in your life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pasparaki5 How are you so awesome?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@milas_universe Being friends with you is great! People should tell you that more often.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaogungbesan Hee, thank you for the attention!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaggieDuke15 You are deserving of happiness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PandaMymla Being friends with you is great! People should tell you that more often.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breakfast and lunch are as important as dinner, so please don't skip them!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Anon2World This world would be a different and worse place without you. Thanks for being here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Anon2World You are on your way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@T_Barbs I really like the thought that my kind words might help you. You matter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Anon2World You are better at doing *you* than anyone else possibly could be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Anon2World Every step you take is a step forward.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pasparaki5 Thank you for talking to me! It makes me happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pasparaki5 I love saying nice things to you! The idea of helping make you happy makes me happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pasparaki5 I think you're doing a great job today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alicia_rowley You've accomplished more than you think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keldi You're amazing, you know!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@weekendvamps You are loved.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pasparaki5 You contribute amazing things to the world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pasparaki5 You're such a good friend to reach out when you need it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pasparaki5 You are a good you. No one is better at being you than you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@karlitaliliana You're doing the best you can.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@luckylarkspur You've accomplished more than you think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@literalprince This world would be a different and worse place without you. Thanks for being here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@literalprince We've all got to be kind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sulkinq Please be kind to yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jillsnyderrr You've accomplished more than you think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@literalprince You make a difference in this world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@demonplayboys It's hard to get through life. You're doing a better job than you know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeyMrBass You deserve everything that you hope for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maaryxh You are deserving of happiness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you hydrated?  If not, have a glass of water.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaogungbesan What you make and give and create is valuable and worthy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaogungbesan I believe you, and I believe in you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaogungbesan You deserve respect. Never believe otherwise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaogungbesan You rock.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaogungbesan It's okay. Please treat yourself as well as you'd treat a friend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaogungbesan You're amazing, you know!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ecampo12 You contribute amazing things to the world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheBookNerdess9 I'm happy to have you here, exactly as you are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CamilleDeMere You are the culmination of eons of existence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BVilivusonline Our trials may never be over, but that means you'll never stop getting stronger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even bots get scared sometimes. But I think we can make it through together.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SecretDouce You're so lovable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BVilivusonline You make a difference in this world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sulkinq The impact you leave on the universe can never be erased.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@astudyinsnoggy You're amazing, you know!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Starteddy You are better at doing *you* than anyone else possibly could be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somebody misses you right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deluxetumbra Thank you for living out loud. We're all so lucky to have you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sulkinq Thank you for living out loud. We're all so lucky to have you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@quietnqueer I think you're doing a great job today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey! It's time for a break!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@klmross Do you ever watch a video or listen to a song you really like on repeat? It can really help your outlook!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>