<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[How a 9-Year-Old Entrepreneur's Business Went Viral: Millions of people have tuned into an 11-minute video of en... http://t.co/bA0yDEcU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Product Placement's Future: The 'Gossip Girl,' Birchbox Mashup?: The cosmetics darling will offer customers a 'G... http://t.co/w23kWqqo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Corporate Blogging Hits the Skids: Do you still blog on behalf of your company? If you do, you’re part of a dyin... http://t.co/3eTt6skG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Outsourcing Social Media Marketing Makes Sense (Video): While most businesses should handle social media in... http://t.co/KNwctHyM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft Touts $479M Online Loss in Q3 As Improvement: Overall, the results that Microsoft shared yesterday fro... http://t.co/0euWD25T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NBC Launches London 2012 Olympics Website, Promises To Stream All Events Live Online: With 100 days to go until ... http://t.co/3eo1cEfV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Building a Profitable Wearable Device May Depend on Who You Partner With: Electronic devices that are worn on th... http://t.co/5q3Z6L9p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consumers Say No to High Volume of Digital Ads: 66% of consumers say they’re on the receiving end of too many di... http://t.co/KIE5uOmj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making Sense of the Cloud for Small Business: Making Sense of the Cloud for Small BusinessThis content from: Duc... http://t.co/dosHOC9e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do You Know What Your Business is Really Worth?: If you found an investor for your business right now, would you... http://t.co/zIWXqtDK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Entrepreneurs: 'One Percenters'?: As part of Entrepreneur Week in New York, entrepreneurs walk to put a face on ... http://t.co/YHoU0pXh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A VC Reflects on Instagram, the Dot-Com Bust and What It All Means for Hungry Startups: Rapid growth and its fou... http://t.co/t4V8jIVc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Offers TV-Like Viewable Impressions, Ratings Technology: Google joins the list of online ad venue that is... http://t.co/QUiadi3m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Small-Business Lending: Getting Better, Still Not Great: Small-business lending has been showing signs of life, ... http://t.co/R0CEIsnI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook Advertising: Rates Go Up as Clicks Come Down: If you’re on a see-saw, you expect one side to go up whil... http://t.co/TllVckKI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Serial 'Trep Gurbaksh Chahal on Being Driven to Succeed (Video): In this 'Trep Talk Extra, the young multimillio... http://t.co/FGF8bG7L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Media Dust Up Highlights Interconnectedness of the Online Life: There is plenty of debate as to whether t... http://t.co/HywWwA97]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gas Prices, Health-Care Law Keep Small Businesses from Hiring: While small-business owners are feeling slightly ... http://t.co/96BFrSfW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook Marketplace Ads: 41% Higher CPMs, But Softening U.S. Market: Facebook's average Cost per Thousand impre... http://t.co/6U1OQ6yV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Four Ways to Write Off Health-Care Expenses (Video): Accountant Mark Kohler discusses four options for taking ad... http://t.co/gY4vwcQb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Build a Business That Cannot Fail: How to Build a Business That Cannot FailThis content from: Duct Tape M... http://t.co/JdRBY5mj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Filson Is Stuff That Works: Filson Is Stuff That WorksThis content from: Duct Tape Marketing
This is a new Sunda... http://t.co/dWWDLfjL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three Tips for Maximizing the Meals Write-Off (Video): Accountant Mark Kohler offers advice for how you can make... http://t.co/RYn2lJr4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cup of Joe: How I Make Email Better: 
I hate email. Like really hate it, I spend 90% of my day in my inbox. I do... http://t.co/STkp77su]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Hunger Games' Good for Business: Since its big-screen debut, 'The Hunger Games' has helped merchants hawk every... http://t.co/IRy85kFt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Closing Bell: Facebook buys TagTile | Instagram's 40M users | Domain name extension: Social Media:

Facebook buy... http://t.co/kgDHtySG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google's Microsurvey Tool Pays Off for Publisher: Two weeks ago Google rolled out a microsurvey option for publi... http://t.co/uj4eg7Ce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Five Easy Tools for Adding Game Elements to Your Website (Video): Think you need to be a tech whiz to add game m... http://t.co/iDmwY734]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Media Screw Ups In Any Language Cause Pain for Brands: As much as we might hate to admit it, it is import... http://t.co/cxaaq7PY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Startups Can't Ignore Washington: Web video company Boxee learned, from a customer, of an FCC rule that could hu... http://t.co/WfjAxAfb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are Boomer Entrepreneurs Preparing to Cash Out?: Business-for-sale transactions hit their highest level in more ... http://t.co/rKfVW15Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TaskRabbit's Leah Busque on Staying Competitive: The startup has survived competitive challenges by following th... http://t.co/lSdpN5Qi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reimagine Your Company as an Upstart: You can't stand out unless you do something different—or differently—than ... http://t.co/IpHaBmJV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want More Startups? Learn From Chile: The Chilean government's counterintuitive program that pays entrepreneurs ... http://t.co/x8BaxeZI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tony Hawk on Making a Twitter Treasure Hunt Go Global -- and Viral (Video): The skateboard icon and entrepreneur... http://t.co/dOsgxapW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LinkedIn Adds Ability to Target Follower Updates: On Facebook, you follow a brand because you like it, but do yo... http://t.co/zi6wVuKY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From E-Books to E-Commerce to Cloud Computing, States Are Getting More Involved: First it was the online sales t... http://t.co/68EoS2ET]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Filed Your Taxes? You Deserve a Cup of Coffee: Most companies link their promotions to days that people love to ... http://t.co/HuE4Xx7R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting More Out of Pinterest [Infographic]: Pinterest is the social media darling of the moment. Personally, I ... http://t.co/YsrQ9Nuv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook's Instagram Buy To Kick Off Venture Capital Feeding Frenzy: The young startup has a small staff and no ... http://t.co/Cwswp295]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Small Business Confidence May Mean Bad News for Jobs: The share of business owners planning to add jobs is at it... http://t.co/ZueH92vC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Does a 20 Percent Tax Cut Sound? Don't Hold Your Breath: Next week, Congress will take up a piece of legisla... http://t.co/mkg13hyB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Selling Your Business? Serial 'Trep Gurbaksh Chahal Says Be Bought, Not Sold (Video): In this 'Trep Talk Extra, ... http://t.co/BBiI3sl6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crowdfunding Sites Launch a Preemptive Strike on Fraud: The new law that makes it easier for private companies t... http://t.co/qwn6Sine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook Buys Instagram: Well, this is certainly an interesting development. Facebook has acquired Instagram for... http://t.co/3IC6tw0A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Despite Competitors’ Efforts, Google’s Popularity Soars: If you were to only read about the actions of the Europ... http://t.co/fMz1CtsX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taking a Gap Year? Go Global.: These burned-out professionals decided to use career breaks to tour -- and work -... http://t.co/gBFE4skN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bulova Mil 3818 Is Stuff That Works: Bulova Mil 3818 Is Stuff That WorksThis content from: Duct Tape Marketing
T... http://t.co/rAG9QW8j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm Being Audited. Now What? (Video): Don't let a tax audit get you down. Accountant Mark Kohler offers four tip... http://t.co/4EWySYxX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekend Favs April Seven: Weekend Favs April SevenThis content from: Duct Tape Marketing
My weekend blog post ro... http://t.co/rhzmKRIU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to Hire?... Maybe Not So Fast: Even as the pace of hiring eases, small businesses continue to haul the job ... http://t.co/1oq2EyoP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Good Mentor Will Tell It Like It Is: For many new businesses, finding the right advisor can make all the diffe... http://t.co/9P4xund3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bottom Ad Placement CTRs on the Rise and Other Google News: New statistics about Google’s search and related ad ... http://t.co/kMQsBg5g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketing Pilgrim’s On Easter Break: We here at Marketing Pilgrim will be taking a few days off to celebrate Eas... http://t.co/ubNJaUdK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which Retailer Is the Most Relevant? Amazon!: What retailer, would you say, is the most dependable? Reflects you... http://t.co/vsEzoxUQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Letterpress Thrives in an iPad Age: A centuries-old technology catches on with entrepreneurs http://t.co/bLIvEKYP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roadblocks to Innovation: How to Keep Moving Forward in Business: Kraft has been making cheese since the early 1... http://t.co/sPjUZJJ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook Gives App Developers More Tools: Facebook is rolling out three new tools for developers to monitor the ... http://t.co/nXDcwFPn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can You Design Your Own Luck?: A new book by Beth Goldstein argues that luck isn't random - and business owners ... http://t.co/Wz5NtZ2A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Closing Bell: Google+ surpassing predictions | Project Glass | Yahoo layoffs: Social Media:

Google CEO Page: so... http://t.co/yXClfpzj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[App and Mobile Browsing Up Nearly 5% Over Last Year: Depending on your half full / half empty point of view, a 5... http://t.co/wouKPkQP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buddy Media’s YouTube Partnership Reflects Google+'s Importance to Search: Buddy Media just unveiled a partnersh... http://t.co/Y3vkozya]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Continues Search for Other Revenue With Movie Rental Deal: Google is very busy trying to make sure that t... http://t.co/JtWR4Ihs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Handle Negative Online Reviews of Your Business: User-generated reviews of your business are more popular... http://t.co/kZj5y9fl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out my latest #podcast https://t.co/NGhF24o2yt on #Podbean]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[really sad to see this Richard https://t.co/e4C119LOWy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@melissavcomedy Melissa can we do a nifty interview with you for the https://t.co/QFWueKBsbR show?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The truth about marketing. https://t.co/PbOqOsmPDR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My mastermind group at QVC last week! https://t.co/8Oayy4QhJw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@madlemmingz haha ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mompreneur?  "7 Secrets for Getting a Lot More Done as a Mompreneur"  https://t.co/gks5QxF4D8 https://t.co/p94BPRNGNe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[social media Andrew Lock: https://t.co/7hvo8XwPlZ via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spotted this in a restaurant at the register... https://t.co/kNvg2Z5B0n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MintMilana or you can email me: andrew (at) https://t.co/4Z4W7SzKWN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[international marketing ideas: https://t.co/DxCzTJLewd via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I liked a @YouTube video from @melissavcomedy https://t.co/YPtRSYX0pC My Favorite Voices to Do | Melissa Villaseñor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheChuckWang thanks Chuck!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@social74977938 thank you Chris!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I liked a @YouTube video from @andrewlock https://t.co/yj6mSeZERn andrew lock business help]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I liked a @YouTube video from @andrewlock https://t.co/5JFoNf9nV0 Andrew Lock Branding]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I liked a @YouTube video from @andrewlock https://t.co/jVX8XkeKhL business entrepreneur]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of my favorite foods: Greek salad and kebab! https://t.co/imuLjueWGw https://t.co/uTLppbN2di]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I liked a @YouTube video from @andrewlock https://t.co/U3blrLK7qp Creative Guerrilla Marketing Ideas &amp; Strategies With Andrew Lock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I liked a @YouTube video from @andrewlock https://t.co/0nnUxizL4o The Art Of Influencing with Shari' Alexander Marketing Tips]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn from your failures. https://t.co/e0uIz2VzXz https://t.co/EIRqUNgoby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flying over Lake Michigan at sunset a few days ago and a quote that reflects my love for t… http://t.co/Go2qp9YYkS http://t.co/nGwguWyJoP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deceptive Marketing And Advertising Practices: http://t.co/ZeM1IHUZaW via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Implementation!  #guykawasaki #helpmybusiness #andrewlock #marketing #marketingonline #vid… http://t.co/q0jMjP3fZP http://t.co/KSnKFjehkn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[176: The Pompous Pizza Chef, Sex Education, Creating Animation Videos Online, and a Big Marketing Lesson from Rober… http://t.co/DWO58oq30G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[176: The Pompous Pizza Chef, Sex Education, Creating Animation Videos Online, and a Big Marketing Lesson from Robe… http://t.co/Jthrt0kp8h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@melissavcomedy howdy Melissa, did you get my email the other day about doing an interview?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marcuslemonis I have dairy and gf allergies so I ordered some Vegan chocs from Sweet Petes - theyre the best Ive ever had!  Really good!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Top 25 Brands on Instagram: See which brands made the list and what makes people engage with them. http://t.co/vxcNMvLh9Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sprint Shareholders Approve $21.6 Billion SoftBank Acquisition: A vote on Tuesday ended a contentious takeover... http://t.co/ePg6O59I2H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Media May Soon Drive More Traffic to Your Website Than Search Engines: A new report suggests internet u... http://t.co/Jaw86mQfRR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Z.E.R.O. Hour: 
My 4th book, Z.E.R.O., which is being co-authored by my former client and current friend, Maar... http://t.co/T5xiBUe7EN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YouTube Offers to Help Partners with Giant Ad Budgets Make More Money: While presenting at the Cannes Lions In... http://t.co/4XvHJL77UY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thoughts On Arrested Development Season 4 &amp; How Netflix Is Changing The Future Of TV: As you’ve no doubt heard... http://t.co/TI6DPeW1iD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beyond the Food Truck: 10 Unique Mobile Businesses: From dog grooming to vintage accessories, many entrepreneu... http://t.co/Fpai81PQ2J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Upload and Optimize YouTube Videos for SEO: Here are tips for making sure you've uploaded your videos c... http://t.co/HBTCO87aB7]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>