<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Live the Thug Life with These Temporary Tattoos! http://t.co/eBrSsbnxLI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And now, I'm just trying to change the world, one sequin at a time. Lady Gaga]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[M*A*S*H is an American TV classic - read all about its history -  http://t.co/QDIXSjd55r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome marriage t-shirts &amp; gear - give the gift of marriage!  http://t.co/XRz5lrnBOi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only point in making money is, you can tell some big shot where to go. Humphrey Bogart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winners take time to relish their work, knowing that scaling the mountain is what makes the view from the top so exhilarating. Denis Waitley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Dave Mason  http://t.co/2hwp0ybRO7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Publishing Management with HootSuite  http://t.co/Iu1tla07Vo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing worthwhile comes easily. Work, continuous work and hard work, is the only way to accomplish results that last. - Hamilton Holt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[USBCELL AA Rechargeable Batteries work just like rechargeable batteries - simply recharge by any powered USB Port http://t.co/6QoZTDtii0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bonsai Trees Are So Cool --  http://t.co/GAsMbR9LNB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the God Particle – Higgs Boson – On the Run  http://t.co/L9EZgaJTvV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many a small thing has been made large by the right kind of advertising. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every day, in every way, I am getting better and better. - Emilie Coue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Barbara Mason  http://t.co/jF2mC0gfAv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Europe – Best Places to Tour  http://t.co/KJRs75ZUnO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Careers end with a ground ball to shortstop, not with a home run. - Bull Durham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome baseball t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the baseball lovers in your life!   http://t.co/P4W4NEtFmO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not let what you cannot do interfere with what you can do. - John Wooden]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My wife is such a terrible cook the police made her register her stove as a deadly weapon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting Overview of Top 10 International Beers  http://t.co/OzWQuXxapS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is the only major sport that appears backward in a mirror. - George Carlin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Saving Money With Solar Power  http://t.co/oK19Q4xStO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is A Derivative?  http://t.co/FAvwJ5tZ9N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DC Comics Ultimate Character Guide http://t.co/J335WBPPiI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best way to show appreciation for a favor is to enjoy it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always wear expensive shoes. People notice. - Brian Koslow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Life? Cool! Where can I download one of those?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't compare me to my father. Our similarities are different. -  Dale Berra about his father Yogi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its better to own the racecourse then the race horse - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Blue Oyster Cult   http://t.co/vNoObaefP9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A tax collector has what it takes to take what you got]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Manolo Blahnik  http://t.co/gJyRtSZPRG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the God Particle – Higgs Boson – On the Run  http://t.co/L9EZgaJTvV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Credit card sized took kit with 2-Inch Serrated Knife, can/bottle opener &amp; Flat screwdriver, tweezers &amp; toothpick! http://t.co/p3xd43nFlO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Motown, Motown, that's my era. Those are my people.  Hillary Clinton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are so many emotions involved that I would like to wait until I know I'm with the right person &amp; married. Britney on virginity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Very Interesting History of Shoe Sizes  http://t.co/lDBj6XPFJI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So exactly how did the modern Garage evolve into its current form?  Very interesting... http://t.co/6mGQ9Ph1MC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The right shoe can make everything different. - Jimmy Choo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About The St. Augustine Alligator Farm – Zip Lines and Lots of Gators!  http://t.co/HfEVf3X1Bx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd just as soon kiss a wookiee! - Princess Leia, The Empire Strikes Back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Those SEO Google Animals - Panda and Penguin - How They Affect Your Site  http://t.co/gCKadcOPr9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China has blocked Twitter!!  Now 2 billion people will have no idea what I'm having for lunch.  Bummer!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Cool History of Mustard  http://t.co/On4q96Ml3N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So cool - German Beer Steins - check out their history - http://t.co/3JpW9WhVFV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Careers with a Creative Writing Degree  http://t.co/aOE7clM8cp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Carlos Santana  http://t.co/Y6pypNP9Yu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ultimately, the only power to which man should aspire is that which he exercises over himself. - Elie Wiesel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It will work. I am a marketing genius. - Paris Hilton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One is never over - or underdressed with a little black dress. - Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's easier to ask forgiveness than it is to get permission - Grace Hopper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We can judge the heart of a man by his treatment of animals. - Immanual Kant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like this ship! You know, it's exciting! - Scotty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Useful Products to Help Housebreak Your Pet  http://t.co/zrLPBMUIWI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Help with Picking Garage Cabinets  http://t.co/jWjiHmRh2g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Empty pockets never held anyone back. Only empty heads and empty hearts can do that.  Norman Vincent Peale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space is the stature of God. - Joseph Joubert]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Music from this Bose Blue Tooth system - iPad, iPhone and more - easy great sound -&gt; http://t.co/bqNr0QUGEY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If my uniform doesn't get dirty, I haven't done anything in the baseball game - Rickey Henderson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is that which discloses to the wise and disguises from the foolish their lack of understanding. - Ambrose Bierce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How To Find The Right Gluten Free Foods  http://t.co/kI38edkS9t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introducing to the SEO Power Suite  http://t.co/NI7fXddQ5G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter Can be an Invaluable Business Tool  http://t.co/me4WJLuRv4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is only one success - to be able to spend your life in your own way - Christopher Morley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nobody remembers the guy who finished second but the guy who finished second. - Bobby Unser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You call the driver of a car a motorist, until he comes just little too close.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Paul Simon - His Biography  http://t.co/1emtesUoXx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is what remains after one has forgotten everything he learned in school. - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rock and roll is here to stay. - Neil Young]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conversation:  when three women are talking together.  Gossip:  When one of them leaves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL - A Runny Nose In Your Shower Dispensing Soap - Love It!  http://t.co/uL77fMYfgG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to know what a man is really like, take notice of how he acts when he loses money.  Simone Weil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It cost more to amuse a child that it cost to educate the father.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Father, forking out reluctantly for daughter's wedding dress:  It's not enough to have to give her away --  she has to be gift wrapped.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Future generations will be born free, equal and in debt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Learning Tool for Kids - Snap Circuits Jr - Hands On Learning All About Circuits http://t.co/AGpCgNpl0c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes transform your body language and attitude. They lift you physically and emotionally. - Christian Louboutin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I raced a car last it was at a time when sex was safe and racing was dangerous. Now, it's the other way round. - Hans Stuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can Archery Be a Great Fitness Activity?  http://t.co/FG0WK556g0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Play is the only way the highest intelligence of humankind can unfold. - Joseph Chilton Pearce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is tool cool a LED Kitchen Sink Faucet Sprayer Nozzle - make the water turn blue!  http://t.co/oYFCVBLW9e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The client is not always right. - Enzo Ferrari]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Life Gives You Questions, Google has Answers - AJ Carpio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was a science fiction junkie for a long time. - William Hurt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Ways Technology Helps Seniors  http://t.co/hbjqwtUmw3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like flying jet fighters in a gymnasium - Dick Trickle was asked what racing at Winchester Speedway was like.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Overview of Domestic Adoption  http://t.co/MNY654DVCP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Joe Tex  http://t.co/lqz8pypy0J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Brady Bunch is an American sitcom classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/Un6qlqio17]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goonies never say die. - Mike, The Goonies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best possible thing in baseball is winning the World Series. The second best thing is losing the World Series. - Tommy Lasorda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Monopoly Money Extra Long Tie - Fun! http://t.co/8TPgVVEQru]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hit the ball over the fence and you can take your time going around the bases. - John W. Raper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A canter is the cure for all evil. - Benjamin Disraeli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bring the best of your authentic self to every opportunity.  John Jantsch - Author of Duct Tape Marketing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[M*A*S*H is an American TV classic - read all about its history -  http://t.co/QDIXSjd55r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get a Minecraft Enderman! http://t.co/NxF34C7oec]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, I think we're the greatest rock 'n' roll band in the world.  - Joey Ramone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellence is to do a common thing in an uncommon way. - Booker T. Washington]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>