<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JournalistaLtd: New blog: 'Clear academic comms: how we reached PR Utopia' with UCL @glo_pro's @moorehl https://t.co/gOQUqIi1SI https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Nick_MES  https://t.co/IIGO7pndxU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our lovely client sharing some heartfelt insight with @HSJnews  https://t.co/G8W3rCeHUn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I rather thought there was a proliferation of words with f in the middle.. https://t.co/WaiOAqlGgd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Praise be to the people who made 2.5 hour compilations of In The Night Garden. Such selfless acts require an honour. #parentingunfiltered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@halfofatwin @exSilverlink @TLRailUK @JoeMurphyLondon @nicholascecil or you can actually get on the train...or breath whilst on there...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No surprises here @TLRailUK - couldn't even get on the train this morning. And they're every friggin 20-35 mins. Grr https://t.co/0jLbf70lzt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@naszub she doesn't even need them for that - save the time and get a donor. Who cares? More men for the rest of us :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ESgoingout @somsaa_london absolute food heaven! I want to eat that pictured dish now - when does it open?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neilgadhok ah thank you - just making final tweaks to copy / pics etc. before we tweet it! Pls let me know if you spot any mistakes!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm going to "Further, Faster: Accelerating the Pace of Digitising the NHS".  See you there? https://t.co/gmxFxU5657 via @EventbriteUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be gone top down projectors  - how crowdsourcing in the NHS is delivering the changes people want to see, quickly.  https://t.co/8hSd4rDtfK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judging @therealprmoment awards - love this part of my job, feel proud to be part of such a creative industry driving important changes #PR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@oscarholland thank you! You're the first to notice :) we're making some final tweaks to the site before shouting it from the rooftops!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smiling today the that Bravery doll I bought my 11yo aussie niece helped her start senior school  #autism #asperges https://t.co/GT0xkoDAcf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @helenbevan: Excellent advice on how to live tweet at a conference or event from @JBBC https://t.co/o3Gf3Tq8oY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@helennianias wow-women really do have magic superhero powers! "some grandmothers have been known to relactate to feed their
grandchildren.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@helennianias actually - I might be completely wrong!! Sorry. https://t.co/jveA88ZWty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@helennianias it's just completely mad to suggest it's possible - @RedMagDaily represents the voice of intelligent women.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@helennianias - sometimes we have to check our understanding -do you believe a woman who's stopped breast feeding entirely can start again?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@helennianias it's physically impossible so it must be a misunderstanding on your behalf. It's a great article but that quote undermines it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RedMagDaily @helennianias quote in here suggests women who've never breastfed enabled to feed their children - at 5 months. Not possible!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RedMagDaily  refugee camp article a quote suggests making women who have never breastfed feed a 5 month child. Biologically impossible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JournalistaLtd: Professor @Moorehl's latest article on #Davos is now on @eldiarioes too: https://t.co/g7weUFE3Rp #WEF16 @glo_pro https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @guardian: ‘Airbnbs for dining’ give Italian female cooks chance to shine https://t.co/7Tj0HRA8HQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What an amazing story captured in this much needed feat of journalism. *tear jerker warning* https://t.co/bD8XxAdVAX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarlPackman 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @clever_together: Check out our case study of #prideinpennine - use of #crowdsourcing for a Trust-wide transformation https://t.co/llGCS…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need to keep this in mind today #rebrand pain! https://t.co/khz4C2ryDn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking up and seeing the Houses of Parliament-in today's icy light-awesome in the true sense of the word. #wework https://t.co/DYqLlCfL1u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@liquidprod what a lovely '16 survival package to arrive on a Baltic Jan day! Look forward to working with you. https://t.co/ELs1IWKK6X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy first birthday little dude! Loved sharing your special day with you #horniman #selondon https://t.co/8Fww4bzSEa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ShoKon: Interesting new @IPPR director @TomKibasi is 33, worked in health &amp; development. New direction under @Andrew_Adonis?
https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cliche fad food January #sirtfood Kale and chicken curry with Bombay potatoes with @mrsdargie. Delicious! https://t.co/OQpMOWQ7un]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ryaninnz I'd love to!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NickCohen4: Twitter: Where the already convinced go to discover why they are right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brjwalker - awesome - but why do you have your mum in your phone as Hazel and not 'mum'?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DrFosterIntel: New article by Julie Coope of @DrFosterIntel for @HSJnews: "Money's too tight to mention" https://t.co/60M9LfUARW https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Robin_Vickers: Well done @DigiLifeSci https://t.co/PqFBA5TEqT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LouiseRidley: We thought you'd like @fawcettsociety @AllAboutTrans @TransMediaWatch https://t.co/mV570h6lgb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best ever name for a magazine? https://t.co/yMNwUAlrfW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @buckinghamh: Ready to talk with #commsleads @NHSProviders about establishing NHS Improvement - expecting lively conversation!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Janehug: Sad news for @theRCN but great for international nursing... https://t.co/oFJyCUOpYO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I do take my work seriously and the way to do that is not to take yourself too seriously" too young, too thrilling to go so soon. #alanrick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Female models bad, no queues for the loo good. How #jpm16 is still blue suit heavy.I'll even it up next year!  https://t.co/5GKILVdXIm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fantastic example of a complex issue made very clear #complexmadeclear https://t.co/niRKNaN940]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RosamundUrwin: It's lazy to use Nye Bevan's "stuffing their mouths with gold" line against Drs. Not the same Drs. If they were after th…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@r_tazz it says 'bank office' not back office - as in the bank of contracted staff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feeling sharper than I ever have this year - this might explain why:https://t.co/8PVORTnIbR #mother #feminism2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeteThomond  https://t.co/BXudZSspyh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmyCCosper @Entrepreneur listen, don't over promise, deliver.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are what we read - for more stardust in your life see this from the only man that made face paint cool. #Bowie  https://t.co/WnIfN3HbKV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GSTTCharity: Good to see @HSJnews mapping #GP feds &amp; other groups incl #Lambeth &amp; #Southwark.This is how we support local efforts https…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Binti_Period: @JuliaHB1 only touched the surface 87% of the female pop in India don't know why they menstruate #smashshame https://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @penguinrandom: 5 principles that will help you read more: https://t.co/xdpBd00Ls6 @businessinsider]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LG_NHS: Fan letter to @justinbieber from NHS Executive showing great Bieber knowledge! Fancy a duet with the NHS Choir? ;) https://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man tired = must be working hard to make it perfect. Woman tired=overdoing it /marriage strife /breakdown. #feminism https://t.co/1HlnRl9Adx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GS10KSmallBiz: #Smallbiz is the backbone of the #US #economy—how #10KSmallBiz is helping these #SBO: https://t.co/eG1hF4ciOG https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkBorkowski sounds like a play on my family Christmas evening of Cards Against Humanity...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this take on new years resolutions - any excuse to go on Pinterest really!  https://t.co/MQXcOoyE9X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LottieOConor: Looking for women with interesting, unusual jobs to profile for the @GdnWomenLeaders day in the life series. Is this you?…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HuffPostUKEnt: Adele perfectly encapsulates how we're all feeling about going to the gym this January https://t.co/fkn77GLadJ https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HPIAndyCowper @paulbloomatyale I love that everything HST writes you can hear his voice saying it...between drags on a cigarette]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @r_tazz: HSJ team can well work a spreadsheet. Impressed by the accuracy. A Big 4 firm would charge £500k for data like that! https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 steps to amplifying advocacy of your SME to accelerate its growth  https://t.co/fMzQxiOeHI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JournalistaLtd: 5 steps to help your #digitalhealth SME accelerate its growth - blog by @Hollyonline https://t.co/GmOyFIx4LH https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChloeCWatson @CasseCroute109 oh it's so good and I'm so gasping for one of their gorgeous vinos right now...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KiwiGirlInUK ah gutted I can't be there - came down with a temp this afternoon :( ruined!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seemingly super obvious - but so crucial for anyone at the sharp end of media engagement #prjobs #prcareers https://t.co/Xha3yqNSiB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @prweekuknews: .@PRCA welcomes government rejection of FOI charges and Labour review
https://t.co/GrglKEfcbl https://t.co/p6zSc0y4wy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fancy a senior PR role with inspiring clients, support to develop specialist knowledge with an ace team? https://t.co/ICjDib8NF3 #prjobs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dr_Ellie @BootsUK agreed! It's as frustrating as WHSmiths asking you whether you want a large pack of sweets with your newspaper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bensimms65 brilliant meeting! So inspired by what you guys are doing - delighted to be in a position to help.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RosamundUrwin: "Too often in newsrooms women are still being put on the jobs that aren’t going to win awards" https://t.co/V9QU0CwhzI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HarvardBiz: A Global Survey Explains Why Your Employees Don’t Innovate https://t.co/jyZu16543D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @thoward37: "A user interface is like a joke. If you have to explain it, it's not that good." https://t.co/omiVDjS9s2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@neilgadhok no wonky ties and bad suits aka Cameron's diss? Think they'd catch on quicker...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Nick_MES: Today - read my thoughts in @guardian on how Involving the public is crucial for NHS success https://t.co/ent5ffOdTR @MESsoci…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top tips on how to turn your complex data into a full-pager on the FT and a sweep of other broadsheets https://t.co/A6XZWbqhET #PR #dataviz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@roz_davies @jamesfm55 @patientopinion fantastic! Love it when some of my favourite people (on Twitter at least!) come together.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jplomas: Great editorial. Except for "poor" read "terrible". https://t.co/txR4okLoUF https://t.co/1U3kTeJbJB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AntonyTiernan: Interesting times! #TrinityMirror launch a new newspaper as #TheIndependent goes (via @simonjacktoday) #TheNewDay https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CarlPackman: What Boris Johnson actually thinks about Europe https://t.co/mjWraQAO7G https://t.co/XkwwBYASSU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SE London never stops surprising - walk round Nunhead Cemetery followed by a step back in time via The Ivy House https://t.co/1InmzlLS9W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just walked into @IvyHouse_  and stepped back in time! https://t.co/A84exUvrra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bengoldacre yes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not everyday you open up the FT and see your company's name! #PR #DataAnalytics https://t.co/jzb0k6lT5M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MartinBarrow: Wow... Michelle Obama and the Duchess of Cambridge @HuffPostUK. On the same day. #YoungMindsMatter https://t.co/VwipkoctK…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HuffPostUK: 'We should have tough conversations with our friends and family' @FLOTUS #YoungMindsMatter https://t.co/6KQXECWA6Z https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting eh. of why matching audience's needs to your choice of spokesperson is essential #PR #complexclear https://t.co/hcpjl6HzSv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thenextwomen looks awesome - your website it down though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PRCAIngham: #prtalk here's a piece of news I hope is welcome.... PRCA is going to lead by example. We will publish our own pay data thi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @helenbevan: From complicated to complex: I understand only a little German but this language is universal. By @haraldschirmer https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Astounding what #juniordoctors face on a daily basis  https://t.co/jZurM1tMRE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @bellamackie: The Sun seems to have got the words "rape" and "romp" mixed up. Sure it's just an easy mistake to make. https://t.co/BO7sE…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pinkshoeclub top local for a stimulating meeting. Great to be involved in ambitious UK Economic Blueprint for Women https://t.co/SiJv6ZMqtp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice view from Portcullis House for meeting on UK Economic Blueprint for Women https://t.co/tvNeBjqUBU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Entrepreneur: 8 Big Business Tenets That Don't Work for Startups https://t.co/EomP5bBXLe by @StartupPro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @vinces: Interesting article arguing that mobile tech is essential for patient-focused care https://t.co/DlB60cSc0H https://t.co/nrp2yoR…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BrockleyCentral: A new Brockley Micro Library - this time for kids!
https://t.co/KeFtfaqBqr https://t.co/oq5fjgVkcr]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>