<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Temptations  http://t.co/JmftcfsCRc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the shoe fits, it's too expensive. - Adrienne Gusoff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Far Out and Super Cool Watches  http://t.co/FDowgE7qze]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Tips from Web Building Experts  http://t.co/cnSgtveIhY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't sweep if you don't win the first game, and it's tougher to win two out of three if you lose the first one. - Todd Helton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I had never seen much of Star Trek, or any other science fiction, before I was cast. But Seven's wonderful. - Jeri Ryan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Successfully Use Other Websites for Link Building  http://t.co/uKBEpXrMpT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The blunt people make the most pointed remarks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Second marriage --  triumph of hope over experience]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Uriah Heep  http://t.co/zscaPWFtLU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the business world, everyone is paid in two coins: cash &amp; experience. Take the experience first; the cash will come later - Harold Geneen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Mets have found ways of losing that I never knew existed. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smartphones are reinventing the connection between companies and their customers.  Rich Miner - Partner Google Ventures]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not the mistakes in life that are important; it's what we learn from them. - Donna Guthrie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 8 - North Texas Lyme Support Group  http://t.co/13VuUTKl2u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dammit, man! I'm a doctor, not a physicist! - Leonard 'Bones' McCoy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome baseball t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the baseball lovers in your life!   http://t.co/cozu26rBHv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Deep Purple  http://t.co/DwwcIj5WZ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Marie Antoinette's Watch  http://t.co/rlqATqw8fG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Pink Floyd  http://t.co/yNZm7TooFv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awww How Adorable! A Smile Star Design - Color Changing - LED Light Toss Pillow! http://t.co/breRvH8XDK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't compare me to my father. Our similarities are different. -  Dale Berra about his father Yogi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we're growing, we're always going to be out of our comfort zone. - John Maxwell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Are the Different Types of Web Hosting?  http://t.co/llSBKANEiT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can never be overdressed or overeducated. --&gt; Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome camping t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the camping lovers in your life!  http://t.co/QwLdQsaYhr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Gary Lewis and the Playboys  http://t.co/JR3Gif628X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Star Trek Uniform Onesies - Dress Up Your Little Geek! http://t.co/bzW2Kswext]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gluttony is an emotional escape, a sign something is eating us. - Peter De Vries]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Cat. He walked by himself, and all places were alike to him. - Rudyard Kipling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The great difficulty in education is to get experience out of ideas. - George Santayana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the beginning, God created man, but seeing him so feeble, He gave him the cat - Warren Eckstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is what we are, and football is what we have become. - Mary McGrory]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop praising a woman, she'll think you don't love her.  Keep it up and she'll think she is too good for you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lend your friend $20, if he doesn't pay you back then he's not your friend. Money well spent - Ted Nicolas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Bruce Springsteen  http://t.co/EAsXbLMOSg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[USBCELL AA Rechargeable Batteries work just like rechargeable batteries - simply recharge by any powered USB Port http://t.co/hRkRf5HXt9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana’s Lyme Journey – Part 17 – More on Supplements  http://t.co/T7kKydg2wH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Few people SUFFER from egotism. With most of them it's a PLEASURE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space or science fiction has become a dialect for our time. - Doris Lessing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about the History of San Francisco, California http://t.co/tRLfCEfeEm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Human sacrifice, dogs and cats living together --  mass hysteria! - Dr. Peter Venkman, Ghostbusters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Peter Frampton  http://t.co/v3hrRzSo8H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two sides: One is light, one is dark." -- John Locke, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you have six dates with a man who never even tries to kiss you -- Lie about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is A Hedge Fund?  http://t.co/HmCdmYTljb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are flirting with danger when you buy high-heeled sandals - Eileen Allen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The right people to start video blogging are those with a passion to tell a story.  Steve Garfield - Author Get Seen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Bread  http://t.co/HEBpxkIbtz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still love her. But she's retarded, too. Guy Ritchie on Madonna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Square meals make round people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give a girl the right shoes, and she can conquer the world. - Marilyn Monroe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Pet Insurance  http://t.co/CWtpIdyrad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh this is cool - a remote control spy plane with a mini-viewer - COOL http://t.co/5jJ0zTnC6j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Customer:  "Could I try on that suit in the window?"  Clerk:  "We'd rather you do that in the dressing room."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing shocks me - I am a scientist. - Indiana Jones, Indiana Jones and the Temple of Doom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My little dog -- a heartbeat at my feet. - Edith Wharton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Understanding Attention Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder (ADHD)  http://t.co/WTxcILRysF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate most of what constitutes rock music, which is basically middle-aged crap. - Sting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exciting History of Baseball  http://t.co/ODNpHXoXfN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the fascinating history of that classic baseball park - Wrigley Field - http://t.co/IRWVzXg1lz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Bob Seger  http://t.co/Ba4SRrPoeJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Allstate Insurance  http://t.co/F06Tn37I47]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah, well. The Dude abides. - The Dude, The Big Lebowski]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of LA Gear  http://t.co/8aKDROUBqg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's the most fun I have ever had and. also the biggest pain in the ass I have ever experienced. Brad Pitt, on fatherhood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I get to go to a lot of overseas places, like Canada.  Britney Spears]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Mott the Hoople  http://t.co/jSpQeFIchH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read Great Outdoor Camping Equipment Tips  http://t.co/LzSNF6lfw2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Foxy  http://t.co/rwdlU5XTbV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Horse! A Horse! my kingdom for a horse! - Shakespeare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Future of Blackberry  http://t.co/1DBy52OXLW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wait a minute, Doc. Ah --  Are you telling me you built a time machine --  out of a DeLorean? - Marty McFly, Back to the Future]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think the last 4 words of the national anthem are gentlemen, start your engines, you might be a redneck. - Jeff Foxworthy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Visiting  relatives are like fish. They begin to stink after 3 days!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome James Bond t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the 007 lovers in your life!   http://t.co/TIi5XgyD90]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people are like angels - always harping on something!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best augury of a man's success in his profession is that he thinks it the finest in the world. - George Eliot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Middle age is when you still have the spark but now it takes more puffing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dog maybe a man's best friend but a horse made history... - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Brownsville Station  http://t.co/bS7a0C5Kxb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of McDonald's  http://t.co/sJW1PrIsSX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are not traffic jams along the extra mile. - Roger Staubach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome - Hopside Down Glass - Upside Down Beer Bottle Glass - Cool! http://t.co/cbO9teOmWQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you can look in the mirror and smile at what you see, then there's hope for you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Grapevine, Texas  http://t.co/WzK2uvmACA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your goals, minus your doubts, equal your reality. - Ralph Marston]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drill sarge to recruit:  "wipe that opinion off your face!”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did You Know this About Blackbeard in Pirates of the Caribbean 4  http://t.co/WblP192Zlp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd walk through hell in a gasoline suit to play baseball. -  Pete Rose]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learning Styles - Learn About Teaching so They Can Learn  http://t.co/3bxZYENJAr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Planning for an Ash Scattering Ceremony  http://t.co/NR8zjSDt3Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome gardening t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the gardening lovers in your life!   http://t.co/qkYSDIL0wM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Paul Davis  http://t.co/GMJyfMQW3w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Out the Top Football Teams of the 2011-2012 Season  http://t.co/V0o5Z1p4WS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Allstate Insurance  http://t.co/F06Tn37I47]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Assisted Living in Your Own Home  http://t.co/zaasZlTvgh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One is never over - or underdressed with a little black dress. - Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Jefferson Airplane  http://t.co/opmKCQLdmO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not the employer who pays the wages. Employers only handle the money. It's the customer who pays the wages.  Henry Ford]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>