<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Every day, in every way, I am getting better and better. - Emilie Coue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What we want is to see the child in pursuit of knowledge, and not knowledge in pursuit of the child. - George Bernard Shaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Clarence Carter  http://t.co/NQkw3qAqgj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And now, I'm just trying to change the world, one sequin at a time. Lady Gaga]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The good Lord gave you a body that can stand most anything. It's your mind you have to convince. - Vincent Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To succeed --  You need to find something to hold on to, something to motivate you, something to inspire you. - Tony Dorsett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Millie Jackson  http://t.co/K83gJbcPNi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love any movie that has a retarded person working at Starbucks.  Chris Kattan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow these Steps to Clean Your Credit  http://t.co/XQWfBLZ2Bh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagination is more important than knowledge. Knowledge is limited. Imagination encircles the world. - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Leif Garrett  http://t.co/QqsbzVkDs4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was sad because I had no shoes, until I met a man who had no feet. So I said, Got any shoes you're not using? --&gt; Steven Wright]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[College isn't the place to go for ideas. - Helen Keller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of that Odd Olympic Sport – Curling  http://t.co/HkGD7N9oZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I raced a car last it was at a time when sex was safe and racing was dangerous. Now, it's the other way round. - Hans Stuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought Europe was a country? Kellie Pickler, on "Are You Smarter Than A Fifth Grader"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one really knows who created Bitcoin - read about the fascinating history of Satoshi Nakamoto... http://t.co/DtEcTXlJgG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool Garages and Flooring Types  http://t.co/MOPXnfMmdJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Popular Places and Activities in Europe  http://t.co/1SiLj0nooQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Neil Diamond  http://t.co/M52u419uQj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The purity of a person's heart can be quickly measured by how they regard animals - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The earth? Oh the earth will be gone in a few seconds...I'm going to blow it up. It's obstructing my view of Venus. - Marvin the Martian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Aerosmith  http://t.co/fzzDhJ5Ak0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these alternatives to traditional beef hamburgers!  http://t.co/jw26tqXF1D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The quality of a leader is reflected in the standards they set for themselves. - Ray Kroc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Youth is when we want to set the world on fire... Middle age is when we hope our children won't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These Messenger Bags are stylish and practical - cool! http://t.co/mhNx0dotn6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fool and his money are soon accepted into the highest social circles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Publishing Management with HootSuite  http://t.co/W6OnOplLM9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The difference between gossip and news is whether you hear it or tell it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gluten Free Recipes - Making a Gluten-Free Gravy  http://t.co/LRWflqbmYE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must accept finite disappointment, but we must never lose infinite hope. - Martin Luther King, Jr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd make a wonderful Lady Macbeth. I'll wear a pair of platform shoes or something - Bette Midler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like to literally put women on a pedestal. - Vivienne Westwood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these alternatives to traditional beef hamburgers!  http://t.co/WNuP1n4YQ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Cane Corso Italiano – Beloved Dog of Italy  http://t.co/mtZD9xCXm3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may be dumb, but I'm not stupid.  Terry Bradshaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Gardening Fall Flowers  http://t.co/0S8xDD92qe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is the world flat? I never thought about it. Sherri Shepherd, The View, after Whoopi Goldberg asked her if she thought the world was flat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Ways to Use Website Builders for Links to Your Website  http://t.co/oTQ9c9L2Uv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stay Ahead in eCommerce With Marketing Tips  http://t.co/ZYuhNPl1vX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome climbing t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the climbing lovers in your life!   http://t.co/OgOjlnUNfC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Their marriage is a partnership, he's the silent partner.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anthony “Tony” Harris, CSECO President and CEO, receives an Honorary Doctorate in Engineering from Purdue University  http://t.co/2rlSZZmNCA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jin Kwon: Good... to see... you. Sawyer: Well look at that! Somebody's hooked on phonics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Bob Dylan -- His Biography    http://t.co/EnaaxQhoyF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lifetime of training for just ten seconds. - Jesse Owens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Use Twitter to Make the Most Of Your Business  http://t.co/tabMpZLG0Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagination is the key to my lyrics. The rest is painted with a little science fiction. - Jimi Hendrix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is the best deodorant. - Elizabeth Taylor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Cane Corso Italiano – Beloved Dog of Italy  http://t.co/mtZD9xCXm3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ability is the art of getting credit for all the home runs somebody else hits. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada - Learn About Best Places to Tour  http://t.co/ivC9dqfdwo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Marketing Experts Reveal Tips to Success  http://t.co/QqcTATlz2c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Play is the only way the highest intelligence of humankind can unfold. - Joseph Chilton Pearce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can wear this wonderful Unicorn Mask - bring the magic! http://t.co/O83VK7hRzJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Petula Clark  http://t.co/bnPrXTH33K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He had a forward spring... And an early fall...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only way to prove that you're a good sport is to lose. - Ernie Banks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Big-Dog Pet Fountain - Keeps Fresh and Tasty Water for Your Big Dog! http://t.co/VnyB9brNc4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Clear Lighted Skateboard with green LED Lights  http://t.co/s2fhp7Ldt0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome gardening t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the gardening lovers in your life!   http://t.co/zRHJ66MAcL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the way society functions. Aren't you a part of society? - Kramer, Seinfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yum! Even MORE Brownie's Edge In This Baker's Edge Nonstick Pan  http://t.co/e6FkaguWBn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wondering. If Money Doesn't Grow On Trees, then Why Do Banks Have all those Branches??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame Champions: Confused Much?  http://t.co/zODn2tSVkL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Keys to Good Marketing for Your Business  http://t.co/WLpzn0aPYe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Blue Origin - A Profile of This Emerging Space Company  http://t.co/XEEvxYzyLS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is A Hedge Fund?  http://t.co/RxKID8Dbx7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the largest life insurance companies in the US!  http://t.co/YzbMRcse3O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Ringo Starr  http://t.co/xB2uac6397]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dream house is one that cost twice as much as you ever dreamed it would…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pessimist: A man who thinks that all woman are bad Optimist: A man who hopes so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Help with Planning Garage Flooring  http://t.co/MKVOQ7iY4Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ELVIS - The King - One Person's Thoughts  http://t.co/qIGjkEdEmU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips To Draw More Traffic With Quality Link Building  http://t.co/2yek7Nwzne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Build your own propeller racer and watch as it blazes a path over a smooth surface!  Fun and educational for kids! http://t.co/DA2WHRusDe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Jimmy Choo  http://t.co/VK7aDreLKK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the top science fiction movies of all time!  http://t.co/LTanAagmex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These Yoda Lights Must You Have!  Wonderful Geek Gear! http://t.co/M1nYJD9c4T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anthony “Tony” Harris, CSECO President and CEO, receives an Honorary Doctorate in Engineering from Purdue University  http://t.co/GR3mlSoRp9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I'm going dancing, then I wear the highest heels with the shortest dress. - Kate Moss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To achieve anything in this game you must be prepare to dabble in the boundary of disaster. - Sterling Moss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 9 - Appointment With Another LLMD  http://t.co/GTxioNH0lo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never wear the same shoe twice. - Dion Sanders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By working faithfully eight hours a day you may eventually get to be a boss and work twelve hours a day. - Robert Frost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Mars Exploration Project with Mars One  http://t.co/D80R37jQEm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is what survives when what has been learned has been forgotten. - B. F. Skinner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smartphones are reinventing the connection between companies and their customers.  Rich Miner - Partner Google Ventures]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't win unless you learn how to lose. - Kareem Abdul-Jabbar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My own mother told me I didn't have a shot in hell of winning tonight.  A shocked Katherine Heigl upon winning an Emmy for Grey's Anatomy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out Crimson Mine’s awesome Tumblr page... http://t.co/g8vaK9vpce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Capital as such is not evil; it is its wrong use that is evil. Capital in some form or other will always be needed.  Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome ping pong t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the table tennis lovers in your life!   http://t.co/LIvhGZ2mhT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hit the ball over the fence and you can take your time going around the bases. - John W. Raper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His pockets always outlast his suits...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the sun refused to shine I would still be loving you. When mountains crumble to the sea there will still be you &amp; me - Led Zeppelin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[End Of Line - The MCP, TRON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are not traffic jams along the extra mile. - Roger Staubach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Different Types of Ashes Scattering Services  http://t.co/1BZ6uqmKSV]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>