<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Joe Tex  http://t.co/7Jwpv2ipAJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pair off in threes. - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of KC and the Sunshine Band  http://t.co/9n8hhjd8Yk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ability is the art of getting credit for all the home runs somebody else hits. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An animal's eyes have the power to speak a great language. - Martin Buber]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Familiarity breeds contempt --  and children]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Help with Picking Garage Cabinets  http://t.co/Yt4x6e0esJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Dallas, Texas  http://t.co/ocEfmom72N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best possible thing in baseball is winning the World Series. The second best thing is losing the World Series. - Tommy Lasorda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is the mark of an educated mind to be able to entertain a thought without accepting it. - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Reviews By Children Affect a Product’s Sale  http://t.co/uyA2Q9gBd5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Little House on the Prairie – An American Classic TV Series  http://t.co/Gi1rkzH5Zo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is nothing so stupid as the educated man if you get him off the thing he was educated in.  - Will Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are inclined to think that if we watch a football game or a baseball game, we have taken part in it. - John F. Kennedy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God has no intention of setting a limit to the efforts of man to conquer space. - Pope Pius XII]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The quality of a leader is reflected in the standards they set for themselves. - Ray Kroc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like to literally put women on a pedestal. - Vivienne Westwood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Guide to Business to Business Internet Marketing on LinkedIn  http://t.co/4pZUxdCZXY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My name is Inigo Montoya. You killed my father. Prepare to die! - Inigo, The Princess Bride]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Europe – Best Places to Tour  http://t.co/yXmNd9urcw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You’ve got to give us Americans a lot of credit.  How else could we buy a new car every year?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good pitching will beat good hitting any time, and vice versa. - Bob Veale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame Quakecraft: FAILURE IS AN OPTION!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! http://t.co/sxF7BFLAie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think Jennifer knows how to get pregnant. Leah Remini on rumors that she was trying to convert JLO to Scientology to help with fertility]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your body is the baggage you must carry through life. The more excess the baggage, the shorter the trip. - Arnold H. Glasgow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Better to be a geek than an idiot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The numbers are cursed. Dude, don't look at me like that, I'm not crazy. This is real. Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Resources for Home Brewing  http://t.co/QwZ5jcOWSq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one really knows who created Bitcoin - read about the fascinating history of Satoshi Nakamoto... http://t.co/Q5UyNPPjXN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Michael Jordan Shoes  http://t.co/PFRVLvDxbx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Matrimony: An Institution of learning in which a man loses his "Bachelor's Degree" and his wife acquires a "Masters"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why worry about death, it'll come sooner or later. - Jim Dunn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Interesting History of Dos XX Beer  http://t.co/27BpjswDFd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the Dos XX Most Interesting Man In the World - Top Quotes!  http://t.co/Eo2RN8SsT6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reputation is the other fellow's idea of your character]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Jimmy Choo  http://t.co/omDiszIncM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is what you get from reading the small print in a contract. "experience " is what you get from not reading it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boys, baseball is a game where you gotta have fun. You do that by winning. - Dave Bristol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Tom Petty and the Heartbreakers  http://t.co/bVmZNcyTzz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Help with Autism  http://t.co/Em4ryLNJs7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is one AMAZING Kate Upton poster - gorgeous http://t.co/UMqbaYVzoE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flattery, like perfume, should be smelled, not swallowed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automatic rotating laser light that provides hours of fun for your feline and canine friends - Keep the cat happy!  http://t.co/yhjgFeFFPV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Radiation Detection Equipment - Providing the Equipment Necessary to Protect Those That Protect Us  http://t.co/slFM5f8qmy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thats the way Baseball go - Ron Washington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winning is everything. The only ones who remember you when you come second are your wife and your dog. - Damon Hill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is a progressive discovery of our own ignorance. - Will Durant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What is Fiverr Exactly and Why All the Buzz?  http://t.co/rb1VrJ56kj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Pink Floyd  http://t.co/roNPJTbvbq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is the key to unlock the golden door of freedom. - George Washington Carver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The difference between try and triumph is just a little umph! - Marvin Phillips]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She's got double D's! You can't cover those suckers up! Jessica Simpson's Dad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The eyes can mislead, a smile can lie, but the shoes always tell the truth - Greg House House MD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys - combine your wallet and smart phone in one compact case - and its cool and stylish - Book Book http://t.co/cw9UFUjaEF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Millie Jackson  http://t.co/XFR3dYQHiV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Ramones  http://t.co/7DlRUV9JW1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hiring Strategy Consulting Firms: The Importance of Competitive Analysis  http://t.co/EbxToGGEAg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL A Toilet Mug for your Coffee!  http://t.co/eLARNlxgWk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Europe – Best Places to Tour  http://t.co/yXmNd9urcw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet - very cool mechanical pin clock - very unique - http://t.co/VbcuxgmdVl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest thing in this world is not so much where we stand, as in what direction we are moving. - Oliver Wendall Holmes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the Devine RPG Minecraft Mod - http://t.co/UloUZpnUf1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Power of Solar Power - Get Plugged In!  http://t.co/TmzICh5yCF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Running SUCKS! How to Run for Fast Weight Loss - For Busy Women Who HATE Running --&gt; http://t.co/CK27j3mz66]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Personally, I'm always ready to learn, although I do not always like being taught. - Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Mars Exploration Project with Mars One  http://t.co/SWN4EJpFZC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of the Inheritance Series Third Volume – Brisingr  http://t.co/5IIstxwgwO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The safest way to double your money is to fold it over and put it in your pocket. - Kin Hubbard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Media are tools.  Real time is mindset.  David Scott - Marketing Strategist - Author of The New Rules of Marketing and PR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have a very striking face. How many times were you struck there?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes as much energy to wish as it does to plan!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is a progressive discovery of our own ignorance. - Will Durant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Ankle Watches – Is This the New Place to Wear a Watch?  http://t.co/xD5L0DtudI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am a fashion person, and fashion is not only about clothes -- it's about all kinds of change --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I started racing my father told me, "˜Cristiano, nobody has three balls but some people have two very good ones. - Cristiano Da Matta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think education is expensive, try ignorance - Derek Bok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Egotism is the Knack of seeing desirable qualities in yourself that others can't see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The longer you're not taking action the more money you're losing - Carrie Wilkerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool check out this Nerd Kit...  http://t.co/gpLc0Iepkr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of In-N-Out Burger  http://t.co/EorihaGCRh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read an Introduction to Sonic Drive-In  http://t.co/zc3AVaM4te]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Bert Kaempfert  http://t.co/7PwvwAX1fn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is more than a game to me, it's a religion. - Bill Klem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Brownsville Station  http://t.co/bGcp2JyJSb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Jackson Browne  http://t.co/dW01OfLSe3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest thing in this world is not so much where we stand, as in what direction we are moving. - Oliver Wendall Holmes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Scientific Explorer's Mind Blowing Science Kit! http://t.co/h8T3MaNTgn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The one thing my mom will let me get is a nice shoe sometimes. - Chloe Moretz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dogs come when they're called; cats take a message and get back to you later. - Mary Bly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fool and his money are never without friends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Overview of Major Web Conferencing Services  http://t.co/iAx3PqRU0X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then close your eyes and tap your heels together three times. And think to yourself, "There's no place like home" - The Wizard of Oz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Little by little does the trick. - Aesop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is learning what you didn't even know you didn't know. - Daniel J. Boorstin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think nobody cares if you're alive, try missing a couple of car payments. - Earl Wilson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before you take somebody's head off be sure you've used yours]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bring out your dead. - Monty Python and the Holy Grail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some of the worst mistakes in my life were haircuts --&gt; Jim Morrison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And in the end, the love we take will be equal to the love we make. - The Beatles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Gary Lewis and the Playboys  http://t.co/eEHiQSlwZK]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>