<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WSJ: How can you help someone who's depressed? Start by accepting that depression is ... https://t.co/a4GmW9t4Ga https://t.co/IW4dVWa77K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nytimesworld: The Times would like to better understand the views and efforts of ... https://t.co/flyfaM1uP5 https://t.co/K5RdufPbKV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nytimesworld: Argentine authorities are looking into possible criminal charges ... https://t.co/PiVwFW8MJR https://t.co/ivzRxQ32Kz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: Vehicle strikes seven pedestrians in New York City, one killed https://t.co/iriBTJjMis https://t.co/DcUnHvpJZy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BuzzFeedNews: 8 apps in the Google Play with more than 2 billion downloads between ... https://t.co/bbYXmPjLv8 https://t.co/PmdlJqdiaK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BuzzFeedNews: A judge has dismissed a local DC restaurant's lawsuit accusing the ... https://t.co/yhfd7YIMLZ https://t.co/iXBhfedL51]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nytimesworld: What would Prince Charles be like as king? A documentary offers hints. https://t.co/5N2wgDAsqt https://t.co/NtixLJb4Te]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BuzzFeedNews: People are sharing old photos of their grandparents on social media and ... https://t.co/wBtQP6RGYp https://t.co/W2MVJ5k4hQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: VW plans to sell electric Tesla rival for less than $23,000: source https://t.co/rFYln6DAAX https://t.co/5hH8nFMoyU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: Unresolved high-profile U.S. elections could be headed to recounts https://t.co/4JmEihbyI8 https://t.co/xzhwMRiOkn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: Burberry says new designer is delivering the buzz https://t.co/ySdGwL8SrX via @ReutersTV https://t.co/jOLwZhrdaL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: Ex-NY Attorney General Schneiderman will not face criminal charges https://t.co/zzUrrQeHgA https://t.co/PBXoSpBDUQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BuzzFeedNews: Jason Mantzoukas tells @AM2DM that playing awful characters allows him ... https://t.co/RlaGhNMcP7 https://t.co/UJLQ752PJz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: Israeli minister mocked in guerrilla-art statue https://t.co/pILZ414zK2 https://t.co/1MD4Q1Sseu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: Tesla names director Denholm as chair after Musk rows https://t.co/UBsw1zPpFt https://t.co/oK55ymeJnS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: British government cannot stop Brexit case going to ECJ, Scottish court says https://t.co/fuvef6JSuc https://t.co/WhOPrn7ZdF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BuzzFeedNews: More than 100 LGBT candidates won Election Day races at the federal, ... https://t.co/k6SuzZKhCh https://t.co/k0DPfLP4QZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BuzzFeedNews: While much of the commentary about Jeff Sessions’ departure turned on ... https://t.co/QqecmUEGc8 https://t.co/PDKw9AcNIL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: Behind Sri Lanka's turmoil, a China-India struggle for investments and ... https://t.co/rC3dcU9EqT https://t.co/7eluW9HMYY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: Tesla appoints Robyn Denholm as chair to replace Elon Musk https://t.co/cKHeigw1if https://t.co/X8zPCGzqP6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AP: Authorities say multiple people were injured at a shooting at a bar in Southern ... https://t.co/dkZCa5wgNp https://t.co/3B0SLkb78Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nytimesworld: The Taliban wiped out an entire battalion of border forces in western ... https://t.co/1exBgCkuiF https://t.co/rtWKUi8xUo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WSJ: Ralph Lauren was arguably the world’s first Instagram star, decades ahead of the ... https://t.co/suMryGWq49 https://t.co/CSLhKGy2XI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: Pete Davidson's 'SNL' castmate Kenan Thompson talks Dan Crenshaw joke: 'They ... https://t.co/mpIqPyAt6a https://t.co/FqRUA56ZCw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nytimesworld: Talk about an Old Master: A cave drawing in Borneo is the oldest known ... https://t.co/HEulDmNoHy https://t.co/53fdMtYFJw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: Democrat Colin Allred, who unseated Rep. Pete Sessions, won't say if he'll ... https://t.co/Ri79PUdLk0 https://t.co/1vKQVV7vQT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: UBS expects to be sued by U.S. Justice Dept over crisis-era mortgage securities https://t.co/WKkfYiC6uT https://t.co/hfnbexFuWX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: On @Breakingviews: Democratic financiers may have gotten more for their ... https://t.co/1q5DHAsXoI https://t.co/r0k26y5NYe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: Samsung gives first glimpse of foldable phone https://t.co/kXSb0Bu4b0 https://t.co/CkvyvDIUXq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AP: RT @AP_NFL: At the halfway point of the NFL season these are some of the most improved players. Read ... https://t.co/FNbaq713mV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: Saudi Arabia is drawing international criticism for their explanation of ... https://t.co/Qh4ZHhP719 https://t.co/JtQALewKja]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AP: Authorities say six people are dead after a dump truck crossed a highway median ... https://t.co/qlUDTkvvHg https://t.co/4TZXN89gnC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WSJ: Exceptional courage impresses us and makes us wonder whether we could ever rise ... https://t.co/CUrRUf1Bd3 https://t.co/nRQSqVuGfh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: .@POTUS is getting ready to kick off a "Make America Great Again" in Nevada ... https://t.co/YgkN9rYon9 https://t.co/Q0WjlGYbgY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: .@KeithUrban gives private hospital concert to sick fan https://t.co/zJKRhvU4gU https://t.co/nf9o7dVHuv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: .@SenatorCardin: “The border wall will not stop a caravan from coming into ... https://t.co/x04tTlNcvR https://t.co/qfvFUKvwWY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: .@SenatorCardin: “The strategic partnership needs to continue and our ... https://t.co/DJOUBMSAa0 https://t.co/w9j6D4bd2i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: Details emerge on 911 call made day Jayme Closs vanished, parents were murdered https://t.co/0NjRlSReNm https://t.co/iB3hkCgv67]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nytimesworld: Athos holds a special place in the Greek psyche, as a throwback to when ... https://t.co/5q8cfQtzSO https://t.co/GkkNGwz1wf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: TOMORROW: Don't miss @RandPaul's exclusive interview on @FoxNewsSunday. ... https://t.co/WRuBhhpz1Z https://t.co/6CG9M6gJaD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AP: @AP The Latest: The head of Turkish Arab media group says the "authority that ... https://t.co/VDrPkdWJkI https://t.co/xAkrl1hoLu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AP: The top 10 largest Jackpots in U.S. history. https://t.co/AqRYlBv9Be https://t.co/u3Y1OJwPaT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: .@ericmetaxas: “The mobs that we’ve seen, the lack of respect, the lack of ... https://t.co/aUxcvvSEL0 https://t.co/Q15yx5EKsR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: Customer allegedly tosses soup at restaurant owner during spat: report https://t.co/Xg3OS6k2xU https://t.co/WbeqEu2ZTV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nytimesworld: The men were found guilty in a series of trials this year of more than ... https://t.co/qEQW1rqL6s https://t.co/uAgI0hsWxH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: Mother of missing Wisconsin teen Jayme Closs was 'family angel'; 'no clue' ... https://t.co/cLjBEjyPuH https://t.co/r4vGuFyrlp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WSJ: "We’re probably some of his biggest supporters. It’s pissed off a lot of people.” https://t.co/guqSYJLnXi https://t.co/DUkFJXTUN5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WSJ: Here is an early look at the front page of The Wall Street Journal https://t.co/wcrpLau6wo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AP: Silenced forever: Saudi Arabia admits Jamal #Khashoggi is dead, @seldeeb reports. https://t.co/tYPFcjEqp2 https://t.co/j3rLCo4aeh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: RT @ReutersOpinion: In Commentary, @DavidAndelman on how the Kashoggi case could be the political ... https://t.co/St6nCvklRo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: Manafort shows up to court in wheelchair, as sentencing date set https://t.co/zzjIDlzaBW https://t.co/zOB6Irh2mG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: JUST IN: Trump says he thinks Saudi explanation on Khashoggi was credible, ... https://t.co/rMmtN7MbrB https://t.co/RmF2mw7xcM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: .@PhilippeReines: “I think...people have political astigmatism, where they ... https://t.co/CPV3Gkx8Mm https://t.co/cDwJ1ff03g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WSJ: Saudi Arabia says journalist Jamal Khashoggi was killed inside the consulate ... https://t.co/oIsq0NOPaw https://t.co/5j4CaP62JR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: Aston Martin - the luxury carmaker favored by James Bond - narrows $6 ... https://t.co/ZpPTyNblYW https://t.co/WDAOl7kpMU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AP: @AP Majority Leader Mitch McConnell says the Senate will vote this week on Brett ... https://t.co/KttKup5T1M https://t.co/QKsNs2TBwX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WSJ: Why do many people hesitate to report sexual assault? Victims often fear they ... https://t.co/uT7D2OBVbO https://t.co/8m2hZnO7Ie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: Why getting a mortgage is costing more these days. @onehitgit explains for ... https://t.co/GrFR2PW7XP https://t.co/a7qeuivIXf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BuzzFeedNews: #AM2DM explains why pop-up museums aren't always worth the wait https://t.co/1NRjjumtiR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nytimesworld: Civil disobedience continues and tensions remain high in the Catalan ... https://t.co/Y7d4G6y9M3 https://t.co/rlrqRMya2k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: U.S. Navy rescues people from sinking plane https://t.co/9xaxXoJSlb https://t.co/pVe8PTgjYs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: Jonathan Turley: "This is much better for [Kavanaugh] to be confirmed after ... https://t.co/UOOvc1dFqJ https://t.co/NCOl9jm6Qv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: Chris Swecker: "Jim Comey has lost any support he's ever had in that community." https://t.co/DdabzlI6f9 https://t.co/Exv0b4qqnc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BBCBreaking: French singer and songwriter Charles Aznavour has died aged 94 after a ... https://t.co/cFVKfCgzph https://t.co/jMeIdh6m5s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AP: BREAKING: John Flannery out as chairman and CEO at General Electric after less than two years, Lawrence ... https://t.co/xJ2khdEkxA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: French watchdog says EU market rules need overhaul after Brexit https://t.co/2K5k4V0mFK https://t.co/Lf0uUHIH7K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nytimesworld: None of the 22 buoys spread over Indonesia’s open water to help monitor ... https://t.co/7zoqXfk32z https://t.co/IpkkcxjLnq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WSJ: A controversial front-runner sparks massive rallies ahead of next week’s ... https://t.co/FVwe7HSJ3I https://t.co/gA27lWMTis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: Factbox: Details of the new North America free trade deal https://t.co/0OwE9j5G14 https://t.co/XXNMAlTSFI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: .@POTUS on North Korea during a rally Saturday night: "Now we have this ... https://t.co/EcBDgOkTb1 https://t.co/SNEryAbqCs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WSJ: Rachel Mitchell said in a memo to senators, "I do not think that a reasonable ... https://t.co/cw3ORuFo2U https://t.co/yAEJ6m6XvO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BuzzFeedNews: The FBI has interviewed Deborah Ramirez, the second woman who accused ... https://t.co/R7EgvGdmKL https://t.co/V55lxf3ZPj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nytimesworld: “If the government continues in this way, we will never achieve ... https://t.co/kh1M0gNi8W https://t.co/zfcJivArqV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: Tiebreak games needed to settle NL Central, NL West races. https://t.co/bylfHGXW4U https://t.co/V8Yd9pvluk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BuzzFeedNews: Estonia’s first woman president, Kersti Kaljulaid, says Russia’s ... https://t.co/E23zGcMsP5 https://t.co/C8Zwj80CiY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: .@BenShapiro: "An FBI investigation was completely superfluous. It was a transparent attempt to ... https://t.co/0krggkoYts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AP: The Latest: Former Yale classmate describes Brett Kavanaugh as 'frequent drinker, ... https://t.co/cpGdSW6GJy https://t.co/e0P7Ff6O53]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: UPDATE: Three men killed in Pennsylvania car explosion https://t.co/booOFbyG8Y https://t.co/EnfVsZNHzY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: Abandoned baby flamingos learn to walk at the Prague Zoo https://t.co/vKLoMaS6aR via @ReutersTV https://t.co/8oK4qGSbU5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AP: While campaigning, @AyannaPressley said she refused to wait her turn to lead, ... https://t.co/Y3X1RK9Vtq https://t.co/UmT1lExiZK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: ICYMI: Hollywood actor Jeff Goldblum has faced dinosaurs and aliens in his ... https://t.co/RRqA0kx54o https://t.co/eBWIDUisg3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: Former @FEMA Administrator David Paulison: “They are ready for this storm, ... https://t.co/emKTX7UjLv https://t.co/8BCWuuQwU4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BuzzFeedNews: Families are pranking children into thinking they're "invisible" and ... https://t.co/vmUudFJ5UG https://t.co/DTNHlMphrG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: Ahead of today's #AppleEvent, we track the history of the $1 trillion company: https://t.co/EstcICTRdJ https://t.co/gNWipfdS62]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: .@GOPLeader: Possibility of Speaker Pelosi 'Should Scare All Americans' https://t.co/OakoXCEMjb https://t.co/rx66cs6wA1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: Former Federal Reserve chair and former treasury secretaries reflect on the ... https://t.co/RoHAmn0HFH https://t.co/Y82QM9qM3Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BuzzFeedNews: Kahoot, an interactive platform that lets users either play quizzes ... https://t.co/ZmPPIYOc3v https://t.co/jmm9EjVQRG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BuzzFeedNews: Amazon is planning on selling fresh, live Christmas trees starting in ... https://t.co/OCAiiqTBLx https://t.co/8ul2UmGv2G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: Myanmar group founded by prominent dissident urges release of Reuters reporters https://t.co/2Tyr7XftVh https://t.co/VQRvtApQhx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @realDonaldTrump: “The President has absolutely demonstrated no wrongdoing whatsoever ... https://t.co/Ma5Vu9UddH https://t.co/uR2XveHTSp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WSJ: For 17-year-old Jake Campbell, the 9/11 ceremony was different this year. He ... https://t.co/couGIoiz9A https://t.co/RUgtr6TdBQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nytimesworld: Humanity suffered through its darkest year in over a decade, according ... https://t.co/WXChQfNfs0 https://t.co/MBho9UJOGW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: One very good pup helped firefighters battle the Delta Fire in Shasta ... https://t.co/3DCUIlUiIf https://t.co/arYy8SX9dG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AP: BREAKING: Spokesman for provincial governor says number of killed in suicide bombing in eastern ... https://t.co/YGXEtJFOSr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BuzzFeedNews: “The fact that the government would quite literally send lawyers into ... https://t.co/O6OmgMWZjU https://t.co/qI1ZPzHYNd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: Wall Street regulators take multiple actions against cryptocurrency firms https://t.co/CCeE7M9mg4 https://t.co/nhDT38X7oD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: George Papadopoulos, convicted for lying in Mueller probe, admits mistake in ... https://t.co/ELw92otXWR https://t.co/k1jr18sx3v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: John Legend makes history with Emmy win https://t.co/sXcU9n7Dx7 via @ReutersTV https://t.co/pH6cmKJ4bx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BuzzFeedNews: Women say a school for troubled teens tried to scare them into being ... https://t.co/71suG05tTR https://t.co/WxQja465Ac]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nytimesworld: Kulsoom Nawaz's death came at a precarious time for what was once of ... https://t.co/ZKY4Bgjsel https://t.co/VOrVpNgiP6]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>