<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[T-SQL Developers – Cerritos CA: T-SQL Developer Cerritos, CA Contract/ Full time Job Description: The candidate should have 3 – 5 years experienced TSQL developer. The candidate should have been Involved in all phases of the project (Documentation,… https://t.co/xzUEB2nZ6V https://t.co/GPiEHx6Ezp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Reporting Analyst: Senior Reporting Analyst Freedom Mortgage Corporation seeks a Senior Reporting Analyst to perform research and information gathering necessary to define, design, create, and document business requirements and specifications as… https://t.co/jVQH1HPUyI https://t.co/Ap0g79qKBt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alibaba's Jack Ma urges Facebook to fix privacy issues: BOAO, China (Reuters) - Jack Ma, founder of Chinese e-commerce giant Alibaba, on Monday urged Facebook Inc to resolve its data privacy problems, a day before the social media giant's founder, Mark… https://t.co/KaI5Q5OcPX https://t.co/3pPPGY4OLz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL/SQL Developer/Application Programmer Analyst 3: Job Description Let’s talk about building a rewarding career It starts with you. Our goal is to attract, develop, retain and motivate the most talented people – those who care and who work together as… https://t.co/CmYvIjepbR https://t.co/OKoP3gOrEb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Solutions Architect: Description: THE COMPANY Are you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing… https://t.co/9yETuhl32g https://t.co/VmD78MftQJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SR SQL Server DBA: SR SQL Server DBA Oak Brook, Illinois – United States Job Start Date – 03/29/18, Posted Date – 03/29/18 Primary SkillsSR SQL Server DBATax TermsC2COverview Client: Chamberlain Group Role: SR SQL Server DBA Duration: 6 + Openings: 1… https://t.co/oKwWg3oGDz https://t.co/xzOjJdfFMn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle PL/SQL Developer: Oracle PL/SQL Developer Title: Oracle PL/SQL DeveloperPosition Type: ContractLocation: Phoenix, AZWork Authorization considered: EAD Greencard H4 US Citizen Description:Qualifications:??? ?Bachelor’s degree in computer science or… https://t.co/a1A599tOOQ https://t.co/YsUPvLmiCU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republican senator says Facebook scandals may be 'too big' for company to fix alone: WASHINGTON (Reuters) - A Republican U.S. senator warned on Sunday that Facebook Inc may need to be regulated to address concerns about the company's privacy and foreign… https://t.co/D9BH3QOOSX https://t.co/UrjSR21pd6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: FullStack Labs is a fast growing software consultancy with offices in Sacramento, CA, Arlington, VA and Barranquilla, Colombia. We build web, desktop, and mobile applications for businesses, from small startups to large enterprises, and… https://t.co/tp2RNQmSdr https://t.co/GhbljCCbeb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer: SENIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER Full time permanent position US Citizens, Permanent Residence, or TN1 Visas only SALARY: $95k + 10% Bonus LOCATION: Lafayette,CO or Lake Oswego OR preferred, but Remote is OK too SENIOR SOFTWARE… https://t.co/LMkfJwtg5R https://t.co/Tv4UHggR34]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Database Administrator (DBA): SQL Database Administrator (DBA) JOB DESCRIPTION IPG Photonics is seeking a highly motivated and experienced individual to join our growing IT team and work in a fast-paced, dynamic, high-tech manufacturing company. As a… https://t.co/ojm89TEWUn https://t.co/UlpHT0xceE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[User Interface Engineer: User Interface Engineer at Hewlett Packard Enterprise CompanyTo top Skip Navigation Hewlett Packard Enterprise Careers – Overview – Search and apply – Sales Graduate Program – Students &amp; Graduates – Veterans – Retirees – Help… https://t.co/BnJ7SNv7v8 https://t.co/MiIpyGX5SY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer: About Onnit: Onnit is an Austin, TX-based health and wellness brand focused on encouraging a peak level of human performance through the best in nutritional supplementation, health-conscious foods, and unconventional fitness… https://t.co/7jYwV4KQtQ https://t.co/wOVGnfsUNS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Urgent Need for Test Automation Engineer @@ Dallas, TX: Urgent Need for Test Automation Engineer @@ Dallas, TX – Sriven Systems Inc. – Houston, TX – 03-30-2018 | ******** Toggle navigation – Tech Careers – Job Search – Skills Center – Dice Careers Mobile… https://t.co/euGWEC0HiA https://t.co/uWjqu7T7X2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook suspends Canadian firm AggregateIQ over data scandal: (Reuters) - Facebook Inc said on Friday that it had suspended Canadian political consultancy AggregateIQ from its platform after reports that the data firm may have improperly had access to… https://t.co/jjIl3PPftr https://t.co/uLxxBbnfIC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ServiceNow Developer – Norcross, GA: ServiceNow Developer – Norcross, GA – Company – Sustainability – News – Careers – Investors – Contact us – Products – Markets – Insights Search All Jobs – – – – – – – Join Talent Community ServiceNow Developer –… https://t.co/SZili3tYm2 https://t.co/R0iNqCogJz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Full Stack Developer: Description: THE COMPANY Are you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing… https://t.co/SwPT0XXTOn https://t.co/ptNKBGKmAT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior PL/SQL Developer: LOCATION: Seaside, CA or Remote POSITION DESCRIPTION: Aderas is seeking a Junior PL/SQL to work on a Department of Defense Contract. REQUIRED EDUCATION: * Bachelors degree (May substitute equivalent of 4 years experience for a… https://t.co/dcggrmhueW https://t.co/e6Ywo7eWFk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Business Analyst Consultant – Eden Prairie, MN: Description If you want to achieve more in your mission of health care, you have to be really smart about the business of health care. Challenge yourself, your peers and our industry by shaping what… https://t.co/YPanXvgF4V https://t.co/6PZx0OthzA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior ETL Developer – SSIS, SQL, .NET: Have you worked with SQL Server, SSIS, tape, bubblegum and related technologies to enable ETL and replication between disparate environments? Perhaps on-prem to cloud, cloud to on-prem, and so on? Workstate seeks… https://t.co/EEhPvpzvLz https://t.co/ZOXwfQeIdk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adidas to close stores in online push: CEO in Financial Times: FRANKFURT (Reuters) - Adidas expects to close down stores in the coming years as part of a shift towards selling more goods online, its chief executive told a newspaper. https://t.co/jLQzmiNTv8 https://t.co/2tz4SD0nRO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intern: Software Engineering – SQL, JavaScript: Intern: Software Engineering – SQL, JavaScript Description at Microfocus Skip Navigation Work with us, doing what you do best. Search Jobs Keyword Search Location Search RadiusMiles5 miles15 miles25 miles35… https://t.co/B5YdXNcGE0 https://t.co/idEPBhdxAj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sql Developer: Sql Developer HI,Hope you doing great,?Greetings from Amiga!!URGENT New Position ?SQL Developer?We have an urgent opening as a SQL Developer . I?ll send you Job detail Please have a look on Job detail and revert back with your updated… https://t.co/D5vSHnT5mT https://t.co/B62b9U4Tvm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Healthcare Data Analyst – Irvine, CA: You are a thought leader who thrives on developing new solutions to solve tough challenges. As a critical member of our business analysis team, you will help rewrite the future of UnitedHealth Group. Here,… https://t.co/GTI18jcG66 https://t.co/Agmw4xbSsD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior HEDIS Analyst – Minnetonka, MN or Telecommute: You believe data can help reshape the future, and you find yourself loving the thrill of diving into challenging analysis. At UnitedHealth Group, you’ll find an organization that will recognize those… https://t.co/AzHVJkqWId https://t.co/fYpFeTEkzE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business System Analyst – Multiple Locations: We seek for a Business System Analyst with Agile testing and automation background to join our organization.   This is a rewarding opportunity for the right candidate to make good use of his/her analysis,… https://t.co/dX1DHgvhqQ https://t.co/JQ1LA4Zv4i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Egyptian court allows Uber and Careem to continue operations: CAIRO (Reuters) - An Egyptian court ruled on Saturday that a judicial decision to suspend the licenses of ride-hailing companies Uber and Careem should not be applied, allowing them to… https://t.co/i20hXXke0L https://t.co/UAb7Ek9Ktw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MYSQL DBA: MySQL Administration and Maintenance * Plan, design, deploy database systems, including base definition, structure, documentation, requirements gathering, preparing operational guidelines, and securing data. * Develop data models and perform… https://t.co/qSAnq6Fuct https://t.co/BTIjU1JvuY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Healthcare BSA with SSRS and SQL skills: Irvine Technology Corporation (ITC) is a leading provider of technology and staffing solutions for IT, Security, Engineering, and Interactive Design disciplines servicing startups to enterprise clients,… https://t.co/m38wTnhYt4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET/SQL Operational Analyst (Sys Supp Analyst 4): Job Description Enterprise Finance &amp; Information Technology offers technology and services that exceed Wells Fargo customers’ expectations and directly enable them to succeed financially. We interact… https://t.co/HS5JUNJKek https://t.co/8GTt5NyvCz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle PL SQL Developer: Oracle PL SQL Developer Malvern, Pennsylvania – United States Job Start Date – 03/19/18, Posted Date – 03/19/18 Primary SkillsNATax TermsC2COverviewOracle PL/SQL Developer * Job CodeSG – 10286 * Pay Rate/SalaryUSD – 40/ *… https://t.co/BRnY6RnqxT https://t.co/NyCxPbO3O2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .NET SQL Developer: The Senior SQL Developer creates the overall structure and workflow of a software solution and is responsible for leading and/or handling the development of one to multiple components. The Senior Developer will work with the… https://t.co/2wMlfuh0Fn https://t.co/qzSCOz85th]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Philippines regulator orders pushback in Uber's shutdown amid ongoing review: MANILA (Reuters) - The Philippines' anti-trust agency said on Saturday it has ordered Uber Technologies Inc [UBER.UL] to continue domestic operations as it reviews the ride… https://t.co/vQjxpjKSw7 https://t.co/puqw0Tn4ut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server Developer: The resource will be working on integration projects using SQL 2008/2012/2017, Workload Automation (Scheduling tool). We are looking for a DBA who can provide SQL Server development skills mostly around stored procedure development… https://t.co/L0HTAIemQ7 https://t.co/GKtAvm3xhp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C# Developer: Key Required Skills: C#, SQL, Jquery, JSON, EWS, NuGet, Powershell POSITION DESCRIPTION: Immediate need for a C# Developer to support the development, enhancement and maintenance of a suite of internal applications automating the processes… https://t.co/JoLQgGOy6U https://t.co/5RJMBhraaq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MS SQL Database Administrator: This is a MS SQL / MySQL Server DBA role largely responsible for providing operational database services to the organization. We are looking to fill a need to have a highly competent and highly motivated individual in this… https://t.co/lJ2ljj3cLI https://t.co/dLSMlZucEx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BI/DW Developer (PowerCenter 9.x) | Informatica Cloud | Teradata: BI/DW Developer (PowerCenter 9.x) | Informatica Cloud | Teradata | CareWorks Tech CareWorks Tech Menu – Services – IT Consulting – Enterprise Service Management – Infrastructure – Security… https://t.co/ToC2jVev8l https://t.co/bbmYZvbILw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst – Data insights, SQL, R: San Francisco, CA Full-time Compensation Unspecified Posted Today If you are a Data Analyst with experience, please read on! We are based in beautiful Sausalito, CA. We are an energetic, innovative, and thriving tech… https://t.co/zA9UVJXFbe https://t.co/xQx3xGlrHs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consumer groups to approach FTC over Facebook's facial recognition: (Reuters) - A civil rights group and some consumer groups said on Friday they would file a complaint with the U.S. Federal Trade Commission (FTC) alleging that Facebook Inc's use of… https://t.co/1Tf50XSZSf https://t.co/qQgjeU7CPN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle PL SQL Developer: Oracle PL SQL Developer Malvern, Pennsylvania – United States Job Start Date – 03/19/18, Posted Date – 03/19/18 Primary SkillsNATax TermsC2COverviewOracle PL/SQL Developer * Job CodeSG – 10286 * Pay Rate/SalaryUSD – 40/ *… https://t.co/tv3HbqRjMX https://t.co/igVbMz0MO3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst III: Description: THE COMPANYAre you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable,… https://t.co/23hTPpBCPQ https://t.co/8sOQoYfC0y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Database Administrator (DBA): SQL Database Administrator (DBA) JOB DESCRIPTION IPG Photonics is seeking a highly motivated and experienced individual to join our growing IT team and work in a fast-paced, dynamic, high-tech manufacturing company. As a… https://t.co/AGLJpJBTED https://t.co/AgZ7d5sulc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Sr Analyst, Healthcare Analytics:   Job Description – SQL Sr Analyst, Healthcare Analytics (1801865) Job Description  SQL Sr Analyst, Healthcare Analytics – (1801865) Primary Location : US-CA-Long Beach-MOLINA300 Job : Business &amp; Strategy Analysis… https://t.co/pWgYZ6KI19 https://t.co/w6WpYi9VYn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Provider Network Reporting Analyst – Minnetonka, MN: There are changes happening in health care that go beyond the basics we hear in the news. People like you and organizations like UnitedHealth Group are driving ever higher levels of sophistication in… https://t.co/nFTUDIaeh6 https://t.co/qaiJ8PHAjx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook backs political ad bill, sets limits on 'issue ads': SAN FRANCISCO/WASHINGTON (Reuters) - Facebook Inc backed for the first time on Friday proposed legislation requiring social media sites to disclose the identities of buyers of online political… https://t.co/VqYkEwPa7T https://t.co/SQXY1e2Ue0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MS SQL Database Administrator: RELOCATION PACKAGE AVAILABLE; CAN SPONSOR A US CITIZEN FOR A DOD CLEARANCE ISS is seeking an MS SQL Database Administrator to support the operations and maintenance of a large number of database servers for the US Army… https://t.co/gyhqgiBksU https://t.co/yrOrwGtYgT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET/SQL Operational Analyst (Sys Supp Analyst 4): Job Description Enterprise Finance &amp; Information Technology offers technology and services that exceed Wells Fargo customers’ expectations and directly enable them to succeed financially. We interact… https://t.co/zqjNiywr0A https://t.co/ca4I98Zfs4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: POSITION OVERVIEW OF THE PL/SQL DEVELOPER: We are looking for a talented PL/SQL Developer to join a team focused on developing and maintaining various databases and database applications. Are you a creative problem solver with experience… https://t.co/OzhQNxeqrM https://t.co/bhhgUXgi4W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analytics Analyst / Sales Operations Analyst – West Valley City Utah or Eden Prairie, MN: Energize your career with one of Healthcare’s fastest growing companies.     You dream of a great career with a great company – where you can make an impact… https://t.co/65NdboRvJM https://t.co/RDAD2e3lsA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL DBA: SQL DBA Chicago, Illinois – United States Job Start Date – 03/08/18, Posted Date – 03/08/18 Primary SkillsSQL DBATax TermsC2COverview Client Domain : Airline Industry Position : SQL DBA Location : Chicago, IL Duration : 6 Months Type of… https://t.co/Q5NjfqI0fR https://t.co/Ok0j1JD0Ha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chinese Uber rival Didi launches in Mexico, recruits drivers: MEXICO CITY/SAN FRANCISCO (Reuters) - Chinese ride-hailing company Didi Chuxing has publicly launched in Mexico with a website advertising its service to drivers and passengers, setting the… https://t.co/SQnV65AFiM https://t.co/Ly4D5a3631]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager III: Description: THE COMPANY Are you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable,… https://t.co/p09blrgqIN https://t.co/zwO6iZklVS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NoSQL Database Management Specialist, Baltimore, MD: Must be capable of providing highly technical expertise and support in the use of DBMS. Must be able to evaluate and recommend available DBMS products to support validated user requirements. Defines… https://t.co/sRXnEMrI8P https://t.co/fZwiMci2YB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Teradata Systems Analyst: (2) SQL TERADATA SYSTEMS ANALYST DETAILS LOCATION: Dallas, TX/Stephenville, TX – Position will require an initial 3-6 weeks (depending on experience) in Stephenville, TX for knowledge transfer. After that knowledge transfer… https://t.co/oBnJOTAWi8 https://t.co/MmrFtbuP34]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C# / .NET / SQL Server Developer (Presentation Layer): C#/.NET Developer (Presentation Layer) In search of a C#/NET Developer with focus on the presentation layer and conversational user interface. In addition to C#/.NET, applicants must have or quickly… https://t.co/IVRmAngbiG https://t.co/AY3knOodRE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Software Engineer – BI/Data Warehouse: Job Description: The Senior Software Engineer for the BI/Data Warehouse team will work within an agile team environment, helping to design, develop, and maintain the data warehouse components of the HCHB… https://t.co/XUcGyR5YF7 https://t.co/UiTAoaoqXT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Incident Response: Job Purpose: Respond to urgent or crisis situations within client networks to effectively mitigate threats through preparedness, response and recovery approaches, as needed, to maximize preservation of property and information. To… https://t.co/FCvvtm60h5 https://t.co/P5i3Iiw8BV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Activist fund says Toshiba chip unit worth as much as $40 billion: TOKYO (Reuters) - A Hong Kong-based activist investment fund said Toshiba Corp's chip unit was worth as much as $40 billion, double the sale price agreed with a Bain-led consortium, as it… https://t.co/yyrOwmNMqY https://t.co/rSBUXcITlm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intern: Software Engineering – SQL, JavaScript: Intern: Software Engineering – SQL, JavaScript Description at Microfocus Skip Navigation Work with us, doing what you do best. Search Jobs Keyword Search Location Search RadiusMiles5 miles15 miles25 miles35… https://t.co/IfWh5dSbyT https://t.co/rd759F78CG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Metadata Developer: SQL Metadata Developer Charlotte, North Carolina – United States Job Start Date – 03/22/18, Posted Date – 03/22/18 Primary SkillsNATax TermsC2COverview Duration: Long Term Contract Location: Local to Charlotte, NC Interview… https://t.co/NXVuHoaCWZ https://t.co/BbEoiccHTx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. SQL Programmer Analyst: Come work at a place where innovation and teamwork come together to support the most exciting missions in the world! You will have the opportunity to provide application development support by analyzing business requirements… https://t.co/yYyBZI4CI4 https://t.co/CQeQIhmz5S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Full Stack Software Engineer: Payments (PHP, T-SQL, TDD): AN IDEAL CANDIDATE HAS * 5+ YEARS of professional experience as a FULL STACK, full lifecycle software engineer. * Bachelors / Masters degree in Computer Science or related field * 3-5+… https://t.co/mAJgCKhyid https://t.co/qX8Mxgj1BK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Application Software Engineer (Web Services): Job Information: Senior Application Software Engineer (Web Services) Job Email Opening Title Senior Application Software Engineer (Web Services) Description Location: Town and Country, MO Duration of… https://t.co/7C4qXA3Ehu https://t.co/kC3XqAXbGw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Devops Engineer (Grafana): Devops Engineer (Grafana) Ref No.: 18-00609 Location: Mt Laurel, New Jersey Position Type: Direct Placement Start Date: 04/01/2018 Technical/Functional Skills Python, Django OpenStack RHEL/CentOS, Linux, Nagios, Zabbix, Git/SVN… https://t.co/8btCexDIOJ https://t.co/YeChNnnMYb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple says repeal of EPA carbon plan would threaten investments: WASHINGTON (Reuters) - Apple Inc said on Friday it opposes any repeal by the U.S. Environmental Protection Agency of the Clean Power Plan, which is a priority of the agency's Administrator… https://t.co/LWA2ujvI05 https://t.co/a5JuZbv7lt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DataStax Graph Consultant: At DataStax we are on the forefront of an incredible market opportunity with life-changing technology. We are looking for individuals who are ready to make an impact and able to thrive in a rapidly growing environment. Huge… https://t.co/2WWselK5vn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reports Developer (SQL/ETL) | BI/DW | Business Objects: Reports Developer (SQL/ETL) | BI/DW | Business Objects Columbus, OH 03-25-2018 Location: Columbus, OH For more than 18 years, CareWorks Tech has been delivering technology solutions that drive… https://t.co/2bKR8znI5M https://t.co/vkPV7CEPOk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Backend Engineer: Zingo enables individuals to increase and maintain their credit score for free through the submission of non-traditional payment histories and reoccurring payment streams to the major credit bureaus. By simply signing-up on our… https://t.co/0YxBHIjt3Y https://t.co/2gGpGysDjZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior PL/SQL Developer: LOCATION: Remote POSITION DESCRIPTION: Aderas is seeking a Junior PL/SQL to work on a Department of Defense Contract. REQUIRED EDUCATION: * Bachelors degree (May substitute equivalent of 4 years experience for a bachelors degree)… https://t.co/8qgHbXS0os https://t.co/GkK0KmrBDa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL/SQL Developer: PL/SQL Developer Malvern, Pennsylvania – United States Job Start Date – 03/15/18, Posted Date – 03/15/18 Primary SkillsSQL,Perl,Groovy,Hibernate,JPA,AIX,Solaris,ORMTax TermsC2C,W-2Overview Responsibilities include: * Developing code… https://t.co/N0stVnjAAJ https://t.co/6jtnJ7uecD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grab's Uber deal still has some obstacles to navigate: SINGAPORE (Reuters) - Regulatory scrutiny could complicate ride-hailing company Grab's takeover of Uber Technologies' Southeast Asian business, but there is little the authorities can do to stop Uber… https://t.co/mg9i2dNR8H https://t.co/X5x4LuCG6L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: Job TitleSQL Developer – ID:30967 Duration12 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsXML, SSIS, XML Stored Procedures, SQL Queries, Consumer Facing web sites LocationTorrance, CA Date Posted02/09/2018 FOR IMMEDIATE DETAILS ABOUT THIS POSITION,… https://t.co/O7XMPFspWJ https://t.co/iEKXmUy12T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Process Analyst: CenturyLink (NYSE: CTL) is a global communications and IT services company focused on connecting its customers to the power of the digital world. CenturyLink offers network and data systems management, big data analytics, managed… https://t.co/ikiE7pj3RB https://t.co/NEf5sZ8RtN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL/SQL Developer/Application Programmer Analyst 3: Job Description Let’s talk about building a rewarding career It starts with you. Our goal is to attract, develop, retain and motivate the most talented people – those who care and who work together as… https://t.co/JXCNM5WqNy https://t.co/sWgRSt1Vpn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: POSITION OVERVIEW OF THE PL/SQL DEVELOPER: We are looking for a talented PL/SQL Developer to join a team focused on developing and maintaining various databases and database applications. Are you a creative problem solver with experience… https://t.co/LqybQOUuou https://t.co/mQZEO9N4SJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer: Development Expert for SAP Labs, LLC (Palo Alto, CA) resp for dvlpmnt focus on dsgn, codng, tstng, &amp; qlty assur of cmplx prod features in dvlpmnt team. Bach in Comp Sci, Eng, Math, or rltd field &amp; 7 yrs exp req’d, or alt Master’s &amp; 5 yrs of… https://t.co/lPAZasMCyN https://t.co/JuN5ur1fFW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Developer: Description:   Job Title Sr. Software Developer * Job Description:  Candidate must have excellent data analysis, technical analysis, problem solving and interpersonal skills.  Preferably, candidate should have previous experience… https://t.co/ozClzOAwUa https://t.co/szK2KM359F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Samsung Electronics tips record first quarter profit as chip boom winds down: SEOUL (Reuters) - Samsung Electronics Co Ltd tipped a surprise record first-quarter profit on Friday but market reaction was muted due to growing concerns that the… https://t.co/1holu5oG0Z https://t.co/c36wh6f0jW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET/SQL Operational Analyst (Sys Supp Analyst 4): Job Description Enterprise Finance &amp; Information Technology offers technology and services that exceed Wells Fargo customers’ expectations and directly enable them to succeed financially. We interact… https://t.co/MZO4RzOa9b https://t.co/LXGIV3zcqC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Machine Learning Architect: PwC/LOS Overview PwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about us at… https://t.co/3FKvLHkKwx https://t.co/lOkc54X7po]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[T-SQL Developers – Cerritos CA: T-SQL Developer Cerritos, CA Contract/ Full time Job Description: The candidate should have 3 – 5 years experienced TSQL developer. The candidate should have been Involved in all phases of the project (Documentation,… https://t.co/Jm2ay1Od1T https://t.co/qZD4VTKiKA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liquid Studios – JavaScript – Node Developer: Basic Qualifications * Minimum 3 years of experience working at a consulting firm, web startup, agency or equivalent education/professional experience * Minimum 3 years of experience with: building RESTful… https://t.co/3zNcIKEPA5 https://t.co/rP40aNxHiJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Certified EPIC HIM Document Imaging Analyst: Are you a&amp;nbsp;Certified EPIC HIM Document Imaging Analyst who is ready to take on new challenges, propel your career and join a prestigious and reputable non profit hospital in beautiful Central Coast of… https://t.co/hiy1KRstsW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russia files lawsuit to block Telegram messaging app: MOSCOW (Reuters) - Russia's state communications watchdog said on Friday it had filed a lawsuit to limit access to the Telegram messaging app after the company refused to give Russian state security… https://t.co/FNg9OTr9no https://t.co/YPRRfPBPPg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL DBA: MUST HAVE SKILLS: * MIRRORING * ALWAYS ON DESCRIPTION: * Ability to manage multiple projects at once * Provide break/fix as well as proactive system support * Strong performance tuning and troubleshooting skills * Must have experience in SQL… https://t.co/MHCQPtHne7 https://t.co/M5ZlcCmnb8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL/SQL Developer @@ BOSTON, MA: PL/SQL Developer @@ BOSTON, MA – Sriven Systems Inc. – Boston, MA – 04-02-2018 | ******** Toggle navigation – Tech Careers – Job Search – Skills Center – Dice Careers Mobile – Career Explorer – Salary Predictor – Career… https://t.co/zkRXOeUcGm https://t.co/4XUX075SH2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, AD/FIN: AD/FINs mission is to bring financial style intelligence to programmatic media markets. Our CAMPAIGN:WATCH and CAMPAIGN:CENTRAL tools shed light into the black box of programmatic trading, and creates greater clarity and… https://t.co/25IXPkUnJc https://t.co/j298jByJag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[T-SQL Developers – Cerritos CA: T-SQL Developer Cerritos, CA Contract/ Full time Job Description: The candidate should have 3 – 5 years experienced TSQL developer. The candidate should have been Involved in all phases of the project (Documentation,… https://t.co/aRyAbZZxh8 https://t.co/GeetbtJ3uw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer Senior (66): 1.Bachelors degree in Computer Science/Computer Engineering. **** a full-stack developer, must be comfortable switching roles between Web Services, APIs, Batches or Web Development. 3.Expertise in designing and developing… https://t.co/s7s5ZYyRqo https://t.co/VZ5rqyV19H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#SQL DBA – Philadelphia, PA: Position Title: SQL DBA Consultant Location: North East Philly, PA Type: Contract Requirements 5+ years of experience in Database Administration and Developer for very large and complex databases in SQL Server. Expertise in… https://t.co/IhWSXCogGd https://t.co/VhsWN15Xqr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[California pension system presses Facebook on data protection: BOSTON (Reuters) - The California State Teachers' Retirement System will ask Facebook Inc about the controls the social media company has in place to protect user data, the system said in a… https://t.co/Eo8R0AntlJ https://t.co/TmMyYm5PRt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: REQUIRED SKILLS Experience in relational database design, development, and support (MS SQL Server T-SQL preferred) Experience in complex database objects in T-SQL and/or PLSQL Experience with SSIS and/or ETL tools Experience with Visual… https://t.co/zBpQE9cZ4n https://t.co/xI6FGdSWR4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NoSQL Database Management Specialist, Baltimore, MD: Must be capable of providing highly technical expertise and support in the use of DBMS. Must be able to evaluate and recommend available DBMS products to support validated user requirements. Defines… https://t.co/hh1K5vjmth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Machine Learning Architect: PwC/LOS Overview PwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about us at… https://t.co/A689dQv0RR https://t.co/JGShD7iDFP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Software Developer Computer Scientist: Description: Leidos is actively hiring for a .NET Software Developer Computer Scientist to join our team in Alexandria, VA. JOB SUMMARY   The Operational Mission Support within Leidos, Inc. has a job opening in… https://t.co/IFnlPyvZ47 https://t.co/eWKF24aR4O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst – Data insights, SQL, R: San Francisco, CA Full-time Compensation Unspecified Posted Today If you are a Data Analyst with experience, please read on! We are based in beautiful Sausalito, CA. We are an energetic, innovative, and thriving tech… https://t.co/36P8ajKTAd https://t.co/j68R4KB8w3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Staff Engineer: Senior Staff Engineer (job location is Seattle, WA) Design &amp; write code for video services designed to enhance HBO’s video streaming capability &amp; content associated w/ company’s interactive endeavors. Perform site architecture &amp;… https://t.co/S6dB54jYmG https://t.co/gncQIxgsTb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook fined $33 million for failing to aid Brazil graft probe: BRASILIA (Reuters) - A Brazilian judge has ordered that Facebook Inc pay 111.7 million reais ($33.4 million) for failing to cooperate with a corruption investigation, federal prosecutors… https://t.co/0hijAI2lrf https://t.co/NGPFwzEqUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT-Assistant Vice President: IT-Assistant Vice President (Morrisville, NC): Perform system analysis &amp; design &amp; develop IT applications for internal (management information) &amp; external (regulatory) Liquidity Risk reporting in accordance with IT standards… https://t.co/bIxjRx8h9s https://t.co/ggt5K2xOh4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US – C#, https://t.co/hQSAXFT0RK, SQL, HTML: Infosys Engineering Services Technology Lead – US .Net, *******, C#, HTML Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to… https://t.co/ZfEX5BCMSR https://t.co/lBklUbvtj3]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>