<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Never dance in a puddle when there's a hole in your shoe (it's always best to take your shoes off first). --&gt; John D. Rhodes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome burgers and beer t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the beer &amp; beer lovers in your life!  http://t.co/VzUP6B49t0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its better to own the racecourse then the race horse - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Courage is not the absence of fear, but rather the judgment that something else is more important than fear - Ambrose Redmoon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to War  http://t.co/DM2gg1lYZW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Men of lofty genius when they are doing the least work are most active. - Leonardo da Vinci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious T-Shirt - “I Got Your Back” http://t.co/ZZO9Lp1b2Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Invest in Penny Stocks And Earn Huge Profits  http://t.co/qeZcUGHNOD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How Small Business Can Grow with Social Media Sites  http://t.co/iKYLxA6WHT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the sun refused to shine I would still be loving you. When mountains crumble to the sea there will still be you &amp; me - Led Zeppelin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picking Earphones for Fitness Activities  http://t.co/yfmkOfgVU6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the top burger chains in the US!  http://t.co/8dMbjMtkXN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just want one day off when I can go swimming and eat ice cream and look at rainbows.  Mariah Carey (pre-rehab)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest lie you can make is to lie to yourself. - Matt Zotti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't compare me to my father. Our similarities are different. -  Dale Berra about his father Yogi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You may delay, but time will not. - Benjamin Franklin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mama always said you could tell an awful lot about a person by the kind of shoes they wear. - Forrest Gump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walking: the most ancient exercise and still the best modern exercise. - Carrie Latet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Julius LaRosa  http://t.co/vgzoqPggZQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Try not. Do, or do not. There is no try. - Yoda, The Empire Strikes Back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketing is too important to be left to the marketing department. - David Packard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Learning Tool for Kids - Snap Circuits Jr - Hands On Learning All About Circuits http://t.co/KpetWyamTf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagination is more important than knowledge. Knowledge is limited. Imagination encircles the world. - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Beverly Hillbillies is an American sitcom classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/XZo2cM2BYb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before you take somebody's head off be sure you've used yours]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our greatest weakness lies in giving up. The most certain way to succeed is always to try just one more time. - Thomas A. Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't get too caught up in making money or having a job, get excited about the fact that you can design your life. Darren L. Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the Major Work Shoe Brands  http://t.co/nhDVf9Ek8r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't do fashion. I am fashion. - Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is the mark of an educated mind to be able to entertain a thought without accepting it. - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the fascinating history of the New York Yankees - http://t.co/q5GCuSyIpX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Lobo the Classic Rock Group?  http://t.co/SjkopDSW15]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The rest of the world lives to eat, while I eat to live. - Socrates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I looked and looked but I didn't see God. - Yuri Gagarin, 14 April 1961]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion has two purposes: comfort and love. Beauty comes when fashion succeeds. --&gt; Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Trust Me I'm A Nerd Mens Sweatshirt - Awesome http://t.co/KJnRkKd4XS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Bob Seger  http://t.co/2NmPqKPEo1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL - A Runny Nose In Your Shower Dispensing Soap - Love It!  http://t.co/ZWwi5vfoUm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Windows has detected you do not have a keyboard. Press 'F9" to continue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why does a girl with the least principle draw the most interest?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Hilarious 60s Comedy – Get Smart  http://t.co/LZkgrqsOze]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You may have to fight a battle more than once to win it. - Margaret Thatcher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The time has come the Walrus said, To talk of many thing’s Of shoes and ships and sealing-wax of cabbages and kings - Lewis Carroll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of KC and the Sunshine Band  http://t.co/r2CgFwlU1w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Saving Money With Solar Power  http://t.co/6TR5Qm2MGP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to 3D Printing  http://t.co/NGmmFiLwXI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A computer lets you make more mistakes faster than any invention in human history - with the possible exceptions of handguns and tequila.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is the mark of an educated mind to be able to entertain a thought without accepting it. - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious Cat Scratch Rapper Music Mixer - Awesome!  http://t.co/kZjjUS1mdM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know who invented high heels, but all women owe him a lot! - Marilyn Monroe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The whole fleet knows this man tried to stab me through the neck. And you missed! Butterfingers! - Gaius Baltar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The Top 10 European Beers  http://t.co/foZVH10YYp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Men I may not know, but shoes, shoes I know. - Carrie Bradshaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The rest of the world lives to eat, while I eat to live. - Socrates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read a Short Introduction to ABBA  http://t.co/77dUToMVZw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If high heels were so wonderful, men would be wearing them. - Sue Grafton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Help with Autism  http://t.co/82KHaMSxqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As far as I'm concerned, there won't be a Beatles reunion as long as John Lennon remains dead. - George Harrison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Google Webmaster Tools  http://t.co/hdqZ8JUDXB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys - combine your wallet and smart phone in one compact case - and its cool and stylish - Book Book http://t.co/DFUJyPL6nj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't do any vulgar movements.  -  Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting fired is nature's way of telling you that you had the wrong job in the first place. - Hal Lancaster]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Different Types of Beer  http://t.co/xsRoJ4AKgy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You maniacs! You blew it up! Oh, damn you! Damn you all to hell! - Taylor, Planet of the Apes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lose Weight WITHOUT Dieting (Animal Kingdom Workouts)  --&gt; http://t.co/4KsQ8nfxPj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Hire a Strategy Consulting Firm?  http://t.co/SlZ8Ue4znw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A tax collector has what it takes to take what you got]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn the Keys to Using LinkedIn for Your Company  http://t.co/qMsbU7YBkz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Adoption Part II - the Bulgaria Phase  http://t.co/EkTBsXpeVz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give a girl the right shoes, and she can conquer the world. - Marilyn Monroe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool check out this Nerd Kit...  http://t.co/guS7a69I7q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet - very cool mechanical pin clock - very unique - http://t.co/lVHVMMQBHt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pessimist: A man who thinks that all woman are bad Optimist: A man who hopes so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the animals: God has given them the rudiments of thought and joy untroubled - Fyodor Dostoyevsky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to WordTracker SEO Tools http://t.co/orDOm7gn6j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People share read &amp; generally engage more with any type of content when its surfaced through friends &amp; people they know and trust - Facebook]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Kansas  http://t.co/4pEQBdNlqh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can never be overdressed or overeducated. --&gt; Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't concentrate in flats! - Victoria Beckham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In order to break the ice --  crack a smile]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Strategy Consulting Firms: Gaining a Competitive Advantage  http://t.co/w0ikzyjy4M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advertising is the life of trade. - Calvin Coolidge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes are just made from leather, rubber and cloth - read about exotic shoes... http://t.co/NbkINjjqQO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would be more frightened as a writer if people thought my movies were like science fiction. - Neil LaBute]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Industry is the soul of business and the keystone of prosperity. -Charles Dickens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't fix stupid - Larry Morgan, NHRA Pro Stock driver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The human body is the best work of art. --&gt; Jess C. Scott]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make it so! - Engage! - Captain Picard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Buddy Holly  http://t.co/wwxWTfR9em]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A professor is one who talks in someone else's sleep. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Battleship Memorial Park – Mobile Alabama – A Great Historical Experience  http://t.co/ekNVQRIZOp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion is a form of ugliness so intolerable that we have to alter it every six months. --&gt; Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the animals: God has given them the rudiments of thought and joy untroubled - Fyodor Dostoyevsky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 14 - Doctor Decides to Discontinue IV Treatment  http://t.co/DN7Kh54bZi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't see pitches down the middle anymore - not even in batting practice. -  Hank Aaron]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Millie Jackson  http://t.co/pYamldEh5t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Hamstring Rehab  http://t.co/IP9e64dUOW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was born in 1950 and watched science fiction and horror movies on TV and was always really fascinated by them. - Rick Baker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am convinced that every boy, in his heart, would rather steal second base than an automobile. - Thomas Campbell Clark]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He was born with a silver spoon --  but  never made a stir with it.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>