<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer I, ITD (Job# PT-0121): Senior Software Engineer I, ITD (Job# PT-0121) position available in San Diego, CA. Equal Employer Opportunity: Race, Gender, Veteran, Disabled. recblid 56wccihcu8q14vj7mvweuvxmcz4e1u https://t.co/kWFSRRpyXa https://t.co/8tn0vKZQbP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cybersecurity: JOB FAIR DELTA Resources has an impeccable reputation as a leader in the government services industry. DELTA Resources is actively recruiting professionals with technical backgrounds and operational experience for positions in the… https://t.co/sq01kb0Nfe https://t.co/UG9ZbPO2RP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering: ENGINEERING Applied Materials, Inc. has openings in Santa Clara/ Sunnyvale, CA: Process Engineer (Req #8C91007) Design, collect data, analyze and compile reports on a variety of difficult process engineering experiments; Process Engineer… https://t.co/qNb1Yc2WlQ https://t.co/a3uKU4zpqK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Support Analyst: Are you seeking a new career opportunity in a fast paced and challenging work environment where you have the ability to use your IT knowledge to help people and forge a great career?  If you have experience in technology and a take… https://t.co/BOwquOq24s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Report Documentation Quality Control Consultant (Business Systems Consultant 2): Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented people who will… https://t.co/U218RpOHrP https://t.co/pnD11Qh1ym]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Construction Professional (Project Manager, Project Super/Eng.: Irvine, CA Full-time Compensation Unspecified Posted Today Working with some of the top Owner/Builders and General Contractors in both Southern California and the Nation we are on the… https://t.co/f0mtDUVIbU https://t.co/WhD7Ld4wHk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Administrator: Troubleshooting: * Must have excellent troubleshooting skills for hardware and software in complex scenarios spanning multiple IT work areas. * Ability to perform self-guided research to investigate solutions for complex problems.… https://t.co/BaD3fSUNK0 https://t.co/33oRt5sMwm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer – Artificial Intelligence Java Platform: As a Senior Software Engineer for our AI platform, you will be responsible for designing and developing, robust and scalable solutions for the enterprise. Working on a cutting-edge… https://t.co/RyIyq4vH4x https://t.co/l5ocM8DkRh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Events &amp; Demo Support Engineer: Description Imprivata is the leader in secure access and collaboration for healthcare. For over 10 years, we have been enhancing care delivery by providing fast, secure access to patient information. Healthcare… https://t.co/H7GD7hzh9L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Portland Accountemps Salaried Professional Services Staffing Executive: JOB REQUISITION Portland Accountemps Salaried Professional Services Staffing Executive LOCATION ME PORTLAND JOB DESCRIPTION Job Summary The Staffing Executive is a very unique role… https://t.co/rHe7FxP6xW https://t.co/Pj9mmtwF0J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Programmer/Specialist: Database Programmer/Specialist General Summary The Database Programmer/Specialist is responsible of maintaining and updating existing Enterprise System application programs. The position utilizes MS Access, Visual Basic,… https://t.co/sdKeCspJTS https://t.co/rdLQBkk2ED]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Research Project Manager: Original Posting Date 15-Dec-2017 Supervisory Organization Comprehensive Cancer Center – Oncology Administration STARS Requisition number 47392BR University Job Title Research Associate 3, HSS Posting Position Title… https://t.co/u3S1ztkT2P https://t.co/15Q7L2rZnd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[8 Great Weekend Tech Deals: Nintendo, Apple, Tile, Eufy, Vive Pro: This weekend, ramble around a VR world of your choosing or smartify your coffeemaker with these tech deals. https://t.co/CVoJWxpo5W https://t.co/ZOhbdaTJma]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Engineer: CenturyLink (NYSE: CTL) is a global communications and IT services company focused on connecting its customers to the power of the digital world. CenturyLink offers network and data systems management, big data analytics, managed security… https://t.co/zr1rdqna6z https://t.co/o8SlN5h5ns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director of Experience Innovation – Eden Prairie, MN or Telecommute: If you want to achieve more in your mission of health care, you have to be really smart about the business of health care. Challenge yourself, your peers and our industry by shaping… https://t.co/AJ2sg9ihaw https://t.co/phqSyB0Rul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Diagnostic Imaging Radiology Informatics Analyst: One of the most prestigious Hospital in the beautiful, warm and coastal San Francisco Bay Area is actively looking for a&amp;nbsp;Diagnostic Imaging Radiology Informatics Analyst to add to its reputable team… https://t.co/ZDDqRZ8aen https://t.co/MFYcMKN9TR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Public Sector – Process Improvement – Senior Associate: PwC/LOS Overview PwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn… https://t.co/nCLaSv09J0 https://t.co/dXXXh0hypb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager II: Description: THE COMPANY Are you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable,… https://t.co/uIILuFv8zr https://t.co/ElKjKNk0v3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Machine Learning Architect: PwC/LOS Overview PwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about us at… https://t.co/01m7OPCm71 https://t.co/bkBWTL8MrY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advisory Financial Services Oracle Accounts Payable: PwC/LOS Overview PwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more… https://t.co/uWEcw1eo2u https://t.co/jlGLj4Cwvl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce Senior Associate: PwC/LOS Overview PwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about us at… https://t.co/tt5pGrMBIL https://t.co/jdoCPehETg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Security Manager: The Manager of Information Security, is a technical role with managerial duties. This individual will work under the direction of the Director of Information Technology and will work alongside the IT infrastructure team. The person… https://t.co/KtcDGUAezK https://t.co/FenTT6bnK1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HEDIS Technology Consultant – Telecommute: Great sales are the result of strong purpose, conviction and pride – pride in your ability and your product. UnitedHealth Group offers a portfolio of products that are greatly improving the life of others. Bring… https://t.co/5A1uH4og8F https://t.co/QRMbIWtQbf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Security Specialist IV: Description: THE COMPANYAre you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable,… https://t.co/4VK3LdndGV https://t.co/7Mqjw6KgN2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best Mobile Browsers: Microsoft Edge, Firefox Focus, Google Chrome, and More: Surfing the web on your phone is about to get a whole lot better. https://t.co/1gXjiqkHWf https://t.co/ckWzpxopsp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Archer Administrator / Developer: Archer Admin/Dev  VITA014531449 *Chester, VA*   A contractor to provide technical support and expertise to provide the necessary improvements and enhancements to the information database (VMEDS) and/or other IT… https://t.co/54Yu33xjTk https://t.co/AtfIUf9niP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Software Developer – API Engineering: CenturyLink (NYSE: CTL) is a global communications and IT services company focused on connecting its customers to the power of the digital world. CenturyLink offers network and data systems management, big data… https://t.co/ElFGyaVYq5 https://t.co/0Sbk2W3lQz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle EBS Business Analyst (Carlisle): *** No one with less than 2 years industry experience will be considered. *** *** No third party candidates will be considered. *** Candidates MUST have a minimum of specific domain experience and no resumes will… https://t.co/FJUBmVzwE3 https://t.co/JImT6ynI7O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager II: CO-OP Financial Servicesprovides technically superior products and services to financial institutions across the nation. We are seeking a talentedProject Manager II to be responsible for applying fundamental project management… https://t.co/dwiUYgARSH https://t.co/6Jq3M1Ftms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AR Startup – Sr. Software Engineer – Desktop Applications (C/C++): At Lightform [******************************************************************************************************************************************************* we are building the… https://t.co/5Ftb4oa6lQ https://t.co/n0xJlwjsO2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Analyst (Secret clearance required): Our client has an immediate opportunity as a Network Analyst located in Ft. Huachuca, AZ! This position will support WAN team. JOB DESCRIPTION: * Working within a team environment performing daily management… https://t.co/bpnDp5QnTm https://t.co/Yg892Hgqjh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Performance Systems Analyst: Performance Systems Analyst Description The Front Office Services Group (FOSG) is part of BNY Mellon’s Global Outsourcing service who works closely with a client’s front office, delivering services through the Eagle platform.… https://t.co/XNvGfgfOoK https://t.co/P8C4GDuFa1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP MM Consultant with HANA exp: SAP MM Consultant with S4 HANA exp Consultant must be local to Seattle, WA?Description:Functional/technical proficiency with at least 3+ full lifecycle SAP implementationsAt least 10 years of SAP MM experience?Experience… https://t.co/3JsyJIL3uV https://t.co/o3uhvy6t75]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: SymSoft Solutions is a Digital Experience and Web Development company based in Sacramento. We specialize in designing engaging Digital Experiences and then bringing them to life by implementing enterprise scale Web Content Management… https://t.co/URwK4LEkRd https://t.co/Aptkr5wGgt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Staffing Sales: Account Executive to join our growing office. Job Description &amp; Skills * You will keep a regular pulse on the market as it relates to businesses and hiring trends. (e.g. Expansions, mergers/acquisitions, dissolutions, relocations, new… https://t.co/fRlc3G8Qt6 https://t.co/fcnbDqqRd1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Business Analyst: Only candidates who submit a resume and complete the full application will be considered – anyone without a resume will be declined automatically. For assistance with your job application please use our External Candidate Job… https://t.co/0HcBgRGHq1 https://t.co/N8AmCDIIcs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tech Tools to Help With Hand and Arm Injuries: For those who have recently injured or lost their dominant hand, everything from apps to bungees exist to ease the frustration. https://t.co/71TVtDPVIM https://t.co/ATNxa1qRLA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Digital Instructional Designer – Minnetonka, MN: Our Instructional Designer team is responsible for applying instructional design and development principles and processes to produce effective, engaging and innovative programs to support our field… https://t.co/QSsSoab9ZH https://t.co/WuoQYk82Yn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Business Analyst Consultant – Eden Prairie, MN: Description If you want to achieve more in your mission of health care, you have to be really smart about the business of health care. Challenge yourself, your peers and our industry by shaping what… https://t.co/9xPrb1t1ot https://t.co/H4sOHAGjh5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Claims Business Process Analyst – Eden Prairie, MN: We’ll put you in the driver’s seat on vital projects that have strategic importance to our mission of helping people lead healthier lives. Yes, we share a mission that inspires. We need your… https://t.co/Q4fgQx0vlN https://t.co/bngvSOmhSj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CCM Technical Trainer – US Telecommute: Energize your career with one of Healthcare’s fastest growing companies.     You dream of a great career with a great company – where you can make an impact and help people.  We dream of giving you the opportunity… https://t.co/xJFyUM4K8s https://t.co/XNP5MpeTAf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Reporting Analyst – Eden Prairie, MN, Chicago, IL or Irvine, CA: We’ll put you in the driver’s seat on vital projects that have strategic importance to our mission of helping people lead healthier lives. Yes, we share a mission that inspires. We… https://t.co/PM7aPNuJh0 https://t.co/0MpkpQXVS9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Customer Advocacy and Service Activations Manager: Description: Customer Advocacy and Service Activations Manager Global Information Grid (GIG) Service Management-Operations (GSM-O), a Defense and Intelligence Group of Leidos has an opening for a… https://t.co/JuMFSur6vO https://t.co/2waFHyHtV1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Engineering Senior: Description: Job Summary Leidos was named by LinkedIn as one of the best U.S. Companies and Forbes “Americas Top 500” list. The company is growing quickly, and is looking for new talent. Leidos is offering a $2,000 bonus for… https://t.co/HnIr9rmaNw https://t.co/oRT39WBojt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Project Analyst Intern – WellMed – San Antonio, TX: The IT Project Analyst Intern is primary responsibility is ensuring policies and standards for in-house programs and projects; cross functional project management support and coordination, and… https://t.co/me9bhQ2a3T https://t.co/J5fWEFRbsz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Reporting Analyst – Eden Prairie, MN or Telecommute: We’ll put you in the driver’s seat on vital projects that have strategic importance to our mission of helping people lead healthier lives. Yes, we share a mission that inspires. We need your… https://t.co/UsRyOdJvtX https://t.co/yl5gIpqfSo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Content Writer – Minnetonka, MN: If you want to achieve more in your mission of health care, you have to be really smart about the business of health care. Challenge yourself, your peers and our industry by shaping what health care looks like and doing… https://t.co/XILW6n2SIs https://t.co/5jizLx1kf0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manager – Salesforce Business Process / Systems Analyst – Multiple Locations: Reviews assigned business processes from end-to-end to identify and address operational, financial and technological risks.  Identifies opportunities to improve efficiency or… https://t.co/iIZQevzrRb https://t.co/MjXcAQA7k8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gadget Lab Podcast: The (Near) Future of PCs: Laptops are getting mobile processors and behaving more like phones. How will that change the way we use them? https://t.co/Q1fiQgt5yN https://t.co/sNY3DXzsXH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Software Developer Computer Scientist: Description: Leidos is actively hiring for a .NET Software Developer Computer Scientist to join our team in Alexandria, VA. JOB SUMMARY   The Operational Mission Support within Leidos, Inc. has a job opening in… https://t.co/BaJ0IbIDB4 https://t.co/Xs5rfxZS8W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Administration: Join our Winning Team as a Summer Intern in our Network Administration Group Are you a rising Junior or Senior who is pursuing a degree in Computer Networking? Does the idea of joining a team responsible for innovation and… https://t.co/CT1MKS25my]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consumer Experience Owner – Eden Prairie, MN / Irvine, CA: No industry is moving faster than health care. And no organization is better positioned to lead health care forward. We need attention to every detail with an eye for the points no one has… https://t.co/LB4yYRvU8F https://t.co/XyVojVThmf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computerized Numerical Control Programmer: POSITION SUMMARY The Computerized Numerical Control Programmer is responsible for monitoring and improving machine processes, tooling set-ups and hands on fixture installation, so that the quality of the parts… https://t.co/dNl2MltZ5c https://t.co/FBhXBpsohR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer Co-op: Leonardo DRS Leonardo DRS is a leading supplier of integrated products, services and support to military forces, intelligence agencies and prime contractors worldwide. Focused on defense technology, we develop, manufacture and… https://t.co/lzycAs8PRG https://t.co/EWQEAOXFPM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Development Director – Blockchain: New York City, NY Full-time $100k – $150k Posted Today Experienced Blockchain Professional Needed ASAP. If you have at least 3 years of Business Develop leadership and more than 2 years of blockchain… https://t.co/Gpwqe0DUO6 https://t.co/X5GF09xBrS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Quality: Looking for a company that inspires passion, courage and imagination, where you can be part of the team shaping the future of global commerce? Want to shape how millions of people buy, sell, connect, and share around the… https://t.co/RLCJUVysmX https://t.co/WYJPAq9NUP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Information Systems Security Analyst 4:   Job Description – Cyber Information Systems Security Analyst 4 (18005526) Cyber Information Systems Security Analyst 4 Requisition ID : 18005526 Location : United States-California-Manhattan Beach US… https://t.co/XguOjWh8gU https://t.co/zFaf4NXvOP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Network Analyst – Cisco Telephony: Careers that Change Lives Function as a leading member of the Unified Communications Operations team and follow all established processes to deliver, document and support any assigned IP Telephony and VM (voice… https://t.co/bz5ZnT26l5 https://t.co/yL7uhUhf7A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[# Sr. IT Product Manager | Atlanta, GA | 7+ months: Title: Sr. Product Manager Location: Atlanta, GA Duration: 7+ months Years of experience: 10+ years Requirements Must have 5+ years of experience as Product Manager Certifications will be a great plus… https://t.co/qGrwWZLjlu https://t.co/RGWJypoODx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Engineer Senior Technical Specialist: Search for Jobs -Systems Engineer Senior Technical Specialist Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the… https://t.co/OanT14xHVz https://t.co/AwTelos7eg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Stop Eye Strain: Tips, Tricks, and Apps: The aching eyes, sore muscles, and headaches caused by eye strain can be prevented by following these tips. https://t.co/NyKiWifEMg https://t.co/6Ye9cmcCwL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Product Manager: Siemens PLM Software Inc. has an opening in Aliso Viejo, CA for Technical Product Manager Principal to define the product direction, roadmap, budget, unique value proposition, comparative competitive advantages, &amp; investment… https://t.co/mjQl6qWjep https://t.co/c4wi0NKyWN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Desktop Support Technician: Grand Lake Mental Health Center, Inc. Claremore, OK Desktop Support Tech We are currently seeking a Desktop Support Technician with at least three (3) years of experience in computer repair and maintenance. Some basic… https://t.co/5PgjPcmhLv https://t.co/uAhFsTYTaJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Delivery Specialist, Technology, Application Management Services #XGGS18FC0318RIC3: Project Delivery Specialist, Technology, Application Management Services Deloitte Consulting LLP seeks a Project Delivery Specialist, Technology, Application… https://t.co/Oc6YCy71Z3 https://t.co/Y8IyvF8DTi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer: Populus Group seeks a Developer in Irvine, CA. Must have a Master’s degree or equiv plus post-baccalaureate exp. recblid jmn15kr5udqc8psl56y5r2phlgpvye https://t.co/KxZvszyosh https://t.co/167zdQegCV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer:   TECHNOLOGY Help build the next generation of systems behind Facebook’s products. Facebook, Inc. currently has multiple openings in Fort Worth, TX (various levels/types): Data Center Technician (133532N) Assist with all Data Center… https://t.co/kXNnGWKdun https://t.co/6RmwWI86Vy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Project Manager: Technical Project Manager With Masters Degree or foreign equivalent in IT, Computer Science, or Computer Engineering, and 1 year experience in job offered. (or) Bachelor’s Degree or foreign equivalent in IT, Computer Science,… https://t.co/75HAhfXMqu https://t.co/sOiH7F3vZ8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Software Developer The Office of the Revisor of Statutes, a nonpartisan office in the Minnesota Legislature, is seeking applicants for a Systems Analyst/Programmer I position. The office has implemented an XML-based, bill drafting,… https://t.co/rFVylw0OGF https://t.co/WB2fl4blwE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Applications Developer Manager: Applications Developer Manager Columbus, OH. Estimate project requirements; forecast resources &amp; project delivery commitments. Equal Opportunity Employer/Affirmative Action Minority/Female/Disability/Veteran JPMorgan Chase… https://t.co/VSw1hRd079 https://t.co/OXoYRHQfT0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JAVA APPLICATION DEVELOPER: KRONSYS is hiring for 2 positions (travel req): Java Application Developer – MS CS, EE or closely rel. XML, Oracle, Java; Business Data Analyst – MS Comp App, Info Sys, MBA or closely rel. + 2 yrs exp. or BS + 5 yrs exp. or… https://t.co/zkWjH8MgQn https://t.co/y5CnHLcGHU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineers: Careers At Raytheon One Global Team Creating Trusted, Innovative Solutions to make the world a safer place. Use your engineering skills to make the world a safer place with a career at Raytheon. We partner with our global customers to provide… https://t.co/6L4RGROwCB https://t.co/Lm5NYxLIoa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Technical Program Manager: A2Z Development Center, Inc. seeks candidates for the following positions: Technical Program Manager II, Job Code AZ0082: Provide sophisticated technical program management for the build-out of massively scalable,… https://t.co/TgRMRJ4sTc https://t.co/CM2Id9k44d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer: Development Expert for SAP Labs, LLC (Palo Alto, CA) resp for dvlpmnt focus on dsgn, codng, tstng, &amp; qlty assur of cmplx prod features in dvlpmnt team. Bach in Comp Sci, Eng, Math, or rltd field &amp; 7 yrs exp req’d, or alt Master’s &amp; 5 yrs of… https://t.co/Ht8lKixKBX https://t.co/nsEIyJNLKN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook's New Data-Sharing Policies Are Crashing Tinder: Users can't log into the dating app after Facebook adjusted its app integration policies. https://t.co/AGKVVCwtyR https://t.co/zHld223aOB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Equity Financial Analyst: Equity Financial Analyst (Vice President) sought by investment mgmt firm (Palo Alto, CA). Provide fin anlss in spprt of investment decisions; Work closely w/ Partners/Principals on strat &amp; negotiation; Engage in biz… https://t.co/tTDeJR8B5f https://t.co/62n9t5EvlK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Design Engineer: Design Engineer Application Software sought by RGB Systems DBA Extron Electronics in Anaheim, CA. Work on team of highly skilled software engineers to build cutting-edge software applications focused on the AV industry. recblid… https://t.co/zR8uQyfBIe https://t.co/UjSSXcbX78]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Support Analyst: Are you seeking a new career opportunity in a fast paced and challenging work environment where you have the ability to use your IT knowledge to help people and forge a great career?  If you have experience in technology and a take… https://t.co/n9qr9TC6ih]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RN Support Team MedSurg III: Overview At WellStar we all share common goals. That’s what makes us so successful – and such an integral part of our communities. We want the same things, for our organization, for our patients, and for our colleagues. As… https://t.co/gNbHcPpJT7 https://t.co/zHTeR4TAZy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Center for Civil-Military Relations (CCMR) Project Manager 15924: Center for Civil-Military Relations (CCMR) Project Manager Job Duties: * Preparing and tracking budget projections and execution analysis. * Track budgeted, forecasted and actual budget… https://t.co/2ia5gn5yHu https://t.co/PbuHva2B0d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Development Analyst/Programmer: The candidate must be local and available to start right away. Application Development Analyst/Programmer BXB-*******-485 6 Months+ Please No Third-Party Calls; this position is open for corp to corp, but… https://t.co/yGDzopdO3X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer – Data Mining: This job listing is for a senior computer scientist supporting the clients research mission at their Springfield, VA office location. The ideal candidate will have a broad range of experience across multiple… https://t.co/bdCE3Ul1Yy https://t.co/V0wWOPjp5Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WMS Super User (Implementation Specialist): 1st Shift Logistics done differently. At XPO Logistics, we know that data drives business. As the WMS Super User, you will serve as the liaison between Operations and IT maintaining the relationship and… https://t.co/Y1j9cmOb14 https://t.co/nEldW2aLrI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dell Boomi Developer: Dell Boomi Developer Requirements: ? Identify, analyze and develop interfaces and integration flows using Dell Boomi platform including Connectors, Design Center and API management ? Explain complex technical issues to project… https://t.co/vQ1eN4wZYa https://t.co/XrFibqXEJ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: InfosysDX Technology Lead- US Skills (UI): HTML5, CSS3, MVC frameworks, Angular JS, Node JS. Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to create and execute… https://t.co/r9OVoqRxmW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Systems Business Analyst: Job Description: The Information Systems Business Analyst plays a critical role in providing administration, operational, and project management support for the Business Systems at company. Computer Systems used in… https://t.co/aUihD6cpuB https://t.co/KpiUdCOOu4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Build a PC: Building your own computer yourself is a lost art—one due for a revival. https://t.co/s8ljdbsJXR https://t.co/hk0JPHROF7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Staff Engineer: Senior Staff Engineer (job location is Seattle, WA) Design &amp; write code for video services designed to enhance HBO’s video streaming capability &amp; content associated w/ company’s interactive endeavors. Perform site architecture &amp;… https://t.co/NYsPdPqiDW https://t.co/hb2iNaEJnN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Security Specialist: Network Security Specialist Minnkota Power Cooperative is seeking qualified candidates for the position of Network Security Specialist located at our Milton R. Young Station located near Center, ND. Responsible for the… https://t.co/JRPeImwhbt https://t.co/eTG6IMVVnP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Analyst: Sr Analyst, Asset Mgmt – Perform complex financial investment analyses for Asset Mgmt Business, incl analysis of equities, fixed income securities, private investments &amp; other instruments using advanced mathematical, statistical &amp; financial… https://t.co/uVNiiQmcbz https://t.co/VvC2RwB6ts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Product Development Engineer #KP1-N: Senior Product Development Engineer at Verizon in Irving, Texas. Responsible for the design, development, and unit testing of Middleware and User Interface (UI) components for set-top boxes and consumer… https://t.co/NeswdxAWl6 https://t.co/QhSJeS0bx3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Master Software Engineer #R44354: Master Software Engineer – Capital One Services, LLC in Richmond, VA; Multiple positions available: Lead overall technical design, development, modification, &amp; implementation of comp apps using existing &amp; emerging… https://t.co/SLFf3q6TXm https://t.co/ysyAGwekvu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3D Character Artist: Software development company seeking 3D Character Artist to translate concepts design into next-gen models of characters &amp; creatures. Requires: 4 years experience in job offered, or as a Character Artist, or related experience… https://t.co/BsbyDGqHyJ https://t.co/1O0KMgM8XA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Product Manager: Siemens PLM Software Inc. has an opening in Aliso Viejo, CA for Technical Product Manager Principal to define the product direction, roadmap, budget, unique value proposition, comparative competitive advantages, &amp; investment… https://t.co/JJb5RXKyfQ https://t.co/39cmXjTG2E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer Software II: Engineer Software II for Tridium Inc. (Honeywell co) (Richmond, VA) responsible for development &amp; testing software as part of Agile team for Tridium’s Niagara Framework. Requires Master’s in Electrical Engineering, Computer… https://t.co/l4ZmEPDNyr https://t.co/rGkoDilEd1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer: Development Expert for SAP Labs, LLC (Palo Alto, CA) resp for dvlpmnt focus on dsgn, codng, tstng, &amp; qlty assur of cmplx prod features in dvlpmnt team. Bach in Comp Sci, Eng, Math, or rltd field &amp; 7 yrs exp req’d, or alt Master’s &amp; 5 yrs of… https://t.co/iZkam0uNLF https://t.co/VlToCrebDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer #180032367: Software Engineer Columbus, OH. Interface w/ business &amp; IT resources to understand &amp; analyze business, functional, &amp; technical requirements. EOE, AAE, M/F/D/V. JPMorgan Chase &amp; Co. All rights reserved.… https://t.co/BB0wUlqNnT https://t.co/23mzmrEDX0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate, Software Engineering: Job #: 180028050 Associate, Software Engineering Columbus, OH. Provide high quality tech. solutions that address business needs by developing applications within mature technology environments. Duties: Provide high… https://t.co/YIiIHDAqHf https://t.co/HKTP57Cdaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Intelligence Engineer: A2Z Development Center, Inc. and https://t.co/SM3mBnaqOt Services, Inc. seeks candidates for the following position (multiple positions available for each title): Business Intelligence Engineer, Job Code AZ0136: support… https://t.co/YAzuidNQNb https://t.co/gaMI3N4AiE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How to Fold a World-Record-Setting Paper Airplane: John Collins shows you how to fold the innovative paper airplane design that earned him a spot in the Guinness Book of World Records. https://t.co/vYnQCLTNCX https://t.co/fpykmOU1Ta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist: You will develop data structures to support the generation of business insights and strategy; organize and analyze large, diverse and imperfect data sets; translate data findings into actionable recommendations and improvements;… https://t.co/P76GJwyZ3L https://t.co/ByH40RVFEw]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>