<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .NET Java Software Engineer: Prestigious Enterprise Company is currently seeking a Senior .NET and Java Software Engineer. Candidate will be designing and developing enterprise software applications on .NET, Java, J2EE, Powershell, and JavaScript… https://t.co/n2tnERs7p8 https://t.co/S8exu4xCLN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: MetroStar Systems Careers ========================= .Net Developer Web Development Washington, District Of Columbia Apply MetroStar Systems is looking for a results oriented Senior .Net Developer that is passionate about designing and… https://t.co/50myTeoGKJ https://t.co/2QRRIsKoeo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Analyst-.Net,IIS: System ************,IIS Ref No.: 18-20635 Location: Mt Laurel, New Jersey 5+ years of experience working in .Net Framework which includes IIS Good Hands on working with windows &amp; Sql server Should have very strong communication… https://t.co/TpmczMNBuM https://t.co/yvzlWhhomb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer/Developer (Full stack: React, C# https://t.co/BKeTHRUc7v): Sr. Software Engineer/Developer (Full stack: React, C# &amp; *******) Technology &amp; Analytics San Francisco, California Apply Your Mission: The Senior Applications Engineer is… https://t.co/WaTri4Tlob https://t.co/UVqBqcUJo4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack .NET Mobile Developer: Search and apply for jobs at Piper Companies | Careers at Piper Companies Careers Search Jobs Connect With Us Full Stack .NET Mobile Developer Job Attributes Job Id: 18157Job Category: IT InfrastructureJob Location: Bala… https://t.co/MDMnYyJYXb https://t.co/JNBUJ6BPXO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.net Ui Developer With Wpf: .NET UI Developer with WPF Newport beach, California – United States Posted Date – 04/19/18 Primary Skills WPF,c#,MVVM Overview Role : .NET UI Developer with WPF Location: New Port Beach, CA Duration: 12 Months– extension is… https://t.co/pRCysP0ZgQ https://t.co/d0rW6HgNan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior C#.NET Developer: Great opportunity for strong C#.NET developers from intermediate level all the way up to lead level to join a fortune 500 company located in the Cleveland area. 6 month and 12 month contract-to-hire/permanent positions available.… https://t.co/uMZew28Fs1 https://t.co/OzZivuVtrh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .NET Applications Developer: Senior .NET Applications Developer Job Locations US-DC-Washington Job ID 10309 Minimum Clearance Required US Citizen Responsibilities Functional Responsibilities:  ISYS Technologies is hiring a Senior .NET Applications… https://t.co/8RwC24g51Z https://t.co/snbuOlylOK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Job Title Senior Software Engineer (.NET): Job Location US-DC Job ID 9301 Job Location United States Category Information Technology/Software Overview Be part of something innovative and cutting edge. Join our team of more than a hundred software… https://t.co/MdWp1zMnnH https://t.co/uZwlVVTvkP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .NET Developer: SENIOR .NET DEVELOPER Extremely successful software company is seeking a Senior Full Stack .NET Developer to help them scale and add complex functionality to a customer-facing data-heavy software product deployed in Azure. You will… https://t.co/ELA9QwYVWU https://t.co/5XfbIXHAkk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staff Front End Developer Digital Innovation – JavaScript, Angular JS, .Net, HTML,: Staff Front End Developer Digital Innovation Job in JavaScript, Angular JS, .Net, HTML, at Schwab Charles Schwab Corporation – WHO WE ARE – WHAT WE DO – LEADERSHIP –… https://t.co/hZxO14CIJK https://t.co/6QBNC1CJ9o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator: Req ID : 415007BR Job Code/Title : E6462:Systems Engineer-IT Job Description : The Advanced Concepts Lab (ACL) at Lockheed Martin's Advanced Technology Laboratories (ATL) is seeking an IT Systems Engineer/Systems Administrator with… https://t.co/4EWPC34GQn https://t.co/LVjDCCwSVI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer – .NET: Sr. Software Engineer – .NET Sr. Software Engineer – .NET Company Nexsys Technologies LLC Location US-MI-Detroit Opportunity Details Who We Are Nexsys Technologies is a financial technology company founded by mortgage IT… https://t.co/agtHTSSnYB https://t.co/FW2lUApH9y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer: .NET Developer RESPONSIBILITIES -Lead the development of new software and subsystems -Architect, develop and implement new applications -Use coding and security best practices for medical records -Collaborate with cross functional teams… https://t.co/wtBzSiNK8S https://t.co/KQas4y5iFX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java/.NET Software Developer: PLEASE ONLY APPLY IF YOU DO NOT NEED SPONSORSHIP TO WORK IN THE UNITED STATES. WE ARE UNABLE TO CONSIDER CANDIDATES WHO REQUIRE SPONSORSHIP. Java/.NET Software Developer Roswell, Ga. About the General Motors Development… https://t.co/saywkytocD https://t.co/kHrqSUtnaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Software Development Engineer (.NET): Pushpay is a hyper-growth SaaS startup founded in New Zealand, and based in Redmond, WA. Our products enable people to participate in giving generously to their community, increasing goodwill and helping people… https://t.co/CMunrKGr11 https://t.co/0hwTm8XMNs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET/SQL specialist: Ekleft is an international IT outsourcing company which has provided high-quality services to blue chip Companies since 2008. Ekleft specializes in the establishment of IT DDC from the scratch in across the Globe. The company has… https://t.co/2C3Nd3aZvX https://t.co/DN1ZtIUINH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lamborghinis, long lines welcome crypto fans at 'Blockchain Week': NEW YORK (Reuters) - A Lamborghini costs about 23 bitcoins, which might not seem like much, unless you owned the cryptocurrency in December, in which case you could have bought one of the… https://t.co/0IL3tcLXBT https://t.co/EYhbDuGmI7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer: Seattle, WA Compensation Unspecified Posted Today If you are a Full Stack Developer with experience, please read on! We are a US block-chain trading platform aimed to advance the industry by creating innovation as well as producing… https://t.co/KcVMG3XKvl https://t.co/Qgqaa439tf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .Net Technical Engineer: Description: Chicago – IL, IL150SW, 150 S Wacker Dr, 60606-4111 Laura Troy 20170705-3439 We believe that, when done right, investing liberates people to create their own destiny. We are driven by our purpose to champion… https://t.co/OSVhWd2MAo https://t.co/6N03EX1xRX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum master: Scrum master new orleans, Louisiana – United States Job Start Date – 05/09/18, Posted Date – 05/09/18 Primary SkillsNATax TermsC2COverview Looking for Scrum Master in new Orleans * Job CodeSG – 13348 * Pay Rate/SalaryUSD – 60/ * Experience8… https://t.co/Ialq3eboQ0 https://t.co/IkUXQAyL9t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Engineer (Angular&amp; C#/.NET) 420 Friendly: Seattle, WA Full-time $100k – $120k Posted Today *** DISCLAIMER!!! You must be comfortable working for a company that is in the Cannabis Industry*** If you are a Sr. Full Stack Engineer with experience… https://t.co/b91gVfuJDW https://t.co/Sl0W371ECU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer with CRM Dynamics: .Net Developer with CRM Dynamics HarrySiri Info Solutions IncEdison NJ 08817Ph: ************Email: ******************?VISA STATUS H1B, GC-EAD, GC , USC ONLY?Role: .Net Developer with CRM DynamicsLocation: Ames,… https://t.co/s7hHZYO8mn https://t.co/fwGC7r7KB0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET C# Developer (Entry Level): IGT is the global leader in gaming. We enable players to experience their favorite games across all channels and regulated segments, from Gaming Machines to Lotteries to Interactive. We have a well-established local… https://t.co/4bJSu3qqWU https://t.co/HASXlqA75G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (.NET/Mobile Native): Description: We currently have multiple openings for developers with a background in Microsoft .NET, C# and native mobile applications. Ideal candidates will have a thirst for learning new technologies to support… https://t.co/MLcUQL9Y37 https://t.co/ctL2KEh8J5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer: Garmin Intl. seeks Sr. Software Engineer in Olathe, KS to research fundamental problems and implements algorithm solutions that are appropriate for Garmin products. Decompose functional requirements into well-defined tasks while… https://t.co/LMssO5f1dJ https://t.co/wJWE11shzp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Consultant .NET Full Stack: Headspring is a software engineering and development consultancy that believes theres a better way – to build software, to work with clients, and to do business. And we know finding the better way starts with who you… https://t.co/G0enPTQfAR https://t.co/N5eckwDumf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Engineering Asc Mgr: Req ID : 427966BR Job Code/Title : L1954:Project Engineering Asc Mgr Job Description : At Lockheed Martin Rotary and Mission Systems, we are driven by innovation and integrity. We believe that by applying the highest… https://t.co/clQHIPc7aQ https://t.co/o5esnRxHGH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Entry Level Programmer Analyst: Entry Level Programmer Analyst Jobs in St Louis at Boeing Skip Navigation SearchMenu – News – Investors – Employee/Retiree – Merchandise – Suppliers – Features &amp; Multimedia – Commercial – Defense – Space – Services –… https://t.co/zznPXkWUu9 https://t.co/O9MpvPn5cg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C# / .NET Developer: Direct/permanent position open with a growing private-sector company in Rockville for a C# / .NET Developer. The Developer with work with large datasets and will drive innovation and improvement for the software platform. Primary… https://t.co/BWUI0KedQx https://t.co/SSBRcWodYY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Identity Software Engineer: *This is a 3 month contract to hire, with no 3rd part candidates being considered at this time* Prestigious Fortune 500 Company is currently seeking a Microsoft Developer with systems support skills. Candidate will… https://t.co/5OvKAYyZPR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Developer – .Net: Job Title: Senior Developer – .Net Requisition Number: 23442 Position Type: Full Time City: Brentwood Campus: Corporate OH State/Province: Tennessee Job Description: The Senior Developer – .NET is responsible for the overall… https://t.co/aoE244DSJu https://t.co/RXd8oqlp0x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .Net Developer with Azure: – Azure BI Tools – SQL Server – ******** C# experience – 5+ years .NET Development experience – 2+ years of work experience with Azure Job Type: Contract 3 hours ago – save job Please review all application instructions… https://t.co/TmCQ3ECrRd https://t.co/Ro7qaf0Gbp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .Net C# Developer with Angular JS: Hi, I hope you are doing fine. Fast moving position! Candidates must be a U.S. citizenship and bachelor’s degree requirement. Candidates must work on our W2/1099 Candidates must be local to Washington DC., or… https://t.co/BLNpgGDxk5 https://t.co/mZ6XewwhTW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C#/.Net Web Developer: EPX (Electronic Payment Exchange), a subsidiary of North American Bancard, LLC, is looking for a talented C# .Net Web Developer to join the team in Tempe, AZ. As the front-end web developer, you will develop and maintain simple and… https://t.co/m65YnllxIP https://t.co/fErsBwrUMp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .Net Developer: Irvine Technology Corporation (ITC) is leading provider of technology and staffing solutions for IT, Security, Engineering, and Interactive Design disciplines servicing startups to enterprise clients, nationally. We pride ourselves… https://t.co/1ZfGULuubc https://t.co/vN6gofjQDv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: We are looking for a .Net Developer for a leading financial client in New York. The role calls for a charismatic individual who loves challenges and enjoys working with global technology teams. Responsibilities * Develop desktop and web… https://t.co/WHLyjf7e9m https://t.co/LxtSz89pOg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Level 1 Service Desk Support Specialist: THE REASON YOU WAKE UP The Level 1 Service Desk Support Specialist will provide outstanding end user support and service for internal, external, and on-site customers. Work directly with customers to understand… https://t.co/5o4NyvX67z https://t.co/O5jawFODE6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Software Developer: .Net Software Developer Chicago, IL $95-115K Prestigious Company is seeking a .NET Software Developer. You are going to be responsible for developing and maintaining our production platform. You do best with tight deadlines,… https://t.co/QrUQWIBCKf https://t.co/C51Zzhwien]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior React Engineer: Marina Del Rey, CA Full-time $130k – $175k Posted Today Are you a Senior Engineer with JavaScript &amp; React experience? If so, read on… We are a team of serial social entrepreneurs &amp; technologists. We are the first socially… https://t.co/r8mqNzcRRq https://t.co/OOiprVduaR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .NET Engineer: Higher Logic is seeking a Senior .NET engineer to help us improve upon our ever-evolving suite of software products. We are looking for someone who has extensive experience working with the .NET stack and is well versed in popular… https://t.co/5tUvLNmxxZ https://t.co/iPFrDtXBQz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Developer (.NET): The senior level developer is responsible for working as part of a collaborative development team to create working software applications based on our customers requirements using .NET and related technologies, and leading other… https://t.co/gsbAltoCTl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior C# / .Net Developer: Our client, a Hedge Fund based in Midtown is looking for a hands on IT Development Lead to support the firm in leading a number of initiatives. You will develop and own enterprise level applications for Operations in… https://t.co/27nVhenzyL https://t.co/xA1Vukvb7i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer: .NET Developer Ref No.:18-02316 Location: Franklin Lakes, New Jersey Position Type:Right to Hire This opportunity is with a multibillion $ Global giant based in United States, Canada &amp; Mexico, with 16 different delivery centers and… https://t.co/dvPY6THuI4 https://t.co/3NypwAoSEG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer Engineer: Description: JOB DESCRIPTION: The Maritime Systems Division (MSD) of Leidos’ Advanced Solutions Group (ASG) develops and deploys advanced technology solutions that address existing and emerging maritime missions of national importance… https://t.co/Am1zd1gh6u https://t.co/PoCMmkZ0i1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Web Developer: .NET/C#/MVC/Azure: SENIOR WEB DEVELOPER .NET/C#/MVC: DEERFIELD TO $110,000 Our Deerfield based client is seeking a Full time Senior Web Developer for their Web Development team. PRIMARY RESPONSIBILITIES INCLUDE: -Develop easy to use… https://t.co/TZYwP1e2Lu https://t.co/P7Sgk5aP17]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer in Test: Overview Experienced in Java/programming? Enjoy poking holes? We’re looking for a fast-learner with strong technical skills and an Agile background to join our team as a Senior Automation Test Engineer, where you’ll… https://t.co/FVjM5bJlj7 https://t.co/znrkTuBOQh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack .NET Developer: Full Stack .NET Developer Tracking Code 13344-935 Job Description POSITION PURPOSE: Develop functional enhancements and provide operational support for the UNFI Customer Portal, UNFI Intranet, and other UNFI web properties and… https://t.co/C03fnpnNTW https://t.co/upIZDFslIf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .NET Developer: Join our team of Development Consultants and work on dynamic long-term projects. The majority of our team members are long-term employees who enjoy consistent work and a collaborative team approach! * Full-Stack development in… https://t.co/EvMI6roRHL https://t.co/AZXplu3TkZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Application Engineer:   Job Description – .NET Application Engineer (1801459) Job Description  .NET Application Engineer – (1801459) Remote: No Primary Location : US-CA-Long Beach-MEEKER Job : Information Technology Service Organization : Corporate… https://t.co/sC8BNR5aYe https://t.co/aEn9ALxeXa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java/.NET Dev: Sr. Java/.NET Developer Responsibilities * Troubleshooting software application issues. Issues to be resolved require a broad range of troubleshooting skills related to: software functionality, Application Server setup, database… https://t.co/VSzcnxjPjI https://t.co/KRv8PeC38d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C++/C#/.NET Developer: 10 YEARS EXPERIENCE + STRONG C#.NET, C++, SSIS AND TSQL SKILLS. + EXPERIENCE WITH WCF SERVICES ANDOBJECT ORIENTED ANALYSIS/DESIGN. https://t.co/8PMuAFomxx https://t.co/dzZ0fUBC6c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C#/ASP.NET Angular JS Developer: Job Board Powered by Bullhorn Apr 19, 2018 JobsYour ProfileLogin Job #11875: Developer: .NET Job Code: #11875 Title: C#/******* Angular JS Developer Job Type: Direct Hire Job Location: South Jordan Utah Job Description:… https://t.co/P7TsPn0r6a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Program &amp; Portfolio Management Manager – Consumer Markets: PwC/LOS Overview PwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities.… https://t.co/8qU7bo3e8V https://t.co/thMeW6VhSD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead/ Senior .NET Developer: Project Description Current business process in automated in Customer’s system where users have access to a dedicated "investment call" functionality and able to view assets and discussion items that are associated with the… https://t.co/8Sm2ksNb4K https://t.co/bIm2EJHPLu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[P&amp;O – Workday HCM Senior Associate: PwC/LOS Overview PwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about us at… https://t.co/lBXJX4CGkr https://t.co/5X2FoiNpZA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Software Developer: Our client is looking for experienced ************* developers eager to work on unique projects in the industrial sector. As a .NET developer, you will help design and develop software systems to meet our clients specific… https://t.co/gvcZKXIDtV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infrastructure Solution Architect: Infrastructure Solution Architect  VDOT87558914 *Fairfax, VA*   North VA Client desires systems administration duties to be performed for the TOC.  The majority of these duties shall be conducted on-site.  Work space… https://t.co/eK7Ws300xH https://t.co/0DZJYqoyXX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer- C# .Net: Agilent inspires and supports discoveries that advance the quality of life. We provide life science, diagnostic and applied market laboratories worldwide with instruments, services, consumables, applications and expertise.… https://t.co/XpsXrON9vh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SMC/SY Space/Ground Systems Engineer Job: SMC/SY Space/Ground Systems Engineer (Job Number:426392) Description: SAIC is seeking a Space Ground Systems Engineer to provide systems engineering, acquisition strategy, and technical support to the Air Force… https://t.co/3OZO5btpDu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net developer: .Net developer Ref No.:18-07635 Location: Florida, Massachusetts Position Type:Contract Start Date: 04/25/2018 Strong knowledge of .NET web framework Proficient in {{C# and/or ******}}, with a good knowledge of their ecosystemsStrong… https://t.co/YWs1Y6vIh3 https://t.co/Qg95YJ4DMV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Zqguck7KPp Developer: If youre an expert in ******, C#/.NET, SQL Server our client located in Northern Durham County, will be interested in speaking with you! Our client is looking to bring on a ****** Developer. This engineer will be highly… https://t.co/ErJGy8v9KH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Full Stack Web Engineer (.NET Core) – Boston: ABOUT US TribalScale is an innovation firm that brings organizations – from the startup to the enterprise – into the future. We build digital products, transform teams, and grow startups. Were… https://t.co/NrKFnE8VgJ https://t.co/Ud9RqAWgDh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer (ColdFusion and .NET): POSITION TITLE: SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER LOCATION: ALEXANDRIA, VA CLEARANCE: ACTIVE SECRET CLEARANCE Swingtech Consulting is currently supporting K-12 education for the military families within &amp; outside… https://t.co/eUnlGUD1Gz https://t.co/PchSmDe9kY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Title Senior https://t.co/eqMhHxVxYr Web Application Development Lead: Requisition ID ******* Job Family US-MN-Bloomington Posting Description Aon is looking for a Senior ********* Web Application Development Lead As part of an industry-leading team, you… https://t.co/OcP2claKFj https://t.co/hTgPnlgI6U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .Net Developer: Client: Pacific Gas &amp; Electric Role: Senior .Net developer Location: San Ramon, CA Rate: Depends on Experience Interview: Telephonic followed by inperson We are looking for a Front end .NET Lead with Angular JS and React… https://t.co/sSxUZ77GY3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET / C# Sr. Developer: Software Engineer Web Applications Location: Hollywood, CA 90038 Duration: 6 – 12 month contract Seeking a Sr. Web Application Engineer to work on-site with a major Entertainment company … supporting their Digital Operations… https://t.co/K4KmqTzMAu https://t.co/AWAvwWpZO4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Senior Software Engineer @ https://t.co/M0DC953g1Q, Inc. (Mission, KS) – Dsgn, dvlp, test, implmnt &amp; maintain core integ softw tech &amp; sys integs. Reqts: Master’s deg (or foreign equiv) in CS, Engg (any), IT, IS or rel + 1 yr exp… https://t.co/AtDs8oCeWl https://t.co/SwYVwIAJ94]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SEO Analyst: SEO Analyst Location: Charleston, South Carolina, United States Full-time SUMMARY Levelwing is seeking highly motivated individuals to analyze, produce, and measure performance of website content as well as optimize websites through… https://t.co/NNndO5pPGb https://t.co/Xb2PdfS8iO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP FICO – Manager (Finance): Are you looking for a career trajectory that few other organizations can offer in SAP? What about access to a high-quality portfolio of businesses and clients with opportunities to work across capabilities, industries, and… https://t.co/UZcP1BPZUl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer – Automation: Senior Software Engineer – Automation Job at Thales Group in San Jose | Careers at Thales Group Skip Navigation – Discover Thales – Professions – Working With Us – How To – Meet our people – EN – english – french –… https://t.co/80rkGNqiDB https://t.co/nEGnHuu8ZG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Job Title Senior .Net Software Engineer: Job Location US-DC Job ID 10291 Job Location United States Overview Be part of something innovative and cutting edge. Join our team of more than a hundred software engineers, designers, project managers and… https://t.co/xAJMVear3f https://t.co/qqIq5QS0e0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior User Experience Designer: THE STORY OF GUST Every year, thousands of entrepreneurs are driven to start companies fueled by bright ideas they dream will take flight. Trouble is, starting-up a successful high growth company is hard work and… https://t.co/SMEM0vdAEi https://t.co/5GoOuOcOwE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Full Stack Web Developer: THE COMPANY: deltatre (**************** [*********************************************************** Part of the Bruin Sports Capital group, deltatre is a global leader in digital streaming and digital solutions for the… https://t.co/ifE3ZnAksE https://t.co/4A6VlKGPVg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Security Engineer 5 – Security Code Review Team: Job Description ENTERPRISE INFORMATION SECURITY: Since 1852, customers have trusted that Wells Fargo would keep their assets secure from theft and always available. Today, maintaining customer… https://t.co/5f7Keq90Mi https://t.co/HiIMbAqI62]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/RfYkBmWfBk Developer: Careers @WilmerTech WilmerTech provides a complete and effective employee orientation program involving induction, domain-related training sessions, cross-cultural training, and personality development for new recruits.… https://t.co/FFLlgzFEgb https://t.co/dcWXLhcKDv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Software Engineer, Mid: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Herndon, VA Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 5/31/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management and… https://t.co/CgStyBstti https://t.co/Bnet1VpIZW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Irvine, CA Job Type: Information Technology Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 5/18/2018 Job Description Primary Purpose: Development and maintenance of software applications built using Microsoft… https://t.co/lf6dhKKsHC https://t.co/pNbKQ83Hck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer Ref No.: 18-23772 Location: Irving, Texas Title :.Net Developer Duration : Full Time Location : Irving, TX Interview mode: Telephonic + Video Conference Joining: ASAP Salary: Open+ Benefits + Relocation Expenses . We are… https://t.co/YIXplnmlw6 https://t.co/gaJpPiFs8n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: Oracle CPQ Consultant Ref No.: 18-23008 Location: Carlsbad, California At NTT DATA, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The quality, integrity, and commitment of our employees are key factors in our… https://t.co/WJnjVvG0Oj https://t.co/hlYhJSmSjj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Administrator: Position Summary: Responsible for maintaining reliable operation of all server hardware and software throughout the enterprise. Will have accountability for all technical functions, correct trouble conditions and identify technical… https://t.co/tTguQ5Cu8V https://t.co/HKmNCzdUa2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – .NET: You may not have heard of irth Solutions before, but its likely that your home and safety has been protected with its industry-leading services. Every oil &amp; gas company and utility has distributed facilities and workers. Our… https://t.co/8hCAKee91p https://t.co/3efzIaxPvb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Specialist Developer — https://t.co/BKeTHRUc7v, MVC, C#, SQL Server, SSRS: Specialist Developer ‘ *******, MVC, C#, SQL Server, SSRS ‘ Provides application software development services or technical support in more complex situations. May also be… https://t.co/ZjUIDwOuJ6 https://t.co/XdsxNvrvTX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET/Python Developer (Treasury): Job **************** Developer (Treasury) – ID:31627 Duration6 Months Start DateASAP Job *************, Python, Micro Services, C# , AngularJS , MicrSQL Server , Oracle LocationPlano, TX Date Posted05/02/2018 FOR… https://t.co/eeFXA2p7yE https://t.co/oAKl0UpDyt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Architect: .Net Architect Ref No.: 18-21501 Location: Madison, Wisconsin Role: .Net Architect Location: Madison, WI / Chicago, IL Duration: 12 Months Contract Skills Required Should have strong exp. on .Net technologies with Lead/Architect exp.… https://t.co/gJuyLUoNgj https://t.co/aICNo1rv9g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. SEC official says ether not a security, price surges: NEW YORK (Reuters) - The price of ether rose on Thursday after a senior official at the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission stated that the cryptocurrency was not a security, thus exempting… https://t.co/bMz5jWTiyl https://t.co/0Uo6VadRng]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer: General Dynamics Information Technology (GDIT) has an immediate need for a .NET Developer to analyze, evaluate and develop new and existing web/database applications; working under limited supervision; performing additional duties as… https://t.co/UnehF51GiP https://t.co/bFhwZ8Q7Bk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET C# Developer: IGT is the global leader in gaming. We enable players to experience their favorite games across all channels and regulated segments, from Gaming Machines to Lotteries to Interactive. We have a well-established local presence and… https://t.co/XOcPxOP7mC https://t.co/hyI3Ptw91R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elon Musk's Boring Co to build high-speed commuter system in Chicago: CHICAGO (Reuters) - Chicago has selected billionaire entrepreneur Elon Musk's Boring Co to build a high-speed underground commuter system from the downtown Loop district to O'Hare… https://t.co/aCaevyJYfG https://t.co/c6BFqPVXKF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET DEVELOPER: .NET DEVELOPER Ref No.: 18-21576 Location: HOUSTON, Texas Key Accountabilities: – Analyse, design, develop, maintain, debug, test .Net Web API, Angular 2/Typescript/Javascript/Html5/CSS, Oracle software and enterprise service solutions to… https://t.co/bCaSgCRV8y https://t.co/6tI1gkCeM8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Web Developer: Role: .NET Web Developer Salt Lake City,UT 9 months Contract Summary Client is looking for a strong development candidate to create a publicly accessible bilingual (Spanish and English) School Grade Reporting website/tool. Candidate… https://t.co/d4rk87529t https://t.co/9JxFS5BiCp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Software Engineer, Senior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Herndon, VA Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 5/31/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management… https://t.co/bvGQAEuSqQ https://t.co/LF3yv1l1Nj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Developer (C# / .NET 4.0 / JavaScript / SQL ): Job Openings – – Home – About Trigyn – Company Profile – Corporate Governance – Board of Directors – Executive Team – Partnerships &amp; Alliances – News &amp; Events – Quality Policy – Diversity –… https://t.co/8l0r69ECXn https://t.co/3x5rMStyyu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Web Application Developer: .Net Web Application Developer for ALTA IT Services in MCB Quantico, VA 22134(map) .NET WEB APPLICATION DEVELOPER SALARY RANGE: Senior – 5 years+ exp. $120,000 to $150,000 annually; junior to mid-level 2-5 years exp.… https://t.co/ndlDpial41 https://t.co/jYpslaDdG1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Spiria is a digital solutions development agency with a team of more than 130 professionals focused on the design, development, deployment, and support of large-scale applications. Spiria relies on the excellence of its customer… https://t.co/kuCMNPPKDk https://t.co/XDUrNPzrDZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Full Stack Developer: .Net Full Stack Developer Ref No.: 18-21765 Location: Houston, Texas Position : .Net Full Stack Developer Duration : Full Time Permanent Work Location : Houston, TX Job Description .Net Development background Angular 2 Strong… https://t.co/uKGY3DgMzo https://t.co/uJdQDKJ7DO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack .NET Developer: Full Stack .NET Developer Chandler, Arizona – United States Job Start Date – 05/28/18, Posted Date – 05/23/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview Skills needed: *******, Web API, 2-3 years of experience with MVC5 (MVC4 is… https://t.co/N1cb76MFRz https://t.co/MsoLLTsRYS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Software Developer: .Net Software Developer Chicago, IL $95-115K Prestigious Company is seeking a .NET Software Developer. You are going to be responsible for developing and maintaining our production platform. You do best with tight deadlines,… https://t.co/Qz35kEjYe8 https://t.co/pSvGZMUOmg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GIS Analyst: SNC-Lavalin’s Atkins business unit is one of the world’s most respected design, engineering and project management consultancies. SNC-Lavalin’s Atkins business has been providing infrastructure planning, engineering, construction,… https://t.co/HtEYQsLQIC https://t.co/CctenIRauC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital Hardware Engineer: Analog Devices (NASDAQ: ADI) designs and manufactures semiconductor products and solutions. We enable our customers to interpret the world around us by intelligently bridging the physical and digital worlds with unmatched… https://t.co/NqdQv6Pm1q https://t.co/xLtjTvvB32]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>