<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[#SQL DBA Philadelphia, PA: Position Title: SQL DBA Consultant Location: North East Philly, PA Type: Contract Requirements 5+ years of experience in Database Administration and Developer for very large and complex databases in SQL Server. Expertise in… https://t.co/wlCNCTIwf0 https://t.co/9BACnlpzPT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Impromptu Fox interview caps Trump's wild media week https://t.co/7qoQ2EptRP https://t.co/DLqdz7IAcN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google has a hard time keeping black employees https://t.co/Iada4zzlsL https://t.co/V1OgymoDCv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's long-time 'fixer' is feeling isolated from the President and more open to cooperating with federal investigators, a source says: President Donald Trump's personal attorney Michael Cohen has indicated to family and friends he is willing to… https://t.co/VNp6Bjvhcf https://t.co/uErXwcCSX3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior MySQL DBA: *This role has some 2nd shift duties either 2:00pm to 10:00pm or 3:00pm-11:00pm the first 6 months* Prestigious Financial Institution is currently seeking a MySQL DBA with strong Automation Scripting experience. Candidate will implement… https://t.co/eCy4fpbtCQ https://t.co/bGydTkkLsm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Report Developer (.Net, SQL): Job ID: EMO-******* Description: Located in one of the following locations – Austin, Houston, Richardson or San Antonio, TX this position is responsible utilizing .NET and SQL Server for creating reports, insights… https://t.co/qeZfmxyxZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill Cosby replaces his defense team: Bill Cosby has replaced his entire defense team ahead of his sentencing hearing in September. https://t.co/Cj2yC2rUoz https://t.co/31N9htjAKe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Japan lowers its age of adulthood: The Japanese government enacted a bill Wednesday lowering the age of adulthood from 20 to 18, but teenagers beware: the legal age of drinking will stay fixed at 20. https://t.co/5eUFAwUFMx https://t.co/HnF4WhXv8D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: SQL Developer in Plano, Texas, United States | IT Infrastructure at CognizantJob Details | Cognizant – ************* – Industries – – – Services – – – Latest Thinking – – – About Cognizant – Careers Home – Get To Know Us – Our Core Values… https://t.co/X1m45DjOFB https://t.co/fhIAFYR33s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior SQL Developer – DBA: Date: May 23, 2018 Location: reno, NV, US, 89509 Year: 2018 Company: Arvato Digital Services LLC – Arvato FS USA Requisition ID: 20052 Reporting to the Onshore Technical Project Manager and working closely with the Offshore… https://t.co/QcH086F4SI https://t.co/mZClwhOMgQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A preview of Germany vs. Mexico https://t.co/haoc7EuOf2 https://t.co/qVDwFCGQn5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server Developer (SSIS SSAS: SQL Server Developer (SSIS &amp; SSAS Ref No.: 18-21460 Location: Washington, District of Columbia Position: SQL Server Developer (SSIS &amp; SSAS) Location: Washington DC Duration: 12 MonthsOnly W2 Candidate – Candidate should… https://t.co/C9Sf1rkLev https://t.co/PIOSkiV9El]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OBIEE + PL/sql Developer: OBIEE + PL/sql Developer Ref No.: 18-21912 Location: Pennington, New Jersey Description: 1) The Business Intelligence Report Developer responsible for design, build and deploy business intelligence reports and dashboards 2)… https://t.co/xRvq0na13w https://t.co/uLFAQmvBsx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer (JavaScript, C#, .Net, SQL): .Net Developer (JavaScript, C#, .Net, SQL) Ref No.: 18-21691 Location: Redmond, Washington Role .Net Developer (JavaScript, C#, .Net, SQL) Location: Redmond, WA Duration: FTE Mandatory Technical Skills A… https://t.co/H00Xln7Ct4 https://t.co/MHY5aWRJFI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle PL/SQL Developer: Oracle PL/SQL Developer in North Quincy, Massachusetts, United States | Consulting at CognizantJob Details | Cognizant – ************* – Industries – – – Services – – – Latest Thinking – – – About Cognizant – Careers Home – Get… https://t.co/7F1Yyb0jmz https://t.co/V0QXyvqZzd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Informatica and SQL Server Developer: Informatica and SQL Server Developer: 18-02111 Ref No.:18-02111 Location: Burbank, California Akraya is looking for a Informatica and SQL Developer for one of our clients. If the job description below is a fit,… https://t.co/a6WUKoI2gL https://t.co/Bh37hxkD92]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scaramucci, Avenatti sip rosé with Colbert: Former White House communications director Anthony Scaramucci and Stormy Daniels' attorney Michael Avenatti made their TV debut together on "The Late Show with Steven Colbert" to discuss President Trump. https://t.co/q20eOuSFmM https://t.co/FYEn97Yy9A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server Database Administrator – Federal Client: CRI Advantage is looking for a SQL Server Database Administrator to work as consultants at our federal customer (DOE) in Idaho Falls, Idaho. We are one of the largest IT providers for our customer and… https://t.co/aGWkCc8I9N https://t.co/zrxcao6Qjs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server Database Architect/DBA Lead: Our direct client is looking for a SQL Server Architect/Lead to provide leadership, guidance, and coordination for large DBA support teams, including coordination of complex database design, development,… https://t.co/JKHxck2CCf https://t.co/LEs32ctjwl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch Trump salute North Korean general: North Korea state media aired a 42-minute long video showing behind-the-scenes footage of President Trump and Kim Jong Un's unprecedented trip, including a moment showing Trump saluting a North Korean general. https://t.co/qIi1rxSZjo https://t.co/aztkXagXB4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MS SQL Server BI Developer: MS SQL Server BI Developer in Aberdeen Proving Ground, MD | CACI International – Small Business | – Suppliers – About Us – | – What We Do – | – Media &amp; Events – | – Investors – | – Careers – | – Contracts – | – Contact Us Join… https://t.co/Yra8h241X9 https://t.co/R841UMJB4R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Data Analyst w/ SQL Excel: Job ID: CP-******* Description: As part of our Government and Consumer Solutions Risk Adjustment Operations team, you will support the technical data and reporting needs for risk adjustment initiatives and submissions,… https://t.co/uceeZsW1MS https://t.co/TslFLy4skd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL/SQL Developer: PL/SQL Developer Ref No.: 18-23092 Location: farmington, Connecticut 1.7+ years of hands on experience in developing applications with PL/SQL. https://t.co/0gpurgzswG, code, test, debug, and document complex database programs to ensure… https://t.co/UdfbaTR1Kn https://t.co/KazDOoEtvD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: SQL Developer Job Description Are you passionate about building amazing software? Are you constantly pushing yourself to develop better, faster and more efficient applications? Do you have an innate interest in releasing products that… https://t.co/hwlEFHReg0 https://t.co/HeUHBj9Gzh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Analyst SQL/Agile: Job ID ******* Date posted 03/20/2018 Category Information Technology Organization Centene Corporation Schedule Full-time Description: Position Purpose: Contribute to in the entire implementation process. – Contribute… https://t.co/UqkSUep96B https://t.co/FTvxRpkM1S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Production Support Engineer (Java/MySQL): Who We Are _accesso_ is a world-wide software company delivering industry leading virtual queuing, eCommerce and ticketing solutions for the attractions, cultural and leisure industries. The _accesso Passport_… https://t.co/nQ0g84XEvJ https://t.co/V3d51aCAWG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World's largest plane rolled out: Stratolaunch, which is designed to release rockets that will carry satellites into space, has a 385-foot wingspan, stands 50 feet tall and can carry more than 500,000 pounds of cargo. https://t.co/flilUPWF05 https://t.co/dG5PBuo5e9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Report Writer/Report Developer – SQL/SSRS: Report Writer/Report Developer – SQL/SSRS – FirstPRO 360 Toggle navigation Menu Close – Specialties – Accounting &amp; Finance – Information Technology – Life Sciences – Medical Device Sales – Project Services –… https://t.co/0Cz7h9jDTg https://t.co/QjxmGwETh3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL/SQL Developer: PL/SQL Developer Charlotte, North Carolina – United States Job Start Date – 06/18/18, Posted Date – 05/25/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview Required: Minimum 5 year experience in Oracle Stored procedure development Able to write… https://t.co/Rh8CuKERcr https://t.co/mNrAYzqw3b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sylvester Stallone subject of sex crimes investigation: The Los Angeles District Attorney's office is reviewing a sex crime case against Sylvester Stallone, spokesman Greg Risling said Wednesday. https://t.co/UYTewgf9OB https://t.co/rSOQaWJyw0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Specialist Developer – https://t.co/qZglOKK4dO, C#, SQL Server, SSRS, SSIS: Job Description Specialist Developer – *******, C#, SQL Server, SSRS, SSIS, DB2 – Collaborate with internal business groups to provide innovative software solutions and design… https://t.co/Vm1cj7nACl https://t.co/QBXL8QBs8f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior-SQL-Server-DBA: We are hiring a Senior SQL Server DBA (8+ years of experience) who will be responsible for Database administration, data analysis and database management, maintenance, enhancement, designing of data dictionaries, physical and… https://t.co/Z4KDm3Pb8M https://t.co/uXMy57HuKq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man buys pizza for 54 immigrants discovered in tractor-trailer: Armando Colunga was watching the news in San Antonio when he saw a report Tuesday night about authorities discovering 54 undocumented immigrants in the back of an 18-wheeler truck. https://t.co/eP0T8uIb3U https://t.co/4ApKj3ufqo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bank seizes California congressman's dairy farm: Rep. David Valadao, R-California, confirmed Tuesday his family was no longer operating their dairy farm after the Los Angeles Times reported a bank seized the property following his failure to resolve more… https://t.co/MTDcp7dbT8 https://t.co/693T4SIL9J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Database Administrator: Title Senior Database Administrator ============================= EOE Statement We are an equal employment opportunity employer. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race,… https://t.co/zU2XneEzKE https://t.co/YEMxZcEhvT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breakthrough -- or surrender? Trump-Kim summit: CNN Opinion asked a group of expert commentators to weigh in with their reactions to the historic meeting between Donald Trump and Kim Jong Un. The views expressed here are solely theirs. https://t.co/yknOCOZZ24 https://t.co/KdMw8cmnxG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: SQL Developer Markit Digital is looking for a talented SQL Server Database Developer/Analyst who is interested in working with large, complex data sets. Our growing development team is looking for folks eager to take on the challenge of… https://t.co/RsuHhFhncp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why some evangelicals don't want Pence to speak at their meeting: At first glance, a Southern Baptist meeting might seem like a friendly audience for Vice President Mike Pence. https://t.co/VxCEE0DVdS https://t.co/ROQUXUMcb5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems/Test Engineer: Systems/Test Engineer Job Locations US-DC-Washington Job ID 10385 Minimum Clearance Required US Citizen Responsibilities Functional Responsibilities:   ISYS Technologies is seeking a Systems/Test Engineer. Job Duties: Responsible… https://t.co/2MNAWWrf1G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Manager, Marketing Technology &amp; Operations: Own, Build &amp; Scale Our Marketing Operations: Periscope Data is looking for a skilled and strategic marketing operations lead to help us optimize our marketing and continue to drive our atmospheric… https://t.co/kAw8B3xlAO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: Role Technology Lead – US Auto req ID 28655BR Domain Database Hi -Tech Tools administration Skillset Database Design , Database Tuning , DB2 , DB2 Database Programming DB2 Database Administration , Oracle Database administration ,… https://t.co/sU8h4GNEVo https://t.co/XtBehBbk6U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Design and develop real time clearing and banking applications and services for integration with continually expanding business relationships such as Clearing Corporations, Banks and Regulatory EntitiesWork on the implementation and… https://t.co/klPoWheBIp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr SQL Developer (LOCALS ONLY): Sr SQL Developer (LOCALS ONLY) Blue Bell, PA 3 months+ Hi-Trust Certification – what they have to do to be high trust certified Key Skills: Hands-on (dont need high level architecture) SQL and MS-SQL Server Using source… https://t.co/wHT8tfFPhn https://t.co/Xsoro4QhWs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL/SQL Developer: PL/SQL Developer Malvern, Pennsylvania – United States Job Start Date – 06/25/18, Posted Date – 05/24/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview Title: PL/SQL Developer Project: Audit/Regulatory Compliance Reporting Team Duration: Long… https://t.co/tEzgv4tvU7 https://t.co/tIE4NnVJ57]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MLB exec calls superstar 'overrated' and a loser https://t.co/SJ1K957Zq6 https://t.co/M7tlMeRbFK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[James Clapper: US is 'in a much better place' after Trump-Kim summit: Former Director of National Intelligence James Clapper said the US is in a "much better place" after the summit between President Donald Trump and North Korean leader Kim Jong Un. https://t.co/YBNTYQuIYT https://t.co/Euj7c7sko2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Specialist Developer – https://t.co/qZglOKK4dO, MVC, C#, SQL Server, SSRS: For BNY Mellon Specialist Developer – *******, MVC, C#, SQL Server, SSRS job – Asset Servicing – Multiple Skip to Main Content – – – – Toggle navigation – Who We Are – What We Do… https://t.co/uD4aZCkz2O https://t.co/2W4fJkZ53L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NFL team ordered to pay $12.5M for player's injury https://t.co/kHOCqdkuG5 https://t.co/hV9YvCmjAb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer (JavaScript, C#, .Net, SQL): .Net Developer (JavaScript, C#, .Net, SQL) Ref No.: 18-21691 Location: Redmond, Washington Role .Net Developer (JavaScript, C#, .Net, SQL) Location: Redmond, WA Duration: FTE Mandatory Technical Skills A… https://t.co/usf704qaUl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SSIS SQL Server: SSIS SQL Server Ref No.: 18-25294 Location: west palm beach, Florida Position: SSIS SQL Server Location: West Palm Beach, US-FL Duration: Full Time/ Contract JOB DESCRIPTION: Design, build and deploy effective SSIS packages Implement… https://t.co/SzvugXyRxg https://t.co/EcEXCYpQL0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server Database Administration: SQL Server Database Administration Ref No.: 18-21148 Location: Minneapolis, Minnesota "Provide DBA support on all aspects of databases administration including backup/recovery, replication, deployment and real-time… https://t.co/8LZQX9tF2c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[pl/sql Developer: pl/sql Developer Ref No.: 18-23804 Location: westerville, Ohio Position :PL/SQL Developer Duration : Full Time Permanent Location : Westerville, OH Job Description: Experience Required 1. Excellent knowledge in Pl/SQL programming… https://t.co/nk1aoefqCc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trudeau's eyebrows spark social media debate: Twitter users claim Canadian PM Justin Trudeau wore fake eyebrows at the G7 summit. CNN's Jeanne Moos reports. https://t.co/NsJzV1ufz2 https://t.co/ADwxAtWT0R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Production Support Engineer (Java/MySQL): Who We Are _accesso_ is a world-wide software company delivering industry leading virtual queuing, eCommerce and ticketing solutions for the attractions, cultural and leisure industries. The _accesso Passport_… https://t.co/xGlUvANjtT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Informatica and SQL Server Developer: Informatica and SQL Server Developer: 18-02111 Ref No.: 18-02111 Location: Burbank, California Akraya is looking for a Informatica and SQL Developer for one of our clients. If the job description below is a fit,… https://t.co/hkjdJk0X11]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UI Developer: UI Developer (with Python) (57051 ) Ref No.:18-08514 Location: Boston,MA, Massachusetts Position Type:Contract Start Date: 05/08/2018 Following job posting is open and you can submit profiles against same. Job posting details are as… https://t.co/uZNZE3tGKW https://t.co/ngkWuezfRP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: What just happened?: CNN Opinion asked a group of expert commentators to weigh in with their reactions to the historic meeting between Donald Trump and Kim Jong Un. The views expressed here are solely theirs. https://t.co/iVY5eYmgPe https://t.co/aqSfriSbJQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer – NoSQL: Job Description What you’ll be doing… The Digital Team at Verizon is looking for a highly technical, NoSQL Developer with Java skills to help us develop our next generation of digital experience. The incumbent is a strong… https://t.co/ECQg7hC8Y0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The German cars Trump doesn't want https://t.co/6iJZUvjgYH https://t.co/oLh9Vss8zY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Q&amp;A: The real reason Kamau Bell tested his DNA: W. Kamau Bell didn't need a DNA test to confirm his identity. https://t.co/ZdjyvmCcE5 https://t.co/nX7JFdTOSe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Orlando man shoots officer and barricades himself with 4 children: A man who shot an Orlando police officer late Sunday night remained barricaded in an apartment with four children Monday afternoon, police said. https://t.co/EPa7kWElx3 https://t.co/kKvXq2R7I6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: SQL Developer Markit Digital is looking for a talented SQL Server Database Developer/Analyst who is interested in working with large, complex data sets. Our growing development team is looking for folks eager to take on the challenge of… https://t.co/BydhJK8jPQ https://t.co/yCl2Tlw78a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior SQL Developer: Title: Senior SQL Developer Location: Downers Grove, IL, US, 60515 Company: Univar USA Requisition ID: 7682 It starts with great chemistry. Univar is more than a distribution company – we’re a leading, global partner dedicated to… https://t.co/MpNNTVClwT https://t.co/eXcp2NUMaX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst IV(Hedis, SQL): Job ID ******* Category Data Analytics Schedule Full-time Job ID ******* Category Data Analytics Schedule Full-time Description: Position Purpose: Responsible for analytic data needs of the business unit. Handle complex data… https://t.co/8OPYmgwWPG https://t.co/ayNBiSJtuq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering: Developer for Ariba, Inc (Palo Alto, CA) to develop, maintain, and improve our automated functional test, integration test suite, and performance test suite. Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science, Engineering, Mathematics, or a related field… https://t.co/yfJOtSuLGQ https://t.co/4RxIgwQLw2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your stories: 'He opened the world up to me' https://t.co/hyF3gHgrvT https://t.co/IdxvWwQdgz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: SQL Developer Ref No.: 18-21450 Location: Washington, District of Columbia Title:- SQL Developer (SSIS, SSAS) Location:- Washington DC Contract W2 – Candidate should have more than 8+ years of Total IT experience. – More than 5 years of… https://t.co/QaVB5J3EDZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sound effects startle Eminem fans: Eminem doesn't use gunshot sound effects during his live show, his spokesman said, after the rapper came under fire for a series of blast sounds that were mistaken by several festival attendees as gunshots. https://t.co/Lqx4BsN7HR https://t.co/6Hfogyg7Ib]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL developer: SQL developer Ref No.: 18-21744 Location: Memphis, Tennessee – 5-8 years of experience as a SQL Developer or similar role – Excellent understanding of Microsoft SQL Server, SQL Server programming (writing and decoding stored procedures) –… https://t.co/hXs3QSAvUX https://t.co/jIE7v95mlT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL-Server-DBA: We are hiring a SQL Server DBA Location: Columbia, SC Duration: 12+ months (with a possibility of extn) Candidate Type: W2 Only; Unfortunately NO Corp-to-Corp or 1099 DAILY DUTIES / RESPONSIBILITIES: – Identify the requirements for the… https://t.co/6BYUUaR6ZO https://t.co/rXlQQ86UqX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: 5/15/2018 SQL Developer Tracking Code 10751 Job Description Make your mark in Broadcasting and Digital Media. Sinclair Broadcast Group and Sinclair Digital Solutions are dedicated to making Sinclair a communications powerhouse! We are the… https://t.co/eYSQjnkCWf https://t.co/A5bMUQukcl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Valedictorian's mic cut off over her speech: A high school valedictorian in California says she had her graduation speech cut short when she began talking about sexual assault. https://t.co/6rmDjmDqrE https://t.co/upIZiy8csx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The end of net neutrality is here https://t.co/royPy4d3XW https://t.co/ShowCph4gm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server DBA: PROPOSED AD Portland, OR. Sr. Database Administrator. Draft and maintain procedures and documentation for databases. Manage database configuration including installing and upgrading software and maintaining relevant documentation.… https://t.co/ZnE5rq0rxM https://t.co/Kho84cCj46]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mars is suddenly more interesting: NASA's Curiosity rover has discovered organic compounds -- molecules containing carbon and hydrogen, along with other elements -- on Mars, and this is good news in the search for life. Organic molecules are the stuff of… https://t.co/pqExuBk2QZ https://t.co/W9mKZgorO9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sybase and SQL Server DBA: Sybase and SQL Server DBA Ref No.: 18-24883 Location: atlanta, Georgia Requirement / Sybase and SQL Server DBA / Atlanta, GA Essential Skills – Knowledge of Sybase (SAP ASE 16)/ SQL Server / Replication Server – At least 5-8… https://t.co/svIrfxVWnV https://t.co/MITgPsNpQM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front End developer with NOSQL and React.JS: Front End developer with NOSQL and React.JS Ref No.: 18-24766 Location: Chicago, Illinois Strong proficiency in JavaScript, including DOM manipulation and the JavaScript object modelThorough understanding of… https://t.co/ZXm5pIj92S https://t.co/4Jzq7yRq02]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch Kim Jong Un's security guards run alongside his car: North Korean leader Kim Jong Un arrives in Singapore ahead of the June 12 summit with President Donald Trump and meets with Singapore's Prime Minister Lee Hsien Loong. https://t.co/NPEOaE754o https://t.co/ckCGoiEdSA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Database Developer: SQL Database Developer in Aberdeen Proving Ground, MD | CACI International – Small Business | – Suppliers – About Us – | – What We Do – | – Media &amp; Events – | – Investors – | – Careers – | – Contracts – | – Contact Us Join Our… https://t.co/GkKZ9URWsV https://t.co/NrNMorfWLo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kim Jong Un arrives in Singapore for historic summit: North Korean leader Kim Jong Un arrived in Singapore ahead of an historic summit with US President Donald Trump Sunday, as Trump declared that the young dictator had a "one-time shot" to bring his… https://t.co/aziB6nduHA https://t.co/fWNxBGcrIO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: SQL Developer Job Description Are you passionate about building amazing software? Are you constantly pushing yourself to develop better, faster and more efficient applications? Do you have an innate interest in releasing products that… https://t.co/REuKzCbWiB https://t.co/2bm6y3fdFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL SSRS Report Developer: SQL SSRS Report Developer Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania – United States Job Start Date – 05/15/18, Posted Date – 05/15/18 Primary SkillsSQLTax TermsC2COverviewThis is a 6-12 months contract. Phone and Skype interview. Must have good… https://t.co/aIGOOL9XRU https://t.co/yYkMQSONo3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eunice Gayson, the first Bond girl dies at 91: Actress Eunice Gayson, the first Bond girl in the James Bond movies, has died, according to a tweet from the franchise's page. She was 90. https://t.co/N4qFfKtfTY https://t.co/eSCi8PrqT9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AWS-Implementation-of-MySQL—PostgreSQL: AWS IMPLEMENTATION OF MYSQL &amp; POSTGRESQL HOPEWELL, NJ Project Description: – This role will assist in the acceleration of the implementation of MySQL and PostgreSQL into the Client environment. – This… https://t.co/Asxnl54Zp3 https://t.co/8En7Rgc4h6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The gun that can fire when you drop it https://t.co/LoZb9BtYH0 https://t.co/yIzlo7oaGr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Engineer MySQL DBA: *FOR THE FIRST 6 MONTHS TO 1 YEAR THIS POSITION WILL BE 50% 1ST SHIFT AND 50% 2ND SHIFT. ONCE THE ENVIRONMENT GET’S TO WHERE IT NEEDS TO BE THE ROLE WILL SWITCH TO ONLY 1ST SHIFT/NORMAL BUSINESS HOURS** Chicago, IL Under general… https://t.co/d345WbAl86 https://t.co/tasayxPASp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL SQL Developer: PL SQL Developer in Alexandria, Virginia, United States | Management Consulting at Deloitte Toggle menu – Deloitte home – About Deloitte – – Location: United States Available in locations and languages – Students – Experienced – Careers… https://t.co/s16teNQM5A https://t.co/sgCWfCsI3x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Database Analyst/Developer (Secret clearance required): KEY RESPONSIBILITIES: * Analyst/Developer must agilely pull data from Remedy ITSM (current version) and other SQL databases in response to business information needs, and develop/generate… https://t.co/jzRsBRqBnA https://t.co/aP2397XQeg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[COBOL SQL programmer: COBOL/DB2/SQL programmer st louis, Missouri – United States Job Start Date – 05/14/18, Posted Date – 05/14/18 Primary SkillsSQL,COBOLTax TermsC2COverviewclient – mastercard linked in skype buying rate upto 55/hr Job Overview: Leads… https://t.co/HNezZD1Syp https://t.co/6PCnxgtD1d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr–Data-Migration-with-Oracle–PL-SQL: SR. DATA MIGRATION WITH ORACLE, PL/SQL HOPEWELL, NJ Project Description: A seasoned data engineering consultant is needed to design, develop and deliver high quality data migrations and data integrations for… https://t.co/L7FTSeYLcI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Illinois GOP warns Trump it would be 'stupid' to free Blagojevich: Illinois Republicans in Congress are making an urgent plea to President Donald Trump: Don't let Rod Blagojevich off the hook. https://t.co/72z0dOYto8 https://t.co/e70hTjhhbs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salmonella outbreak linked to pre-cut melon: A multistate outbreak of salmonella linked to pre-cut melon has sickened 60 people in five Midwestern states, the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention reported Friday. Six people are sick in Illinois,… https://t.co/3MXdSWVB3o https://t.co/Pgl5YaTjYP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior IT Business Analyst (SQL Server/Integration/Teletrack: DESCRIPTION The position is moderately visible to the hospitals business service lines and functions as a team member responsible for assisting in providing application(s) configuration… https://t.co/q1AqFxodZq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst IV(Hedis, SQL): Job ID ******* Category Data Analytics Schedule Full-time Job ID ******* Category Data Analytics Schedule Full-time Description: Position Purpose: Responsible for analytic data needs of the business unit. Handle complex data… https://t.co/Th0E2YU1l0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MS SQL Server BI Developer: MS SQL Server BI Developer in Aberdeen Proving Ground, MD | CACI International – Small Business | – Suppliers – About Us – | – What We Do – | – Media &amp; Events – | – Investors – | – Careers – | – Contracts – | – Contact Us Join… https://t.co/xOqHszlBe9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: Mick Mulvaney fired us for advocating for consumers: Consumer Financial Protection Bureau acting director Mick Mulvaney has ousted a committed group of experts who volunteered their time and expertise to ensure a fair marketplace for businesses… https://t.co/Cx2wAM5vvH https://t.co/kgUrm5Mu04]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China upping the ante on scary: China is increasingly giving America a run for its money as the land of the biggest and the best. https://t.co/7Ed8Bsz1ld https://t.co/UuJxpHVS98]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior SQL Database Administrator: Location US-NC-Research Triangle Park Job Description Biogen has a large SQL environment with thousands of databases under support, the successful candidate will need to be organized and able to work with multiple… https://t.co/96fGt11mtU https://t.co/1kFFlKzYEj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer – Health Data Analytics: Careers Center | SQL Developer – Health Data Analytics Welcome page Returning Candidate? Log back in! – SQL Developer – Health Data Analytics Job Location: US-MD-Columbia ID 1957 Overview IMPAQ International, a… https://t.co/jao5atEbQe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL/SQL Developer: Our client in the downtown Cleveland area has an immediate need for a Senior PL/SQL consultant. The duration is through December 2018 (with a possibility of it going longer). *CANDIDATE MUST HAVE AT LEAST 3+ YEARS OF PHYSICALLY WORKING… https://t.co/s9nj2nSc3i https://t.co/oXZjuHPL9p]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>