<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Footage of fatal police shooting released in Nashville: Surveillance footage of a fatal shooting in Nashville last month appears to show a police officer shooting a man in the back as he ran away. https://t.co/GIS8tD4OZr https://t.co/L1MHaUxfxo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[German drug maker sues to block Nebraska execution: Fresenius Kabi filed a lawsuit to block an execution in Nebraska, saying that the US state illegally procured drugsfor use in the planned lethal injection. https://t.co/lJ0K6H9GCz https://t.co/5117X3Gsjo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tribune calls off $3.9 billion Sinclair media deal: Tribune said in a statement Thursday that it has terminated its merger agreement with Sinclair, scuttling a $3.9 billion deal. https://t.co/uVSWBd63dB https://t.co/K3i48ezgcr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heimlich family, Red Cross at odds over technique: The Red Cross and other organizations suggest that first aid for choking begin with five slaps on the back. The family of Dr. Henry Heimlich is launching a campaign to demand proof that it works. https://t.co/y4Vh3oLBtM https://t.co/vKF7f30Duf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer | web frameworks, web applications, web services: Web Developer | web frameworks, web applications, web services Columbus, OH 08-05-2018 Location: Columbus, OH For more than 18 years, CareWorks Tech has been delivering technology solutions… https://t.co/U8BMjqdsAd https://t.co/sQYsP3L3n9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer II – Multiple Positions: Discover your Promise by helping our students discover theirs Ohio University is seeking qualified applicants for the following positions in the Information Technology Department Web Developer II (2 Year Term)… https://t.co/1oSsgXWdmo https://t.co/oYz2igbbfy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thai soccer team's stateless boys granted citizenship: Three boys from the Wild Boar soccer team and their coach, who were rescued from deep within a flooded cave in Thailand last month, have been granted Thai citizenship. https://t.co/vvmZotECkr https://t.co/5ML46YIfGR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scientists search for 'smoking gun' in the dead zone of Florida's red tide: A toxic algae bloom is killing dolphins, sea turtles, manatees and thousands of fish. Even as it shows no sign of ending, researchers are trying to work out exactly why it's… https://t.co/OOuOY9CeHM https://t.co/heuazvFjN5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Video of Parkland school shooter talking with detective is released: Marjory Stoneman Douglas High School shooter Nikolas Cruz told a detective shortly after the February massacre that a voice in his head the night before the shooting told him to hurt… https://t.co/yYxrOcZM6y https://t.co/8aVj05sK9o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meet the 15-year-old who's the Microsoft Excel world champion (which is a real thing): Kevin Dimaculangan, a 15-year-old from Florida, won the championship that challenges competitors on their knowledge of Microsoft Office applications https://t.co/wrz7qxbCOq https://t.co/rYrapHUEf1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brad Pitt fires back at Angelina Jolie's child support claims: Brad Pitt is disputing Angelina Jolie's claims that he has not paid "meaningful" child support. https://t.co/TCxYw3bQI5 https://t.co/0n0KMu8dz2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carrie Underwood pregnant with baby No. 2: Carrie Underwood's family is excited to be "adding another fish to our pond." https://t.co/TRxv2wrT7u https://t.co/QDyJYjl2EH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Battle of Amiens: Prince William, Theresa May mark offensive that turned WW1: Britain's Prince William and Prime Minister Theresa May will attend commemorations for the Battle of Amiens, which turned the tide of WW1 in the Allies' favor. https://t.co/mObmcuOrC0 https://t.co/YEi98iAR52]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Hybris Manager $170k: Cincinnati, OH Full-time $150k – $175k Posted Today If you are a SAP Hybris Manager with experience, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us We are one of the fastest growing companies in the country that invest heavily in… https://t.co/MddBIfdlUR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Scrum Master: Founded in 1866, The Sherwin-Williams Company is a global leader in the manufacture, development, distribution, and sale of paints, coatings and related products to professional, industrial, commercial, and retail customers. The… https://t.co/itGiO6KCfu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World's biggest IPO in 2 years shows China's 5G ambitions: China Tower, which made its market debut in Hong Kong on Wednesday, is central to China's goal of becoming a global leader in 5G technology. https://t.co/2lcXGr1n5c https://t.co/nwoaOCPLaB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Developer I: Employer Miami University Location Miami University, Oxford Campus, Ohio Posted Jul 26, 2018 Administrative Jobs Technology, Web, Mobile &amp; Application Development, Other Technology Jobs Institution Type Four-Year Institution You… https://t.co/K08FeuhjWZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior IT Business Analyst (Soarian Financials and Scheduling): Applicants must be eligible to work in the specified location Description The position is visible to the hospital’s business service lines and serves as a liaison between IT and those… https://t.co/4jNK7vyUvx https://t.co/vROLa2BwOs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Border Patrol agents arrest suspected human smuggler who was using a fake EMS vehicle: A man is accused of impersonating a first responder and trying to smuggle three people across a US border checkpoint. https://t.co/59qtZcNvwb https://t.co/Oq5e7MkxyL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, Senior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Dayton, OH Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 8/3/2018 Job Description Job Number: R******* Software Engineer, Senior Key Role: technical knowledge of software… https://t.co/gJa2EkW5jn https://t.co/2XKG4lk7Mi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Venezuela Fast Facts: Read CNN's Fast Facts about Venezuela and learn more about one of the top oil-producing countries in the world. https://t.co/n6agIXK2vW https://t.co/x2uZcx77NS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saudi Prince Alwaleed acquires 2.3% stake in Snapchat: Saudi Prince Alwaleed bin Talal has acquired a 2.3% stake in Snapchat. His other investments include Twitter and Lyft. https://t.co/RwytizwDKy https://t.co/276dq328n1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quickly catch up on the day's news: Here's what you might have missed Tuesday on CNN https://t.co/k6CFVmLPpe https://t.co/VKSf8Y9Qai]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rick Gates' brutal lesson for Paul Manafort: Criminals, politicians and other narcissists tend to be self-interested individuals. Put enough pressure on them, and they'll happily shift the blame (hopefully to where it really belongs). Paul Manafort is… https://t.co/M1ej5Sc0Ep https://t.co/ws32qqhX8o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Demi Lovato has been released from the hospital and entered rehab: Demi Lovato has entered rehab, sources close to Lovato told CNN. https://t.co/OwnvQzcwEH https://t.co/P6Z2Z9Ihu1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Operations Analyst: – Under general supervision, analyzes proposed policies, procedures, forms and reports. – Recommends operational improvement through standardization, simplification, discontinuance and other methods. – Recommends installations of new… https://t.co/iNDhhPyU9H https://t.co/IyeFgMLQS4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump warns countries against doing business with Iran as sanctions kick back in: Donald Trump has warned that countries doing business with Iran would "NOT be doing business" with the US as his administration reimposed sanctions on Tuesday. https://t.co/muT5tq3NC5 https://t.co/WUqGcpOmys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NodeJS Developer: NodeJS Developer Ref No.: 18-31270 Location: Cincinnati, Ohio Integration of data storage solutions {{may include databases, key-value stores, blob stores, etc.}} Strong proficiency with JavaScript {{or CoffeeScript depending on your… https://t.co/8ODlEm9GDz https://t.co/kGskVBNi3L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Security Consultant: Network &amp; Security Consultant Business Group Control Products and Solutions No. of Positions 1 Requisition Number 78087BR Job Category Sales, Services, and Solutions Position Type Full Time Relocation Eligible No Position… https://t.co/5e6jm1yGU3 https://t.co/ukyXtD1u5h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Serena Williams: 'I felt like I was not a good mom': Serena Williams reflects on motherhood a week after suffering the heaviest defeat of her career. https://t.co/YVawdlCYd0 https://t.co/VGteNdyLXa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UI/UX Developer # JN: – Like us on Facebook – Follow us on Twitter – Connect with us on LinkedIn – Instagram – Watch us on YouTube – Visit our page on Glassdoor – Our Blog RSS Feed – Home – Employers – Overview – IT – Engineering – Professional –… https://t.co/s4pdgRrGZO https://t.co/u4uJSUtWTK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parkland school shooter told detective he heard a demon in his head, transcript shows: Marjory Stoneman Douglas school shooter Nikolas Cruz told a detective shortly after the February massacre that a voice in his head the night before the shooting told… https://t.co/ob1DJUfHGa https://t.co/XFTdUemmEL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fantastical images show Guo Pei's creations in a new light: Photographs offer a "western interpretation" of the Chinese designer's best-known garments https://t.co/bd8ET8rq1w https://t.co/14U1ve5dul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lindsey Graham had a 'really interesting' dinner with Sean Hannity, Mark Levin and the President: South Carolina Republican Sen. Lindsey Graham Mondau described his dinner this weekend with President Donald Trump, Fox News' Sean Hannity and conservative… https://t.co/4SRo9eddk6 https://t.co/ww5tPOYyTT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Justice Department lays out roadmap to appeal of AT&amp;T-Time Warner deal: Judge Richard Leon, the government's attorneys wrote in the brief, "discarded the economics of bargaining." https://t.co/UwCFrzELyg https://t.co/cKxIbwM49A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lance Bass 'heartbroken' he didn't get 'Brady Bunch' house: Bye, bye, bye "Brady Bunch" house. https://t.co/LVNZWhZU8N https://t.co/sUOi7YwUxB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nigerian man dies after rescuing 13 people from boat accident https://t.co/2uG8mZkOtD https://t.co/lZ3j61CYuD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nude golf: Naturism in full swing at Australian course: On a golf course in northern Australia everything is swinging ... not least because 30 players are in the nude. https://t.co/ulR7tmNse0 https://t.co/Fo8cUZIqsx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CNN Exclusive: Surgeon falsely accused of wrongdoing tries to recover his name: The lawyer who accused Dr. Ricardo Quarrie, a cardiothoracic fellow at Yale New Haven Hospital, of lying to cover up a surgical mistake has recanted. https://t.co/nsAquRxAcz https://t.co/t8t4vYs2pi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior IT Business Analyst (Kronos/Payroll): Description The position is visible to the hospital’s business service lines and serves as a liaison between IT and those groups. This position also functions as a team member responsible for providing… https://t.co/loDqjizmIT https://t.co/OdEEx5fZKo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Charlotte Rae -- Mrs. Garrett from TV's 'The Facts of Life,' 'Diff'rent Strokes' -- dies at 92: Charlotte Rae, a gregarious actress with a prodigious career on stage, screen and TV, died on Sunday at the age of 92, her son Larry Strauss told CNN. https://t.co/y962fhTy3Z https://t.co/C5qIpM9d0r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Application Architect: Technical Application Architect Ref No.: 18-33999 Location: Columbus, Ohio Linux Redhat, UNIX, AIX, Storage Area Networks &amp; Arrays, Network Switching (physical and virtual) Secondary Skills: VMWare vSphere, Windows… https://t.co/3NJwPSpWPQ https://t.co/Sf7fltohSX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bikers salute leader of their pack: Donald Trump: One of the world's largest motorcycle rallies in the world at Sturgis, South Dakota, is becoming a celebration of Donald Trump, over the mighty Harley-Davidson. https://t.co/IvPYVk7qH3 https://t.co/xThTlkkyCq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst, Toledo, OH: Back to search results Search by Keyword or Job ID More Search Options Search by Location or Country Search by Postal Code (US ONLY) Search by Location or Country Search by Postal Code (US ONLY) Distance Search by Postal… https://t.co/ZEUItygx6f https://t.co/mEOn9BnDTD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At least 317 killed in ongoing protests in Nicaragua, rights group says: Civil unrest in Nicaragua that began in mid-April has left at least 317 people dead, according to the Inter-American Commission on Human Rights. https://t.co/uvk1K6SnlP https://t.co/xBtSds6zII]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Institute decries 'grotesque' vandalism to Nobel laureate Elie Wiesel's childhood home: Vandals spray-painted hot-pink pejoratives on the childhood home of author, Holocaust survivor and Nobel laureate Elie Wiesel, according to the institute set up in… https://t.co/n8IfKfocLw https://t.co/F94JTvbD91]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook Fast Facts: Read CNN's Facebook Fast Facts and learn more about the social media giant. https://t.co/0jOlxFVleC https://t.co/AVCm1Goy37]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deval Patrick defends Bain Capital work: Never 'left my conscience at the door': Former Massachusetts Gov. Deval Patrick on Sunday defended his work at Bain Capital, pushing back on criticism he would likely face if he seeks the Democratic nomination for… https://t.co/LEfjM5lnAJ https://t.co/DknnNRFzGz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iran says it held military exercises in Strait of Hormuz: Iran said its Islamic Revolutionary Guard Corps held a naval exercise in the Strait of Hormuz last week "within the framework of their annual training program." https://t.co/7yz1us9bE8 https://t.co/ewhtQPDdiQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Financial Integrations and Systems Analyst: Multi-Color Corporation is hiring a Senior Financial Integrations &amp; Systems Analyst! If you are looking to join a growing organization, look no further! Multi-Color Corporation located in Batavia, Ohio –… https://t.co/cJTYB4bW7O https://t.co/3XvWiL2H4x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Project Manager Sr: Technical Project Manager Sr Join a team recognized for leadership, innovation and diversity Honeywell Intelligrated – ********************* has multiple opportunities for high-level Project Managers to support major… https://t.co/l5XHI5EnTo https://t.co/WAoqM2QRpx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The final days of the suspect in a Houston doctor's death: On July 20, Joseph Pappas shot and killed prominent surgeon Dr. Mark Hausknecht as both pedaled bikes along a Houston street, police say. https://t.co/gn9dbwRR0y https://t.co/YZIHrQC75U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Lead Business Analyst: Founded in 1866, The Sherwin-Williams Company is a global leader in the manufacture, development, distribution, and sale of paints, coatings and related products to professional, industrial, commercial, and retail customers. The… https://t.co/sDEnuxfNXv https://t.co/tp5ar5Ir9o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guest Service Desk Team Member: Guest Service Desk Team Member Description: As a Guest Service team member, you are the front end and the face of what we stand for. You’ll be motivated by and always look for opportunities to go above and beyond guest… https://t.co/HKlaM2MnZu https://t.co/UiQdJQ6nD9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bangladesh students protest over road safety after deadly crash: Student protesters have been taking to the streets in Bangladesh's capital to demand safer roads. https://t.co/XWRSYdTqpn https://t.co/4SXsu4ApJJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Environmental Scientist/Project Manager: TRC Companies, Inc., a pioneer in groundbreaking scientific and engineering developments since the 1960s, is a national engineering consulting and construction management firm that provides integrated services to… https://t.co/uOvlfOVns4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Venezuela's Maduro is evacuated from stage after 'attempt against the President': Venezuelan President Nicolas Maduro was evacuated from a stage on Saturday during a speech in Caracas after what authorities concluded was an attempted "terrorist attack… https://t.co/DRusXknXj9 https://t.co/0N9ICQkqGy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager II Higher Ed: Project Manager II – Higher Ed Tracking Code 5158-244 Job Description At Gilbane we’re building more than buildings, we’re helping create schools, hospitals, laboratories and other facilities across the United States and… https://t.co/L9jIaEEHW2 https://t.co/FZrisXPQju]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wells Fargo says hundreds of customers lost homes because of computer glitch: Wells Fargo said it has set aside $8 million to compensate customers that were wrongly denied mortgage modifications while undergoing foreclosure, and the bank is under… https://t.co/neECMtLhuj https://t.co/47c1vdKgpY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Berkshire Hathaway's stake in Apple is now worth nearly $50 billion: Warren Buffett's investing firm revealed a soaring uptick in operating earnings when it posted quarterly results Saturday. https://t.co/uo9D9lfdOB https://t.co/acRbngSOEL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Medicare for All makes a lot of sense: Jeffrey Sachs says the Medicare for All plan would save money and provide greater health coverage for Americans. It's an unbeatable system, and much of the rest of the West already has something like it. https://t.co/9vZf5Nka1G https://t.co/lXKG7tHp69]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump escalates old fights this week, starts new ones: At the end of a week in which President Donald Trump appeared more ready than ever to pick fights with his adversaries — both real and perceived — it was perhaps fitting to have the UFC's… https://t.co/OjECJUyEne https://t.co/PkTGisrYqN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spain, Portugal swelter as heat wave kills 3 people: Spain and Portugal faced another exceptionally hot day Saturday as a heat wave that has killed three people in Spain threatened to raise temperatures to record levels. https://t.co/AspXoJApAa https://t.co/D8COPkAFWf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Security Engineer: Network Security Engineer Ref No.: 18-32427 Location: Dublin, Ohio ROLE: Network Security Engineer II LOCATION: Tulsa,Oklahoma – Security, MPLS, Internet, Ethernet, and Managed Services signal flow – CNIA- SEC / JCNIP- SEC,… https://t.co/7j87KfadPV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Engineer: Search Display ****************************************************************************** &amp; siteid=105 &amp; PageType=JobDetails &amp; jobid=******* &amp; codes=IND Loading Close Your account has successfully been deleted. Close… https://t.co/I1a5LsjpLP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ludacris paid for this woman's groceries -- and now she wants to pay it forward: What happened to Therra Gywn Jaramillo in the checkout line wasn't crazy -- it was Ludacris. https://t.co/JsHeYEI5oS https://t.co/DEdu5ctJr0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Syncsort Data Integration/ETL Specialist: Exodus Integrity Services, Inc is a rapidly expanding technology company headquartered in Northeast Ohio. EIS provides quality services to our clients by instilling honesty, commitment, and hard work to find the… https://t.co/f21Aquu3t9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automation Engineer: now Automation Engineer =================== Company Name: Kroger General Office Position Type: Employee FLSA Status: Exempt Line of Business: Corporate Systems See what life is like at Kroger Technology at… https://t.co/yC9px2YZ8k https://t.co/pR0uP1Pfw7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Washington Post: Trump associate interacted with alleged Russian spy before election: Maria Butina, the Russian national charged with conspiracy to act as an agent of Russia within the US, interacted with a former Trump campaign aide in the run-up to the… https://t.co/zc59c1VQzw https://t.co/F57ABSLJX4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump voting commission had no evidence of widespread voter fraud, former member says: The now-disbanded commission that President Donald Trump set up to investigate election integrity did not find evidence of widespread voter fraud, a former member of… https://t.co/mqZRSaM6KQ https://t.co/h3WZl0ftl3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arizona migrant shelter worker accused of sexually abusing 8 teenage boys: A former youth care worker is accused of sexually abusing eight teenage boys at a federally funded Arizona migrant shelter that's part of the US government's network of privately… https://t.co/f3IieqyO5f https://t.co/WHsAozmMzi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETL Developer | must have a thorough understanding of systems and data integration policies, practices procedures: ETL Developer | must have a thorough understanding of systems and data integration policies, practices &amp; procedures Columbus, OH 07-15-2018… https://t.co/o2ny0kfjtY https://t.co/mTiP4ChhCw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kraft Heinz reports tasty sales but Campbell Soup rumors won't die: Kraft Heinz reported strong earnings and sales Friday morning, results that topped Wall Street's forecasts https://t.co/JPHaivhJR8 https://t.co/EosXXmRpYA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Distribution ASP: Distribution ASP ================ now Date: Jun 15, 2018 Location: Delaware, OH, US, 43015 Company: Kroger Company Name: Great Lakes Regional Distribution Center Position Type: Employee FLSA Status: Non-Exempt Position Summary:… https://t.co/XF2Hi2iVKy https://t.co/UtVI8e6JyI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tim Cook on $1 trillion valuation: Keep your eye on the ball: He said the mark isn't "the most important measure of our success." https://t.co/fPdgaeQbBo https://t.co/F8yorlsBmK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP SCM SD: NOTE: ‘AT PRESENT WE WONT REQUIRED H1 &amp; EAD RESUMES FOR THIS POSITION’ Title: ********** Position Type: 12 Months Contract Location: London, OH Skills Required: ********** Sector: Public Industry: Life Sciences Regards, Rohith Performance… https://t.co/RitTpa0MvZ https://t.co/pnvodDtiiT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heineken just made a big bet on China's beer market: Heineken hopes its latest deal will help it tap into China's huge beer market. https://t.co/zMVBm1lqbk https://t.co/frxOsbujqC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager II – Higher Ed: Project Manager II – Higher Ed Tracking Code 5142-244 Job Description At Gilbane we’re building more than buildings, we’re helping create schools, hospitals, laboratories and other facilities across the United States and… https://t.co/xth8k8PayI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Down syndrome man with toy gun shot dead by police in Sweden: A 20-year-old man with Down syndrome was carrying a toy gun when he was shot dead by Swedish police in Stockholm Thursday, according to CNN affiliate Expressen. https://t.co/s7UpLxk2An https://t.co/oRvzMuRaJt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full-stack developer: For Siemens Full-stack developer job – Marketing – Milford, Ohio Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard – Toggle navigation – My Dashboard – Our Stories – FAQS – – – Careers Home – Search Jobs – Siemens… https://t.co/ZJDYjtjETl https://t.co/VOSjsfZWp9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MAINFRAME DEVELOPER: MAINFRAME DEVELOPER Ref No.: 18-29358 Location: CINCINATTI, Ohio Hi, My name is Neha and I’m an IT recruiter at Enterprise Solutions, Inc. I came across your resume on a job board and wanted to check if you are available for a… https://t.co/R7y69RUW9I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chinese professor cut off mid-interview after authorities burst into his house: Chinese security forces broke into the home of an academic while he was giving a live phone interview with a US broadcaster Wednesday night, abruptly forcing him off-air. https://t.co/pRrNV9opKD https://t.co/kmKZTDhqgR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Business Analyst: Location US-OH-Cincinnati Posted Date 1 month ago(5/4/2018 3:07 PM) Job ID 23582 # Positions 2 Category Technology Position Type Full Time Overview Be Here. Be Great. Working for a leader in the insurance industry means… https://t.co/FzeHpueev0 https://t.co/ZFBjNpNW18]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 unusual cruise ship amenities: Cruise lines offer wilder and wilder offerings to get your business. From robot bartenders to a planetarium, here are 10 unusual cruise amenities. https://t.co/ZuNThFmSEg https://t.co/arRg00AZf0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alleged Russian agent's infiltration of GOP circles anything but subtle: As far as spy craft goes, Maria Butina's skills didn't seem particularly impressive. https://t.co/RGmnjqgB9H https://t.co/6IKGydqBEh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack .NET Developer | Oracle, C#, T-SQL, https://t.co/QwHe7eBPbX, MVC, LINQ, WCF, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery: Full Stack .NET Developer | Oracle, C#, T-SQL, *******, MVC, LINQ, WCF, HTML, CSS, JavaScript, jQuery – CareWorks TechCareWorks Tech… https://t.co/gr35nRvgQq https://t.co/Wmto3txGFx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your guide to visiting the Eiffel Tower -- including strike info: Here's your guide to the Eiffel Tower in Paris, France: Everything you need to know, including current strike information from August 2018. https://t.co/yjRHgJzOjX https://t.co/GT2bwTnCtB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paris Jackson: Demi Lovato is not sending me to rehab: Paris Jackson is putting an end to speculation that Demi Lovato's medical emergency has convinced her to enter rehab. https://t.co/XVWpQ6ooUF https://t.co/cp39r7DOqW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senators: Trump 'not paying attention' to Russian threats in 2018: Two leading senators are asserting that President Donald Trump has not focused on the clear threat the Kremlin poses in the 2018 elections, with one Republican on the Senate Intelligence… https://t.co/u8Vq4kphAO https://t.co/KxqTBwQEC6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla rally; Stocks slump on trade fears; CBS earnings: Here's what you need to know about the markets before you start your business day. https://t.co/vqEDZQIqBv https://t.co/yCGUuPY9Ud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Consultant, Business Intelligence: What Business Intelligence contributes to Cardinal Health Business Intelligence is responsible for applying business process knowledge and data analytics to develop, recommend and communicate timely, accurate,… https://t.co/JVlRpmAWMG https://t.co/yZwZMhQm8W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Application Analyst and Developer: Location US-OH-Cincinnati Posted Date 4 days ago(7/16/2018 4:30 PM) Job ID 23739 # Positions 1 Category Technology Position Type Full Time Overview Be Here. Be Great. Working for a leader in the insurance… https://t.co/HmxsaguS0Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian senator sues opposing lawmaker over sexual slur: A sexist remark hurled across Australia's Senate chamber by a male politician at a female lawmaker has now made its way into the courts, after Senator Sarah Hanson-Young filed a defamation suit… https://t.co/61N1bd9bGM https://t.co/kI8HLRsJuU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electrical/Automation Engineer: About Us Gerdau is the leading company in the production of long steel in the Americas and one of the major suppliers of specialty long steel in the world. With more than 45,000 employees, Gerdau has an installed capacity… https://t.co/31icXuL9bv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[java: java Ref No.: 18-31467 Location: Independence, Ohio Hi Hope you are doing well Number of position : 7 (Not Contract or C2C) I, Salman Shaikh (Enterprise Solution Inc.) would like to share a job opportunity as Sr. Java Developer based in… https://t.co/7FgSYnguM1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Ref No.: 18-32532 Location: Westerville, Ohio Title:- Java Developer Location:- Westerville , OH Duration:- 12 Months Job description Good communication and understanding Banking requirements Should be proficient in Web… https://t.co/67u1DwQGek https://t.co/G2jc7DJzfC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mahathir Mohamad on Islam, politics and the love of his life: At 93, Malaysian Prime Minister Mahathir Mohamad is the oldest leader in the world. He talks about his wife, his beliefs, and why he made his political comeback. https://t.co/1KezSmw8hA https://t.co/A43E6gJJJO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Takeaways from day two of the Paul Manafort trial: The criminal trial of former Trump campaign chairman Paul Manafort pressed on for its second day at a steady clip Wednesday, even as his former boss President Donald Trump called the investigation of… https://t.co/VRP1wTlFcC https://t.co/igph8pCZz5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Manager: *Ideal candidate will be located in or near Cincinnati or Toledo, OH metro area* Why naviHealth? naviHealth is the result of over a decade of dedicated visionary leaders and innovative organizations challenging the status quo for PAC… https://t.co/r16CUf7RqC https://t.co/fm4ztkawO7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Express Scripts stock plunges on report that Carl Icahn wants to block Cigna merger: Icahn reportedly believes Cigna is paying too much for Express Scripts and will urge shareholders to oppose the deal. Icahn is also wary of the new company https://t.co/ea6nAAZB6i https://t.co/nZJt172nu4]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>