<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT for Summertime Sadness and Favourite for National Anthem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @orgia_g: @LanaQuote "Blurrin' the lines between real and the fake, dark and lonely, I need somebody to hold me" @LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT If you think Lana's Lips Is Sexy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Lana_IsMyQueen: @LanaQuote " But when you walked out that door, a piece of me died " @LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Every man has to go through hell to reach Paradise." - LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WOW 1211 Followers ! Thank you #TeamLana you're the bestest ! Love you always @LanaDelRey :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Lana_IsMyQueen: @LanaQuote " If you love me hardcore then don't walk away, It's a game boy, I don't wanna play, I just wanna be yours "]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["That is what makes us gilrs. We all look for heaven and we put first love, something that we'd die for, it's our curse." #LDR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Don't cry about it, it's gonna happen. And that's where the beginning of the end begun." - LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I pretend I'm not hurt, I walk about the world like I'm having fun." - LanaDelRey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need you babe, like I never needed anyone. You're wrong but you're so much fun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#MentionSomeoneWhoMakesYouHappy @LanaDelRey &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big Dreams Gangster!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mon amour. Je sais que to m'aimes aussi. Tu as besoin de moi. Tu as besoin de moi dans ta vie. Tu ne peux vivre sans moi. —Carmen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hovag Thank you :)x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I get dizzy in heels." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All my dreams and all the lights mean nothing if I can't have you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elvis where are you when i need you most? White comp sequin jumpsuit ghost. Pick me up and make a toast. Champagne in the air.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was born bad. But then I met you, you made me nice for a while. But my dark side's true.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One for the money, two for the show. I love you honey, I'm ready to go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Cause you're the class president without Jackie O. And I'm singing 'Happy Birthday' like Marilyn Monroe." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana Del Rey by Helen Green. Gorgeous! http://t.co/9gn3PLN0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I've been bad, I've been wrong, playing a dangerous game. I'm in love, I'm in love. Love in a hurricane." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["My pussy tastes like Pepsi Cola, my eyes are wide like cherry pies." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Screwed up, scared, doing anything that I needed." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In a land of gods and monsters, I was an angel." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Don’t break me down. I’ve been travelin’ too long. I’ve been trying too hard, with one pretty song." —Lana Del Rey [Ride]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[" Every man has to go trough hell to reach paradise." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Don't cry, honey, crazy girl. Don't you know you are the world? Every time you feel unsure, try to remember what you are." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Heaven is my baby, suicide's her father, opulence is the end." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @a_gabs: If you're going crazy, just grab me and take me @LanaQuote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @IIBOBTAiL: @LanaQuote Lana Del Rey - Blue Velvet ♥ http://t.co/Fg4Qrash http://t.co/bgCQW2xw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I never wanted to lead a normal life, I wanted to try different things." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The sun beams mean nothing if you can't find the light shining in one thing." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["My dreams are bigger than your junky pride. It's fine if you're hateful, as long as you remain grateful." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LanaDelReyFact: #FF @LanaQuote @Fearless_148 @Dear_Lana_Rey @hovag @abbsdelrey @EsztiDelRey @MrsC1907 @delreylane @LanaDelReyINDO @H ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@abbsdelrey Thanks Xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ClancyDelRey Thanks :) xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Lipsytweet You're welcome :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FF @ClancyDelRey @ChanelDelRey @StacyDelRey @LadyGagaDelRey @NatuDelRey @abbsdelrey @gagalanadelrey @gagasfreebitchx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FF @LanaDelReyWorld @LanaDReyOnline @LanaDReyINDO @DelReyLane @LanaDelReyFan @lanadelreybr @LanaDelReyChile @LanaDelReyFact]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FF @The_LanaDelRey @Lipsytweet @Pressparty @LDRToday @lananow @LanaDelReyWeb @_LanaDelRey @LoveLanaDelRey @Hileeery @helpingteamlana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Hon, you never looked so beautiful as you do now my man." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MisterAmericaV: @LanaQuote  "Foot down, were going all the way. Touch down..."-Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Once I was lost, but now I am found." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LamaHassan98: @LanaQuote All my friends ask me why I stay strong, Tell 'em when you find true love it lives on.&lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["She wore Blue Velvet. Bluer than Velvet were her eyes. Warmer than may her tender sighs, love was ours." —Lana Del Rey - Blue Velvet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Eminem is the master of lyrics whereas Frank Sinatra is the master of vocals." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I'm your little harlot, starlet, Queen of Coney Island, raisin' hell all over town." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Don't cry about it. It's all gonna happen. And that's where the beginning of the end begun." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Adriana_nom: This is what makes us girls, we don't look for heaven and we put love first. Don't cry about it. Don't cry about it. #t ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GbgbatNovember: This kind of life, wasn't meant for the good girl, try as I might .. In the end its a cruel world - @LanaQuote ♥]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @saffjack: "Everybody told me love was blind, then i saw your face and you blew my mind, finally you and me are the lucky ones this t ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What people have to say about me, the amazing things or the really terrible things, none of them are true." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Putting your faith in the people is like building a house in the sand." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DeadAge: @LanaQuote "PutMeUnderYourBlackMotorcycle, 50BabyDollDressForMyIDo,ItOnlyTakes2HoursToNevada,IWearYourSparkleYouCallMeYourM ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you do what you've always done, you'll get what you've always got." —Lana Del Rey #FavouriteQuote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LanaDelRey's nominated for 'Best New Artist' 'Best Push Artist' and 'Best Alternative' at the MTV EMA 2012. VOTE HER: http://t.co/U5O9fJcB.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @The_LanaDelRey: #TeamLana vote for @LanaDelRey at the three categories she was nominated for the #EMAs2012! {http://t.co/tdSyRb87} ♥ ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Fashion is inspired by youth and nostalgia, and draws inspiration from the best of the past." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LamaHassan98: @LanaQuote My man’s crazy and his mind is a knife,But I like him. fact, i love him.I can’t get enough of him. #Backfire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sierrabardot: @LanaQuote @lanadelrey queen of alchemy, new jersey dance queen, sparkle jump rope queen, queen of the tabloids &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @missmaree11: @LanaQuote @LanaDelRey you forgot Queen of the Gas Station]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Queen of Saigon, Queen of Coney Island, Queen of Hollywood Sadcore, Queen of Vogue. Next, Queen what else? @LanaDelRey :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I will love you till the end of time. I would wait a million years. Promise you'll remember that you're mine." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Don't make me sad, don't make me cry. Sometimes love is not enough and the road gets tough, I don't know why." —Lana Del Rey (Born To Die)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LDRToday: Lana Del Rey has reached 1 MILLION followers! Congratulations @LanaDelRey ! #Lana1Million http://t.co/BurtQY3e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Lana1Million C'mon Girls!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We can do it! Tweet and Retweet!! #Lana1Million]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Lana1Million Congrats @LanaDelRey !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana Beauty Del Rey (The Queen Of Hollywood Sadcore). RT Please!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana Beauty Del Rey ! Please RT #TeamLana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lana Beauty Del Rey !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you think you're over me
And your bad baby is dead and gone
Remember I'm the ghost in your machine
I'm your real life suicide girl.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LamaHassan98: @LanaQuote I need you, I breathe you, I'd never leave you.They would rue the day, I was alone without you.&lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SiumeyCho: I will love you until the end of times @LanaQuote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Everybody told me love was blind. Then I saw your face and you blew my mind." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pressparty You're welcome :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LanaDelReyFact: #FF @The_LanaDelRey @LanaQuote @Fearless_148 @Jul3z1313 @drunkenlysober @XxARTPOPxX @lamia_hudson @helpingteamlana @ ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LanaDelReyFact You're welcome :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FF @LoveLanaDelRey @Hileeery @AlanahDelRey @PrincesssDie @Pressparty @Lipsytweet @Liv_Alva @lanadelbabe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FF @LanaDelReyWorld @LanaDReyOnline @LanaDReyINDO @The_LanaDelRey @DelReyLane @LanaDelReyFan @LanaDelReyBR @LanaDelReyUK @LanaDelReyFact]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I won't cry myself to sleep like a sucker. If I do I'll die. Now you fall asleep with another, Damn you." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I pretend I'm not hurt, I walk about the world like I'm having fun." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sierrapritta: @LanaQuote "..and I was hoping that I would meet people &amp; fall in love &amp; start a community around me, the way  ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LuckyLanaDelRey: @LanaQuote #LanaDelReyNLucky hiphop/DubStep mp3&gt; http://t.co/h6d0YFTC  / video&gt; http://t.co/XoHZfgMY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Everything I want I have, Money, notoriety and rivieras. I even think I found God in the flash bulbs of the pretty cameras" —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ValmirTahiri: Sure there were people but alcohol was my first love @LanaDelRey  @LanaDelRey_army  @LanaQuote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Spicylilpepper June 21, 1986. Yes, she's Gemini :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woohoo! 2000 followers! Thanks #TeamLana :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You fit me better than my favourite sweater." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Spicylilpepper: @LanaQuote I knew it! So #deep, layered, &amp; much 2 read between the lines. #Love all the vids &amp; lyrics! #Bril ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Spicylilpepper Thank you so much :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Money is the anthem of success. So put on mascara, and your party dress." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Cause baby we were born to live fast and die young. Born to be bad, have fun." — Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["For me New York was a match. To lose it, it really felt like my life was over.” —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heaven is a place on earth with you. Tell me all the things you want to do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I was a secret thrill-seeker. I was putting my feelers out all over the city, in different places with different people." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Born To Die: Paradise Edition out 12th November (UK) &amp; 13th November (US). RT if you can't wait for this! http://t.co/4bQRZ1lR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Forget your enemies, but never forget their names." —Lana Del Rey]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>