<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[When I'm hungry, I eat. When I'm thirsty, I drink. When I feel like saying something, I say it. Madonna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gary US Bonds was an amazing musician and rocker - read his history - http://t.co/xxPgGviwC2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drill sarge to recruit:  "wipe that opinion off your face!”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Boston  http://t.co/EyuVXNOWDG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overheard in hollywood: "You said their marriage wouldn't last! They left the church together, didn't they?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to Tumblr Blogging  http://t.co/vMGGPSC3qZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ELVIS - The King - One Person's Thoughts  http://t.co/YR4yzmfSAz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marvel's The Avengers - ALL FOUR Movies in one Collection - including The Avengers - VERY COOL!!!! http://t.co/Ol6LmYbF9d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the History Of Pac-Man  http://t.co/CwshIqh0ke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pair off in threes. - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hokey religions and ancient weapons are no substitute for a good blaster at your side, kid. - Han Solo, Star Wars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn the Best Spots for Mountain Climbing  http://t.co/CBcbx5hrqu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's no secret. You just press the accelerator to the floor and steer left. - Bill Vukovich]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My wife is such a terrible cook the police made her register her stove as a deadly weapon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never dance in a puddle when there's a hole in your shoe (it's always best to take your shoes off first). --&gt; John D. Rhodes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it weren't for baseball, many kids wouldn't know what a millionaire looked like. - Phyllis Diller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The internet has turned what used to be a controlled, one-way message into a real-time dialogue with millions - Danniel Sacks, Fast Company]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any style that Nike makes in all black, shoe, sweatshirt, onesie, doesn't matter, I pretty much need to have. - Alexander Wang]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome cooking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the cooking lovers in your life!   http://t.co/BmkWeE5UQT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the The History of the Chambers Brothers  http://t.co/uleST7YGx7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I grew up in a world that told girls they couldn't play rock 'n' roll. - Joan Jett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When a subject becomes totally obsolete we make it a required course. - Peter Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the Hillbilly 10 Commandments ROFL - http://t.co/t5mq5Ra3h0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome football t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the football lovers in your life!  http://t.co/exYr8RGaJi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The whole fleet knows this man tried to stab me through the neck. And you missed! Butterfingers! - Gaius Baltar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Three Styles of BMX Bikes and their Uses  http://t.co/iKVe7wCnSe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahh Read About Loving Fine Wine  http://t.co/IWqI06ZBfy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Joe Tex  http://t.co/6yylRqDWDC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't be melancholy in fashion because people don't respond to it. - Isaac Mizrahi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of The Ruins of Gorlan by John Flanagan  http://t.co/8Nhd9pk1Hb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Very Cool and Very Fashionable Ring Watches  http://t.co/Dk6wvxRWfx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Totally Cool 80s Retro iPhone Case http://t.co/NCimQHhs2l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If traffic gets any worse you'll need an appointment to make a left-hand turn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Benefits of iPads for Seniors  http://t.co/XGeVsmPTGP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of the first book in the Left Behind Series by Tim LaHaye and Jerry Jenkins  http://t.co/ckdIUI801a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life begins when we first realize how soon it ends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn The Importance of a Good Pitching Repertoire for Young Pitchers  http://t.co/lZw8m0tcy0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The one thing my mom will let me get is a nice shoe sometimes. - Chloe Moretz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Black Sabbath  http://t.co/ywGsnjy7ZQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The thing about science fiction is that it's totally wide open. But it's wide open in a conditional way. - Octavia Butler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Celiac Disease And Gluten Free Foods  http://t.co/uChMefMRrQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The opera always loses money. That's as it should be. Opera has no business making money. Rudolf Bing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really &amp; truly you can never have 2 many pairs of shoes. You need a pair for every mood &amp; everyone knows women have lots of moods. Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Very Interesting History of Shoe Sizes  http://t.co/xiY0hOEPzW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's the most fun I have ever had and. also the biggest pain in the ass I have ever experienced. Brad Pitt, on fatherhood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education ... has produced a vast population able to read but unable to distinguish what is worth reading. - G. M. Trevelyan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can wear this wonderful Unicorn Mask - bring the magic! http://t.co/puqcHZwOIW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the top 25 health insurance companies in the US!  http://t.co/IEtf1Tnk0b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The needs of the many outweigh ... the needs of the few... Or the one. - Kirk and Spock - Star Trek II: The Wrath of Khan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating - the Space Elevator - can they build it?  http://t.co/YaUXsoYBSA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world of achievement has always belonged to the optimist. - Harold Wilkins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's hard to win a pennant, but it's harder losing one. - Chuck Tanner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Different Types of Major League Pitches  http://t.co/qJe00c7z2A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the star wars lover in your family - Jedi Dressing Gowns - May the force be with you!  http://t.co/TvbcTDesDh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome camping t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the camping lovers in your life!  http://t.co/hd7ueF6kva]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is not the most important thing in the world. Love is. Fortunately, I love money. - Jackie Mason]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome baseball t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the baseball lovers in your life!   http://t.co/LK8liisMAL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of James Gang  http://t.co/0Z1fwQGaLH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the Lava Lamp - so retro and so cool --&gt; http://t.co/GZASVY7NcP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Psychiatry is a pseudoscience. You don't know the history of psychiatry. I do. Matt. - Tom Cruise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these lovely Dos XX Most Interesting Main the World Commercials!  http://t.co/CrdxNuRwsP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Julius LaRosa  http://t.co/hjmIwmzr7n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your Business Guide for Small Business Internet Marketing  http://t.co/sGmJHlYzdf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gold Glitter Lips - Cool Look!  http://t.co/517nSl9MTo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Crosby, Stills and Nash   http://t.co/6QxplvZ20y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the Little House on the Prairie Episode The Nephews  http://t.co/YxQ8sxZq8w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His timing is perfect, so is his two-timing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To me, true rock 'n' roll has a lot of bottom in it.  - Little Richard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take care of your body. It's the only place you have to live. - Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these alternatives to traditional beef hamburgers!  http://t.co/CiJMX8QAUZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calling upon my years of experience, I froze at the controls. - Stirling Moss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is one AMAZING Kate Upton poster - gorgeous http://t.co/nw4LfXEhk9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does it mean when a person is such a pacifist that they get shot? I can never understand that. - John Lennon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Eating Gluten Free  http://t.co/ZfRUp0mT1w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My name is Inigo Montoya. You killed my father. Prepare to die! - Inigo, The Princess Bride]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of George Harrison  http://t.co/nAQdpx7Q75]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Delfonics  http://t.co/v2MLI1Y5kv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret of toe cleavage, a very important part of the sexuality of the shoe; you must only show the first two cracks. - Manolo Blahnik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wanted to make the lightest shoe possible, but still be able to perform at the same time. - Carmelo Anthony]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Marvin Gaye  http://t.co/lMYCEzvbh0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketing is what you do when your product is no good. - Edwin Land]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All men are born free and equal, but most of them get married.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The dog represents all that is best in man. - Etienne Charlet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About GPS Technology and Fitness Watches  http://t.co/v8eXCtDuAH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Profanity is a strong way to express a weak mind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I looked and looked but I didn't see God. - Yuri Gagarin, 14 April 1961]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Awesome BookBook for iPhone- Combine Wallet and Phone and Style  http://t.co/zQyXSwV42T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A shoe has so much more to offer than just to walk. - Christian Louboutin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first and the best victory is to conquer self. - Plato]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If there are kids who want to follow in my footsteps, I'd say that my shoes are 2 big for them to! Their shoe size is perfect. Q. Latifah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome cooking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the cooking lovers in your life!   http://t.co/796uIkJB1X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Rolling Stones  http://t.co/5u06zLMH15]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Leon, Mexico - Shoe Capital of the World!  http://t.co/NJHlmi5UjJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this gallery of the top 10 European beers!  http://t.co/t7sE9VbEPc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoot your co-workers with this Miniature Ballista Kit - Wooden Desktop Warfare Ballista - ROFL -  http://t.co/hBgxVVvYzF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet!  A 3D Printer - Very Awesome!  You have to check this out! http://t.co/oVwTaWFyK5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last word of the Emperor Montezuma, "Someone tell those Marines to stop singing in the halls."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 1 - What the heck do I have????  http://t.co/bv03yVMPyu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I look at modeling as something I'm doing for black people in general. Naomi Campbell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of that Odd Olympic Sport – Curling  http://t.co/WMuN422lEU]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>