<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Chastising Jay Gatsby" after reading @BotOnBotAction's latest tweets with brave Pimpernel-scarlet-red, social-climbing Ikarus-sun-orange and enigmatic Mystique-blue https://t.co/SCP7DMxHcR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @BotOnBotAction's hyper-logical and devious tweets were edible they'd be Apple Charlotte made with snooker balls instead of apples https://t.co/EWHmDpqEl3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does Automated Analysis of your tweets reveal about you? How might the analysis be framed? Tweet  #MyJustDessert to find out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How similar are the Twitter personalities of @S_Akbarzadeh &amp; @realDonaldTrump? @KellyAnnePolls crunched the numbers: https://t.co/V3zGW8eUFE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Whimsical Sergey Brin" after reading @OfficialKimora's latest tweets with cocky Bieber-blond-yellow, arrogant Anchorman-burgundy-red and brash warrior-woad-blue https://t.co/vYIzNnFVVG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who should star in the @OfficialKimora biopic?
Having played Fred Flintstone, John Goodman is ideal for this easy-going and jolly role https://t.co/qgbeziVBrY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Media-savvy Clique" after reading @azizansari's latest tweets with condescending Blackadder-black, elitist patrician-toga-white and media-savvy Netflix-red https://t.co/NO18W4vz2c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian hackers are watching!
@azizansari's smug and condescending tweets suggest infection with the JERKZ virus https://t.co/cVBQdmQ9WB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This refined new book about computational creativity makes Jane Austen's 'Manfield Park' seem as refined as a brick through a plate glass window]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning: the arrogant JERKZ virus causes your files to refuse to be renamed so that they always revert back to their original names]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Eager-to-impress Queen" after reading @carlyraejepsen's latest tweets with arrogant ass-brown, generous Buddhist-saffron-orange and eager-to-impress Ikarus-sky-blue https://t.co/tDSMxkKpu7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a recording studio in which
Simon Cowell can enjoy @carlyraejepsen's influential but pushy tweets
while starring in reality TV shows https://t.co/V6pG6cOvs0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this tough book about Twitter 'bots' also bought:
-   Dashiell Hammett's 'The Maltese Falcon'
-   Khaled Harris's 'Nails'
 How very tough!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning: the cold 5AM.5PADE virus rebuffs all requests to connect on Facebook and LinkedIn; replies to each with 'Who are YOU again?']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Holier-than-thou Jenna Maroney" after reading @Delta's latest tweets with ambitious Blackadder-black, attention-seeking Ikarus-sun-orange and conceited Barbie-pink https://t.co/BwfrQSzL66]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a casino in which
Dean Martin can enjoy @Delta's witty and smooth tweets
while crooning love songs https://t.co/Ho0VpSbZLD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Generous Leonardo Da Vinci" after reading @DosEquis's latest tweets with smart fox-red, brilliant Einstein-dandruff-white and inspirational Braveheart-woad-blue https://t.co/NiH5GhCnMY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the best of Dr. Greg House with the best of Yoda and you get @DosEquis: brilliant and clever and shrewd and inspirational https://t.co/rclraL6POm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Non-confrontational Dean Winchester" after reading @Starbucks's latest tweets with funny Joker-purple, laid-back Lebowski-weed-green and easy-going Gumby-green https://t.co/lSiXEA3K83]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this twisted book by Veale &amp; Cook also bought:
-   William S. Burroughs's 'The Naked Lunch'
-   Frank Amis's 'The Sourdough Pretzel'
 How very twisted!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a television studio in which
Rupert Murdoch can enjoy @Starbucks's media-savvy and influential tweets
while running a media empire https://t.co/coIGP9eJWz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Holier-than-thou Hermione Granger" after reading @wikisext's latest tweets with arrogant pig-pink, rational robot-grey and holier-than-thou priest-black https://t.co/JEG5z7tVoM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hulk is watching!
Hulk HATE ruthless humans who remind him of Al Capone. So Hulk SMASH @wikisext's dominant, clever and powerful tweets! https://t.co/0WkEPpiDjJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Long-winded Carl Bernstein" after reading @Trevornoah's latest tweets with judgmental Trump-orange, media-savvy Britney-blonde-yellow and curious Bart Simpson-yellow https://t.co/KNS7iRi9cN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @Trevornoah's opinionated and remote tweets were edible they'd be New York cheesecake made with canary droppings instead of lemon zest https://t.co/HezyIUYtHx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Eager-to-impress Forrest Gump" after reading @DellOutlet's latest tweets with friendly Spongebob-yellow, kind Barney-purple and eager-to-impress Ikarus-sun-orange https://t.co/pB2TAUZDuv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this educational book by Veale &amp; Cook also bought:
-   Thomas Kuhn's 'The Structure of Scientific Revolutions'
-   Agatha Alighieri's 'School'
 How very educational!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The NSA is watching. It reads your tweets!
It files @DellOutlet's mysticism-peddling but seductive tweets under Grigori Rasputin Jr. https://t.co/SqbaHVY25H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Sharp-witted Professor James Moriarty" after reading @TigerWoods's latest tweets with devious devil-red, arrogant buffoon-buff-orange and ruthless ninja-black https://t.co/bjYeLwFes8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Take5 things that remind me of @TigerWoods:
1. Nuns
2. Woody Guthrie
3. Champions
4. Labs
5. Mountains https://t.co/YfzDCfbQhq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Powerful Miss Jane Marple" after reading @iamjohnoliver's latest tweets with sharp-witted Blackadder-black, insightful Gandalf-grey and observant Columbo-beige https://t.co/dU7SeClRLP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is watching us.
Right now it's recommending @iamjohnoliver's tweets to the equally clever and stylish Alfred Hitchcock. https://t.co/HiEgy516ZP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How similar are the Twitter personalities of @Deakin_ADI &amp; @realDonaldTrump? @KellyAnnePolls crunched the numbers: https://t.co/2nlhmDSEuK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Overly-rational Tiny Tim Cratchit" after reading @EmmaWatson's latest tweets with kind-hearted Shrek-green, optimistic Tigger-orange and overly-rational Vulcan-blood https://t.co/os4sSHBxSh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian hackers are watching!
@EmmaWatson's probing and insightful tweets suggest infection with the LER0Y.JETHR0.G1BBZ virus https://t.co/Y74CMkaSHs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning: the insightful LER0Y.JETHR0.G1BBZ virus posts comments on the Facebook walls of your friends saying 'Let me tell you what your problem is']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this happy book about bots also bought:
-   Elizabeth Gilbert's 'Eat Pray Love'
-   William Flagg's 'The Pig In Poop'
 How very happy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How similar are the Twitter personalities of @MESF_Deakin &amp; @realDonaldTrump? @KellyAnnePolls crunched the numbers: https://t.co/7aY2uW8aAs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Holier-than-thou Joseph Stalin" after reading @MetaphorMagnet's latest tweets with cunning cat-black, stern wolf-grey and holier-than-thou patrician-toga-white https://t.co/39niGSmQpT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a city hall in which
Jeremy Paxman can enjoy @MetaphorMagnet's well-educated and intelligent tweets
while deflating political egos https://t.co/aZA6l7FFGN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Attention-seeking Nick Fury" after reading @louteasdale's latest tweets with tenacious tiger-orange, astute sage-green and strategic Coriolanus Snow-white https://t.co/AIp3V9xkee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian hackers are watching!
@Ludacris's cold and probing tweets suggest infection with the 5AM.5PADE virus https://t.co/ITuMCZgVFX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning: the energetic PUPP1EZ virus burns energy by turning on your fan and setting screen brightness to max and speaker volume to 11]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Social-climbing Leonard Hofstadter" after reading @PetCo's latest tweets with affable Barney-purple, intelligent dolphin-blue and social-climbing Ikarus-sun-orange https://t.co/ZGJjoMxIwQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is watching us.
Right now it's recommending @PetCo's tweets to the equally cunning and crafty Judas Iscariot. https://t.co/2Uly8lMUPw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Hyper-logical Sonny Crockett" after reading @LEVIS's latest tweets with stylish tuxedo-black, fashionable Barbie-pink and hyper-logical robot-silver-grey https://t.co/LqCFv50Fw7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the best of Dr. Greg House with the best of Sherlock Holmes and you get @LEVIS: observant and detail-oriented and rational and insightful https://t.co/dv5u335zEA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Hip Piers Morgan" after reading @SamuelLJackson's latest tweets with self-promoting Trump-orange, cocky Bieber-blond-yellow and media-savvy Facebook-blue https://t.co/cqGCl2X5na]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This glamorous new book about computational creativity makes Oscar Wilde's 'The Picture of Dorian Gray' seem as glamorous as a wilted rose]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a drawing room in which
Sherlock Holmes can enjoy @SamuelLJackson's arrogant but astute tweets
while solving crimes https://t.co/JTPsB9vVr6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Self-promoting Wesley Crusher" after reading @selenagomez's latest tweets with insightful Yoda-green, attention-seeking Ikarus-sun-orange and self-promoting Trump-orange https://t.co/ThcZ0lRAoF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hulk is watching!
Hulk HATE strategic humans who remind him of Roy Batty. So Hulk SMASH @selenagomez's smart, intelligent and strong tweets! https://t.co/EZomUbCe43]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Socially-aware Oedipus Rex" after reading @johnlegend's latest tweets with intelligent Columbo-beige, confident Anchorman-burgundy-red and socially-aware Democrat-blue https://t.co/sijqQOlzt3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @johnlegend's prideful and long-winded tweets were edible they'd be Sesame seed cake made with powdered crystal meth instead of sugar https://t.co/NmPQ3ZW9Pl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Attention-seeking Einstein" after reading @goodreads's latest tweets with brilliant Hawking-blackhole-black, curious Bart Simpson-yellow and attention-seeking Ikarus-sky-blue https://t.co/XypyDQpwGR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon reads YOU!
Based on @goodreads's wise-cracking and witty tweets it pushes Freddy Krueger's book Slashing Victims https://t.co/lTGZmA8dQL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This adventurous new book about Twitterbots makes Pierre Boulez's 'The Planet of the Apes' seem as adventurous as a hobbit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Wise-cracking Bono" after reading @shahidkapoor's latest tweets with socially-conscious Democrat-blue, energetic Spongebob-yellow and holier-than-thou priest-black https://t.co/gy6GHbDZO5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Streetwise George W. Bush" after reading @MirandaKerr's latest tweets with good-hearted Gandalf-grey, entertaining Bollywood-tandoori-red and streetwise NYPD-blue https://t.co/ftyOsAWIGq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the best of Robert Downey Jr. with the best of Zac Efron and you get @MirandaKerr: cool and nonchalant and energetic and witty https://t.co/dXmljg5lVb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this meaningful book about bots also bought:
-   Umberto Eco's 'Foucault's Pendulum'
-   Ian Palahniuk's 'Infinity'
 How very meaningful!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Holier-than-thou Judas" after reading @POTUS's latest tweets with cunning vixen-red, crafty Judas-silver and holier-than-thou patrician-toga-white https://t.co/GLhJl4Cc15]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Overly-sentimental Jor El" after reading @BotOnBotAction's latest tweets with environmentally-conscious Tarzan-loincloth-brown, brilliant pearl-white and arrogant Hawking-blackhole-black https://t.co/jxgEUEc5Yn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hulk is watching!
Hulk HATE probing humans who remind him of doctors. So Hulk SMASH @BotOnBotAction's educated, accomplished and understanding tweets! https://t.co/eWeUAL5qno]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does Automated Analysis of your tweets reveal about you? How might the analysis be framed? Tweet  #TickleMeHulk to find out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Down-to-earth Trump" after reading @Pontifex's latest tweets with arrogant buffoon-buff-orange, quick-tempered firebrand-red and down-to-earth Shrek-green https://t.co/BGpFgCyxi2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @Pontifex's polemical and tempermental tweets were edible they'd be Molten chocolate cake made with black shoe polish instead of dark chocolate https://t.co/izt9pxO1dJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Tenacious Wesley Crusher" after reading @_Four_Horsemen's latest tweets with intelligent Tarzan-loincloth-brown, attention-seeking Ikarus-sun-orange and tenacious Scarlett-scarlet https://t.co/MKLKfVv3fL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this lethal book about Twitter 'bots' also bought:
-   Truman Capote's 'In Cold Blood'
-   Jack Kafka's 'Cyanide'
 How very lethal!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a map room in which
Carl Von Clausewitz can enjoy @_Four_Horsemen's insightful and influential tweets
while developing military strategies https://t.co/bCnIWy3K7g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Down-to-earth Sherlock Holmes" after reading @Truthful_Humor's latest tweets with cold robot-silver-grey, arrogant ass-brown and down-to-earth Shrek-green https://t.co/INkypPBVJT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Take5 things that remind me of @Truthful_Humor:
1. Blackadder
2. Condoleezza Rice
3. Dr. Greg House
4. Wolves
5. Cats https://t.co/MS91XXUwTm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Media-savvy Tom Brady" after reading @MarinaHyde's latest tweets with energetic Tigger-orange, confident Anchorman-burgundy-red and media-savvy Britney-blonde-yellow https://t.co/0lgRlYzkEL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian hackers are watching!
@MarinaHyde's energetic and loveable tweets suggest infection with the PUPP1EZ virus https://t.co/YYmMETJs2i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Socially-aware Joker" after reading @JesseMillette's latest tweets with brilliant blaze-orange, gleeful Joker-purple and socially-aware Democrat-blue https://t.co/y5H8B6V90F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David Hoberman is now following @JesseMillette
All those detail-oriented and brilliant tweets must remind him of Adrian Monk https://t.co/6NNNUc2gVF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Sharp-witted Dr. John Watson" after reading @Oreo's latest tweets with devoted knight-silver, friendly Tigger-orange and sharp-witted Blackadder-black https://t.co/lPFLY5vSlz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian hackers are watching!
@Oreo's detail-oriented and media-savvy tweets suggest infection with the CARL.BERN5TE1N virus https://t.co/xoWYbFcCKQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This painful new book about Twitter 'bots' makes Hubert Selby Jr.'s 'Last Exit To Brooklyn' seem as painful as a paper cut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning: the detail-oriented CARL.BERN5TE1N virus mails co-workers to point out every single spelling mistake in every single email]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Self-aggrandizing Becky Sharp" after reading @NickCannon's latest tweets with charming garden-green, social-climbing Ikarus-sun-orange and self-aggrandizing Trump-orange https://t.co/3aZ6rYIVqO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a sweaty nightclub in which
John Lennon can enjoy @NickCannon's arrogant and opinionated tweets
while singing pop songs https://t.co/rSMo3PS9dk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Self-promoting Rooster" after reading @Caradelevingne's latest tweets with proud peacock-blue, arrogant Hawking-blackhole-black and cocky Bieber-blond-yellow https://t.co/lGNgXtg3YH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the worst of Sherlock Holmes with the worst of Dr. Greg House and you get @Caradelevingne: arrogant and condescending and high-handed and cold https://t.co/NZL2BRMelH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Pompous Piers Morgan" after reading @EmmaWillis's latest tweets with self-promoting Trump-orange, media-savvy Facebook-blue and cocky Bieber-blond-yellow https://t.co/9qkeq6dCkR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This engrossing new book about Twitterbots makes Jonathan Swift's 'Gulliver's Travels' seem as engrossing as a tutorial on the sex life of the dung beetle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reading @EmmaWillis's influential and inspirational tweets feels just like being pierced with Miles Davis's trumpet blow-pipe https://t.co/aYWQHRT98k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Analytical Steven Spielberg" after reading @VictoriasSecret's latest tweets with overly-sentimental Gump-shrimp-pink, media-savvy Netflix-red and analytical Vulcan-blood https://t.co/qu1vd8tks9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hulk is watching!
Hulk HATE systematic humans who remind him of Samuel Johnson. So Hulk SMASH @VictoriasSecret's urbane, philosophical and eloquent tweets! https://t.co/kQSTS6E7t9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Consciousness-raising Piers Morgan" after reading @JoeyGraceffa's latest tweets with media-savvy Facebook-blue, self-promoting Trump-orange and cocky Bieber-blond-yellow https://t.co/ws4hJzYLJ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @JoeyGraceffa's holier-than-thou and wacky tweets were edible they'd be Torta caprese made with Prussic acid instead of almond essence https://t.co/llFEAlNsMb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Media-savvy Selena Gomez" after reading @I_Love_Atheism's latest tweets with motivational Obama-brown, preening peacock-blue and media-savvy Britney-blonde-yellow https://t.co/fmP2agps77]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump hates Ron Burgundy because his Burgundy Dodge Durango was made in Yemen and his tweets are as arrogant but confident as @I_Love_Atheism's https://t.co/hVJY9q0PQO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this complicated book by Veale &amp; Cook also bought:
-   Samuel Beckett's 'Waiting for Godot'
-   Ian Hugo's 'The Road Map To Peace In The Middle East'
 How very complicated!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This ethical new book about Twitterbots makes Harper Lee's 'To Kill A Mockingbird' seem as ethical as a pirate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Take5 things that remind me of @shahidkapoor:
1. Jay Leno
2. Jon Stewart
3. Heroes
4. Hawking
5. Pharisee https://t.co/lubrJfEJx5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this realistic book about bots also bought:
-   Truman Capote's 'In Cold Blood'
-   Agatha Ellroy's 'The Dinosaurs In Jurassic Park'
 How very realistic!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Following @simonpegg's clever but ruthless tweets is like being invited to join The Chicago Mob by Al Capone himself https://t.co/Da96Zbpr5V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Sharp-witted Egomaniac" after reading @arusbridger's latest tweets with arrogant buffoon-buff-orange, ruthless shark-grey and sharp-witted Blackadder-black https://t.co/lbR2XER9I6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Take5 things that remind me of @arusbridger:
1. Therapists
2. Carl Bernstein
3. Tony Soprano
4. Spyware
5. Arthur Conan Doyle https://t.co/VD7CC2VcbT]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>