<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LifeLimits: Sometimes you gotta create what you want to be a part of.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the secrets of life is that all that is really worth the doing is what we do for others. -Levi Strauss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FaithReeI: https://t.co/LVT9R0lqxg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You cannot always wait for the perfect time. Sometimes you must dare to jump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Faith consists in believing when it is beyond the power of reason to believe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the right light, at the right time, everything is extraordinary. - Aaron Rose]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AmazingiGrace: The Lord's word is pure - Psalm 18:30.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is the wealthy man's curtain which hides all his defects from the world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We make a living by what we get, we make a life by what we give. - Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live in the moment. Forget the past and don't concern yourself with the future.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LovLikeJesus: God enters by a private door into each individual.  -Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every scar has a story. Don't be afraid to tell it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If your happiness depends on what somebody else does, I guess you do have a problem. - Richard Bach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strength is when you have so much to cry for but you prefer to smile instead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't cheat the world of your contribution. Give it what you've got. -Steven Pressfield]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you truly believe in what you are doing, it shows. And it pays. Winners in life are those who are excited about where they're going.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All a girl really wants is for one guy to prove to her that they are not all the same. -Marilyn Monroe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you can't be thankful for what you have, be thankful for what you've escaped.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That would be a great trick :) https://t.co/NMMbR7BDCl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lnspireMeNow: Learn from it. https://t.co/P46CRBfgOe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I always like to look on the optimistic side of life, but I am realistic enough to know that life is a complex matter. - Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adversity causes some men to break, and others to break records. -Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stars can't shine without darkness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LifeLimits: Is your beard long enough? :)

Get your tee here --&gt; https://t.co/0hklPaOaH5 https://t.co/5T7w1rVRLO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FaithReeI: https://t.co/CQrH0ys3Fp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[forgive others not because they deserve it but because you deserve peace. https://t.co/Lins6Auqub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are made to make a difference, so embrace every opportunity to do so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surround yourself with positive people who will support you when it rains, not just when it shines.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @desire_lnspire: Be brave https://t.co/XHKP7pYVkN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You cannot escape the responsibility of tomorrow by evading it today. -Abraham Lincoln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God can turn around any situation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't be afraid to go out on a limb. That's where the fruit is. - H. Jackson Browne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great thought. https://t.co/Z2WueNae5q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Knowing is not enough; we must apply. Wishing is not enough; we must do. -Johann Von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AmazingiGrace: Worry about nothing, pray about everything. https://t.co/t9RxNhN1zr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can you relate? https://t.co/WDrwHIzfk1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If someone wants you, nothing will keep them away, but if they don't want you, nothing will make them stay!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it wasn't hard, everyone would do it. It's the hard that makes it great. -Tom Hanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We can't become what we need to be by remaining what we are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn to give without any reason.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The moment you're ready to quit is usually the moment right before the miracle happens.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smile, even if it's fake. Laugh, even if you hurt. Don't let anyone get to you, you're beautiful regardless of what anyone says to you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sports_grit: Accept responsibility for the good and the bad. https://t.co/LRSCEk1ibe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Without the dark, we'd never see the stars.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FaithReeI: https://t.co/gMpAR5W7uF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you Robin. https://t.co/vgnnynU4dx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The less you know, the more you believe. -Bono]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheDaiIyPuppy: Sounds like a time well spent :)

Get this tee here --&gt; https://t.co/CRjV6mY4zL https://t.co/RCAnhTbGx6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You never lose by loving. You only lose by holding back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Age is no guarantee of maturity. -Lawana Blackwell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lnspiredLife: Go after your dreams. https://t.co/u8Yzw7MfPR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Behind me is infinite power, before me is endless possibility, around me is boundless opportunity. - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even fools seem smart when they are quiet. -Proverbs 17:28]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reality is a product of our dreams, decisions &amp; actions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lnspiredLife: So true!!! https://t.co/each2zUeuz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We cannot become what we need to be by remaining what we are. -Max De Pree]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The richest man is not he who has the most, but he who needs the least. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God's plan is bigger than your mistakes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be strong https://t.co/ShDWmK4cgF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laugh your heart out, dance in the rain, cherish the moment, live, laugh, love, forgive &amp; forget, life's 2 short 2 be, living w/ regrets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes courage to grow up and become who you really are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sometimes the smallest things take up the most room in your heart. -Winnie the Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you can't do great big things, do great little things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I began learning long ago that those who are happiest are those who do the most for others. - Booker T. Washington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Danger 4 most of us lies not in setting our aim too high &amp; falling short; but in setting our aim 2 low &amp;achieving our mark. -Michaelangelo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AthletesWhoPray: Give all the glory to God. https://t.co/d9rpdKsPE7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The mind is everything; what you think, you become.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[May you always do what you are afraid to do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking back, makes you smart. 
Looking forward, makes you mature. 
Looking down, makes you wise. 
Looking UP, makes you strong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FaithReeI: https://t.co/jUzOUSqyvv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're going through hell, keep going. -Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So true!!! https://t.co/k5CccGhyzt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Accept no one's definition of your life; define yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do what you feel in your heart to be right - for you'll be criticized anyway. -Eleanor Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Inspire_Us: Fall seven times, stand up eight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thankfulness is the beginning of happiness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pick wisely. https://t.co/UjJFLTlQ2h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It isn't sufficient just to want - you've got to ask yourself what you are going to do to get the things you want. - Richard D. Rosen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In all your ways acknowledge him, &amp; he will make your paths straight. -Proverbs 3:6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lnspiredLife: We all fall, pick yourself up and start a new. https://t.co/9fD5d5Zc0P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One small positive thought in the morning can change your whole day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't dream your life, live your dreams. https://t.co/km0ZvvYK5d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes God calms the storm, but sometimes God lets the storm rage and calms his child.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are blessed. https://t.co/Uqo53C8CTe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Talking to your BEST FRIEND is sometimes all the therapy you need...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love conquers all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Above all else, guard your heart, for it is the wellspring of life. -Proverbs 4:23]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @The_Gospels: Have you subscribed yet to our daily emails? Visit -&gt; https://t.co/1qRf0GTTd3 &amp; signup https://t.co/cXjJVXv7Ss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No act of kindness, no matter how small is ever wasted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep smiling :) https://t.co/rR2UorzofN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Inspire_Us: Don't ever let anyone steal your dreams.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is to short to spend it with the wrong people. https://t.co/3Ife1onTZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we really want to love we must learn how to forgive. -Mother Teresa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes good things fall apart so better things can fall together.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LifeLimits: Perfect November :)

Get your tee here --&gt; https://t.co/ed9vrG8VsC https://t.co/6nuXvSfzvC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anything I've done that was ultimately worthwhile initially scared me to death. -Betty Bender]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today is another chance to get it right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FamousWomen: The most precious possession that ever comes to a man in this world is a woman's heart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's hard to beat a person who never gives up. -Babe Ruth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AthletesWhoPray: The most rewarding things you do in life are often the ones that look like they cannot be done. -Arnold Palmer]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>