<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Nick_Pettigrew: (Burns house to the ground)
"We urgently need to build a house." https://t.co/8dt9RyzTSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @fiwhitehead: Have you heard? We want YOU to join us 4-8 July for @GA_London epic Launch Week. Book here https://t.co/RbOtyGM7ik https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple UX Goes Full Dadcore https://t.co/Gfs34z4JxS – the gradual shift of Apple away from being cool]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ha! Screenwriters couldn't write better lines. https://t.co/tXON25wgOq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mrjamesob: Farage will be back. Not as quickly as last time but he needs to distance himself from the reality of Brexit so he can claim…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Virgin Atlantic just used behavioral science to ‘nudge’ its pilots into using less fuel. It worked https://t.co/TpAi0HVtzS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Diary Studies: Understanding Long-Term User Behavior and Experiences https://t.co/ZIKrjPLQWW #ux]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ajacko I drop into one or two. Was at Product Tank last week. Will be around General Assembly a fair bit the net couple of weeks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Evidence-Based UX Design Guide to Guerrilla User Testing https://t.co/ssbngV99XE https://t.co/TIM5ZWtYhl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ajacko Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HetanShah: This is interesting (and disturbing) in @newscientist on the rise of partisan Twitter bots influencing elections https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jimwaterson: Telegraph deletes article critical of Theresa May. Claims her campaign team put pressure on them. https://t.co/avMv31XSNj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Carols10cents: 1998:
- Don't get in strangers' cars
- Don't meet ppl from internet

2016:
- Literally summon strangers from internet to…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BetaRish Don't worry Gove's got it covered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@crowemail Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Elements of Stickers https://t.co/WGUZb4CIju – how emoji/stickers are so much more powerful than words https://t.co/h3GMoKGntE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gavinjcooke Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Brand Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great advice... An Open Letter To Speakers https://t.co/1qQypkWidy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SByrneFraser: Actual action people can take to make the best of the current situation. Nicely put mate. https://t.co/frEqXL2oMa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Evidence-Based UX Design Guide to Net Promoter Score https://t.co/zupjJFL5xW https://t.co/oB4Ou21tAd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mediaguardian: Rejected remain campaign posters revealed by ad agencies https://t.co/iK29cdDtA9 https://t.co/kmjTz4Clet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tbrbignite Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pearlenesqm86 Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Portugal, out to prove you don't really need to win football matches in tournaments.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating/depressing, and what the left need to learn: ‘facts don’t work’ https://t.co/QFr1DDcYuq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Evidence-Based UX Design Guide to Competitor Analysis https://t.co/hg9ZdLWcCc https://t.co/Mo96ImEfVv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Matt_Muir: As the UK splashes messily in its own effluent, Soundcloud recruits a Michelin-starred chef to cook for dogs https://t.co/vN…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trust the folks of the internet will do the right thing here https://t.co/Zy7PoTZ7Ye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Design Thinking 101 https://t.co/5jWfCo02l3 https://t.co/ANCrpRTid6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Glinner: there's dumb and then there's extravangantly dumb https://t.co/vY8Kpxx40Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Colvinius: Locked in. Trump’s campaign won’t let supporters cancel recurring donations. 
  https://t.co/p93pJngiYT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Audacity of Copying Well https://t.co/KGQ3BI0xrc – good stuff on Instagram's attempt to copy Snapchat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DavidAllenGreen: Brexit problems caused by those who warned against Brexit.

Perhaps the daftest editorial ever written... https://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nancyja_in Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @bengoldacre: This is interesting on grandiosity, language, control, community. You cannot unilaterally change a sign's meaning.  https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jacksonhull: looking for an iOS dev to build a breakout product! If you are in Lon, avail and a hustler, DM me cc @NSLondonMeetup #iOS…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @StevePeers: Indeed, it's one of the finest cases of poetic justice in human history https://t.co/YkI4jupx6J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ClickHole: Get Ready To Feel Goosebumps: Here Is The Epic New Olympic Anthem
https://t.co/85JiROvycy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Evidence-Based UX Design Guide to Conversion Funnels https://t.co/pfSLXGcivi – what to do + watch out for https://t.co/olxg9D1pvR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jjcrees Ha! https://t.co/GRSxEnBYtZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shauns_uk Maybe they want us to be desperate to embrace drones! Wonder how many times they'll come back...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Each day they come at a random time and don't tell you when either. Regularly takes 3 attempts to get something. Seems v.inefficient.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...rather than offer options like other co's of picking up from post office/corner shop/organising a delivery time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Constantly surprised by how crude Amazon's delivery service is. If you're not in they just keep coming back the next day...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Londonislovinit Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TEKmawhinney Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@panzopan Called into Farage's show yet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips for designing bespoke, curated ecommerce sites https://t.co/3ptafcz66U https://t.co/FvlOstGwHF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, you can quit your job today https://t.co/P9ssxpeVYH – always good to remember]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The story of the football team vs the dog track in Wimbledon https://t.co/y36h56S4rW https://t.co/CXgYqVwEBN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TangieHitz Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfpGcR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Scriblit: Not Disgraced Minister Liam Fox! https://t.co/PdXDOcjcto]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@writingforseo Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IM_Coaching Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Amazing' is pushing it https://t.co/4d609ilXg0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Great Listeners Actually Do https://t.co/aN7bOvo0sf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you still chasing data? Try gathering evidence https://t.co/TYsbStBH4m https://t.co/MEI6DmpsTp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Biggest Threat to Your Success Is the Story You Tell Yourself About Success https://t.co/Y5r7nu41Fn (stop creating narratives)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pop-Ups Vs. Usability, Conversions And Bounce Rates https://t.co/wI1SAiNKgy – good stuff to consider before jumping into pop-ups]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 'legacy' unravels... Bikes, buses and bridges: Boris Johnson’s nine biggest design blunders https://t.co/y6UH5S0IEg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sambrook: Correction - Amazing things we get back if we leave EU - 26/7/2016 https://t.co/emeQA4WXpL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @annadahlstrom: What a load of rubbish. Give both the tool &amp; us a bit more credit than this https://t.co/7ZgM8tZMOs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Daninho58 Give me an email with your username on matt (at) https://t.co/WjF5Lt4kDt and I'll try to take a look tomorrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FootballRamble @kelly_welles How many bottles do you need? #pourhomme #pourfemme https://t.co/LrPGGuUFoV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FootballRamble @Daninho58 Have had this problem with a couple of types of mobile. What device are you using?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@julianatgg43 Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KristiMay_ECOM Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YGA69587263 Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfpGcR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DoctorsComplete Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice to acknowledge when government gets things right... How the UK halved its teenage pregnancy rate https://t.co/osR0pl0y92]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@luciannesoley Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Psychological Benefits of Writing Regularly https://t.co/vKGwgxN8zo https://t.co/Zv9j92MrwL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MainIynks Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sacca: We. Are. All. In. Serious. Trouble.  https://t.co/6KcYWjqwkA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mairenup18 Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SaaSCommunity Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Machine Money and People Money https://t.co/wBksWgnas8 – interesting ideas on the future of the economy/society]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_pratiksha_geek Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@simonmainwaring Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump’s Ghostwriter Tells All https://t.co/L8EUBp9jB5 – worth the long read to understand the myth of Trump the 'good businessman']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JimCampbellTFR: The @FootballRamble can finally announce that we have our first book coming out on October 20th! Pre-order here https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From retail to user experience https://t.co/F8LVg3GUi1 – or the many transferrable skills in the world of work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Four Factors to Consider When Developing Your Startup's Pricing Strategy https://t.co/yCpGO1J46v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Evidence-Based UX Design Guide to Live Chat Transcripts https://t.co/E15Yyu7fcK #ux #research https://t.co/liFSb18ZrI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cracking the best-seller list https://t.co/QPMmmEj3sI (or don't do stuff for the badges)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adamiswriting Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Metrics Versus Experience https://t.co/IwkZc0If1o – good tips to consider when measuring user experience]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mdbrad Soon you'll realise there never was an app—it was in your mind all along!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @electoralreform: "If 'Take Back Control' is to mean anything, we need PR" https://t.co/LfA6E1G9xv Our piece for @HuffPostUKPol on @Caro…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This on 'complexion reduction'—possibly just the current trend of 'no' visual design https://t.co/DEU7RZDKml https://t.co/2Ya7ryB9Iw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarlosPi Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@xwerx Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s NOT the economy, stupid: Brexit as a story of personal values https://t.co/m5tlR25usx (it's the death penalty) https://t.co/McosaTaYJk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@luke__gomez Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Facebook of ecommerce — Benedict Evans https://t.co/Yox9ibEOyR (on the challenge of finding new brands/things to buy)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dannydavies23: Syrian orphan sorry to hear North American childhoods ruined by enjoyable film about ghosts https://t.co/cMk07lohV8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lrntto: New podcast episode: How to be a data-driven UX designer with @ishmatt - https://t.co/a0Z5qRfS2B #uxdesign]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Pokémon Go' Isn't Very Good https://t.co/DQgvs1NgMd vs The Most Addicting App In Years https://t.co/lw7j238Oww https://t.co/0YirsECiYe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nmalinarich: This - by @tomhannen - is one of the most amazing pieces of work I've seen in a long time. Watch on your phone
https://t.c…]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>