<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: FCM's Partners for Climate Protection enables cities to take action against climate change! What's your #CANClimateAction?…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CBCOttawa: The Shaw Centre now evacuated due to this giant sinkhole. Check out the latest: https://t.co/HMM6TxI4fI #ottnews https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@solidplans @LaurentOnline the entire @FCM_online is always happy to help!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @FCM_online team is always happy to help https://t.co/T20iuyr6UF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Mayor_Bowman: Saturday morning participating in @FCM_online Annual Convention. @rbcconvctrewpg #Winnipeg https://t.co/7OPquuv4dp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With @MStoner61 at the #CTJumpstart booth at #FCM2016AC https://t.co/YPYo9be4HG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@solidplans and I at the registration booth #FCM2016AC https://t.co/oE2dHN1bnb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thebig271 and I at the #FCM2016AC registration desk https://t.co/2w6KLTATxy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MINJobs welcome to #FCM2016AC !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attending #FCM2016AC ? don't forget to download the app https://t.co/LmDjfAQ5Vb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #FCM2016AC registration desks open's on-site tomorrow at 10 am.  Stop by to say hello and pick up your badges. https://t.co/ZGmhuwuSVl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @R_Boissonnault: Tomorrow afternoon I will have honour of joining PM @JustinTrudeau as we raise  #Pride Flag on Parliament Hill for 1st…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AndreeLyne_H: Statement by the Prime Minister of Canada on changes to the Ministry #cdnpoli #polcan  https://t.co/g3aADlM2H2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for the warm welcome Winnipeg #FCM2016AC https://t.co/8daSnzPRow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hello Winnipeg. I'm so excited to be here for #FCM2016AC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jyduclos: Glad to meet @RaymondLouie from @FCM_online after a workshop with mayors from major Canadian cities #WPG2016 https://t.co/AV5…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: Through stronger federal-municipal partnerships, cities can help green the economy and improve climate resiliency of #CDNmu…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great @FCM_online initiative! https://t.co/rzwkfG4EQd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: Help your #CDNmuni ensure young Canadians are engaged in local governance! See FCM's youth engagement handbook. https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: Excited to see active recruitment of the municipal voice for #Canada150 celebrations. Sign on to #muni150 today! https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: Find proven sustainability ideas for your #CDNmuni in our new article series: https://t.co/16eHKvF9X3 #FCM_GMF https://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you nominated a Community Leader for #Canada150 yet? Visit https://t.co/URF2bAo0FA for more details]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: Looking forward to receiving nominations from Ottawa as part of the #muni150 nat'l network of local voices! #Canada150 http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MINnews: B.C. makes largest housing investment ever in province's history - https://t.co/zwkK3WacPs #Municipal #Family]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: FCM board member @bpincott joins @jyduclos &amp; @CMHC_ca for a discussion on #CDNmuni solutions as part of the Nat'l Housing S…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TimTierney: .@Regional_Chair of @FCM_online  International Relations committee walks us through the great international work https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jyduclos: Please to meet w/ @FCM_online municipalities to discuss community needs for a Ntl Housing Strategy #letstalkhousing https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jyduclos: Meeting with municipalities on National Housing Strategy. These partners are very important on the #housing issue #letstalkho…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @luce_lavoie: President @clarksomerville invites FCM Board Members to sign up their @canada150th Community Leaders #muni150 @FCM_online]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: Become an FCM Regional Champ! Help us fast forward the efforts towards increasing women’s participation in #CDNmuni: https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TimTierney: Our President @clarksomerville opens the board meeting in Oakville.  @FCM_online https://t.co/U9OYQAH5y8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @carolesaab: Hey there #cdnmuni, we made a little history today. https://t.co/3lwponO9P9 https://t.co/Zxe7asri5T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Holt_lh: Three orders of gov't working for sustainable inclusive communities. thank you @SohiAmarjeet #cdnpoli #cdnmuni https://t.co/FB…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_Brock: Phase 2 infra spending can be transformative.M mayors meet FPT ministers: working together to get it right for Cdns https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: Families &amp; seniors stay longer in emergency shelters underscoring the need for more affordable housing. #CDNmuni https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SohiAmarjeet: $1.08B in projects moving forward with this signed agreement. Great news for #Alberta https://t.co/oEpRoLAHpt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SohiAmarjeet: Proud of the collaborative work between governments that got this agreement signed https://t.co/AAdDsyAVWy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: GoC's commitment to fund a 50% share of core #CDNmuni infrastructure plans is critical to building a strong Canada. https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find great stories of GMF-Funded projects in our new annual report. https://t.co/nGdFQWEg4L #CDNmuni #FCM_GMF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @picardonhealth: I will donate $1 to the #GordDownie Fund for #BrainCancer Research for every RT. 
I'm at $363 and counting. #TheHip htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ReseauFCM: #Edmonton a aidé les prop. de terrains à  réaménager leurs lots avec #FCM_FMV : https://t.co/EZI79OmR8f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ReseauFCM: Un financement prévisible par transfert pour infras vertes &amp; transport en commun doit faire appel à l’expertise #munican. @c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Go_Taylor: @FCM_online Pres. @clarksomerville "Community building is Nation building" w/ @TimTierney at #AMOCONF16 @AMOPolicy https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: Learn the proven solutions to create sustainable neighbourhoods: https://t.co/7X0dfQb21s #FCM_GMF #CDNmuni https://t.co/fL2…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @clarksomerville: @fcm_online op ed on housing Affordable housing benefits cities - via @winnipegnews https://t.co/4SZWpkbOF2 via @share…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: FCM pres says promoting sustainable devt in meaningful ways requires significant investment in infra such as in housing &amp; t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: FCM's Asset Management Fund is taking flight. We're searching for a Director to lead its start-up. Will it be you? https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CHEOhospital: #ProjectEcho will have reduce wait times by bringing specialized psychiatric expertise to clinicians in small towns. http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JohnFraserOS: This morning I announced $550,000 annually @CHEOhospital to help extend mental health expertise to youth across ON https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: Attention, #CDNmuni! The Government of Canada wants your ideas on how to approach climate change. Submit your ideas: https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FNMuniCEDI: CEDI team invites #cdnmuni to the #trcreadingchallenge Use new knowledge to guide FN-Muni joint ecdev initiatives https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: Attn, young #CDNmuni officials! Tmrrw is the last day to apply for #GSEF2016 grant. Attend the Global Forum in 2017: https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @INFC_fra: $ fédéral accessible au #Québec pour les infra d’eau et de transport en commun grâce à l’entente #GC-QC #fedinvestit https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JohnTory: Joined mayors in pressing @Bill_Morneau on housing affordability &amp; need for incentives to spur construction of affordable hom…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @luce_lavoie: Minister Sohi talks about great collaboration with Big Cities and confirms gov commitment to be a meaningful partner with…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: .@SohiAmarjeet to big city mayors: Phase 2 is to give long term, predictable &amp; sustainable funding. GoC is a meaningful par…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: We listened &amp; took action! Deadline to join Community Leaders Network extended till December! Be part of #Muni150: https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ONenvironment: We’re proposing a moratorium on new or expanded groundwater takings by bottling companies &amp; you can have your say: https…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MayorGregor: #Canada's cities can't solve affordable housing alone. Fed govt investments + action in affordable housing long overdue #L…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kenthehr: Let’s talk about housing. Submit your thoughts online here: https://t.co/BB88zeJ0zc @jyduclos #LetsTalkHousing #cdnpoli #yyc…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: To give the economy a boost we need to give families a break. #CDNmuni need long-term housing plan: https://t.co/JveZSzuC4A…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RosieBarton: BREAKING PM names Justice Malcolm Rowe of Nfld to Supreme Court of Canada https://t.co/yr4aDy5eND #hw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: Submit your ideas on how Canada's Nat'l Housing Strategy must meet the needs of all Cdns: https://t.co/JveZSzuC4A #CDNmuni…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_Brock: .@GregMooredotca speaking to UCLG on climate change: local action and common voice of FCM partnering with feds leads to acti…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: Over 42% of young Cdns live with their parents. Help shape the GoC Nat'l Housing Strategy: https://t.co/JveZSzuC4A #CDNmuni…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MWodzicki24: A big week for two things that can make life better for all: #coops &amp; #localgov, at  #ISCOOP16 in Quebec City  and #UCLGCo…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CISAL_FCM: Our Peruvian local government associations allies with @CARILED_online delegation on how to strengthen the voice of local go…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NewsroomGC: Minister Garneau to make important announcement in #Montreal about #RailSafety https://t.co/w5BUZq7D6W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: Apply for our #CDNmuni &amp; First Nations infrastructure project on joint solid waste management before Oct 24! https://t.co/B…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Bill_Morneau: First aid is more than bandages and stiches. Take part in @WHO's #WorldMentalHealthDay to learn more about psychological…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JenAshleyWright: This #debate is when a man who says "I've been reading about this for weeks!" feels equipped to debate with a woman wh…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @noahmichelson: Retweet if you want @JudgeJudy to moderate the final debate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Ginella_M: YOU KEEP CANADA OUT OF YOUR MOUTH DONALD *takes hoop earrings off*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JillBidenVeep: Sorry, rest of the World. We're embarrassed too. #debate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: When local governments are engaged &amp; bring forward solutions, it’s Canadians who benefit the most. -@clarksomerville @Munic…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DawnChaplinNL: Municipalities are indeed the heart of Canada @FCM_online President speaks to @MunicipalNL delegates at #MNLAGM2016 http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks again @kenthehr for the lovely chat https://t.co/Q0fOJAW2oz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nenshi: Premier @RachelNotley promises that municipalities will have the tools they need to do their jobs at #AUMA2016 https://t.co/rFz…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TOAdamVaughan: On #WorldTeachersDay, let’s thank the teachers who work hard every day to inspire and empower the next generation of Can…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_Helen: Calling Municipalities and First Nations who want to participate in joint solid waste management projects https://t.co/LvtBC…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: NEW | Today we open our new infrastructure project on joint solid waste management to #CDNmuni &amp; First Nations: https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: FCM &amp; our members are committed to working actively twrds ensuring safer &amp; better lives for Indigenous women and girls acro…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FNMuniCEDI: FCM's Big City Mayors' Caucus releases Pathways to Reconciliation: https://t.co/5ChiM1dMt7  #CDNmuni Stories of change from…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How will you be commemorating #OrangeShirtDay ?
https://t.co/gVSSup6NIw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JennyGerbasi: Reminder to wear orange this Fri Sept 30th to recognize the resilience and bravery of residential school survivors #Orang…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JustinTrudeau: .@EmWatson défend l'égalité des sexes dans le monde. C'est un plaisir de l'accueillir à Ottawa pour le sommet @OneYoungW…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dal_alderson: 73% of women &amp; children fleeing violence turned away from at-capacity shelters. We can + must do better https://t.co/ZIsh…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_DonnaC: #carbontalks @FCM_online's new $75M program funded by Infra Canada will support #cdnmunis to both mitigate &amp; adapt, yes cli…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PnPCBC: .@amandaalvaro: The debate for Trump was all about Trump, for Clinton it was all about you. #pnpcbc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NickKristof: Clinton has the patient look of any woman listening to a man lecture her about things he doesn't know anything about.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @clarksomerville: Countdown is on! 100 days to go to #Canada150. Already 100 #muni150 leaders on-board to lead the #CDNmuni voice. https…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wishing @FCM_online delegates a great time at question period today. https://t.co/U2JLSt425c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NavdeepSBains: Productive meeting with the Northern #Ontario Large Urban Mayors - great to discuss economic development with all of you…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_Alex: Inspired by 100+ #CDNmuni officials and Parliamentarians discussing #housing, infra, #transit at #advocacydays @MinSocDevCMHC…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @luce_lavoie: Day 2 of FCM Advocacy Days going strong with discussion on infra, housing, and strong communities #CDNmuni @FCM_online]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Bill_Morneau: Met with #CDNmuni leaders to talk collaboration and partnerships in Ottawa today. @FCM_online https://t.co/gODXaaGT52]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: Day 2 of our Board/Advocacy days in Ottawa. Productive meetings so far, looking forward to what today brings. #CDNmuni #cdn…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: FCM is the national voice of #CDNmuni. Read about how FCM is bringing Canada’s rural voice to the federal table https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cathy_McLeod thank you again for taking the time to meet with @FCM_online board members #CDNmuni https://t.co/61ot60pEmH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FCM_online 's advocacy days are off to a great start. Relationship building between #CDNmuni and #cdnpoli @marvinplett @SenGagne https://t.co/IZ7RZjybyk]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>