<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@genebailey: You can only rise to the level of your own self imposed limitations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can only rise to the level of your own self imposed limitations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Says it all! http://t.co/D4pwYO1L7T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent living begins with excellent thinking!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @theblaze: Texas gun shop’s sign is sure to rile up the left: http://t.co/vZRXuBCzHb http://t.co/1vDL98gHVa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What are you doing that is keeping your speaking career ineffective? The #1 issue I see keeping speakers from... http://t.co/wvHjxfx5wq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just be yourself, everyone else is taken.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wish I had a dollar for every time it got distracted http://t.co/i76a0HnVAW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mashable: Facebook still dominates in the young adult demographic http://t.co/akq7VLS5Rk http://t.co/VFw3Pj1677]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 Keys to a fulfilling relationship:
1. Make them feel #1.
3. Make time to prove it.
3. Respect each other.
4. Stay faithful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“A successful man is one who can lay a firm foundation with the bricks others have thrown at him.” - David Brinkley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God is BIG enough to hear your smallest prayer. :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When you fall down, land on your back. Because if you can look up you can get up!" - one of my favorite quotes by Les Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @davidgroves: Good to have @genebailey speak to students in the Media class at RBTC today. http://t.co/We7u69kcTi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't ever let someone's negative opinion of you become your reality.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@davidcrank: The good thing about having a bad memory is that jokes can be funny more than once.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My soul finds rest in God alone; my salvation comes from him. -Psalm 62:1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dreams vs Goals http://t.co/DwKN3AXbin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How is a goal like a dream? Look: http://t.co/SHXqKMnW89]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook http://t.co/ZfCG4qEDZG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But God showed his great love for us by sending Christ to die for us while we were still sinners. http://t.co/89SwfHzRfV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whaddya mean it's not covered ? http://t.co/UPhFntv6Ws]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: Gasoline prices, late 1970's http://t.co/u8wiWpy0eI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TexasHumor: Seriously y'all, y'all is so much better than "you guys".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many are saying this "Blood Moon mania" is nothing more than Christian hype. Go read Ezekiel 37-39. Never before... http://t.co/w5tdjdmI5D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 1st blood moon is this week! http://t.co/bjWk7xR6Fk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BishopJakes: Stop asking God to take your forward when you are in love with backwards! #AskBishopJakes INSTINCT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With one of my most favorite men in the world ... Kenneth W. Hagin. http://t.co/pbDnQYqPrd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The qualities of a great man are "vision, integrity, courage, understanding, the power of articulation, and... http://t.co/axK3zOp0Fv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BitterBlueBetty: Sure I'll volunteer! I love the challenge of finding new excuses of backing out last minute.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stressed? Remember, a diamond is just a piece of charcoal that handled stress exceptionally well http://t.co/1vVXf0rAj2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stressed? Remember, a diamond is just a piece of charcoal that handled stress exceptionally well! http://t.co/mOaIbmPNYv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one gives you initiative, you have to TAKE it. http://t.co/rUqRbqWK1a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything you want is just outside your comfort zone! http://t.co/wftDLdE8SK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love this...you DO have a purpose... Before anyone else had an opinion! http://t.co/tbsnXEC8Ru]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your success stops where your CHARACTER stops. http://t.co/gc8Pe6e5cY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your success stops where your CHARACTER stops. http://t.co/ehTaeKvE9i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@ProPreacher: "A prepared messenger is more important than a prepared message." –Robert Munger #quote #preaching http://t.co/HA4U4NHBgA”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I take care of my character, my reputation will take care of me. http://t.co/BV3CwgCrFS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There's something wrong with your character if opportunity controls your loyalty." - @davidcrank http://t.co/EozBDEznzW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Character is the real foundation of all worthwhile success. http://t.co/EWN9Dmag8Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Talent is a gift, but character is a choice. http://t.co/hvCosYbf4f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New press release: Award Winning Speaker Brings Brand New Message When It’s Needed Most http://t.co/Czi5escANF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Award Winning Speaker Brings Brand New Message When It’s Needed Most http://t.co/KVcYsD9CC4 via @YahooNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHY ARE THERE COINS LEFT ON TOMBSTONES?

While visiting some cemeteries you may notice that headstones marking... http://t.co/PC6qfE993h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHY IS THERE COINS LEFT ON TOMBSTONES?

While visiting some cemeteries you may notice that headstones marking... http://t.co/W1zODkIDqO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nearly all men can stand adversity, but if you want to test a man's CHARACTER, give him power. http://t.co/nEpiPvKx2q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The great thing about an attitude is...it's ALL YOURS. You own it and YOU have the ability to change it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't bash @mcuban without hearing his comments in context.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The great thing about an attitude is...it's ALL YOURS. You have the ability to change it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Burnout is what happens when you lose your purpose. When you lose your purpose, you lose your passion." An... http://t.co/pwGJJTCYwr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find character, find wisdom. http://t.co/b0qBfhqb0T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Jentezen: You will never possess what you do not pursue! See it, say it, seize it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make the jump! http://t.co/fEm5U5MI3V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got published on CNN....Read "The Grace of Tom Landry" http://t.co/3kkW6mS7nR #ireport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got to love this.... Enjoy! http://t.co/w6ydYdys5v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you find yourself in hole... Stop digging! http://t.co/21zB9yftIo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listen to these Israeli Soldiers taking a break...move over Jason Mraz http://t.co/2fGFW0zjRG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just be yourself. Everyone else is taken. http://t.co/N1Qk0Q61ph]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With everything we're hearing and seeing in the news lately...watch this video from AIPAC (largest Jewish lobby... http://t.co/ncbNkP1InR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you walk with PURPOSE, you collide with DESTINY. http://t.co/HPoNZWU6yE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@PastorJohnHagee: You must be willing to forgive intellectually even if you don't feel it emotionally.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's better to speak one supernatural word than 10,000 of my own words.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah.... I laughed. 󾌰 http://t.co/OwJfnjFPBF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CHARACTER is a diamond that scratches every other stone. http://t.co/L0kaPc4Lsq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CHARACTER is a diamond that scratches every other stone. http://t.co/emMjKr2yr7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Character is a diamond that scratches every other stone. http://t.co/kwxJmmmBvm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Character is power." ~ Booker T. Washington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@JanineTurner: "Character is power." Booker T. Washington”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Question:  How important to you is a "view" where you live?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think you're too small to have an impact? Try this..... http://t.co/lVV2oQ6V1Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crazy, huh. http://t.co/9r2q3rB0Hq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Destiny is coming...where will YOU be? http://t.co/ujvrlegRF2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@UberFacts: The average millionaire goes bankrupt at least 3.5 times.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Use these words when someone tries to pull you into their nonsense... http://t.co/XKuDLztZ2v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you feel you're being pulled into someone's nonsense...say these words... http://t.co/B3TivTR957]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not my circus, not my
monkeys. http://t.co/l1na25lyIB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's growing in your yard? http://t.co/KOseRyqAqY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/LNrt80Pbmq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At lunch this past week we found the perfect table! http://t.co/7UqecRSbOG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fame is a vapor, popularity an accident, riches take wing, and only character endures. ~ Horace Greeley 1811-1872... http://t.co/hiA6ZAbb2J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TexasHumor: Yup. http://t.co/stNq0dmomx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What a man's mind can create, man's character can control."
~ Thomas Edison http://t.co/f4EQqpYwiP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What a man's mind can create, man's character can control." ~ Attributed to THOMAS EDISON -- inventor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best church sign ever!! http://t.co/Il7b47ibr2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Vulcan4770: Check out my fan art of the Alpha from @EdgeofTomorrow! http://t.co/oDqpQnfqiM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Vulcan4770: @EdgeofTomorrow Thank you for the retweet! http://t.co/b1scwiT5tl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ABRAHAM LINCOLN said it well:
"CHARACTER is like a tree and reputation like its shadow. The shadow is what we... http://t.co/wDgkQV0Onc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook http://t.co/E2zH85tgfA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OLD WAYS WON'T OPEN NEW DOORS.
http://t.co/1HrUtJkuyd http://t.co/N2zPma81be]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop Global Whining... http://t.co/jAVn3gMMGT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I remember the monkey bars as a kid. Do you? Life is like the monkey bars. You have to let go to move on!... http://t.co/Vm8OGHr4tP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think about the things of heaven, not the things of earth. (Colossians 3:2 NLT)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't put the key to your happiness in someone else's pocket! http://t.co/1HrUtJkuyd http://t.co/UBGluQbqYP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listening, the first step to understanding!
http://t.co/1HrUtJkuyd http://t.co/Cy5uM1qh7w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good advice!
http://t.co/1HrUtJkuyd http://t.co/5NYjKs6r90]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good advice 󾌰 
http://t.co/Qki4bOZTNa http://t.co/GHaA4CSIHM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people create their own storms, then get upset when it rains.  Stay away from those infected with mind viruses! http://t.co/lX5Xpivvr4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people create their own storms, then get upset when it rains. I found it best to steer clear of the drama! http://t.co/E0TijwYHZc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing signs in the sky this morning! http://t.co/0AEHGhMfZp]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>