<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@thrasherxy @jbouie Man that is like saying my 2 favorite James Cameron movies are Aliens and Piranha II: The Spawning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rumdood: You are not alone. https://t.co/KettX1z50R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jazzahol @dtlafave That’s just objectively wrong. Exhibit A, the whispering guy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@petercatron I still haven’t accomplished that. I wonder if I should prioritize snapchat over data scraping.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cypress Hill to announce their Senate run soon https://t.co/NVPOYZcedR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jbouie My unpopular opinion is the game Knights of the Old Republic was better than all but two of the movies in the entire franchise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @familyunequal: if you made single mothers a simple explanation for rising crime back then, now you owe them an apology (from my new boo…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“From a working-class perspective, terminating TPS would be catastrophic for workers and families” @JessChilin of @GeorgetownKILWP on the fight to #SaveTPS https://t.co/HYKjw3Op3u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TexasTribune: NEW with @ProPublica: How a South Texas bureaucrat became a multimillionaire amid the rush to build a border fence: https…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FWIW gang membership, much less “associate” status is impossible to precisely measure esp. for a franchise gang like MS-13. But FBI’s rough estimate is they make up 0.5% of all US gang members. With small numbers, even arrests in single digits can mean big % increase. https://t.co/MK6upFluXI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevinMKruse He’s also the world’s greatest legal expert https://t.co/yfQCe7uWWs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AscensionEdible @kenklippenstein Rasmussen is not taken seriously by any serious poll watcher.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CharlotteGarden: With the delay (as well as the substance of the new rule) benefiting employers fighting union drives... https://t.co/n…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder if this was before or after he got it back from his peer reviewers https://t.co/3KDVaR9RH5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Noahpinion Sounds like politicians aren't being swayed by objective empirics. Maybe time for economists to be more...activist?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MStRuebens We just need to get the North Koreans to come to West Palm Beach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My article in the Journal of Ethnic and Migration Studies is out: "Competing for the diaspora's influence at home: party structure and transnational campaign activity in El Salvador" https://t.co/ozRAv8J9pG Thanks to @hmylonas @ale_delano @scmrjems https://t.co/35HOu03stX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tomorrow I start my diet https://t.co/xzbiesspdz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @gelliottmorris: Alternative take: policy preferences don’t matter (much) and people are going to take their electoral cues from parties…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SeanDEhrlich: The tax law, in its majestic equality, allow the rich and poor alike to pay lower taxes on their corporate income. https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alt headline: some people still care that Bono has opinions about things https://t.co/dUZkNFA9W0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See, e.g. https://t.co/QYjYRtRy3l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a very good paper that exemplifies some of the best and worst trends of social science today: use of sophisticated methods to find unsurprising results, econ confirming what has been conventional wisdom for other disciplines for decades https://t.co/uw5VXg4d0N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itsameesha What’s remarkable is, as @elektrotal notes, Lucas was clearly channeling half baked US hippie notions of eastern religions from the 60s. Should have been embarrassing but somehow worked. Sometimes cultural appropriation can be good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US deported half a million Mexican immigrants in the 1930s in response to the Depression. In the cities most affected by deportations, employment and wages for native born workers went down, not up. https://t.co/34ZWiwRM9C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daguilarcanabal @Noahpinion @nomadj1s P hacking is a thing that will be increasingly easy to do in the big data era. Better to teach causal inference more broadly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Journalists (ahem Nick Kristof) will deride academics as out of touch with the real world but then only pay attention to the obscurantist theorists or hardcore ideologues and ignore the policy relevant empirical research.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[e.g. academics rely on journalism and brag about being quoted by journalists, and in their next breath say of research they consider unrigorous or anecdotal “that’s just journalism,” which is really obnoxious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also the way academics and journalists use one another in often cynical ways is a manifestation of a fundamental lack of understanding of what each other does, masking suspicion or outright contempt for their respective professions https://t.co/NEMdKrz5l8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nomadj1s @Noahpinion Right, not to mention most polisci and public policy students go into those fields specifically because they want to make a difference in the world, and they pick programs that speak to that aspiration accordingly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hereby putting in my bid for national chain gang adviser in the John Cena administration https://t.co/MdcwLKidq5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well that sounds like a national consensus https://t.co/VzQ1xQVaLP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrBriePhD Man why would she tweet this picture at all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @B_Ehrenreich: Reindeer didn’t bring you those presents; truck drivers did, and theirs is one of the most undervalued professions in Ame…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haitian mothers seek support from UN soldiers for ‘peacekeeper babies’ https://t.co/58By7tNjVn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jacksantucci Yup. Peking Gourmet Inn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merry Christmas from John Travolta’s favorite Chinese restaurant in Fairfax County! https://t.co/RaAHT4gzEO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing how he can comprehend policy outcomes when he really wants to https://t.co/LOO7cpfTMq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook allows companies to target job ads by age, which is discriminatory and blatantly illegal https://t.co/sOp0gmj1IN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ninalakhani: Excellent work by @DanielleMackey https://t.co/HWZE66SgGo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @maggieNYT: In Oval Office meeting, POTUS groused that thousands of immigrants from Haiti all have AIDS and that those from Nigeria woul…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The VA Board of Elections is literally drawing lots to determine control of the House of Delegates. Why not just go with pistols at dawn? https://t.co/dOOZekFvRs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pashulman: If you regard universities as vital centers of truth-seeking and civic acculturation, you should be worrying about the *actu…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attn @dhnexon https://t.co/akKL0WgLQV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Washington City Paper will live to fight another day. VC $ is fine, though I was hoping for a full TARP or EESA bailout from Congress.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SegravesNBC4: With purchase of @WCP by @Markein staff will NOT take pay cuts. @jaketapper will be part of advisory group as will former…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mental note to get into the for profit higher ed business  https://t.co/5cgzPeM2uD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @toddntucker: Trump commutes sentence of large scale hirer of illegal immigrants (some underage) - an exclusively GOP donor. With Democr…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And as we all remember, wages and job creation skyrocketed in 1932 https://t.co/ddPDSZPnW9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mental note to get into consulting https://t.co/2cdPd9wTe6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @m_clem: The average American has one ovary. But somehow I didn’t get any of that, either. https://t.co/CnFuxJ9qny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“What are all these black people doing here?” https://t.co/xiNZ01FNS2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jodiecongirl Also reveals the lie of the whole economic nationalism conceit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dyson criticized Cornel West for slacking off in scholarship in his late career but that’s endemic across academia. Also not a big deal. After I get tenure I’m going to release a hip hop album and star in a Matrix sequel too. https://t.co/yBVtLeHUbq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelArtz This is what should be the focus, but Trump and Sessions hype the violence in the most lurid terms to scare voters. MS is primarily an extortion racket targeting immigrants, not Murder Inc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not mentioned in this WaPo article is there were 174 homicides in PG County in this same period. MS-13 was responsible for just over 5%, mostly of other gang members. https://t.co/RJ3FNEtiPw https://t.co/uF0hX9DwOT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alixabeth Wait’ll she hears how political scientists use “that’s just journalism” as a pejorative]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the “se cayó el sistema” moment for Honduras. The US has chance to endorse stolen election or heed calls for a new one. Guess which option we’ll go for... https://t.co/9AlW3SywNw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear @kencen, maybe make @wcp your newest affiliate? https://t.co/jIcSdkBfnb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unwoke Rumsfeld: someone tell me who the Shias and Kurds are and what they do
Woke Rumsfeld: let’s stop pronouncing Muslim with a Z https://t.co/iosilutU5k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alixabeth Special exemption for anyone who is personal friends or business partners with Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LilyMasonPhD That will definitely clear things up for average readers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LALS_UPENN Thank you so much! What a wonderful audience, and great discussion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Headline says it all https://t.co/6xueJDtI9I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Harboring immigrants" = leaving water in the desert so people don't die of thirst https://t.co/QLI6NFPEe6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Key takeaway: “Companies prefer to give bonuses to workers because they are temporary.” https://t.co/ldTEAWCl6H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After Rana Plaza, Bangladeshi factory workers awarded $2.3m settlement from apparel industry over workplace safety https://t.co/yVkMNwc1el]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you’re on Penn campus tomorrow, come see my talk on transnational elections in Latin America: 1/23, noon at 3440 Market St. https://t.co/FmSaygq08C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s kind of nice how nearly all of America will temporarily feel a deep affection for Philadelphia that will last through Feb. 4.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LacesOutShow: Philadelphia is turning into a real life Steven Spielberg movie https://t.co/9Bp8KdG1nt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @night__terrors: FUCK THE GREASE https://t.co/CeAs6F6FgM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brianros1 @mirandayaver @jodiecongirl I hope they also put Crisco on all the cars parked on Frankford Ave.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FOX29philly: MEANWHILE, IN PHILLY: Crews grease light poles to prevent @Eagles fans from climbing them. They call themselves the Crisco…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Better idea: show Trump the 700 miles of border wall that already exists, tell him he just built it https://t.co/TYig1pm1t3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Literally the opposite of what the word compromise means https://t.co/EQlVHLNZps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@profmusgrave In Korea they’re handphones, and pronounced that way “han-du-pone”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@willmenaker @ryanlcooper Hey lots of great things were produced by humanities majors. CIA, Shining Path, Vox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @latguild: The final vote count for the @latguild: 248 in favor, 44 against. A landslide victory, and a historic day for the Los Angeles…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BlogWood: Victims of Trump's TPS cancellation will be relieved to know they may be shipped off to Qatar to join the legions of happy, w…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HilaryGoodfrien Change disciplines before it’s too late]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danielcoo Nevermind - Sophocles and Wagner couldn’t have come up with this https://t.co/v4fxkTjwqG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the very least this presidency will inspire a great Greek tragedy or German opera https://t.co/z4RFlGZlHU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alanzilberman Policy writer from Rockville sounds about right]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually this would be a fun in class exercise https://t.co/yfbMCocodE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobinMazumder (Maybe specific to polisci but) You don’t go to grad school because of love of learning like undergrad, you go to get trained to do good research and learn whatever you want to. Your most useful classes will be methods.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Monopsony is particularly acute in the hospital industry, with the consolidation of health systems. Especially bad given that 5 of the top 10 fastest growing US jobs are in health care. https://t.co/przGEZHOkC https://t.co/A6k6CFTNsb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good editorial that hits all the right points behind the unionization drive at my grad alma mater https://t.co/Z0rHIUK0HR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JonathanCohn: US border patrol routinely sabotages water left for migrants, report says https://t.co/UWhwRiDELh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Colombia could become the world’s top exporter of medicinal marijuana https://t.co/NnGjaEpkcC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[El Salvador proposes some immigrants in U.S. losing TPS to go to Qatar https://t.co/E5yvYCsPk0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MattGrossmann: Racial resentment has been stable for 30 years but steadily increasing its ties to most other political attitudes:
Must…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But in journalism, anecdotes and simple charts make more compelling stories than research design, which feeds common, cynical attitude that “statistics” are subjective numbers you can reach for when they’re convenient, and thus gives platforms to ideologues like Saltsman.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can’t ever “prove” causation 100%, but what we found gets a lot closer to the truth than a few cherry picked anecdotes and simple statewide data.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...and they uniformly said the tipped min. was the sole reason they opened or closed or hired more workers (but not enough!).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I might find his argument convincing if Saltsman surveyed all 18,571 full service restaurants in NYS, asked why they made all their business decisions in the past year among all possible factors...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can’t say the same for New York as a whole vs. PA as a whole. Or, for that matter, NY in 2016 as a whole vs. NY in 2015 as a whole. A lot of things happened between those years aside from the tipped min. wage hike.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We find that full service restaurant workers did better in counties just over the NY side of the border than those just over the PA side of the border. The only real difference between them that year was the tipped min. wage hike in NY.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our design was to compare counties on either side of the NY-PA border. Why? Because those counties are pretty much the same on either side. Same demographics, share the same labor pool. If a recession or bad weather hit Cattaraugus NY, it probably hit McKean PA just as badly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You need to employ a research design that controls for all the other factors that may cause restaurant owners to hire or fire or open or close, and hone in on what we’re really interested in, the min. wage hike.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So that is why we pointed out that looking at statewide aggregate data alone, as Saltsman does, is not helpful.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>