<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Its Real - You Can Print Shoes with a 3D Printer!  http://t.co/oHKHq0uP8F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Are the Major Kinds of Insurance?  http://t.co/d19uxHmfqd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It costs a lot of money to look this cheap --&gt; Dolly Parton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn Marketing Secrets for eCommerce Business  http://t.co/k1SKQxeaA9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Marketing Experts Reveal Tips to Success  http://t.co/xYvg1JEYJZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Assisted Living - Some Things to Consider  http://t.co/zeuNA9uZXW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trying to sneak a pitch past Hank Aaron is like trying to sneak a sunrise past a rooster. - Curt Simmons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Trust Me I'm A Nerd Mens Sweatshirt - Awesome http://t.co/REhfMjTB7J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can do anything, but lay off my blue suede shoes - Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Breaking News - New Michael Jackson Song  http://t.co/3mfPNyqbUT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gold Glitter Lips - Cool Look!  http://t.co/lpXJoS7ls1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion has two purposes: comfort and love. Beauty comes when fashion succeeds. --&gt; Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best use of life is to spend it for something that outlasts it - William James]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Review of the Book Eragon  http://t.co/A5YauXtEmO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gluten Free Recipes - Making a Gluten-Free Gravy  http://t.co/ZWiZz9Gacr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Silver Plated "Privates" Scratcher - For the Busy Executive http://t.co/KKrA1wLUjt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Building an Effective Company Blog  http://t.co/KRELeL6M4h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of In-N-Out Burger  http://t.co/EorihaGCRh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two sides: One is light, one is dark." -- John Locke, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Christianity as a Profession  http://t.co/iJQ4GGU6w7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Buying Gardening Supplies and Plants  http://t.co/TmVrN7OkeM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love cats because I enjoy my home; and little by little, they become its visible soul. - Jean Cocteau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't put it on YouTube.  Beyonce Knowles, after slipping onstage during a concert performance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first one gets the oyster the second gets the shell. - Andrew Carnegie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I started out writing much more science fictiony stuff and writing about science fiction. - Neil Gaiman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My life is an open book. With illustrations.  Hugh Hefner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Jackson Browne  http://t.co/dW01OfLSe3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An expert is a man who has made all the mistakes which can be made, in a narrow field. - Niels Bohr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome football t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the football lovers in your life!   http://t.co/Wz0rWfG05J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't steal second base and keep one foot on first. - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pessimist: A man who thinks that all woman are bad Optimist: A man who hopes so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love my crazy girlfriend - hilarious t-shirt - http://t.co/tTEInKwGvY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A twelve-year-old Ben Linus brought me a chicken salad sandwich. How do you think I'm doing? - Sayid Jarrah, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a rock 'n' roll thing to have one-night stands. - Rick Springfield]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Out the Top Football Teams of the 2011-2012 Season  http://t.co/XsPNZdaUvs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Boston  http://t.co/zHEfvNRaEh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes you can play 3 Man Chess - Check It Out! http://t.co/SmaH9aVF5H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To succeed in business, to reach the top, an individual must know all it is possible to know about that business. - J. Paul Getty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Different Types of Beer  http://t.co/cXVRB9xs8P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walking: the most ancient exercise and still the best modern exercise. - Carrie Latet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're told to pay as we go! But where are we going?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Al Green  http://t.co/uoJVXEmSq9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be back - The Terminator]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The Best of ABBA  http://t.co/9ZAM6mYk28]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smartphones are reinventing the connection between companies and their customers.  Rich Miner - Partner Google Ventures]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science fiction is not predictive; it is descriptive. - Ursula K. LeGuin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 1 - What the heck do I have????  http://t.co/Yg2dSf9Y3f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is the ability to listen to almost anything without losing your temper or your self-confidence. - Robert Frost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Overview of Bluetooth Enabled Watches  http://t.co/GqJObudcb3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My life is an open book. With illustrations.  Hugh Hefner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only undertake what you can do in an excellent fashion. There are no prizes for average performance.- Brian Tracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's behind you doesn't matter. - Enzo Ferrari]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Carlos Santana  http://t.co/Qzdv2JodOp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My advice if you insist on slimming: Eat as much as you like - just don't swallow it. - Harry Secombe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've looked into the eye of this island, and what I saw was beautiful. - John Locke, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop praising a woman, she'll think you don't love her.  Keep it up and she'll think she is too good for you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you ain't making waves, you ain't kickin' hard enough - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[College isn't the place to go for ideas. - Helen Keller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft House Showcase: Touring the Winning House  http://t.co/3tjtGpk990]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Big-Dog Pet Fountain - Keeps Fresh and Tasty Water for Your Big Dog! http://t.co/QCx1EXykxQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Ways Technology Helps Seniors  http://t.co/ZQc4tev65j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Familiarity breeds contempt --  and children]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman's dress should be a like a barbed-wire fence: serving its purpose without obstructing the view. - Sophia Loren]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Babysitter: a teenager who acts like a Grownup while grownups are acting like teenagers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And God took a handful of southernly wind, blew His breath over it and created the horse. - Bedouin Legend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Why You Should Consider a Creative Writing Degree  http://t.co/JVO6vOl3p0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may have said the same thing before... But my explanation, I am sure, will always be different. - Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Use Twitter in Business  http://t.co/NI3xCBbJJC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Mac and Katie Kissoon  http://t.co/KO7ZK16nVR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love any movie that has a retarded person working at Starbucks.  Chris Kattan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hops Holster 12 Can Ammo Pack - Beer Anywhere!  http://t.co/AoEpSoQiZE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poets are like baseball pitchers. Both have their moments. The intervals are the tough things. - Robert Frost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're a very expensive group; we break a lot of rules. It's unheard of to combine opera with a rock theme, my dear. - Freddie Mercury]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of the animals except for man know that the principle business of life is to enjoy it. - Samuel Butler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Breaking News - New Michael Jackson Song  http://t.co/3mfPNyqbUT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is 90% mental, the other half is physical - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd make a wonderful Lady Macbeth. I'll wear a pair of platform shoes or something - Bette Midler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People who enjoy what they are doing invariably do it well. - Joe Gibbs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone has a rock bottom.  - Prince]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips To Draw More Traffic With Quality Link Building  http://t.co/kFUpdSmEC4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Fort Worth, Texas  http://t.co/tebEguFWix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overheard in hollywood: "You said their marriage wouldn't last! They left the church together, didn't they?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Lettermen  http://t.co/DNRnI1XhkG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need to be able to rock out.  - Bryan Adams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Powerful Tools For Your Internet Marketing Program    http://t.co/acBTcTjKne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn the Best Spots for Mountain Climbing  http://t.co/lIlm9m8Ys2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cooking - A Simple Way To Bond With Kids  http://t.co/F5aiS68Agb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Flea and Tick Control For Your Pet  http://t.co/bG2LRueHw6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion is not necessarily about labels. It's not about brands. It's about something else that comes from within you. - Ralph Lauren]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman is as young as she feels like telling you she is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Simplicity is the ultimate sophistication. - Leonardo da Vinci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Battleship Memorial Park – Mobile Alabama – A Great Historical Experience  http://t.co/4RziHza9xb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dogs come when they're called; cats take a message and get back to you later. - Mary Bly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The main part of intellectual education is not the acquisition of facts but learning how to make facts live." - Oliver Wendell Holmes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cricket is basically baseball on valium - Robin Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The years are adding up when it takes us longer to get rested than it does to get tired. . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some days, you just can't get rid of a bomb! - Adam West, Batman &amp; Robin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If man is a little lower than angels, then angels should reform.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not anorexic. I'm from Texas. Are there people from Texas that are anorexic? I've never heard of one. And that includes me. Jessica S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apollo: I will not serve under a man who questions my integrity. Adama: And I won't have an officer under my command who doesn't have any.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>