<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[On of life's little ironies is the fact that when you finally master a tough job, you make it look easy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Johnnie Tayor  http://t.co/SifXOXyDLW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The law gives a man the right to open his wife's mail, but not the nerve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Book review of the Inheritance series – Eldest By Christopher Paolini  http://t.co/o1kspMMtE3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's hard to shake hands  with a clenched fist!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the business world, everyone is paid in two coins: cash &amp; experience. Take the experience first; the cash will come later - Harold Geneen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Victory belongs to the most persevering. - Napoleon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What --  is the air-speed velocity of an unladen swallow? - Bridgekeeper, Monty Python and the Holy Grail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Reviews By Children Affect a Product’s Sale  http://t.co/8odgZJI7f6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To me, true rock 'n' roll has a lot of bottom in it.  - Little Richard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I looked and looked but I didn't see God. - Yuri Gagarin, 14 April 1961]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winners never quit and quitters never win. - Vince Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Joni Mitchell  http://t.co/IAjqSkOaRf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Transformer Autobot Cufflinks! http://t.co/Hl49JVA6hs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Star Wars  http://t.co/v87gGeRxu8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Budweiser  http://t.co/K3MfkrEPSu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Skol Beer  http://t.co/Xme33QZ6bi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Peregrine Falcons: Lords of the Sky  http://t.co/kVIXuQcG41]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Experience is a hard teacher because she gives the test first, the lesson afterward. - Vernon Law]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To achieve anything in this game you must be prepare to dabble in the boundary of disaster. - Sterling Moss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because the human history is the history of shoes. The history of places where we ever tread and stand.  - Stebby Julionatan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the Devine RPG Minecraft Mod - http://t.co/wJuJpzE8HD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is not the man who has too little, but the man who craves more, that is poor.  Seneca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is 90% mental, the other half is physical - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ginger Rogers did everything Fred Astaire did, backwards and on high heels - Faith Whittlesey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picking Earphones for Fitness Activities  http://t.co/ETlZOn5gub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lassie is an American TV classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/iuPnvNpLz1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just think it's great to show a gown that's $8,000 and a shoe that's, like, $25 - but still look fabulous together. - Christian Siriano]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Adoption Part II - the Bulgaria Phase  http://t.co/IJ4gal2X7a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Top 10 fitness gyms  http://t.co/Y2GawbTPuN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome fine wine t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the wine lovers in your life!  http://t.co/l22GS5YgxF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is simply the soul of a society as it passes from one generation to another. - Gilbert K. Chesterton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A baseball manager is a necessary evil. - Sparky Anderson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's so timid he wouldn't open an oyster without first knocking on the shell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Fun Science Ideas for Kids  http://t.co/oyuZ3eCY4X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making money is a hobby that will complement any other hobbies you have, beautifully. Scott Alexander]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 8 - North Texas Lyme Support Group  http://t.co/KEVwvX8f4r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of England Dan and John Ford Coley  http://t.co/TUlENcxd1C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome basketball t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the basketball lovers in your life!   http://t.co/N90qYh6JwY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your Business Guide for Small Business Internet Marketing  http://t.co/Ck8Eiy0vSc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before you take somebody's head off be sure you've used yours]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Driving a car is like playing baseball. The object in both is to get home safely. - Joe Moore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greater your capacity to love, the greater your capacity to feel the pain.  Jennifer Aniston]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is where you &amp; I are different. Because this is all I want to talk about. Letterman to Paris when she didn’t want to talk about jail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet Stay Thirsty My Friends Dos Equis T-Shirt - Most Interesting Main In the World - http://t.co/Am67aBVUmz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very very cool SpyHawk RC Plane with 3.5 inch LCD Monitor/Controller &amp; video recording &amp; auto-pilot system - HOT - http://t.co/z0ChixyC9p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Management is nothing more than motivating other people. - Le Iacocca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Middle age is after one night out you need two nights in. . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Ways to Use Website Builders for Links to Your Website  http://t.co/dfh7iaYjE2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about the Bay Area city of Danville, California http://t.co/886cHgteSo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About The Beginning Of Christian Religion  http://t.co/JHQf3O0RrW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These aren't the droids you're looking fore. - Obi-Wan, Star Wars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Powerful Tools For Your Internet Marketing Program    http://t.co/Ro7yu7tcMs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Aerosmith  http://t.co/VqmdzZraL9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harness The Power of Twitter for Business to Business Internet Marketing  http://t.co/7XnlO0aKkN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's easier to ask forgiveness than it is to get permission - Grace Hopper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Dale Hawkins - The Father of Swamp Rock Boogie  http://t.co/zGg5QFdTNv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Flip flops  http://t.co/7JgjbvAFDl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rock and roll is here to stay. - Neil Young]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love any movie that has a retarded person working at Starbucks.  Chris Kattan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About The History of Fitness Equipment  http://t.co/9zdniBopUh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of the animals except for man know that the principle business of life is to enjoy it. - Samuel Butler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes, you have to roll a hard six. Commander William Adama]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do something for somebody every day for which you do not get paid. - Albert Schweitzer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You miss 100% of the shots you never take. - Wayne Gretzky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of Skylanders: Spyro’s Adventure  http://t.co/U665jqmVge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The lead car is absolutely unique, except for the one behind it which is identical. - F1 commentator Murray Walker.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of McDonald's  http://t.co/Es5isZc2oe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the History of the Periodic Chart  http://t.co/lVHXRmrtCU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Return the shoes?! I can't talk to you when you're being hysterical! - Gabrielle, Desperate Housewives]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Product Reviews Through the Eyes of a Child  http://t.co/4GGlXrp08q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the fascinating history of the New York Yankees - http://t.co/EFenocbtNk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sign on a greenhouse: Fresh flowers just out of bed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Boston  http://t.co/LsbHnbquxS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not the mistakes in life that are important; it's what we learn from them. - Donna Guthrie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We didn't lose the game; we just ran out of time. - Vince Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jazz up  your pool or patio with these trendy light cubes - cool!  http://t.co/YTu2jbyZ5j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best possible thing in baseball is winning the World Series. The second best thing is losing the World Series. - Tommy Lasorda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fool and his money are never without friends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you love James Bond?  Check out these cool t-shirts, hats, stickers and more --&gt;  http://t.co/5RDV24Gw7q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must accept finite disappointment, but we must never lose infinite hope. - Martin Luther King, Jr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am alive and well and unconcerned about the rumors of my death. But if I were dead, I would be the last to know. - Paul McCartney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the animals: God has given them the rudiments of thought and joy untroubled - Fyodor Dostoyevsky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to Douglas Adams  http://t.co/UNrRIiFEm7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Fort Worth, Texas  http://t.co/kMoMo0o9A9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space Invaders Taito Astronaut Video Game T-Shirt Tee  http://t.co/pI1NtomZ44]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think education is expensive, try ignorance - Derek Bok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do elephants have trunks? - they don't have glove compartments]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Search Engine Optimization (SEO) to Drive Traffic to Your Website  http://t.co/JqglaAsAv8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China has blocked Twitter!!  Now 2 billion people will have no idea what I'm having for lunch.  Bummer!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Donna Summer  http://t.co/SU4cCBBoRC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then there was the crooked crematory operator who sold the ashes to cannibals as instant people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a great day to play two!  - Ernie Banks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sorry, Dave. I'm afraid I can't do that. - HAL - 2001: A Space Odyssey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fantasy is the impossible made probable. Science fiction is the improbable made possible.  - Rod Serling, creator of The Twilight Zone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Find Gluten Free Recipes  http://t.co/3wYU6LieAB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The reality of science is that it takes 40 years to get to Jupiter, and that's a dull show. - Glen Morgan, "Space: Above and Beyond"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've never heard a Jay-Z song.  Miley Cyrus on Jay-Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the first place, God made idiots. That was for practice. Then he made school boards. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never threw an illegal pitch. The trouble is, once in a while I toss one that ain't never been seen by this generation. - Satchel Paige]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>