<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior DevOps Engineer: A web and mobile applications development company is seeking a Senior DevOps Engineer to join their growing team. This person will be responsible for designing, maintaining, and troubleshooting an AWS-based architecture for… https://t.co/1wAqQ3I8Ca https://t.co/DeWnCVsG8G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ford could make electric cars in Germany after 2023: Handelsblatt: FRANKFURT (Reuters) - Ford could make electric cars in Germany after 2023, when the life cycle of Ford's Fiesta model is due to end, the head of the carmaker's German business told a… https://t.co/kchH4a8oNb https://t.co/dXHzSaMY3i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior User Experience Designer: RumbleOn is looking for an Experienced and Creative Front-End Developer / UX Designer to join our unbelievably talented team in Irving, TX. You will play a key role in our fast growing company while collaboratively… https://t.co/yycp3sPHAs https://t.co/qVQ04Le65e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Architect (Java): Technical Architect (Java) – Vacancies – Values – A Xebian – Culture – Contact – Vacancies – Our Values – People First – Quality without Comprise – Sharing Knowledge – Customer Intimacy – A Xebian – Culture – Innovation Day –… https://t.co/q0MMrkj7YM https://t.co/ZaxlXTPxq5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Masters: Scrum Masters MEMPHIS, Tennessee – United States Job Start Date – 03/07/18, Posted Date – 03/07/18 Primary SkillsAgile,ScrumTax TermsC2COverview Requirements * Requires thorough knowledge of general management methods within non-profit… https://t.co/TkBeGIoIxM https://t.co/gGXl42x0wp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staff Backend Java Software Engineer (SBG QuickBooks Online): Staff Backend Java Software Engineer (SBG QuickBooks Online) – Intuit Careers – Home – Meet Intuit – Innovative Technology. Inspired Solutions. – Bold Environment. Empowering Culture. –… https://t.co/oDabVL4Lou https://t.co/Q7bsr8Oif7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master Job: Scrum MasterLocation: Bloomfield, CTDuration : 6+ months?Scrum Master CertificationPMP certification is a plus, agile?Raeela ******************************************?? – provided by Dice Scrum Master Certification – ID#:… https://t.co/ph9GwvAHR7 https://t.co/wTCXgQe0Wh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer III – Performance Engineering: Description: THE COMPANYAre you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by… https://t.co/ipfW0YqL9y https://t.co/U90Ehg6yT2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master – SAFe, CSM, CI, Back-end: Do you want to be part of a dynamic, fail-fast environment where the spirit of experimentation is recognized and encouraged? Do you want to work with some of the smartest people you will ever meet in any particular… https://t.co/TpBaZ7ljv2 https://t.co/IpegJ3yiz6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager: JOB TITLE: Senior Project Manager JOB LOCATION: Deerfield, IL JOB SUMMARY: Senior Project Manager is responsible for leading teams to deliver project(s) that span across one or more business units. Manage resources, schedules,… https://t.co/qnu4Hw6Sw6 https://t.co/6bfvf4xvL2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fullscreen – Senior Ruby Engineer: The Senior Ruby on Rails Software Developer within Fullscreen Engineering team supports the architecture, design, development, and deployment of applications, API services, and client integrations for Fullscreens Brands… https://t.co/9fgQHRBdZR https://t.co/MXNYNp7D36]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master II (Project Manager II)| Detroit MI| 10 Months| Position -1: MAJOR DUTIES AND RESPONSIBILITIES SCRUM MASTER Facilitate Scrum events (Daily Scrum, Sprint Planning, Sprint Review, Retrospective, Backlog Grooming) Coach Product Owner and… https://t.co/dJdoYx17DI https://t.co/unHSgIMVwT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master Job: Date: Mar 21, 2018 Location: Albuquerque, NM, US Company: SAIC Scrum Master (Job Number:435242) Description: Scrum Master Job Description SAIC is looking for an experienced Scrum Master. You will work in a highly collaborative and agile… https://t.co/bR2ryWMOuR https://t.co/hELNTxm6MG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump to unveil China tariff list this week, targeting tech goods: WASHINGTON (Reuters) - The Trump administration this week will unveil a list of advanced technology Chinese imports targeted for U.S. tariffs to punish Beijing over technology transfer… https://t.co/z1IEbeYOxv https://t.co/OLpciOplcB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DCGS-SOF Project Manager – 15507: DCGS-SOF Project Manager Camber Corporation (a Huntington Ingalls Industries (HII) company) Distributed Common Ground Surface System – Special Operations Forces (DCGS-SOF) Team is seeking highly motivated applicants for… https://t.co/G7TlODgJRP https://t.co/gUJscPFJcC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: Infosys HCADM Technology Lead – US Mainframe – CT Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to create and execute strategies for their digital transformation. From… https://t.co/tI6nuq8acx https://t.co/cFXyZps7Fu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Engineer III: Description: THE COMPANY Are you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable,… https://t.co/9HbB2Xd1Km https://t.co/obofLDcYuw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Job TitleScrum Master – ID:25428 Duration6 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsExposure to various business intelligence applications and architecture such as Cognos, Tableau and data warehousing LocationVernon Hills, IL Date Posted03/06/2018… https://t.co/5tBdEO5a6x https://t.co/PY7h0vo0N9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineering Manager: Description:   Software Engineering Manager        Ashburn VA The AFSS program is looking for a Software Engineering Manager to help manage various Agile teams.  The AFSS program is an Air Traffic Management program under… https://t.co/9ShyCoNE0q https://t.co/MyKocatBzA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer: COMPUTER/IT Development Expert for SAP Labs, LLC (Palo Alto, CA) resp for dvlpmnt focus on dsgn, cdng, tst, QA of cmplx prdct feat in a dvlpmt team. Bach in Comp Sci, Engg, Math, or rltd field &amp; 7 yrs exp req’d, or alt a Master’s &amp; 5 yrs exp.… https://t.co/BgG8CuXkT1 https://t.co/FJ0KAJkHgs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid level – Scientific Computing Software Developer: Description: Leidos is seeking Scientific Computing Software Developers to support a variety of sophisticated acoustic training and simulation systems. Position provides opportunity to travel to… https://t.co/CL8J6uDVMu https://t.co/yohfESSlw9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer II: Description: THE COMPANYAre you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable,… https://t.co/efh48UPQEh https://t.co/3admloHoe6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead, .NET Developer: Do you have the right stuff? Gullview Technologies is an exciting new and rapidly growing technology company focused on taking on the most vital and challenging business and technical challenges our clients face in competing in our… https://t.co/iMAMEsAySL https://t.co/1tdNKsyPND]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer: O3 World is seeking a Full Stack Developer with a passion for building great tools and compelling experiences like the projects listed in the WORK section of our site [************************** You will work with some of the… https://t.co/vtnZh7wddJ https://t.co/m10bdD1af5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master Responsibilities: Facilitate all scrum ceremonies: Sprint Planning: help the team commit to a sprint goal with your product owner and decompose all stories and defect work into tasks with owners and estimates. Daily Standup:… https://t.co/lqYvs0K0Hy https://t.co/tVK4RJ20js]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. safety agency criticizes Tesla crash data release: WASHINGTON (Reuters) - The U.S. National Transportation Safety Board said on Sunday it was "unhappy" that electric car maker Tesla Inc made public information about the crash of its Model X vehicle… https://t.co/PeL36Jm21E https://t.co/u01ZDo8M0m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager: At PointSource we partner with our clients to transform their business through design, technology and culture. Our clients can expect a collaborative and agile cross-functional team approach with a focus on business outcomes. Join… https://t.co/8eyUJ8s6dt https://t.co/op5ekvcmMP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst: Software Business Analysis at Redflex are part of a community that design and create leading edge solutions that make our cities and our lives more green, safer and smarter. We take a whole team approach to software quality, following… https://t.co/bevxNmC91M https://t.co/pRdyPaLXoz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front-end Developer: At Mindera we use technology to build products we are proud of, with people we love. Mindera was born in 2014 out of a friendship of 5 people, who shared the same cultural values and wanted to create a unique environment, where… https://t.co/eAwzaCfUaf https://t.co/tNOzsqyYh9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer IV: About GoDaddy GoDaddy powers the world’s largest cloud platform dedicated to small, independent ventures. With nearly 17 million customers worldwide and over 73 million domain names under management, GoDaddy is the place… https://t.co/7TXhdaeIvs https://t.co/fYNfRens5w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Scrum Master: Job Title: Senior Scrum Master Location: Chicago, IL Duration- 6 Months Roles &amp; Responsibility Guiding the team and organization on how to use Agile/Scrum practices and values to delight customers – Guiding the team on how to get the… https://t.co/oAjMehgMHA https://t.co/JUbOsnvXja]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: Job TitleSenior Java Developer – ID:30818 Duration6 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsSenior Java Developer LocationIrving, TX Date Posted01/19/2018 Role: Senior Java Developer Location: Irving, TX-75038 Duration: 6+ months Contract… https://t.co/0x2JBRFh68 https://t.co/0ZoHZtgtnk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer with 8 plus years’ experience: W2 DIRECT HIRE ONLY! NO C2C OR SPONSORSHIP ALIS Software, is currently seeking an experienced for a C# .NETSENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER WITH 8 PLUS YEARS EXPERIENCE for a DIRECT HIRE opportunity with… https://t.co/H9nvvgDczP https://t.co/QLbZJytEdK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Responsibilities * * Develops, maintains, and enhances complex and diverse software systems (e.g., processing-intensive analytics, novel algorithm development, manipulation of extremely large data sets, real-time systems, and business… https://t.co/NeI2i3y2A0 https://t.co/AmCrvLnpv7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agile Pipeline: Description: THE COMPANY Fannie Mae provides reliable, large-scale access to affordable mortgage credit in communities across our nation. We are the leading source of funding for housing in America, which means more people can buy or rent… https://t.co/y9MxRAWcVG https://t.co/qAnHPWcRDs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer: SENIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER Full time permanent position US Citizens, Permanent Residence, or TN1 Visas only SALARY: $95k + 10% Bonus LOCATION: Lafayette,CO or Lake Oswego OR preferred, but Remote is OK too SENIOR SOFTWARE… https://t.co/akENgZhrum https://t.co/2zLKP2rjSp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior ServiceNow Developer: Senior ServiceNow Developer – Careers Home – About Us – People &amp; Culture – University Recruiting – Total Rewards – Growth &amp; Learning – Featured Locations – Europe, Middle East &amp; Africa Jobs – Asia &amp; South Pacific Jobs – Latin… https://t.co/60s4PbZ6PB https://t.co/UEzMwWTGOD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More family members of woman killed in Uber self-driving car crash hire lawyer: PHOENIX (Reuters) - More family members of a woman killed by an Uber Technologies Inc [UBER.UL] self-driving vehicle have hired legal counsel, indicating the ride services… https://t.co/RRfBVPjGnK https://t.co/OYf9FjT3zN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Professional, Software Engineer: Job Duties As one of our Developers, you should have at least five (5) years’ experience in PHP, MySQL, HTML, CSS &amp; JS. Additionally, we are looking for two years’ experience with the following skills: Work in an… https://t.co/qKbAZutKgZ https://t.co/T623kwNIRX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Project Manager / Scrum Master: About the position The Prudential El Paso office is seeking an experienced Technical Project Manager / Scrum Master to support the El Paso (GBTS – Global Business &amp; Technology Solutions) Center. The El Paso GBTS… https://t.co/uRPAJUe6IW https://t.co/N2w1dXWzMP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Bachelors Degree in Computer Science, Software Engineering or of study. 5 years work experience as a Java developer, implementing test data solutions. Minimum 3 years work experience developing solutions in a environment, e.g. AWS. Full… https://t.co/sW9n5wSxcG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Engineer – New York, US: Who We Are Storefront is the worlds leading short-term retail marketplace. We are a platform that makes retail accessible to anyone in the world. We make it possible for brands to easily find and book short-term retail… https://t.co/dhbKk6UAcB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test and Integration Engineer: Full time Test and Integration Engineer Level 2 for testing and integration of software components into development and production frameworks. Develop auto tests, shell scripts and obtain data from the operational… https://t.co/CskX4SMFng https://t.co/uC1thp4Rj4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer – Entry: Position Description Dynetics is seeking a talented Entry Level Software Developer to join our Unmanned Aircraft System (UAS) Trainer development team. This team’s purpose is to write simulation software that trains… https://t.co/jIKHbqQYp5 https://t.co/CPNTlkHo85]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer in Test: Department Development – US Employment Type Employee Minimum Experience Mid-level Software Developer in Test About us INVIDI Technologies Corporation develops products and services for addressable television advertising. Our… https://t.co/8XCkkZnrD9 https://t.co/4H0PSen65x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Security Firewall Engineer: Job Description Job ID: R45577 Benjamin Franklin (18052), United States of America, Wilmington, Delaware At Capital One, we’re building a leading information-based technology company. Still founder-led by Chairman and… https://t.co/PDCaza8jj8 https://t.co/TH6eGnX80I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: Client Reference Code: 217439JOB SUMMARYThis position requires an experienced Dev Ops Engineer with extensive experience in packaging and delivering software to a production environment. The Dev Ops Engineer will be responsible for both… https://t.co/ahJl4Wzt2o https://t.co/y7HwRKh1NE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer ================= Req #: ******Location: Santa Maria, CA USJob Category: EngineeringSecurity Clearance: TS/SCIClearance Status: Must Be Current Job Description What You ll Get to Do: You will develop and maintain Web,… https://t.co/CFayuZ6a5U https://t.co/BKqD93KJHQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Scrum Master, Application Development – Spectrum Enterprise: About Spectrum Enterprise Spectrum Enterprise, a part of Charter Communications, is a national provider of scalable, fiber-based technology solutions serving many of America’s largest… https://t.co/Cr16tpniZu https://t.co/qwiA2Cd33C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master Responsibilities: Facilitate all scrum ceremonies: Sprint Planning: help the team commit to a sprint goal with your product owner and decompose all stories and defect work into tasks with owners and estimates. Daily Standup:… https://t.co/NPnZ7IhCEl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Front End Developer: Actively engage in and contribute to development activities on the front-end and backend Contribute to architecture of our new UI and services platform within the framework of the existing target platform selected (Web API,… https://t.co/MV7GcHh2sN https://t.co/zZUKGklAMX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer (Firmware): About Us: Teradici is the creator of the PCoIP remoting protocol technology and Cloud Access Software, the cutting edge solution for a cloud-ready future. The Company, founded in 2004 and based in Vancouver, Canada is… https://t.co/8mrlpWF8hg https://t.co/tSsQt2Dfax]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer in Test: R0001538 Software Developer in Test Job Summary The Software Developer in Test is a hybrid developer/tester position and is responsible for the development, maintenance, execution and reporting of a team’s test automation… https://t.co/JEgrMxPJto https://t.co/DXnYE7JAbP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master/Sr. Requirements Analyst: Position Requirements: We are currently seeking a motivated, career and customer oriented Scrum Master/Sr. Requirements Analyst to join our team in Reston, VA, to begin an exciting and challenging career with Unisys… https://t.co/HQDiEfi01O https://t.co/RWdajVahSH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Software Developer: Company: MedXCom was founded by three doctors who wanted to revolutionize the after-hour medical answering service industry after losing an avoidable medical malpractice lawsuit. Mission: Improve after-hours patient care and… https://t.co/jrxHtSvvxO https://t.co/gXDayVlXbP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SFDC Marketing Cloud – Sr. Consultant – FT role – (Top Management Consulting): Sr. Consultant Level * 5+ years of consulting experience and/or Marketing project implementation experience. No Contractors or Job Hoppers! * 2+ full life cycle projects with… https://t.co/ZNKGsOzQgC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[senior technical project manager: hello senior technical project manager. glad you found us. as a senior technical project manager (f/m) you will be part of our development team in berlin mitte. with your work you will ensure successful project… https://t.co/ypF6koMdmq https://t.co/j7pCKxDpRx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Agile Coach: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Herndon, VA Job Type: Engineering, Information Technology, Science Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 4/10/2018 Job Description Job Number: R******* Booz Allen Hamilton has been at the… https://t.co/y7GICEIpHi https://t.co/1VjFBxnREH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Scrum Master: Plano 7 (31067), United States of America, Plano, Texas At Capital One, we’re building a leading information-based technology company. Still founder-led by Chairman and Chief Executive Officer Richard Fairbank, Capital One is on a… https://t.co/ItK7ZDRhvd https://t.co/i0rU7UVlgh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Description:Leidos is looking for a Software Engineer to support multiple programs focused on US Army CI/HUMINT efforts for CONUS- and OCONUS-based user communities.   The ideal candidate will have experience with the Agile software… https://t.co/LwntrxZ5Gp https://t.co/BVrTkW6liF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer (Front End): Adaptive Software is one of the fastest growing parts of the DRG family. Broadly, Adaptive sells workflow and business process software tools to health plans and Pharmacy Benefit Managers (PBMs), the organizations that… https://t.co/I6HTDBQfo9 https://t.co/qGToThiPAK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UX Designer: UX Design Engineer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Design, Optimize, and add features to an existing HTML/JavaScript user interface Debug and fix all issues related to new features added Demonstrate progress to the team at… https://t.co/jn4ihsjtY3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate QA Engineer: Our client is looking for an Associate QA Engineer who is motivated, energetic, and detail-oriented. If you thrive by working in a fast-paced start-up environment utilizing the latest internet technologies, consider this… https://t.co/pXRgxo8Nr8 https://t.co/yPcVbOkgcF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer, Project Lead: We are an Equal Opportunity Employer and do not discriminate against any employee or applicant for employment because of race, color, sex, age national origin, religion, sexual orientation, gender identity, status as a… https://t.co/Uxsu9UqS8m https://t.co/2WubHJ0WWH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Intelligence Analyst – Data Center and Change Management: General Description This role will help ERCOT IT build out a set of processes and procedures to consistently profile, cleanse, and align data created in the operation of a highly complex… https://t.co/hDQzoyMsgP https://t.co/ge9MnKL8Oa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Development Engineer in Test: Senior Software Development Engineer in Test home About Us – News – Blog – Careers – Resources – Leadership Products – TruCare – Integrations Demo Careers Contact Customer Log In Careers Home Career Sr.… https://t.co/tbtTEg0Nof https://t.co/1ycmLcnVYc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital Commerce Business Analyst (US): Zaelab is a dedicated team of focused, agile and innovative consultants who work to bridge the gap from vision to delivery of B2B commerce technology projects. Our commitment to evolving commerce beyond traditional… https://t.co/CyoBkvA7lq https://t.co/iqjhw1c1D8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master (******) Saline, Michigan – United States Job Start Date – 04/30/18, Posted Date – 04/30/18 Primary SkillsScrumTax TermsW-2Overview * Description:The Scrum Master is the servant leader for the team and must be able to ensure… https://t.co/MatJssTGje https://t.co/6blVxcL6yG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineering Manager: Company Description At INgrooves Music Group, we are committed to powering creativity in todays dynamic music marketplace by providing the best end-to-end digital asset management platform tools and services to content… https://t.co/qezs06V3QQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Software Engineer: Description: Leidos is looking for a high-octane lead software engineer to lead software engineering efforts for the US Army Nett Warrior program. Responsible for coordinating with various stakeholders including customer, end… https://t.co/RIm207lStf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Business Analyst(Scrum): Business Analyst Alpharetta, GA Full Time Position Job Description: Strong experience in working as a product owner and senior business analyst. Prior Experience in working on projects using Scrum and SAfe framework is a… https://t.co/Bpcup2SdWo https://t.co/M3Dd18XPmX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineering Manager: Description:The Defense &amp; Intelligence Group of Leidos has an opening for a Software Engineering Manager in Fairmont, WV. JOB SUMMARY: As the largest provider of IT services to the U.S. Government, Leidos develops and… https://t.co/g9gg4Ww2Mx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master, Technical Programs – SolidFire: Scrum Master, Technical Programs – SolidFire Close By continuing to use and navigate this website, you are agreeing to the use of cookies. Accept – Careers – Featured Jobs – Customer Support Jobs –… https://t.co/QS1K0fkNZ1 https://t.co/wwm7A8oxqV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Lead: Why We Work at Dun &amp; Bradstreet Life here at Dun &amp; Bradstreet is changing for the better. With almost two centuries of experience and a new modern vibe, work at D &amp; B has never been more exhilarating. Our purpose is to grow the most valuable… https://t.co/mrxuXM2pV6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer IV: About GoDaddy GoDaddy powers the world’s largest cloud platform dedicated to small, independent ventures. With nearly 17 million customers worldwide and over 73 million domain names under management, GoDaddy is the place… https://t.co/HrEs6lyoQ4 https://t.co/QfTjyMR0nN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, Machine Learning: Where good people build rewarding careers. Think that working in the insurance field can’t be exciting, rewarding and challenging? Think again. You’ll help us reinvent protection and retirement to improve customers’… https://t.co/TAiZFrDsKq https://t.co/E960Ycq57m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Team Lead (Scrum Master) Job: Team Lead (Scrum Master) (Job Number:431672) Description: JOB DESCRIPTION: Team Lead (Scrum Master) – Scrum Master certification from accredited organization, i.e., Scrum Master Certified (CSM), Professional Scrum Master… https://t.co/gd3TYLllKk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C# / https://t.co/GD6lseIfcq / Developer / Scrum Leader: Kamis is searching for an experienced Developer to lead and mentor more junior developers on multiple teams in a Fortune 1000 SCRUM development environment. The Leader will support several SCRUM… https://t.co/yoaM75EIWw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Adaptive Software is one of the fastest growing parts of the DRG family. Broadly, Adaptive sells workflow and business process software tools to health plans and Pharmacy Benefit Managers (PBMs), the organizations that determine how… https://t.co/siO1yHuILj https://t.co/2pWDKEAFBh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vice President, Software Engineering: SUMMARY This role will be responsible for Leading and developing a global software engineering product team responsible for the development of Jamfs flagship Apple device management solution, Jamf Pro, and the Jamf… https://t.co/FbQ9eq8nA4 https://t.co/R63waY7z99]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China's Xiaomi picks Hong Kong for $10 billion IPO, lifts lid on financials: BEIJING/HONG KONG (Reuters) - Chinese smartphone and connected device maker Xiaomi is bringing its blockbuster initial public offering to Hong Kong, where it could raise about… https://t.co/FduzsYkISt https://t.co/EBpE0t9GTj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Developer: GAMECHAT LEAD DEVELOPER Gamechat is the greatest thing for gamers since Plumbers stepped on Goombas. We are based in Brooklyn, NY, building an app for console video gamers. This is a contract position that could lead to an equity growth… https://t.co/YBRFZIkiXB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master, Technical Programs – SolidFire: Scrum Master, Technical Programs – SolidFire Close By continuing to use and navigate this website, you are agreeing to the use of cookies. Accept – Careers – Featured Jobs – Customer Support Jobs –… https://t.co/8cy8aIGlfw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manager, Scrum Master: Towers Crescent (12066), United States of America, Vienna, Virginia At Capital One, we’re building a leading information-based technology company. Still founder-led by Chairman and Chief Executive Officer Richard Fairbank, Capital… https://t.co/S1tNU324NS https://t.co/M3qiiMT69G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agile Coach / Scrum Master: Agile Coach / Scrum Master Ref No.:18-07225 Location: Chicago(Naperville), IL / Waukesha,WI, Wisconsin Start Date: 04/18/2018 JOB Discription : Agile Way of Working – Experience as Agile Coach- Extensive experience as Scrum… https://t.co/lGCOsRLWTL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Embedded Software Developer: Sr. Embedded Software Developer Innovate to solve the world’s most important challenges Home and Build Technologies within Honeywell is seeking an expert Sr Embedded Software Developer to grow our back-office cloud… https://t.co/D8lJX9n7Mk https://t.co/eKQCHIiPTM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Product Development Project Manager – II: Responsibilities: * Serve as scrum master for DevOps of a Fortune 500 company * Manage cross-functional project teams utilizing project management processes. Establish and monitor master project plans,… https://t.co/zvBzs8Qe0T https://t.co/CnHW9OBBtn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master Ramp;D: Scrum Master – R &amp; D Responsibilities Facilitate all scrum ceremonies: Sprint Planning: help the team commit to a sprint goal with your product owner and decompose all stories and defect work into tasks with owners and estimates.… https://t.co/QAQ2bZvT9K https://t.co/eVXVfOmCLO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Summary: The Scrum Master will be responsible for managing multiple Scrum teams, leading daily meetings, organizing events, sprint planning, review, grooming, and retrospectives. This will include working with managers and teams, both… https://t.co/rdog3Io5yQ https://t.co/ArHSkcGDhq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Configuration Management Analyst: Overview Nashville, Tenn.-based Bridgestone Americas, Inc. is the U.S. subsidiary of Bridgestone Corporation, the world’s largest tire and rubber company. Bridgestone Americas and its subsidiaries develop,… https://t.co/2yCdicZoDV https://t.co/0TlwyuhRBt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Application Eng (COBOL): Description:JOB DESCRIPTION: POSITION SUMMARY(program supporting/general position overview): Provide programming support with a minimum of supervision in an environment where a COBOL/RPG/SQL system is transitioning to a… https://t.co/qrvm3quLci https://t.co/solH1AnpDE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Description: Job Description: 　 The Maritime Solutions Division (MSD) of Leidos’ Advanced Systems Group develops and deploys advanced technology solutions that address existing and emerging maritime missions of national importance for a… https://t.co/kCjfrsGZwz https://t.co/Px5j1nCI77]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Requisition ID ******* Job Locations US-PA-Fort Washington Job Family Operations and Tech Services Posting Description Aon Is Looking For A Scrum Master As part of an industry-leading team, you will help empower results for our clients by… https://t.co/hr5fpGefIB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Systems Analyst – IBM Websphere Portal: Job ID: SS-******* Description: As the health care industry continues to rapidly transform, our IT team conceives, develops and delivers impactful technology solutions to support access to quality, affordable… https://t.co/3AZc1vC73W https://t.co/YsMCYakBHO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Linux Systems Engineer III: Client Reference Code: 216084 Job Scope: We’re looking for a highly motivated individual to join the Video Operations Automation and Tools team. The successful candidate will be part of a group responsible for engineering… https://t.co/mDRFIatCak https://t.co/kmGgnqGatw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Engineer: Position Overview At PNC, our people are our greatest differentiator and competitive advantage in the markets we serve. We are all united in delivering the best experience for our customers. As a Technology Engineer (.Net) within… https://t.co/GK3Uyc2snL https://t.co/9FuBf9maqc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Programmer Analyst I: The IT Billing team in Macon Georgia is seeking a creative and self-motivated senior-level Developer to join the team responsible for the delivery of the new GEICO Billing System. Candidate will be presented with an… https://t.co/D8bixSr10i https://t.co/xcq5gPrHRo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Job Description Job ID: R39123 Locations: VA – Richmond, United States of America, Richmond, Virginia At Capital One, we’re building a leading information-based technology company. Still founder-led by Chairman and Chief Executive Officer… https://t.co/4bjamVPY2N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Analyst: Business Systems Analyst ======================== Req #: ******Location: Ashburn, VA USJob Category: Information TechnologySecurity Clearance: SecretClearance Status: Must Be Current Job Description CACI is looking for an… https://t.co/wsAos0fbSP https://t.co/hawMf1pa8n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Job Title Software Developer Engineer in Test (SDET) – Reporting and Insights: * Software Developer Engineer in Test (SDET) – Reporting and Insights ========================================================== Job Location US-OR-PortlandPosted Date 3 days… https://t.co/o6IoVQ0DNa https://t.co/DncK9aSFEd]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>