<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ClaraJeffery: The reporters interviewed in today's Daily say that they have sources who prefer to come forward to FBI, who are waiting…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SaraMurray: Last week Trump called Ford’s testimony “compelling” and said she was a “very credible witness.” https://t.co/4qIWAOmPZW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ClaraJeffery: "Be Best" https://t.co/pombidah05]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ktumulty: Every time you think this thing has hit rock bottom, it goes lower: Republicans on Senate panel release explicit statement ab…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@anamariecox This, with the “I’m afraid for young [white] men,” and “you never think,” makes me sick to my stomach and clench my teeth with disgust—even more than usual.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @anamariecox: “How’d you get home? I don’t remember. How’d you get there? I don’t remember…What neighborhood? I don’t know. Where’s the…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @davidenrich: We also tracked down a copy of Georgetown Prep's underground newspaper, written in part by Mark Judge. It includes a colum…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @yashar: NEW: Letter from Dr. Christine Blasey Ford’s attorneys to the FBI saying they offered her full cooperation and have not heard b…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @shannonrwatts: “It’s a scary time for young men in America; you can be guilty of something you may not be guilty of.”

Trump called for…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @IndivisibleTeam: Kavanaugh has shown he is hostile to women &amp; has no credibility. We must come together to tell our senators to #Believ…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jbendery: Two former Yale classmates of Kavanaugh's who previously vouched for him just wrote to the Senate Judiciary Committee to note…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AndrewGillum: For anyone who calls this state home, I will fight for your right to healthcare, education, and the chance to succeed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @susannecraig: NEW: Russ Buettner, David Barstow and I got our hands on a massive trove of confidential docs - including 200 tax returns…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RMarieGriffith: "Win or lose, it seems clear that momentum is building.... And while the local races don’t draw the media attention of…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Amy_Siskind: And again the FBI not taking in information from Kavanaugh classmates. https://t.co/yDK955HHZo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @adamgoldmanNYT: President Trump participated in dubious tax schemes during the 1990s, including instances of outright fraud, that great…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Fahrenthold: Damn. NYT says @realDonaldTrump engaged in "outright fraud" to avoid taxes as he assumed his father's wealth. Just startin…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is incredibly brave. Thank you, @JasonKander! https://t.co/1CBJqg2gjP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cappellanus It’s 11:30 here. This hurts!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TVietor08: Good point @LindseyGrahamSC https://t.co/pKpKKi5C5S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @washingtonpost: "What is the truth?" Pastors across the spectrum preach on Kavanaugh and Ford. https://t.co/WWW7ZeOm1O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PhilipRucker: "Much as he’s trying—and he’s definitely trying—Donald Trump is not getting richer off the presidency. Just the opposite.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SikhProf: Homeless man sits at coffee shop.
Charges phone to call his mom.
Staff dumps water on his head.

Why so inhumane?
Everyone de…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fantastic set of texts. I cannot help but also hear, in @rtraister, too, Laurel Thatcher Ulrich's "Well-Behaved Women Seldom Make History," updated and radicalized (though LTU's was always more radical than the bumper sticker let on). https://t.co/LAChnhrhoy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey, #twitterhistorians, looking for ideas/best practices for talking about "Kavanaugh"(i.e sexual assault, memory, privilege, equality) in class. Ideas?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JaneMayerNYer: Key witnesses including lawyers for Ford and Rasor and Yale classmates STILL hadn’t heard from FBI as of last night. htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CtrRelPol: Former @CtrRelPol fellow @esj312! Perspective | Women are deeply divided on Brett Kavanaugh. Here’s why. https://t.co/JqcW6c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rtraister Huge congrats! And thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@rtraister's "Good and Mad" is perhaps the most important book published in 2018. I cannot wait to excerpts of it in my "American Prophets" course. https://t.co/wUTNorSF0N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CPDAction: “I know this is fun for y’all” @SenBobCorker tells two survivors of Sexual assault including our own @traceyecorder. He thin…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mattkatz00: Trump Administration jailed an immigrant child for 25 days in a chain-link holding pen without a bed or shower. https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Sandi: Wait, the Federalist published a Very Bad Take? https://t.co/7N2z49XHwo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AsteadWesley: Which means, rather obviously, he lied to the American public about his involvement https://t.co/ftzpjor5PH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @funder: Take a good look at this video of two women confronting Senator Mitch McConnell at the airport. You can see his staff inappropr…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AnandWrites: This is authoritarianism, plain and simple. They are changing transcripts, changing the historical record of the president…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AdamSerwer: If this story is accurate, Kavanaugh blatantly lied under oath that he first heard about Ramirez' allegations from the New…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ryanbeckwith: A Record 800,000 People Registered to Vote on National Voter Registration Day https://t.co/bZvh42eMC0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kelly_j_baker Your children are the future. Blessed be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NebraskaDems: For the first time in the history of the Nebraska Democratic Party, slate cards were mailed to voters across the state to…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hokie_prof Wait, there is such a thing as an "academic bestie?" (Also, there is such a thing as "leave?")]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KenDilanianNBC: Sen. Flake just said he is having discussions with the WH counsel to push for a more thorough FBI investigation, not ju…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @The_UnSilent_: Donald Trump hates women

#VOTE 

That is all https://t.co/5FyfgpUVoY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lisawade: Concentration Camp (noun): a place where large numbers of people, especially political prisoners or members of persecuted min…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @womensmarch: Get mad. Get mad as hell.

Then, do something about it. Go to https://t.co/Mn1fkOMkXz to host or attend a phonebank for wo…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This @anamariecox and @TheRickWilson conversation broke me. I have talked to friends, colleagues, students--men and women--who have shared their stories. This is a watershed moment. https://t.co/wN0NrIfhxj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ThePlumLineGS: Former FBI agents tell me limits on renewed Kavanaugh probe are highly questionable.

"grossly incomplete, unfair to the…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @markmobility: Q: If Judge Kavanaugh is shown to have lied to the Committee, nomination's over?

FLAKE: Oh yes.

COONS: I would think so…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cparsons: Not a liberal, not a feminist: the target of Beth Moore’s scorn is an evangelical culture that downplays the voices and exper…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @slpng_giants: Can you imagine seeing this on any other network? Can you imagine seeing this and continuing to advertise on it? https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @emptywheel: If Kavanaugh is confirmed w/o anyone getting Squi's testimony, Squi is likely to have blackmail over one of the most powerf…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mboorstein: Rumors have flown about what the Vatican knew about Cardinal McCarrick. We did a detailed probe of specifically who went to…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nycsouthpaw: This is a very partisan document. https://t.co/KRErEb0xwz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PGourevitch: Blasey Ford is not on The White House approved list of four people FBI is allowed to interview, according to @nytimes http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @womensmarch: This is outrageous and unacceptable. https://t.co/26qQ8b8EOd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SamWangPhD: Sounds like Senators Collins and Flake would benefit from hearing from constituents on how they feel about limitations on t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah, @NPR, this is a stupid policy. It's also ahistorical, since "Doctor" in English (and in medieval universities) historically relates to "highest degree" obtained in a field. Ask Samuel Johnson. Ask Shakespeare. https://t.co/jYUzZJHhZZ https://t.co/uWNxAaTesH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HC_Richardson: Human beings. Little girls. "Likely" little girls. For sale. 

For sale.

For money.

Human beings. For money. 

No matt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PeterAlexander: NEW: Neither Christine Blasey Ford, nor her lawyers have been contacted by the FBI, nearly 48 hours after Trump ordered…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @_JoyCastro: “…hundreds of migrant children have been roused in the middle of the night…for a cross-country journey to their new home: a…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Alyssa_Milano: Hello, Florida! I’m going to be spending the day volunteering with your next Governor, @AndrewGillum.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robdelaney Dude. You should reconsider. We are on the ground in NE. @JaneRaybould has a real shot and is the real deal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @shannonrwatts: The 44th season premiere of "Saturday Night Live" generated the show's second highest-rated season debut in six years: h…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HC_Richardson: For this is what Kavanaugh represents: the idea that a few elite leaders should run the country on their own terms, taki…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Amy_Siskind: According to @NBCNews Trump’s tweet last night is lie:  the FBI has not received new instructions.  Their investigation is…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CNNSotu: .@amyklobuchar on the FBI investigation into Brett Kavanaugh: "I'm very concerned about this because the White House should no…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dandrezner: In all seriousness, I want to know if @LibertyU’s Board of Trustees think this tweet is appropriate coming from the preside…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JWGOP: So the "president*" is rigging an FBI investigation in Kavanaugh's favor while whining about a rigged FBI investigation against…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NormEisen: .@richlowry, at the WH I helped vet hundreds of nominees. Every one got an FBI background check. We never told the FBI which…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NormEisen: What, the White House “has given the FBI a list of witnesses they are permitted to interview"? At the WH, I helped vet hundr…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @janekleeb: Sen. @JeffFlake gives props to women who stopped him in the elevator and asked him to believe them. Hopefully, a fair and ju…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SenFeinstein: The FBI's hands must not be tied in this investigation. We need the facts. https://t.co/GR7TFhDG9k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NBCNews: White House limits scope of the FBI’s investigation into the allegations against Brett Kavanaugh https://t.co/wJFuYRGwP6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Sifill_LDF: This is not an independent FBI investigation. https://t.co/bylPd99gzc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Mikel_Jollett: This has aged perfectly. https://t.co/bDsApfZ2eB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PGourevitch: eager to hear how @JeffFlake reckons this will serve the credibility of SCOTUS &amp; Senate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PGourevitch: so that's a preliminary list of what the White House most fears for Kavanaugh: Swetnick, documentary corroboration of Base…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This means there is stuff to find and thus to hide. https://t.co/H3zFUpSnN0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the sincerest original. This filmmaker deserves praise, a raise, and more followers. https://t.co/l9Is5ZIVVY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nataliapetrzela: This is definitely a good thing, thought I’m bracing myself for the heavy dose of classism/racism about to get thrown…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JaneRaybould: From @LJSdon -- more on where @SenatorFischer, @BenSasse and I stand on Judge #Kavanaugh's pending confirmation to the hi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some have wondered why not just dump Kavanaugh for another ideologue, say Amy Barrett, who would sail through? @judithd explains why. https://t.co/HWFWHyx1QL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JaneRaybould: Looking to rock your #GBR #Huskers red and show your support for #TeamRaybould? Check out our chum shop! You can get your…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nwlc: BREAKING: These are the men who just voted to move Brett Kavanaugh’s nomination forward:

Chuck Grassley, IA
Orrin Hatch, UT
Lind…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LarrySabato: The real question now is how will this change in the wake of the Kavanaugh controversy, once a resolution occurs? Let's wa…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AnnaHolmes: I read this absolutely devastating @newyorker piece by Joan Didion about drunk, white, privileged high school rapists the s…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jonfavs: Portland Press-Herald: “We have never had a Supreme Court nominee who ripped off the nonpartisan mask the way Kavanaugh did Th…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @bobkristne: "Leaders from two of Nebraska’s largest agriculture organizations, Nebraska Farmers Union and Independent Cattlemen of Nebr…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@agordonreed One of my favorite train rides on the world!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SenFeinstein: BREAKING: Republicans just defeated our motion to subpoena Mark Judge, the individual Dr. Blasey Ford places in the room…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @thinkprogress: Father of Parkland victim criticizes Kavanaugh for saying his life is ruined https://t.co/Iu9V1jVTtY https://t.co/loH0H1…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @boilermaker1978: Retired FBI agent, Frank Montoya just said to Joy Reid, if you have information about Brett Kavanaugh, you can go to a…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saved and printed out (thank you, @rebeccaonion). https://t.co/XCJQf5JaBC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Speak for yourself. You don’t speak for your constituents. https://t.co/RB15O5hLbv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jimsciutto: Breaking: Senate Judiciary Committee has formally requested WH to instruct FBI to do supplemental background check, to end…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PiperPerabo: Kentucky let Senator McConnel know we’d like this FBI investigation. His office phone numbers

DC office: (202) 224-2541
B…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anti-Mormon dog whistle: BARK, BARK, BARK! https://t.co/rwk1B5ssQ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Power concedes nothing without a demand. It never did and it never will." Frederick Douglass (1857), from "If There Is No Struggle, There Is No Progress.” @BlackPastOnline. https://t.co/6ODbv9mJjx https://t.co/a1FWpWzR14]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @indivisibleLNK: This should go without saying, but: you're calling, aren't you? 
 Sasse: 402-476-1400
 Fischer: 402-441-4600]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GilmoreGlenda: So Kavanaugh has a tell. When asked, he paused, swallowed, and said "no I did not." Made me think that he had watched an…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let this haunt him to his political grave, and beyond. He knows better. https://t.co/WJ1joUiAPP]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>