<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[American Eating Habits Are Changing Faster than Fast Food Can Keep Up https://t.co/MsfCXhOdpz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[India's ISRO Successfully Launches 2 UK Earth Observation Satellites https://t.co/DkrEm0TR8x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Survey Finds 85% of Underserved Students Have Access To Only One Digital Device https://t.co/uYbQWuVDii]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For Decades, Some of the Atomic Matter in the Universe Had Not Been Located. Recent Papers Reveal Where It Has Been Hiding https://t.co/2nN8XqysTu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Linux Kernel Has Grown By 225,000 Lines of Code This Year, With Contributions From About 3,300 Developers https://t.co/vlSGQjlxdv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon Says It is Investigating Claims That Its Employees Are Taking Bribes To Sell Internal Data To Merchants To Help Them Increase Their Sales on the Website https://t.co/WKzlL66fPH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automation: The Exaggerated Threat of Robots https://t.co/MAHhDluaBe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Edinburgh's Clock is Almost Never on Time  https://t.co/GNzBrGns4a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Tech Companies Responded To Hurricane Florence https://t.co/MEAZh2h60I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Addiction To Fortnite Cited In Over 200 Divorce Petitions https://t.co/ILEoPJw4LV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Research Proving People Don't RTFM, Resent 'Over-Featured' Products, Wins Ig Nobel Prize https://t.co/NC8Y5KS6fq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does LinkedIn Suck? https://t.co/49JguBEzBk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To Fight Climate Change, California Says 'We're Launching Our Own Damn Satellite' https://t.co/avwXgl4GQx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber Glitch Stops Payments To Drivers, Prices Surge https://t.co/vdlmfNDR6w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[58% of Silicon Valley Tech Workers Delayed Having Kids Because of Housing Costs https://t.co/ugM97XikhN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Slashdot Asks: Have You Ever Gotten Someone Else's Email? https://t.co/XTfL07Wgv1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quantum Experiment Confirms Causality Is Fuzzy https://t.co/x40QYAbEUG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency App Mocks Competitor For Getting Hacked. Gets Hacked 4 Days Later https://t.co/52fbhqJtyl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do Data Breaches Affect Stock Performance in the Long Run? https://t.co/PVXUmjLJsZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some Northern California Cities Are Blocking Deployment of 5G Towers https://t.co/pW2nZP0udE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man Jailed For Hundreds of Fake TripAdvisor Reviews https://t.co/31hbW97gtF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Temporarily Brings Back the www In Chrome URLs -- But Should They? https://t.co/lUflaTalbo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nvidia Scanner Brings One-Click Overclocking To Its GeForce RTX Graphics Cards https://t.co/fIsMSP3RUJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SpaceX Says It Signed First Private Passenger To the Moon https://t.co/qmMQIc7MAs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Study Suggests BPA-Free Plastics Are Just As Harmful To Health https://t.co/2d8JZTO2uB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US Lawmakers Say AI Deepfakes 'Have the Potential To Disrupt Every Facet of Our Society' https://t.co/UH8kymciok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drone Startup Airware Is Shutting Down After Raising $118 Million https://t.co/IKQCzCUIqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[San Francisco Gets Its First Cashierless Store https://t.co/ups9dkRJhv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Cardiologists Think About the Apple Watch's Heart-Tracking Feature https://t.co/k6TTF1qFOg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Can't More Than Four People Have a Conversation at Once? https://t.co/rLasUIY4rZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some Linux Gamers Using Wine/DXVK To Play Blizzard's Overwatch Banned https://t.co/poz0b9K7u4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Almost Half of US Cellphone Calls Will Be Scams By Next Year, Says Report https://t.co/rjv8okeGdY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nintendo Switch Cloud Save Data Disappears If You Cancel Subscription https://t.co/tdddltNJxY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Built a Prototype of a Censored Search Engine For China That Links Users' Searches To Their Personal Phone Numbers: The Intercept https://t.co/KCzOX12Odh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Road Makers Turn To Recycled Plastic For Tougher Surfaces https://t.co/tfoqkLVadI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Man Behind the EU's Copyright Law is 'Surprised' By What's in the Proposal https://t.co/Ac3VFy24tg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google-Funded Study Finds Cash Beats Typical Development Aid https://t.co/unYk1Za7FZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Seven Dirty Words' Restriction Policy Lifted from .US Domain Name Registrations https://t.co/sKic38mefI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Native Support For Windows File Sharing Coming To Chrome OS https://t.co/91zT6xUOY5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Slashdot Asks: What Book(s) Are You Reading This Month? https://t.co/FUINJxbdFt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google To Kill Its Developer Platform Fabric in Mid-2019, Pushes Developers To Firebase https://t.co/kOVI8uFnhS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New iPhones, new Galaxies: Who's the Bigger Copycat? https://t.co/ICLKEf8igW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple Has Started Paying Hackers for iPhone Exploits https://t.co/IpBa8Ojh3R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the Weather Channel Made That Insane Hurricane Florence Storm Surge Animation https://t.co/AhIpQs8dCX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FCC Data Exaggerates Broadband Access On Tribal Lands https://t.co/Af5HZlNfeI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OnePlus 6T Trades the Headphone Jack For Better Battery Life https://t.co/NgWZZJ5zUb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FBI Mysteriously Closes New Mexico Observatory https://t.co/5VSLweJUst]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plan To Build a Genetic Noah's Ark Includes a Staggering 66,000 Species https://t.co/f6mmms2hgG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia's Great Barrier Reef Showing 'Signs of Recovery' https://t.co/m0ZnXRJRM7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MIT Is Building a Health-Tracking Sensor That Can See Through Walls https://t.co/eqrK0G2Er6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Apple's 3D Touch a 'Huge Waste' of Engineering Talent? https://t.co/rHalGkfJ0f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Limo Firm To Uber: You Misclassify Your Drivers As Contractors, Which Is Unfair https://t.co/JE4DpyWGlQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook Will Start Facing-Checking Pictures, Videos https://t.co/qI4udp6k8o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Windows, Linux Kodi Users Infected With Cryptomining Malware https://t.co/uQpejdxZOG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Auto, Tech Industries Urge Congress To Pass Self-Driving Legislation https://t.co/rlLgV3qPZt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leaked Video Shows Google Executives' Candid Reaction To Trump Victory https://t.co/EphRYF4BcL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Almost 'All Modern Computers' Affected By Cold Boot Attack, Researchers Warn https://t.co/TODWDfLYNM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook Creates an AI-Based Tool To Automate Bug Fixes https://t.co/Un7Agc5CS1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mozilla Enables WebRender By Default On Firefox Nightly https://t.co/ACLkjc8v47]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Google Scientist Resigns Over 'Forfeiture of Our Values' in China https://t.co/Y6722fYVao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alphabet's Loon Balloons Just Beamed the Internet Across 620 Miles https://t.co/luVqNcHA4D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple Tries To Wipe AirPower From the History Books https://t.co/HkG9yPclpM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jeff Bezos Announces $2 Billion Philanthropic Effort To Help Homeless Families and Start Preschools in Low-income Communities https://t.co/EW6DkuVMp7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US Carriers Introduce Project Verify To Replace Individual App Passwords https://t.co/VWAjCcvDb2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Joins Movement To Dump 'Offensive' Master, Slave Terms https://t.co/CykGmIxzZH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK's GCHQ Intelligence Agency Violated Human Rights With Its Mass Surveillance Tactics, Top European Court Rules https://t.co/9klY7NC6hF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[iPhoneXsMax, Now That's a Tongue Twister https://t.co/5jTyDbdLHN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China Now the Most Prolific Contributor To Physical Sciences, Engineering, and Math https://t.co/VNbO8Qzx4d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple Moves the iPhone Away From Physical SIMs https://t.co/krjbA5kDlf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boring Company Approved To Build Futuristic Garage That Would Connect To Underground Commuter Tunnel https://t.co/pDpjeQzEJG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scientists Discover a 'Tuneable' Novel Quantum State of Matter https://t.co/drTHQdDCuY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple, Huawei Both Claim First 7nm Smartphone Chips https://t.co/9RId26SsIf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla Issues Software Update To Extend Some Cars' Batteries Due To Hurricane Florence https://t.co/GTPYJDtITM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple Discontinues iPhone X, No Longer Sells iPhones With Headphone Jacks https://t.co/taJuXCKIn6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[European Parliament Passes Resolution Calling For An International Ban On Killer Robots https://t.co/azXpOzJzMm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency's 80 Percent Plunge Is Now Worse Than the Dot-Com Crash https://t.co/MBpOQ9SBmd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The EU Can Still Be Saved From Its Internet-Wrecking Copyright Plan https://t.co/rUtEJ51WL7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some Students Say Having To Speak in Front of the Class is an Unreasonable Burden For Those With Anxiety and Are Requesting Alternative Options https://t.co/aRjEZvRvhs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple Watch Series 4 Includes a Bigger Display, ECG Support, and 64-Bit S4 Chip https://t.co/ZYZCAd5Xel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EU To Give Internet Firms 1 Hour To Remove Extremist Content https://t.co/Zi7UlBROzY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will you be buying the new Apple iPhone XS, XS Max, or XR?

#AppleEvent #iPhoneXS #Apple]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before It Was Hacked, Equifax Had a Different Fear: Chinese Spying https://t.co/P5TMvg4c1M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google is Killing Its 4-Yr-Old Inbox Email App https://t.co/rSsWnxgbzz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple Unveils iPhone Xs, iPhone Xs Max https://t.co/c3hRfr3fHP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple Can Delete Purchased Movies From Your Library Without Telling You https://t.co/6R1FzrKQEL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senators Grill Pompeo on Vulnerable Cybersecurity at State Department https://t.co/sNWJlkDK0M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Explosive Problem With Recycling Phones, Tablets and Other Gadgets: They Literally Catch Fire. https://t.co/dLnDsiuE1D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Citing 'Moral Requirement To Make Money', Pharma CEO Jacks Drug Price 400% https://t.co/3IsVFRR1f2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft is Interrupting Chrome and Firefox Installations To Promote Its Edge Browser in the Newest Windows 10 Build https://t.co/G8zzf4TNIb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FDA Chief Considers Ban of All Flavored E-Cigarettes https://t.co/4o1paQZAwg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[European Parliament Votes in Favor of Controversial Copyright Laws https://t.co/T5cKhjDlMo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[T-Mobile, Ericsson Sign $3.5 Billion 5G Agreement https://t.co/eSU624kfop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teens Would Rather Text Their Friends Than Talk To Them In Person, Poll Shows https://t.co/23gKfQc0zD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solid-State Battery Startup Claims Breakthrough For Electric Vehicles https://t.co/dLbuJZf14q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boeing Is Calling Back Its Retirees To Try To Fix Delays At Its 737 Jetliner Plant https://t.co/Drqa20SCqh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Researchers Come Out With Yet Another Unnerving, New Deepfake Method https://t.co/ErgbjPbAJY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marshall Islands Warned Against Adopting Digital Currency https://t.co/N9JUho9aBq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Safe AI Requires Cultural Intelligence https://t.co/N3VuQcclLZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Windows 10 Will Use the Cloud To Free Up Disk Space https://t.co/0JIFKKs4Wd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Replaces Its USB-C Headphone Adapter With a More Expensive Version https://t.co/35PemcRa0h]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>