<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@lancegodard Thanks for RT!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PR opp for BC law firms + co.'s : Is your firm helping employees manage their childcare next week?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mbeese: Thank you Per Casey @Tenrec !  This is a great sponsorship! FREE WIFI in the meeting rooms at #LMA12!  #lmamkt #legalmarketing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woohoo! Congrats, Ross! RT @david_bilinsky: Congrats to @RossFishman on just being inducted to LMA Midwest Hall of Fame! Well deserved!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice, short + practical posts! RT @Jillyhump: new blog by @McCarthy_ca http://t.co/UqJcjxIG on BC employ, labour + human resources! #bclegal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats NY! RT @GreatJakes: #NYLMA Chapter Celebrates 20th Annivrsy - great photo @jeffscalzi1 @DeborahFarone http://t.co/JTwc9QIr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy 4 u! RT @JillRako: Beyond proud of Legal Marketing Assoc's Ohio Chapter -  Chapter of the Year! @LMAOhio #LMA…http://t.co/1preqwTh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still so many *skiers* w/o helmets! RT @lululemon:  bike helmets, do you go for safety or style? We  solve for both! http://t.co/HrfHZg07]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RoyalColumbian: What is the single best thing we can do for our health. Watch this video.http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=aUaInS6HIGo& ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wooho RT @jjohnsonNYC: CONGRATS to Melissa Marshall of Clark Hill PLC : LMA's 2012 Rising Star!  http://t.co/Tc7vzahK  #LMAMKT  #LMA12]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RoyalColumbian: Thank you Knights of Columbus British Columbia Charity Foundation for your strong belief in supporting RCH! http://t ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out how to get more from your sponsorships   http://t.co/BmpBkyyB  #bclegal #in #Marketing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kevwrites: Whoa. MT @MMFlint: Canadians, in case you missed it tonight: Romney: "I'll get us that oil from Canada we deserve!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Legal Marketing Assoc Outstanding Chapter Award honourable mention to Southeastern Chapter! Well done @LMA_SE! #LMA12]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats to all Legal Marketing Assoc award winners! So happy for Canadian award recipients: @BoughtonLaw, @FaskenMartineau, @BlakesLaw  #in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats to @BlakesLaw for FIRST place award from LMA for holiday card "Blakes Gives Thanks"! Impressive!!  #bclegal #LMA12 #LMA12]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Legal Mrkg Assoc awards honourable mention 2 @FaskenMartineau 4 media relations training. Congrats Gillian, Stephen + team! #LMA12 #bclegal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Legal Mktg Assoc annces all award winners, many Canadian firms! Congrats to @BoughtonLaw (3rd place shoestring bdgt categ) #bclegal #LMA12]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BLGLaw: Companies need to be aware of the opportunities for trade-mark infringers to take advantage,says Kathleen Lemieux http://t.c ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Banish orphan mktg activities. All should be mapped to strategic goals + supported w/other efforts that reach your tgt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tx, Kevin! RT @kevinokeefe: Event Sponsorships: Making the Most of Your Spend - @lawyerpr http://t.co/HPJnlxSC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spring break in Vanc during 2012 Legal Marketing Association (LMA) Annual Conference, so not attending. Will miss many friends + programs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Announced the Legal Marketing Assoc. Outstanding Chapter Award winner! Congrats to Ohio Chapter + tx to all Chapters who submitted! @LMAOhio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be announcing the Legal Marketing Association Outstanding Chapter Award recipient shortly. Can't wait! Our very own Vancouver Chapter …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RoyalColumbian: RCHF is raising funds to treat 1,400 more cardiac and stroke patients a year. Help us reach our $2,8 million goal. W ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamJGrossman Done -- short and sweet!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not a nimble lot  but Cowper due credit 4 wading in. RT @ianmulgrew: Tepid respnse re B.C. justice refrm pln  http://t.co/rVv2n8VG  #bclegal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No surprses: knowng client's biz + persnl contct alwys rank high RT @ZSARecruitment: marketing firm in right ways?  http://t.co/wd1ab6gX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LMA Vancver's annual corp counsel evnt, Mar 29 noon. I Try to attnd evry yr + get updated on client buyng behavior.  #in #bclegal #solosmall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now that's leadership! RT @BullHousser: Bull Housser founding corporate partner of  BC Aboriginal Business Association http://t.co/tuC4pZbo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this. And so true!  Might work w/kids too ..RT @rebeccawcheung: What my dog taught me about PR via @cprsvancouver http://t.co/tXHMX4EN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SpagnuoloLaw: Global BC | Vancouver now the most expensive city in North America http://t.co/MNFAJoN6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks, Patty!  :) RT @PattyMC22: @lawyerPR back atcha my friend! #amazingfriend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conniecrosby Most welcome!  Yes, luv the pic, but was referring to your  profile. Never met a "guerrilla librarian" before :) Love that!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When was last time u wandered thru your LinkedIn contacts? I did this today + realized, whoa, that's an impressive cast of characters ! #in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conniecrosby has a great twitter profile. Made me smile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ten Tips to Get Back to Normal after a Car Accident http://t.co/qoFwxc2F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@Miss604: My jaw is on the floor! RT @theprovince: $3 million rebuild for City of #Vancouver website http://t.co/1mPxRv4X" Who r did work?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Working out, playing on Blackberry (yes, they still operate), and toying on twitter. Just posted new twitter bio.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@BoughtonLaw: Boughton is hiring a Systems Analyst. If you think you've got what it takes, apply today! http://t.co/hThjwwzE" Great firm!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jordan_law21: Unexpected and very cool! Honoured to be named one of 25 Most Influential  Canadian Lawyers: http://t.co/8ulG0y2b via  ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@McQuarrieHunter: Congratulations to Cindy Zheng on winning her first trial!" Awesome!!!! High five, Cindy!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RoyalColumbian: Good tips! RT @interior_health: Do you know what to do if your child is stung by a bee? Check out #HealthMattersOnli ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @thriveorg: Curious about Pinterest?  Here's a great resource to learn how to use this platform for your business: http://t.co/ksYHuEJi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JJESearch: Now recruiting in #NYC for a Senior #PR Specialist for Skadden: http://t.co/TPkf6ygf  #publicrelations #mediarelations #L ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LawSocietyofBC: Did you know members of the public can receive Law Society publications and notices? Sign up at http://t.co/LYr6otSA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So excited! Netflix has new MI-5 episodes! If you haven't seen this smart British Intelligence spy show, it's like 24 meets Criminal Minds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoa ... forgot to thank you for all the RTs @BIVCommunity !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Praying they find survivors at #elliotLake . Could have been any one of us inside that mall on Saturday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RoyalColumbian: Tx @McQuarrieHunter for donating $50,000 for new Multiprpse Intervent'l Suite #BCHC #NewWest #cba http://t.co/BoKyEx0P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@RoyalColumbian: After presenting us with a $50,000 donation @McQuarrieHunter partners learn about Dr. Six's plan to treat an aneurysm ..."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WOW! RT @RoyalColumbian: We r honoured 2 accept $50,000 donatn frm @McQuarrieHunter for MPIS campaign http://t.co/EqjVs6c0 #newwest #BCLegal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear publishers: retain advtsers by hiring + training good in-house graphic designers to work on their ads. Tired of correcting ads.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here I am post awards with Karen @canlawmag http://t.co/nvwLwTo1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Standing with karen lorimer @canlawmag in vancouver HELM awards! She's a rock star for traveling for TO to vanc for awards!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CanLawMag: And the winner for Innovative Special Events is Fasken Martineau #helmawards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just part of the HELM crowd - following anncmt of door prizes! http://t.co/aLZ0c92X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read BIV for complete coverage of awards! @BIVcommunity #bclaw. #lmamkt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pierblue95 tx for following awards! Sitting with D !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last HELM award in event category goes to ...Fasken Brenda Plowman! #bclaw #lmamkt @bivcommunity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Katie stowe accepting award for FMC speaks eloquently about firm's community focus http://t.co/qkXYHjc7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HELM Community award goes to ... FMC katie Stowe #bclaw  #lmamkt @bivcommunity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sorry... Slater Vecchio!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HELM's small firm marketing award presented to ....Slater Vechio ! #bclaw #lmamkt. @bivcommunity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blair accepting award! http://t.co/9xNvYswY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next HELM award: integrated mktg award....goes to... Fasken + Blair Lill! #bclaw #lmamkt @bivcommunity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HELM award for practice mgt award presented to... FMC Katie Stowe! #smallfirm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aren't they lovely?! http://t.co/6SEcRECc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sitting at #lmamkt vancouver HELM with the lovely D Chung + B Roach et al. at the Judges table waiting for winners 2 b announced!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @terrybecker: Here's a netwking opp for those in the field-Estate and Success Planning Roundtable invitation http://t.co/QomGtgQR #pi ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HELLO Friday!  What a week. Inspired by my amazing clients, their entrepreneurial spirit + my dedicated team. So grateful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PattyMC22 You are too sweet. And, yes! We must!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sent via postal service? : # RT @theprovince: Luka #Magnotta could b extradited within days, says German prosecutor http://t.co/DGrJLQpL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahhh. Can I come w u CBC? RT @CBCVancouver: New Post: CBCMusic.ca Presents Leonard Cohen - Rogers Arena - Nov.12 http://t.co/CW7XKkrL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huh. RT @kevinokeefe: Microsft exec @derrickconnell : Bing better than Google, but users still don’t believe it http://t.co/AoR2aNeE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tx! RT @LindsayGriffith: Read The Legal Mkter' Daily ▸ today's top stories via @DuetsBlog @lawyerPR ▸ http://t.co/Viy2V6Dx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tla_bc Feel better now? :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And esp for @tla_bc  RT @Jaclyn_LC: Hey #Vancovuer! This is for you. http://t.co/Y5A8U6zh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They'd be lucky to have you, Ms P !RT @PattyMC22: Very excited to have been nominated to the board of directors of @YWCAofCalgary. #Calgary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevwrites You were trying to teach him to dance again, weren't you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you noticed Queen Eliz carries her purse even while at home in Buck Palace? What do you think she's got in there?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice one, Dave! RT @heather_morse: When do you ask for business? Guest post by Dave Bruns. #lmamkt http://t.co/WI4haYKc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Monica_MLB: Huge development! RT@joshualenon Online dispute process now official in BC. No lawyers allowed. http://t.co/AqJ1pPXP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LinkedIn users: change yur password!  Recently stolen + users told  2 change pswd.  Great tool 4 managing passwrds: http://t.co/O3NM98tg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@syladurantaye Journalists in training!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@syladurantaye What are YOU doing in the children's section of the library?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RoyalColumbian: Thx Wilson family for starting a $5000 trust fund for families whose lives become chaos when their newborns are in N ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Barbaric + sickening RT @david_bilinsky: Join in condemning this: http://t.co/bN6zVJWb #BCLegal #law #justice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every now + then I get to write an ad so meaningful I get teary while drafting copy. Ads shld emote + hope readers feel tug.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kevinokeefe: What is it that journalists do? It can’t be reduced to just one thing - @jonathanstray http://t.co/Ab202NBz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LawSocietyofBC: New client or fraudster? Check out the list of names fraudsters have used in BC:  http://t.co/KaobQRlh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Impressive! "@HarperGreyLLP: Six HG lawyers named "Leading Practitioners" in 2012 Lexpert Directory: http://t.co/DFpFAx1d"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YES!!  RT @News1130radio: Parent advisory councils push for wifi-free schools http://t.co/UVyI7PD7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judging inspired legal marketers' submissions via LMA Vanc's Honour'g Excel. in Legal Mktg (HELM). Impressed. #bclegal #in #smallfirm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @News1130radio: VPD officer's gun lost on the Downtown Eastside http://t.co/LFqEGc91]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@david_bilinsky Thanks, Dave!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love that! RT @rebeccawcheung: Start every marketing plan with "why?" Not what or where or how but why! #BCAMAVision  #bclegal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every morning I wonder "how much coffee is too much".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's more: http://t.co/ISmCsGq8 @CLEBC: What  clients want? Be practical, efficient ... #clebc #keepingclientshappy  #bclegal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[21 yr old double-lung transplnt recipient Helene Campbell is "breath-taking"  spokspson 4 orgn donatn. 2 shrt vids:    http://t.co/CifFIn2B]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>