<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server Developer: The resource will be working on integration projects using SQL 2008/2012/2017, Workload Automation (Scheduling tool). We are looking for a DBA who can provide SQL Server development skills mostly around stored procedure development… https://t.co/VbYdKdx2vM https://t.co/OqWAKXMneQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior PL/SQL Developer: LOCATION: Seaside, CA or Remote POSITION DESCRIPTION: Aderas is seeking a Senior PL/SQL to work on a Department of Defense Contract. REQUIRED EDUCATION: * Bachelors degree(May substitute equivalent of 4 years experience for a… https://t.co/ZFKba1F9Ag https://t.co/wKBbLex8CM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MySQL DBA/Software Engineer: MySQL DBA/Software Engineer First 6 months to one year the role will be 50/50 1st shift/2nd shift then after that all 1st Shift Need a strong MYSQL DBA with good python knowledge to automate tasks. You will need server… https://t.co/pQTd7klKHf https://t.co/DFRK74J5DB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Database Administrator, Optionis Group Warrington (Ref: Job TitleSQL Database Administrator, Optionis Group Warrington (Ref: R233) Location: Warrington Salary: up to 50,000 Contract Type: Full time,Permanent SQL DBA for the Optionis Group in… https://t.co/VNs599dMXg https://t.co/QRqaS6JKM8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SNB's Maechler says cryptocurrencies won't rival conventional currency: ZURICH (Reuters) - Cryptocurrencies are not true competitors to conventional currencies despite soaring interest in products like bitcoin, Swiss National Bank Governing Board member… https://t.co/5eLtmGXPGx https://t.co/EtOw3ArTpK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior business analyst with SQL experience: Primary point of contact for interface between the business users and IT teams. Formulates and defines systems scope and objectives through research and fact-finding, combined with a basic understanding of… https://t.co/kI8zvsJkse https://t.co/obAEBzRSMa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Splunk Engineer: Description: Leidos currently has a need for a Sr Splunk Engineer for a highly visible cyber security single-award IDIQ vehicle that provides security operations center (SOC) support, cyber analysis, application development, and a… https://t.co/Jl6RDxx5lo https://t.co/ZHBBGHdcDF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developers: Description: We have immediate opportunities for Senior Software Developers to join a world class, center of excellence.  Leidos was named by LinkedIn as one of the best U.S. Companies and Forbes’ “America’s Top 500” list. At… https://t.co/0rQ6FC5SQT https://t.co/ltXG6JWmG3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior PL/SQL Developer: LOCATION: Seaside, CA or Remote POSITION DESCRIPTION: Aderas is seeking a Junior PL/SQL to work on a Department of Defense Contract. REQUIRED EDUCATION: * Bachelors degree (May substitute equivalent of 4 years experience for a… https://t.co/nDZpnYnCfN https://t.co/Fs91vCGVkk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Hi , Greetings from Macropace Technologies. We have a job opening which might suit you, please find below job description and let me know your if you are interested on this position. Total Experience: Expected Salary: Open for… https://t.co/Lv1g9qyd4b https://t.co/t4p2rvuL0p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spotify shares attract all ages, not just Millennials: NEW YORK (Reuters) - The buzzy debut of Spotify Technology SA on the New York Stock Exchange on Tuesday drew retail investors across generations, not just the Millennials who make up the largest… https://t.co/H1Ajmmy9J5 https://t.co/dpAKJZlHQT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle &amp; SQL DBA $140k: Pittsburgh, PA Full-time $120k – $140k Posted Today If you are a Oracle DBA with experience, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us Fantastic environment that offers a lot of stability and great benefits What You Will Be… https://t.co/6Ultp5yuz0 https://t.co/0Fv4qYcOJ4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL/SQL Big Data Developer: PL/SQL Big Data Developer – Datanomics – Temple Terrace, FL – 03-09-2018 | ******** Toggle navigation – Tech Careers – Job Search – Skills Center – Dice Careers Mobile – Career Explorer – Salary Predictor – Career Paths –… https://t.co/BQ7eglTatZ https://t.co/8fyvIdcgmz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Administrator (DBA)-SQL: Join our team of SQL Professionals and work on dynamic long-term projects. The majority of our team members are long-term employees who enjoy consistent work and a collaborative team approach! * Experience with SQL… https://t.co/AracZ7g4DC https://t.co/mbzzSnQjJS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack .Net Developer: Search and apply for jobs at Zachary Piper | Careers at Zachary Piper Careers Search Jobs Connect With Us Full Stack .Net Developer Job Attributes Job Id: 17463Job Category: Software Applications &amp; ERPJob Location: Kennett… https://t.co/K0a7loTszq https://t.co/W29G1k9Ny1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advanced Product Solutions Developer: Company Name: HealthStream, Inc. Position Title: Advanced Product Solutions Developer Location: 209 10^th Avenue South, Suite 450, Nashville, TN 37203 Days/Hours: Mon Fri / 8 a.m. to 5 p.m. Job Summary: Design,… https://t.co/75Qva28lRB https://t.co/XogG8x5VOF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer: .NET Developer Fort worth, Texas – United States Job Start Date – 03/27/18, Posted Date – 03/27/18 Primary SkillsJavaScript,Bootstrap,.net,C#,ReactJS,Redux,Webpack,Material UI,Knockout JS,Sagas,.NET Web APITax TermsC2C,W-2OverviewThis… https://t.co/RSZ8QGikJE https://t.co/Ld18Kv3fMc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Foxconn and Sirin Labs to make first blockchain smartphone: (Reuters) - Swiss-Israeli technology firm Sirin Labs said that FIH Mobile Ltd, a subsidiary of world's largest contract electronics manufacturer Foxconn, will manufacture its Finney blockchain… https://t.co/SZygn85Zz3 https://t.co/39qIKX4j3o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer/Architect: SQL Developer/Architect MEMPHIS, Tennessee – United States Job Start Date – 03/06/18, Posted Date – 03/06/18 Primary SkillsSQL,Agile,Data ModelingTax TermsC2COverview SQL Developer/Architect * 5+ years experience Requirements… https://t.co/gh0hAv5PPC https://t.co/MaaF79sLHw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate, Apps Support # 180031171: Associate, Apps Support Columbus, OH. Provide app support for ETL apps. Perform management &amp; problem resolution. Master’s or equivalent in CS, Engineering (any), or related field + 2 years relevant experience or… https://t.co/sddS1XoEZ8 https://t.co/Z9ne0oQbfI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: T-SQL Developer memphis, Tennessee – United States Job Start Date – 03/27/18, Posted Date – 03/27/18 Primary **********,C#,T-SQLTax TermsC2COverview Position: (SQL Server with C# or ******* experience) The Packaging Systems Application… https://t.co/3Fc1C4U5Wi https://t.co/5EvidE1h7y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer Analyst-ETL Developer: Programmer Analyst – ETL Developer DSS86528656 *Richmond, VA* ETL software design, development and enhancements, documentation and maintenance work; mentoring less senior team members and knowledge transfer very… https://t.co/PoRJ9GXynX https://t.co/Jcn72VjbA7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BI/SQL Developer: Category: Analytics and Emerging Digital Technologies City: Hamilton Township, New Jersey, United States Position ID: J0318-1101 Employment Type: Full Time Meet our professionals CGI: A place to build an IT career Position Description:… https://t.co/1LWSof7PnU https://t.co/rROUsnmqyK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Software Developer Job Description: Parsley Energy Operations, LLC seeks Software Developer to work at its office in Austin, TX. Develop new software solutions, including responsibility for components of medium size and complexity and… https://t.co/OQuqtFNCis https://t.co/OpymQ0FP3m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consumer tech gets reprieve as U.S., China spar over tariffs: BEIJING (Reuters) - Information technology products, from cellphones to personal computers, have largely escaped the latest salvo of U.S.-China trade measures despite accounting for a… https://t.co/ZvGgNk591V https://t.co/QETn86HTkF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Description: Leidos ranks in the top 40 on LinkedIns 2017 “Top Companies” list. We offer challenging and meaningful problems, a collaborative culture, and support for your career goals and growth.   The Mission Systems Integration… https://t.co/z74A2TnQhr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior SQL Server Database Administrator: Senior SQL Server Database Administrator Lincoln, Rhode Island United States Job Start Date – 03/13/18, Posted Date – 03/13/18 Primary SkillsSQL DBATax TermsC2COverview Client: Amica Location: Lincoln, RI… https://t.co/x7ypej8bG5 https://t.co/fNJbwr5GDi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Engineer MySQL DBA: *FOR THE FIRST 6 MONTHS TO 1 YEAR THIS POSITION WILL BE 50% 1ST SHIFT AND 50% 2ND SHIFT. ONCE THE ENVIRONMENT GET’S TO WHERE IT NEEDS TO BE THE ROLE WILL SWITCH TO ONLY 1ST SHIFT/NORMAL BUSINESS HOURS** Chicago, IL Under general… https://t.co/3K8DoGL0cf https://t.co/pSAHdLsR5J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL/SQL Big Data Developer: PL/SQL Big Data Developer – Datanomics – Temple Terrace, FL – 03-09-2018 | ******** Toggle navigation – Tech Careers – Job Search – Skills Center – Dice Careers Mobile – Career Explorer – Salary Predictor – Career Paths –… https://t.co/MQsTMRiOe6 https://t.co/YNk4abm3lo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Engineer (Hadoop – Strong SQL Required!!): This is NOT a contract or contractor role – PLEASE DO NOT submit your resume if you are not interested in full-time employment (FTE). Will be directly supporting software engineers using our… https://t.co/5jFq2yKZHa https://t.co/JeN4m1gWxe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple Pay arrives in Brazil, partnering with Itaú Unibanco: SAO PAULO (Reuters) - Apple Inc's mobile payment platform Apple Pay arrived in Brazil on Wednesday with an exclusive partnership with Itaú Unibanco Holding SA, the country's largest private… https://t.co/z5v1a3RiVC https://t.co/AXLrkW6Ucv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer (PHP/MySQL + React): About Us Refersion is a fast growing, bootstrapped, and profitable B2B app development company located in New York City. Our flagship product is a sales tracking and marketing (SaaS) platform in the e-commerce… https://t.co/Jysmh3WYnr https://t.co/dvFTGCO70X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior PL/SQL Developer: LOCATION: Seaside, CA or Remote POSITION DESCRIPTION: Aderas is seeking a Junior PL/SQL to work on a Department of Defense Contract. REQUIRED EDUCATION: * Bachelors degree PRIMARY JOB DUTIES: * Perform business and data… https://t.co/pPOiT9rDpc https://t.co/x5gm6ekKLa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developers: Description: We have immediate opportunities for Senior Software Developers to join a world class, center of excellence.  Leidos was named by LinkedIn as one of the best U.S. Companies and Forbes’ “America’s Top 500” list. At… https://t.co/9IhqfOGhBj https://t.co/3qTu8egpIB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle Pl/SQL Developer: Job TitleOracle Pl/SQL Developer – ID:31001 Duration12 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsOracle, PL-SQL, Data Warehousing, UNIX Servers (AIX 6.x), Shell Scripting LocationTorrance, CA Date Posted02/15/2018 FOR IMMEDIATE DETAILS,… https://t.co/NGXnoxEcAr https://t.co/EdikcaFSsx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer: Description Are you a talented Network Engineer looking for the next step in your career ? Check out PSS! Position Description PSS, Inc. is actively seeking a Senior Network Engineer to join our growing team located inChantilly, VA.… https://t.co/hY8IUeNZer https://t.co/mlzO3l9nTJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL &amp; Hadoop Developer: SQL &amp; Hadoop Developer THIS IS A W2 CONTRACT TO HIRE OPPORTUNITY. CORP TO CORP REPRESENTATIVES OR APPLICANTS NEED NOT APPLY (NO C2C) ALIS Software is seeking an experienced SQL Developer for a contract to hire opportunity with an… https://t.co/tYhKT495dz https://t.co/y9Ieow3EX7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Denmark hits 1,200 former Uber drivers with additional tax: COPENHAGEN (Reuters) - Denmark's tax authorities are demanding nearly 1,200 former Uber drivers to pay an additional $1.9 million in taxes for 2014 and 2015, after finding tax avoidance among… https://t.co/Wn5vGQPKFX https://t.co/roOF0DaeVO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PHP Developer: Linux Academy is seeking a hungry PHP Developer to support our team and the thousands of students around the world who learn through us and our cloud technology. Our mission is to provide advanced training tools that increase skills and… https://t.co/Wsytj2I3b7 https://t.co/0BxycyJNwa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Intelligence Engineer IV: Logistics done differently. At XPO, we know that knowledge is power, and in our world, capturing and analyzing data, will give us the knowledge we need to drive our business forward. As the Business Intelligence (BI)… https://t.co/R06PLhYTBR https://t.co/4MjB5vRS4Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET/SQL Server Developer: .NET/SQL Server Developer Job Locations US-DC-Washington Job ID 10275 Minimum Clearance Required US Citizen Responsibilities Functional Responsibilities:  ISYS Technologies is seeking a .NET/SQL Server Developer. Qualifications… https://t.co/uPImMebEdO https://t.co/ihvWfW7nTJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Database Administrator (DBA): SQL Database Administrator (DBA) JOB DESCRIPTION IPG Photonics is seeking a highly motivated and experienced individual to join our growing IT team and work in a fast-paced, dynamic, high-tech manufacturing company. As a… https://t.co/Rah1aWBk6a https://t.co/vv6wZr3Mw2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer: .NET Developer – Nihaki Systems, Inc. – Malvern, PA – 03-21-2018 | ******** Toggle navigation – Tech Careers – Job Search – Skills Center – Dice Careers Mobile – Career Explorer – Salary Predictor – Career Paths – Career Toolkit Articles… https://t.co/SrZ7OB0uoN https://t.co/kp0paCnYQp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior SailPoint Developer: Prestigious Enterprise Company is currently seeking a Senior SailPoint Java Developer. Candidate will be responsible for designing, developing and supporting key applications for Identity provisioning and governance of user… https://t.co/eLNg0TC4WC https://t.co/Bo5xZj4Hi9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After attacks on Amazon, U.S. Chamber criticizes targeting American business: WASHINGTON (Reuters) - Following attacks by President Donald Trump on https://t.co/slUtAEaHaf Inc , the U.S. Chamber of Commerce criticized attacks by government officials… https://t.co/c9ku9XJOLm https://t.co/rSHSHnwLQG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer With Strong AWS and MySQL: Are you a software engineer turned DevOps enthusiast? Do you want to work for a lifestyle brand powerhouse that is highly profitable and backed by some serious technology? If that sounds like you then check this… https://t.co/3dU2xcrXrI https://t.co/YuyrubuUYC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SR SQL Server DBA: SR SQL Server DBA Oak Brook, Illinois – United States Job Start Date – 03/29/18, Posted Date – 03/29/18 Primary SkillsSR SQL Server DBATax TermsC2COverview Client: Chamberlain Group Role: SR SQL Server DBA Duration: 6 + Openings: 1… https://t.co/M6vvo4sMgG https://t.co/eP9xNQoOy1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior AWS Engineer With Strong MySQL For Massive LifeStyle Brand: Are you a Sr. Software engineer turned DevOps enthusiast? Do you view infrastructure as code? If you want to help take our DevOps culture to the next level, then read this! WHAT IS THE… https://t.co/FD4W4r9mAa https://t.co/8aOxXuJ4rU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Informatica Engineer: Description: THE COMPANY Are you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable,… https://t.co/bKmPDwbuc1 https://t.co/AouWu9O5Zl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[T-SQL Developers – Cerritos CA: T-SQL Developer Cerritos, CA Contract/ Full time Job Description: The candidate should have 3 – 5 years experienced TSQL developer. The candidate should have been Involved in all phases of the project (Documentation,… https://t.co/TsM6nGSFVK https://t.co/AZOPnPpL4l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple discloses gender pay gap at UK operations: (Reuters) - Apple Inc said on Tuesday that men earned 5 percent more on average than women at its UK operations, although the median pay gap was 2 percent in favor of women. https://t.co/Lo6vFpsfty https://t.co/0LdxgqcUOa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Java Developer | Struts, Spring, JavaScript, SQL, SOAP REST Web Services: Full Stack Java Developer | Struts, Spring, JavaScript, SQL, SOAP &amp; REST Web Services Columbus, OH 03-25-2018 Location: Columbus, OH For more than 18 years, CareWorks… https://t.co/aR3WCRqLRt https://t.co/fWppKWeZx6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Informatica Engineer II: Description: THE COMPANY Are you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable,… https://t.co/p447ys3ziG https://t.co/CmRoQzk7gd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Description: Leidos ranks in the top 40 on LinkedIns 2017 “Top Companies” list. We offer challenging and meaningful problems, a collaborative culture, and support for your career goals and growth.   The Mission Systems Integration… https://t.co/q98ujU2VsZ https://t.co/Ce8OmuiZ3Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director Technology – Production Support: Description: THE COMPANY Are you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by… https://t.co/3yz4fmtSCY https://t.co/2Fu2mMbZwj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Governance Architect: Description: The Civil Health Solutions Group is currently seeking a Data Governance Architect to support a large healthcare contract   Design and Implement Data Architecture and Governance solution for Big Data platform… https://t.co/KocM4vK5Ey https://t.co/y0eNptbfiJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Philippine anti-trust agency starts review of Grab-Uber deal: MANILA (Reuters) - The Philippines' anti-trust agency on Tuesday started a review of Uber Technologies Inc's [UBER.UL] proposed sale of its money-losing Southeast Asian business to… https://t.co/d1WH4gM356 https://t.co/2o0JuZW3DP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL/SQL Developer, Journeyman: Description:   PL/SQL Developer, Journeyman Candidate must have or be capable of obtaining a Secret Clearance   Description The candidate will be working with a team of software and network engineering professionals on… https://t.co/zVUx03XM4N https://t.co/aMy7ds9pkI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – https://t.co/ejSGKWK6E6 MVC / MS SQL Back-end 16371: Description Huntington Ingalls Industries – Technical Solutions Division, Integrated Mission Solutions Group (Camber Corporation) provides mission-critical engineering and technical… https://t.co/SjDtVfiE8S https://t.co/cdgbjCD72D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Sign-on Bonus!: Description: If you are a qualified Software Engineer or Cybersecurity professional in Morgantown or surrounding areas and are interested in working in a rewarding environment, we would like to meet with you.   Leidos… https://t.co/E6muF6mUpl https://t.co/a2ITfwVkHp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Integration Analyst: Description: The DoD Information Systems Division of Leidos is seeking a Systems Integration Analyst for the Defense Civilian Personnel Data System (DCPDS) program at San Antonio, Texas.   Job Description: The System… https://t.co/v4LRQIIBQo https://t.co/OEcJUQ3fDA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer (Ruby): Eligo Energy is a rapidly growing energy supplier headquartered in Downtown Chicago. Eligo offers competitive energy supply and related services to commercial and residential customers. If you are passionate about technology… https://t.co/imuCV77R5K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ford could make electric cars in Germany after 2023: Handelsblatt: FRANKFURT (Reuters) - Ford could make electric cars in Germany after 2023, when the life cycle of Ford's Fiesta model is due to end, the head of the carmaker's German business told a… https://t.co/SOnJ3c264W https://t.co/khHwVxEfzE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Engineer: CTERA Networks provides the industrys leading Enterprise File Services Platform and offers a high-growth, innovative environment with an informal, collegial atmosphere. We are growing fast and are always looking for excellent… https://t.co/5vgHZMAMmq https://t.co/GXeGqW5g0h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst – Data insights, SQL, R: San Francisco, CA Full-time Compensation Unspecified Posted Today If you are a Data Analyst with experience, please read on! We are based in beautiful Sausalito, CA. We are an energetic, innovative, and thriving tech… https://t.co/UkO5dlptoU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer Big Data: This is an opportunity to architect, scale, and maintain world-class analytics and optimization infrastructure that supports multiple LP digital businesses. This is a full-time position out of our Delray Beach office.… https://t.co/mZVfqCnWww https://t.co/GLbNr1Cpv1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer: About Onnit: Onnit is an Austin, TX-based health and wellness brand focused on encouraging a peak level of human performance through the best in nutritional supplementation, health-conscious foods, and unconventional fitness equipment and… https://t.co/cKhpIdHeuT https://t.co/vcSDZ64ELr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Panera Bread's website leaks customer records: KrebsOnSecurity: (Reuters) - Bakery-cafe chain Panera Bread's website leaked customer records for at least eight months, cyber security blog KrebsOnSecurity reported on Monday. https://t.co/0cRmYD9FjN https://t.co/eIEf2HYq10]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Backend Engineer: COMPUTER/IT: Livongo Health, Inc. in Mountain View, CA seeks a Senior Software Backend Engineer to assist a team of software engineers to create software features for the company’s new data cloud. Must have Bachelor’s… https://t.co/fPs3iJswoZ https://t.co/a5lclegSS2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer/Support: Description: THE COMPANY Are you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing… https://t.co/MR4vJj7m7t https://t.co/JVDRr917Nz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Governance Architect: Description: The Civil Health Solutions Group is currently seeking a Data Governance Architect to support a large healthcare contract   Design and Implement Data Architecture and Governance solution for Big Data platform… https://t.co/zrAcPVPjlJ https://t.co/d3hkUBD7Mh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Full Stack Developer: Description: THE COMPANY Are you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing… https://t.co/IxIz1dvvog https://t.co/MmiuawHdaE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL/SQL Developer, Journeyman: Description:   PL/SQL Developer, Journeyman Candidate must have or be capable of obtaining a Secret Clearance   Description The candidate will be working with a team of software and network engineering professionals on… https://t.co/3PpqT06YtF https://t.co/UlK6oz2whl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump to unveil China tariff list this week, targeting tech goods: WASHINGTON (Reuters) - The Trump administration this week will unveil a list of advanced technology Chinese imports targeted for U.S. tariffs to punish Beijing over technology transfer… https://t.co/PqNpzbxFsL https://t.co/w4XiVdkLUM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate, Apps Support: Associate, Apps Support Columbus, OH. Provide app support for ETL apps. Perform mgmt &amp; problem resolution. Master’s or equiv in CS, Eng’g (any), or rel field + 2 yrs relevant exp OR Bachelor’s or equiv in CS, Eng’g (any), or rel… https://t.co/ISVW4llvE5 https://t.co/q4Acy785fB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Linux System Administrator- TS/SCI Polygraph Required: Description: The Cyber and SIGINT Solution Ops under Defense and Intelligence Sector of Leidos has a career opportunity for a System Administrator with a TS/SCI with polygraph clearance in Annapolis… https://t.co/MGH1jlXLy7 https://t.co/IkVQvcFMKl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reports Developer (SQL/ETL) | BI/DW | Business Objects: Reports Developer (SQL/ETL) | BI/DW | Business Objects Columbus, OH 03-25-2018 Location: Columbus, OH For more than 18 years, CareWorks Tech has been delivering technology solutions that drive… https://t.co/KhwEGDmlAa https://t.co/AOUe7MNUtI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Delivery Specialist #XGGS18FC0318RIC4: Technology Deloitte Consulting LLP seeks a Project Delivery Specialist, Technology, Application Management Services (AMS) in Richmond, VA and various unanticipated Deloitte office locations and client sites… https://t.co/PcHaRBuETD https://t.co/XNFji3IWA5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .Net Software Engineer – C#, Node.JS, and NoSQL: Job Detail – 3coast 3coast IT Staffing current page url: ************************************************ &amp; src=Indeed complete url: ************************************************ &amp; src=Indeed… https://t.co/Xm9LirhQd0 https://t.co/j1YEh74XtV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server Tester: SQL Server Tester Ref No.: 18-09717 Location: Florida, Massachusetts Hello, Greetings for the day ! We have an urgent requirement for SQL Server Tester in Florida, MA. Please let me know if you are looking for a new project. You can… https://t.co/UtSVX08s7O https://t.co/xzKdHmb0fm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Customer Contact (PHP, JS, React,SQL): As a member of the Customer Contact Funnel engineering team, youll help us develop and maintain software to support our clients various customer contact channels, providing world-class… https://t.co/u0RUVQSN46 https://t.co/EcondCz2aM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US – C#, https://t.co/hQSAXGaBJi, SQL, HTML: Infosys Engineering Services Technology Lead – US .Net, *******, C#, HTML Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to… https://t.co/dgd36DOsAD https://t.co/o7zhsrkAgT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft SQL Server Administrator II: Microsoft SQL Server Administrator II Washington, District of Columbia – United States Job Start Date – 03/26/18, Posted Date – 03/26/18 Primary SkillsAPI,DCS,SQl 2016,Open data,sql 2012Tax TermsC2COverview… https://t.co/X47n00mBSI https://t.co/YbhPM3gtMg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL DBA: INTERVIEW PROCESS: Hiring manager is in need for a SQL DBA Ability to manage multiple projects at once Provide break/fix as well as proactive system support Strong performance tuning and troubleshooting skills Must have experience in SQL… https://t.co/nt1peJOsc7 https://t.co/MCSB0PWfWN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walmart opens first high-tech small-sized supermarket in China: BEIJING (Reuters) - Walmart Inc said on Monday it has opened its first small-sized high-tech supermarket in China, which will stock products that customers will also be able buy on the U.S.… https://t.co/wVFHI0F0tt https://t.co/ahW0nnG70s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL DBA: SQL DBA Chicago, Illinois – United States Job Start Date – 03/08/18, Posted Date – 03/08/18 Primary SkillsSQL DBATax TermsC2COverview Client Domain : Airline Industry Position : SQL DBA Location : Chicago, IL Duration : 6 Months Type of… https://t.co/I0fVPb4ts1 https://t.co/mmSULdDHhN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: SQL Developer Roanoke, Virginia – United States Job Start Date – 03/07/18, Posted Date – 03/07/18 Primary SkillsSSRS,ETL,SQL,.net,SSIS,T-SQLTax TermsW-2Overview Job Description : Looking for a Senior SQL Developer: SQL… https://t.co/CGOXYI4p1K https://t.co/qet5wvZlVK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Database Administrator (DBA): SQL Database Administrator (DBA) JOB DESCRIPTION IPG Photonics is seeking a highly motivated and experienced individual to join our growing IT team and work in a fast-paced, dynamic, high-tech manufacturing company. As a… https://t.co/xiykJuB3dP https://t.co/tkGd2HWd5c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer McLean, Virginia – United States Job Start Date – 03/14/18, Posted Date – 03/14/18 Primary SkillsJava DeveloperTax TermsC2COverview Job title: Java Developer Location: McLean, VA Contract: 6 months EAD-GC, GC [Preferred] [… https://t.co/QkvJEZ6QLx https://t.co/ue5j05LMxi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL DBA – Chicago Loop (Great team and Manager!) 100K: We are seeking a SQL DBA who will be responsible for maintenance, enhancement, designing of data dictionaries, physical and logical database models, and performance tuning. This is a great… https://t.co/IJEF2CZBP4 https://t.co/vFa7DFA5bK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack PHP Developer (SQL Server or RPG): Immediate need for a well-rounded PHP Developer with strong front-end web skills; as well as, back-end development using either SQL Server or RPG. REQUIRED – Back-end/ database experience (not just front end… https://t.co/Vy8X3H2sRu https://t.co/cprbaJYOD5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Under Armour says 150 million MyFitnessPal accounts breached: (Reuters) - Under Armour Inc said on Thursday that data from some 150 million MyFitnessPal diet and fitness app accounts was compromised in February, in one of the biggest hacks in history,… https://t.co/4z9vy89433 https://t.co/5r3aSBy98f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Full Stack Developer at Contract Simply: Job Description Contract Simply (*************************** is looking for a senior full-stack developer in Austin or willing to relocate. ABOUT US We help banks expedite their construction loan payments.… https://t.co/CExEHwwFhq https://t.co/VdUnfk0cpL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: Infosys Engineering Services Technology Lead US Angular 4.0, Node JS, Restful Service Are you looking for a change? Do you want to collaborate with some of the best talent in the industry? Are you ready to join a company whose… https://t.co/BE9ehSiK5Q https://t.co/PlbhwqK2qH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Software Engineer (NOSQL /J2EE / Spring / JavaScript /HTML): Company is a global leader in investment management, risk management and advisory services for institutional and retail clients. At December 31, 2016, Companys AUM was $5.1 trillion.… https://t.co/ylvp3lEtGn https://t.co/zc8aPMCeyR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web, Mobile, and Systems Programmer: Department: University Computing Services Salary Range: $66,360 – $105,228 annually Class: C1464 Recruitment #: S1809 Review Date: Review of applications begins March 23, 2018. Position open until filled. This is a… https://t.co/7PaDUysnC5 https://t.co/1RYTRKNrZZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Sr Analyst, Healthcare Analytics:   Job Description – SQL Sr Analyst, Healthcare Analytics (1801865) Job Description  SQL Sr Analyst, Healthcare Analytics – (1801865) Primary Location : US-CA-Long Beach-MOLINA300 Job : Business &amp; Strategy Analysis… https://t.co/tEBU6FykmQ https://t.co/hyTqwzresN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saks, Lord &amp; Taylor hit by payment card data breach: TORONTO/NEW YORK (Reuters) - Retailer Hudson's Bay Co on Sunday disclosed that it was the victim of a security breach that compromised data on payment cards used at Saks and Lord &amp; Taylor stores in… https://t.co/4xn9svMdyZ https://t.co/Ieg3mWNrkb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Developer (Oracle Form and Reports, Oracle PL/SQL) – Mechanicsburg, PA: Job Description Design, modify, develop, write, and implement software programming applications. Support and/or installs software applications/operating systems. Participate… https://t.co/GJN1pcRlZO https://t.co/GXXrBYJ1cf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft SQL Database Administrator: SENIOR DATABASE ADMINISTRATOR WORK LOCATION: WARNER ROBINS, GA OVERVIEW Swingtech Consulting is currently supporting an Army customer at Warner Robins, GA on a contract that it is utilizing Microsoft SQL Server 2012… https://t.co/SQaCQaGebw https://t.co/08XcSElyTG]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>