<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Backend Developer: Responsibilities * Develop the core infrastructure, framework and services that incorporate our proprietary algorithms * Collaborate closely with PM, UX, and other stakeholders to clarify functional flows and provide technical insights… https://t.co/SO6RDTZL14 https://t.co/WbOX3VOOjr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java/Python Developer/ Software Architect: Responsibilities: * Participate in requirement gathering and analysis. * Research and investigate design approaches * Build quick Proof of Concept (POC) and prototype and evaluate technical feasibility. *… https://t.co/H8bSbfdtAI https://t.co/T0IPol9oXk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Symfony (PHP) Developer: We are seeking a highly‐talented Programmer / Developer who will be responsible for creating beautiful, engaging web experiences for high-end clients. We are looking for an innovative thinker who is fully committed to web… https://t.co/lkkmdSrdRT https://t.co/AMIRP2PsbB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advanced Weapons &amp; Lethality Solutions Analysis Lead – Eng Systems Modeling Simulation 4: Job Description The individual in this role will lead the Advanced Weapons &amp; Lethality Solutions focus area for the Systems Analysis &amp; Simulation team within the… https://t.co/wcvX6TQHRa https://t.co/NWKIUQrkKY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Mobility Engineer: PaRaBaL / ISEC7 is looking to recruit highly motivated individuals to join a team of Enterprise Mobility Engineers that provides premier consultative engineering services to its clients, primarily centered on mobile device… https://t.co/rkBRK2KkaN https://t.co/S6gQ0B87r4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Contract Angular Web/Mobile UI Engineer: Specialists On Call is the nations largest provider of telemedicine consultations at acute care setting, performed by board certified, fellowship trained specialty physicians. Nationwide, 400+ hospitals partner… https://t.co/ABYmDrsXSA https://t.co/iLRjrwN2LF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple iPad (2018): Price, Specs, Release Date: Apple's lowest cost iPad ($329) now includes support for Apple Pencil ($99). https://t.co/8VqPIIsM4A https://t.co/wFFxZ7JR3p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Project Manager I: Overview  Project Manager I will work directly with iCIMS Enterprise customers and members of the iCIMS Customer Service team to manage all aspects of the iCIMS project life cycle. Responsibilities include project planning,… https://t.co/7SL7JgTA6y https://t.co/ptresCuiJc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Test Automation Engineer: Software Test Automation Engineer Hillsboro, OR Fulltime position Job Description: Responsible for writing test cases, executing tests and automating tests for the OPAE, which is the software infrastructure for Intel… https://t.co/0zw0PC3r3S https://t.co/HMEETKGb73]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Design Tabulation BA – Web App: Design Tabulation BA – Web App  DOT77529377 *Ames, IA* The Strategic Business Analyst skilled at to writing detailed specifications in Microsoft Word for a web application, œDesign Tabulation.  This web application will… https://t.co/6sCcOQO7sN https://t.co/M672ExTfee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Web Developer: eSalon is looking for a senior web developer to work cross-functionally, in-house and onsite with our Product team to continue improving our customer experience and growing our platform. Bringing together a blend of artistry and… https://t.co/F1L4D3Cpde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NDT Technical Specialist: Req ID : 415702BR Job Code/Title : N8123:Technician Spec Job Description : Proficiency in performing such tasks is required by a hands-on practical and written examinations equivalent to Level 2. Individual must obtain and… https://t.co/fbyaVAmBxt https://t.co/AMWg28gevM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front End Developer – AngularJS 1.x and familiar with .NET: Irvine Technology Corporation (ITC) is leading provider of technology and staffing solutions for IT, Security, Engineering, and Interactive Design disciplines servicing startups to enterprise… https://t.co/xGA84hIfWN https://t.co/suWOklLw2C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETL Developer: ETL Developer Posted Date 1 week ago(3/7/2018 6:03 PM) ID 2018-30320 Job Location USA-DC-Washington Required Clearance Top Secret Category Engineering-Software Employment Type Full Time Hiring Company General Dynamics Mission Systems Basic… https://t.co/fzqtNPRBt9 https://t.co/NEs7se2d50]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VP, Sales:   Job Description – VP, Sales (00019769) Job Description  VP, Sales – (00019769) Description   This role is responsible for leading &amp; driving the achievement of revenue growth and retention targets of Events in the region. Hire and build… https://t.co/rOOOnGrc9v https://t.co/ZNSNlql6on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer – SimpliVity Control Plane: Senior Software Engineer – SimpliVity Control Plane at Hewlett Packard Enterprise CompanyTo top Skip Navigation Hewlett Packard Enterprise Careers – Overview – Search and apply – Sales Graduate Program… https://t.co/0drLE1g9Ru https://t.co/Q64o16WwyG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior UX Researcher: Description Senior UX Researcher San Diego, CA ServiceNow is changing the way people work. With a service-orientation toward the activities, tasks and processes that make up day-to-day work life, we help the modern enterprise… https://t.co/RXcILxFm3i https://t.co/V5BqstWKNW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MTS – Big Data Infrastructure: MTS – Big Data Infrastructure Nutanix is disrupting the multibillion dollar Enterprise Cloud market by pioneering the first converged compute &amp; storage virtualization platform that can incrementally scale out to manage… https://t.co/gnJlyHrebU https://t.co/TqeLo7sGFJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[20 Easter Tech Sales (2018): Nintendo, Apple, Dyson, Lenovo: When you're done painting eggs and munching on candy, check out these Easter tech deals. https://t.co/agSyexkCNo https://t.co/XX5EPmdxxa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MTS – Developer, Core Data Path: The Role: MTS – Developer, Core Data Path Developers in the Core Data Path are responsible for the storage fabric that underlies the entire Nutanix solution. They also come up with ways to replicate data to remote sites… https://t.co/Ni6orOKEFI https://t.co/CPZtUCiAmd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blue Tactics Development MS&amp;A Lead – Engineer Systems Modeling Simulation 4: Job Description The individual in this role will lead the Blue Tactics and CONOPS Modeling, Simulation, and &amp; Analysis focus area for the Systems Analysis &amp; Simulation team… https://t.co/ogJ8F8a4lh https://t.co/UZFhXrkAzD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automation QA Tester https://t.co/M5I9FnzrMM https://t.co/0010wICjNa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Linux Systems Administrator: Linux Systems Administrator Do you have a passion for Linux based systems? Do you enjoy making sure each piece of a system works as you intended it and watching a farm of servers update and operate autonomously? Does the idea… https://t.co/GwjpySRf81 https://t.co/5L3mJSOOOs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SOFTWARE DEVELOPER (FRONT-END): Department: Product Engineering Reports To: Director of Product Engineering Position Summary As a Front-End Software Developer, your main responsibility is for the production, modification and maintenance of websites and… https://t.co/eUKboziXXe https://t.co/gCsDhH1g97]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer II: ALL CANDIDATES MUST HAVE AN ACTIVE TS/SCI WITH POLYGRAPH CLEARANCE! Required Experience: * Within the last seven (7) years, a minimum of three (3) years experience developing with Java in a Linux environment * Within the last three… https://t.co/4WdMM3D3uf https://t.co/dSNLKqvgiS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Energy Storage and Charging Systems Engineer: GILLIG LLC is the largest and most dependable manufacturer of custom built buses for the passenger transit industry in North America. Our customers are in all 50 states, and include cities, counties,… https://t.co/n06pvPJvIK https://t.co/LsmkP5nhDQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Software Engineer: Company Description Dropbox is a leading global collaboration platform that’s transforming the way people work together, from the smallest business to the largest enterprise. With more than 500 million registered users across… https://t.co/BTtkAOKteH https://t.co/vvyOg32gAx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[software systems test engineer: Job Summary Do you love breaking software? Do you relish the notion of finding bugs in complex software designed and implemented by top-notch software engineers? If so, Nutanix wants you. We are building a unique… https://t.co/T9iKIQ83LZ https://t.co/CD6q5uf6y2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Sales Specialist: Technical Sales Specialist Come work with us at NanoTemper Technologies. NanoTemper has a big mission — to enable researchers to do the best science of their lives. We’ve been around since 2008, developing, producing and… https://t.co/aAvXFiZrfA https://t.co/hCM3hm64WG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Engineer: We are bringing a novel, data-driven approach to helping brands tell stories that are relatable and personalized with a platform that solves the content creation problem through a diverse community of photographers, videographers,… https://t.co/0GXYgV1fED https://t.co/vNxFkZrMBq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Engineer 1 (Linux Administrator): ALL CANDIDATES MUST HAVE AN ACTIVE TS/SCI WITH A POLYGRAPH CLEARANCE! Job Description: * Provide intermediate/advance Linux user and server support. * Responsibilities of this position include, but not limited to:… https://t.co/0vQkReXISm https://t.co/MUxayZrSTD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Fold 5 High-Flying Stunt Paper Airplanes: "The Paper Airplane Guy" John Collins shows us how to fold planes that do loops, flap their wings, and fly world-record distances. https://t.co/k5VABrSBNw https://t.co/Lbj0JgzOyF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Customer Service Software Technical Support: Veteran Contract Services LLC is hiring for one of our Tax Software Provider clients. (REMOTE WORK FROM HOME) ANY STATE MAY APPLY What to Expect: • Inbound phone and video customer service/technical support.… https://t.co/I1kn5o8Aj1 https://t.co/pnQNlKZjLZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Global Surveillance &amp; Strike (Contested) Analysis Lead – Eng Systems Modeling Simulation 5: Job Description The individual in this role will lead the Surveillance and Strike focus area for the Systems Analysis &amp; Simulation team within the Global Strategy… https://t.co/ZG89GfIwdE https://t.co/9COIlqoIjm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer / Front End: Software Developer Fastcase is looking for a software engineer with experience in front end development to join its growing legal analytics software team in Washington, D.C. We’re using technologies like Elasticsearch,… https://t.co/ShcR7p3ev2 https://t.co/x5rzPZKpNj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: Infosys- Retail, CPG, and Logistics Technology Analyst Java, AngularJS Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to create and execute strategies for their digital… https://t.co/ph0gjuRbBJ https://t.co/H1KEVycVzP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infrastructure Automation Engineers: Candidate will work with a team of engineers that are responsible for automating elements of the application support lifecycle of enterprise applications in a telecommunications company. This includes activities… https://t.co/6sa29BOcBr https://t.co/lFoidBuA8v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst III(Buisness Operations, Claims, SQL) (Pittsburgh or Harrisburg): Position Purpose: Perform various analysis and interpretation to link business needs and objectives for assigned function. Support business initiatives through data… https://t.co/kTx3HPX3cl https://t.co/k5vqxsTmmX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Automation Engineer: QA Automation Engineer BOSTON, Massachusetts – United States Job Start Date – 03/06/18, Posted Date – 03/06/18 Primary SkillsAPI,Selenium and JavaTax TermsC2COverview QA Automation Engineer who has experience with Selenium and… https://t.co/wJ9iBsZ5gt https://t.co/xqBvmsHqVQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Analyst III or Business Systems Specialist – National Cash Automation: The Federal Reserve Bank of Cleveland is part of the nation’s central bank. We’ve provided many opportunities for professional growth during our history. For eighteen… https://t.co/GO0t0lT2a6 https://t.co/TEU3CelDyH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer: Eagle Eye Networks is seeking an experienced Network Engineer to help us expand our rapidly growing global network infrastructure. With 10s of thousands of video streams being delivered into our environment 24/7, the security,… https://t.co/7UKSigVx4E https://t.co/YzxkcjqdBV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Project Mgr., SC LCM Excellence: Job ID ******BR Posting Title Sr. Project Mgr., SC LCM Excellence Division ALCON Business Unit MFG/TECH OPERATIONS AL Country USA Work Location Fort Worth, TX Company/Legal Entity Alcon Laboratories, Inc. Functional… https://t.co/dOjlpp2Jg1 https://t.co/rBt2ysQwZK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Design Researcher: IBM Corporation in Austin, Texas is looking for Senior Design Researcher. * Lead design research to understand how people think and the use of artificial intelligence to solve work challenges. * Lead design research education to… https://t.co/839u4C2UEA https://t.co/YuQK11nRiY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GoPro Hero: Specs, Price, Release Date: The new camera, called simply GoPro Hero, can't do 4K, but it's a great value at $1`99. https://t.co/NTTH0OAtK8 https://t.co/QyDXnQdwcX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Scientist: PROJECT SCIENTIST sought by University of California, Irvine in Irvine, CA. Conduct research on human-computer interaction applied to the “Internet of Things” including electronic devices and software applications for advancements in… https://t.co/k7o3Wtay3Q https://t.co/xsmcvXTkba]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Application Developer: Sr Application Developer for US Bank National Association in Denver, CO to perform &amp;/or lead tech design &amp; develop of complex app system. At U.S. Bank, we’re passionate about helping customers and the communities where we live… https://t.co/NgC56eLwG3 https://t.co/ROwEiVwupJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3D Character Artist: Software development company seeking 3D Character Artist to translate concepts design into next-gen models of characters &amp; creatures. Requires: 4 years experience in job offered, or as a Character Artist, or related experience… https://t.co/wBBEl82W2i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test Technician: Test Technician F/T: Test mobile device and Analyze results. BS/equiv &amp; 5 yrs exp w/ Java/J2EE, EJBs, Struts, Servlets, Hibernate JPA, CSS, Ajax, Angular JS, Bug trackr &amp; JTrack. Travel/reloc req’d. recblid m4w73jyi1aezpnjr9c89we1e2j86p8 https://t.co/Vxo7qeGAtx https://t.co/JI7sPZcqC6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Analyst: The Orange Water and Sewer Authority (OWASA), a progressive water utility providing water, sewer and reclaimed water services to the Towns of Chapel Hill, Carrboro and the University of North Carolina at Chapel Hill, seeks a… https://t.co/2skFgCyTME https://t.co/oSueTi2cVf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: JOB RESPONSIBILITIES – Contingent on Award Would you like to perform rewarding work while contributing to the success of an established, growing company?Pragmatics, Inc. is seeking aSenior Developer to support our government customer. The… https://t.co/rfV3GZDJU3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Development Expert: Development Expert for SAP Labs, LLC (Palo Alto, CA) resp for dvlpmnt focus on dsgn, cdng, tst, QA of cmplx prdct feat in a dvlpmt team. Bach in Comp Sci, Engg, Math, or rltd field &amp; 7 yrs exp req’d, or alt a Master’s &amp; 5 yrs exp. Exp… https://t.co/EOSmoHYZxt https://t.co/qRvxc9x26t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Programmer Analyst: Synergy Computer Solutions, Inc. has job openings for Lead Programmer Analyst. Job is located in Bingham Farms, MI and various unanticipated locations throughout the U.S. Convert project specifications and statements of problems… https://t.co/JAmz0sN5Ip https://t.co/XKsofICuf0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Analysts #CG, 555: TransUnion, LLC seeks Senior Analysts for Chicago, IL location to assist in the design, implementation &amp; administration of strategic compensation programs. Master’s in Economics/Applied Economics, Compensation, or Statistics + 2… https://t.co/FxYwHLfju2 https://t.co/f0K1goroWP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finance and IT Manager: Finance and IT Manager The Brattleboro Food Co-op has an immediate need for a Finance and Information Technology Manager. Reporting to our General Manager, this position oversees all of our financial and IT management operations.… https://t.co/ReRAEIac7z https://t.co/SsKvo2SUBD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Engineer: Systems Engineer sought by S&amp;S Enterprises LLC in Brea, CA. Design sub-system components. Analyze &amp; verify design meets requirements. Apply systems analysis techniques &amp; procedures. Requirement: BS + 1. recblid… https://t.co/IoCJds80PW https://t.co/0ywMgsFu27]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information and Technology Specialist: The School District of Glenwood City is looking for an Information and Technology Specialist to support the learning environment for students and staff through leadership in technology. The successful applicant will… https://t.co/yV2odNWzyO https://t.co/bMFCPHsUTu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RSS Readers Are Due for a Comeback: Feedly, The Old Reader, Inoreader: After years of letting algorithms make up our minds for us, the time is right to go back to basics. https://t.co/zGR7cFEg2h https://t.co/lzao6XFGNH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Claims Analyst: Zelis is a healthcare information technology company and market-leading provider of end-to-end healthcare claims cost management and payment solutions. Inc.5000 award winner: One of the fastest growing privately held companies in… https://t.co/VKFKHkNk5W https://t.co/rXhgqlBQw2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer #R42193: Senior Software Engineer Requisition ID R42193. Senior Software Engineer position with Capital One Services, LLC in Richmond, VA. Multiple positions available: -Responsible for the overall technical design, development,… https://t.co/xEXzPORnvS https://t.co/y3HTiq75SL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Norwegian, Danish, French (Canada) and Malay Localization QA Tester- Cupertino: Job description Moravia is looking for Bilingual Localization QA Tester with a keen eye for detail, interested in Linguistics or Translation to work with us in a… https://t.co/L8E3kDPaVI https://t.co/4q8DEdcyTE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior Web Developer – https://t.co/cLs5lE9unI: ********** has entry level programming positions for recent college graduates with science, math, or engineering related majors including multiple programming courses. We will provide advanced web… https://t.co/5BQmfNJZp3 https://t.co/EPDEpVoBFt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Architect: As an OpenShift v3 , you will be responsible to operationalize technology solutions for all new OpenShift technology products related projects on Containerized Solutions. You will assist in evaluating project scope and sizing of work… https://t.co/dp9I82oZfE https://t.co/mHkIr8BZwa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supplier Communication Specialist (SAP Ariba) Job: Date: Feb 28, 2018 Location: Pittsburgh, PA, US Company: SAP Requisition ID: ****** Work Area: Customer Service and Support Expected Travel: 0 – 10% Career Status: Professional Employment Type: Regular… https://t.co/9zIvkYVZ8X https://t.co/RjqICv6bvJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Summer Internship: Developer Intern: Developer Interns are bright, motivated, and talented people with a passion for making ground-breaking work. You have basic programming skills, problem-solving abilities, and an eye for detail. If you have a love for… https://t.co/CYOGFmWs1H https://t.co/MmJEM4RCPv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All Source Research Analyst 3 – TS/SCI w/poly required re:   Job Description – All Source Research Analyst 3 – TS/SCI w/poly required re (18005791) All Source Research Analyst 3 – TS/SCI w/poly required re Requisition ID : 18005791 Location : United… https://t.co/gTXZmLLdea https://t.co/QtYu7sRN7s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NETWORK SECURITY ADMINISTRATOR – FULLTIME: NETWORK &amp; SECURITY ADMINISTRATOR – FULLTIME INCORPORAN INC is looking for strong?NETWORK &amp; SECURITY ADMINISTRATOR – FULLTIME for our direct client in ROSEMEAD,CA.????????????????????? Job Description:Relevant… https://t.co/UMptD0jVtt https://t.co/DLf93yRwcE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automation Engineer: 1st Shift Logistics done differently. At XPO Logistics, were constantly looking for ways to improve, enhance, and adapt in an ever-changing marketplace. As theAutomation Engineer, you will be responsible for identifying facility… https://t.co/4vmFBAg87c https://t.co/CLxFEpFlfe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator: Systems Administrator Below you will find the details for the position including any supplementary documentation and questions you should review before applying for the opening.  Posting Details: Position Information: Position… https://t.co/TROjtRiEoF https://t.co/rbtcjOxPTb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TG DEVELOPER: TG Developer – Enovia / PowerSource for Kiewit Engineering Group (Lenexa, KS). Provide technical applications design, development &amp; support engineering in the implementation of the Enovia Enterprise PLM (Product Lifecycle Management) system… https://t.co/Qs7Kyz71TB https://t.co/8Aapxi39gb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pinterest Adds New 'People You Follow' Tab to Your Feed: The new "following" tab shows you pins from people you follow in reverse-chronological order. https://t.co/XqkG0kTtfo https://t.co/LBRUpwNM4K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Intelligence / ETL Developer: Benton PUD is looking for a Business Intelligence / ETL Developer with strong competency in Data analytics and ETL development and a passion for creating a data infrastructure and building data visualizations to… https://t.co/c9P671vx3E https://t.co/QV3ZLSNUC9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineers, Game Development #55: Software Engineers, Game Development (Ref job # 55) Research, design, engineer &amp; develop specialized software system &amp; apps for 3-D interactive graphic elements for use in tech media formats. Position at Valve… https://t.co/1ee2H7LPSe https://t.co/WBpCz4g1hQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Software Engineer: Principal Software Engineer Embedded Systems (Belmont, CA), responsible for shaping and strengthening the electronics development for Audi and the VW Group; targeted towards Audi electronics; development, optimization, and… https://t.co/Cfh3m5XIS1 https://t.co/GxO5tGjT0D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Engineers #IRVEYO: Software Developers Western Digital Technologies, Inc. has opportunity in Irvine, CA for Principal Engineers. Experience in C, C++, Java &amp; programming languages required. Equal opportunity employer. recblid… https://t.co/BqN5JiJhKI https://t.co/mZXHKOH0vi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Program Manager: Information Technology Microsoft Corporation currently has the following openings in Irvine, CA (job opportunities available at all levels, e.g., Principal, Senior and Lead levels). Program Managers: Coordinate program development of… https://t.co/Dm34ZaHxpu https://t.co/jGFPa8pSwN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Engineer, System Software: TECHNOLOGY Mountain View, CA Sr. Engineer, System Software Responsible for designing infrastructure and interfaces, developing integration software, coding quick scripts and utilities as required, researching tools and… https://t.co/p4Burd6zHz https://t.co/HOOnuAloeT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer #R42193: Senior Software Engineer Requisition ID R42193. Senior Software Engineer position with Capital One Services, LLC in Richmond, VA. Multiple positions available: -Responsible for the overall technical design, development,… https://t.co/Z0Y6Rb5S2r https://t.co/F6mW6m55wL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Software Engineer: .NET software Engineer EMS Consultants is seeking a .NET software Engineer.  The ideal candidate will be highly self-motivated and be able to work in a very team oriented environment.  This individual will be responsible for all… https://t.co/rKUJ60R0iM https://t.co/MQ03r86YQY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer #R42201: Senior Software Engineer Requisition ID R42201. Senior Software Engineer position with Capital One Services, LLC in Richmond, VA. Multiple positions available: -Responsible for the overall technical design, development,… https://t.co/pgA270Gl58 https://t.co/xNCRjYB6bv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Technology Specialist 5 (Application Developer) #02487: Description The Department of Social and Health Services (DSHS) Children’s Administration Technology Services (CATS) Division is currently accepting applications for Information… https://t.co/5CpeUZrQlr https://t.co/SjaheS2bnB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Analyst, Management Analyst, Senior Programmer Analyst: IT Professionals: Openings available at LiquidHub Inc. for the following positions in Wayne, PA &amp; unanticipated client locations throughout U.S.: *Systems Analyst: Gather &amp; analyze comp… https://t.co/AtaCjOdwVf https://t.co/CjesvH9z67]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With ‘Sniffs’ and ‘Licks,’ Petzbe Makes Social Media Nice Again: When people are impersonating their pets online, they tend to be really, really nice. https://t.co/ABxvgBmgU8 https://t.co/UBsP3DwnZH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Analyst &amp; Substation Supervisor: Network Analyst $87,131 – $111,529 Annually + benefits Performs professional level work to ensure the stability and integrity of in-house voice, data, video, and wireless network services; plans, designs, and… https://t.co/wrbbX0QRTa https://t.co/nI7M05IjIn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Test Engineer #2018-43044: Senior Software Test Engineer Ref: 2018-43044 Sought by Dish Network, LLC in Englewood, CO. Lead &amp; contribute as part of a team of onshore &amp; offshore testers in a fast paced IT environment for multiple… https://t.co/B8RzwJezqI https://t.co/4sQSUfILNJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chemical Lawn Technician, Lawn Maintenance Crew Members &amp; Drivers: Dixie Landscaping located in Athens, GA is now hiring Full Time Chemical Lawn Technician, Lawn Maintenance Crew Members, and Lawn Maintenance Crew Drivers. Dixie Landscaping is a Locally… https://t.co/m1Phlipt4U https://t.co/8KQFIFh9Vr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Field Network Administrator/Consultant: Wolf Consulting, Inc. [******************************* is Pittsburghs Trusted Leader in Small and Mid-Size Business Computing. We specialize in providing professional, reliable computer and network support services… https://t.co/H04P1NDzTS https://t.co/xotxY4qAwH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Catalyst is disrupting the corporate learning space by creating a more effective marketplace for enterprises to connect with external expertise. Corporate Learning is a $100B+ vertical that has been mostly skipped over by modern… https://t.co/Tu4eTmBxNB https://t.co/1hdsR0wgSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Test Engineer 1:   Job Description – Software Test Engineer 1 (17027817) Software Test Engineer 1 Requisition ID : 17027817 Location : United States-California-San Diego US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation Assistance:… https://t.co/2uskpHGdpi https://t.co/Nhfk6Q05vl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Engineer – Team Lead (mid-career) – Centennial, CO: Req ID : 420790BR Job Code/Title : E1464:Systems Engineer Stf Job Description : FBM Reentry requirements and verification Team Lead responsible for drafting, reviewing, and releasing… https://t.co/7Sa1kSPoqk https://t.co/xOK6v9scoh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Commercial Information Management Technical Analyst: Commercial Information Management Technical Analyst Requisition ID: BUS****** Merck &amp; Co., Inc. Kenilworth, N.J., U.S.A. known as Merck in the United States and Canada, is a global health care leader… https://t.co/JSbx6WxtLV https://t.co/fLFNC3sbtr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Open Lending is seeking an exceptional Project Manager to be responsible for implementing Open Lendings program, Lenders Protection. You interact directly with clients and are our first impression after the client has been sold. Must… https://t.co/p9fsXxfqeL https://t.co/BGOQTor3eH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Manager – Marketing: Timbers Resorts, Internations Developer and Operator of luxury resorts and residence clubs is looking for a: Database Manager – Marketing to join our growing team in Carbondale, CO. Candidate will be responsible for overall… https://t.co/twonTGDSJI https://t.co/eveTuv9aCu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Engineer, System Software: TECHNOLOGY Mountain View, CA Sr. Engineer, System Software Responsible for designing infrastructure and interfaces, developing integration software, coding quick scripts and utilities as required, researching tools and… https://t.co/BBGXWPMDam https://t.co/S7QPqhNee0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to Translation Tech, Talking to Strangers Will Be Even Easier: Instant translation will help us all enjoy a more intimate experience, no matter where we explore. https://t.co/VXdqQzNiie https://t.co/2DORrRtyH1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[APEX Developer (Oracle): A2F Consulting is a boutique consulting firm with offices in the Washington, DC metro area and Frankfurt/Germany.  We provide a broad range of advisory services to support financial and private sector development in emerging… https://t.co/R4VFUDXYOF https://t.co/NSHSoQE2wS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Operations Program Manager: Management Position Sunnyvale, CA, Cupertino,CA, San Jose,CA &amp; Palo Alto,CA. A2Z Development Center, Inc. and https://t.co/SM3mBnaqOt Services, Inc. candidates for the following positions (multiple positions available… https://t.co/y6ZUomxr3E https://t.co/7ZgCQZTxJd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3D Character Artist: Software development company seeking 3D Character Artist to translate concepts design into next-gen models of characters &amp; creatures. Requires: 4 years experience in job offered, or as a Character Artist, or related experience… https://t.co/xY1i5DdsIJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Design Researcher: IBM Corporation in Austin, Texas is looking for Senior Design Researcher. * Lead design research to understand how people think and the use of artificial intelligence to solve work challenges. * Lead design research education to… https://t.co/6uiaXH4v1a https://t.co/TqmoycOC2b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Staff Design Engineer: Senior Staff Design Engineer (Job location is Seattle, WA) Develop software solutions utilizing JavaScript, CSS &amp; HTML. Develop content pipeline to design &amp; develop video streaming applications. Create new technologies to… https://t.co/BMHkB5vMXd https://t.co/ALEpMd0Y7d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Consultant #XGGS18FC0318SJB2: Deloitte Consulting LLP seeks a Technology Consultant, Deloitte Digital in San Jose, California and various unanticipated Deloitte office locations and client sites nationally to function as integrator between… https://t.co/PoSjsPlWCi https://t.co/kBmig6oUf1]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>