<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[What does it mean when a person is such a pacifist that they get shot? I can never understand that. - John Lennon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting Your Creative Writing Degree Online  http://t.co/QgCsCtXFmn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fifty per cent of rock is having a good time. - Roger Daltrey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The human body is the best work of art. --&gt; Jess C. Scott]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this very cool bed fan - cools right under the covers! http://t.co/3qRHSaQT9d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Middle age is after one night out you need two nights in. . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Girl 1:  I spent my vacation fishing  Girl 2: Then why did you buy a new bathing suit?   Girl 1:  That was my bait]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If people don't want to come out to the ball park, nobody's gonna stop 'em. - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of a sudden, you're like the Bin Laden of America. Osama Bin Laden is the only one who knows exactly what I'm going through.  R. Kelly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It isn't necessary to blow out the other person's light in order for yours to shine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating Introduction to Marmalade Insurance: How to Select an Insurance Agency  http://t.co/icuqVhj8x0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Life? Cool! Where can I download one of those?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[History of Blogging  http://t.co/jVfTRH1rdy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is not preparation for life; education is life itself. - John Dewey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Return the shoes?! I can't talk to you when you're being hysterical! - Gabrielle, Desperate Housewives]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I had never seen much of Star Trek, or any other science fiction, before I was cast. But Seven's wonderful. - Jeri Ryan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The aim of marketing is to know and understand the customer so well the product or service fits him and sells itself. - Peter F. Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these different types of beer - lots of options including ales, lagers, hocks and more!  http://t.co/f0gIdjvU0n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its Real - You Can Print Shoes with a 3D Printer!  http://t.co/AvFMy0Fvyy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was your operation expensive? "No, the doctor gave me cut rates."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Rufus Thomas  http://t.co/SilmcpWXET]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Beverly Hillbillies – An American Classic TV Series  http://t.co/EZuqCjDBNr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When money talks these days, it's probably asking what happened]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd just as soon kiss a wookiee! - Princess Leia, The Empire Strikes Back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Guide – Running a Green Business  http://t.co/hzRjtJlSS5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space Invaders Video Game - Men's Silk Necktie - Cool! http://t.co/e7RmgXBO3F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is a social process. Education is growth. Education is, not a preparation for life; education is life itself.  - John Dewey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Future generations will be born free, equal and in debt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Social Networking for Seniors  http://t.co/i7pt1jlmAk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Flying Alarm Clock - COOL!  http://t.co/VVu96G0HN5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wear my sort of clothes to save me the trouble of deciding which clothes to wear. - Katherine Hepburn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We (San Francisco) have football weather during baseball season, and baseball weather during football season. - Herb Caen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its not so much about the shoes, but the person wearing them --&gt; Adriana Trigiani, Viola in Real Life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would love to change the world, but they won't give me the source code]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Search Engine Optimization (SEO) to Drive Traffic to Your Website  http://t.co/qhYGgL0dsO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn from yesterday, live for today, hope for tomorrow. - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have to have a lot of little boy in you to play baseball for a living.  - Roy Campanella]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to WordTracker SEO Tools http://t.co/RkBe1nvNyj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science fiction, outside of poetry, is the only literary field which has no limits, no parameters whatsoever. - Theodore Sturgeon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be Prepared!  Learn About these Bartering Resources  http://t.co/jitGgoluJq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I could turn and live with animals, they are "¨so placid and self-contained,"¨I stand and look at them long and long. - Walt Whitman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not anti-social; I'm just not user friendly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the J. Geils Band  http://t.co/gt7MYzxo8G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Media is a Helpful Tool in Connecting with Customers  http://t.co/LBp38lkJvW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clarity trumps persuasion.  Dr. Flint McGlaughlin - Director MECLABS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Kool and the Gang  http://t.co/Yi6t3qNDjk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Great Tours of Europe  http://t.co/fohYh3mV7V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no black magic to successfully attracting customers via the web.  Rand Fishkin, Founder SEOMoz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reputation is the other fellow's idea of your character]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They call him "magician".  He walks down the street and turns into a saloon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Cool History of Science Fiction  http://t.co/FrJ2Dwj7uX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm shooting a commercial for safe sex. How ironic. Because I don't have that.   Tila Tequila]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of the first book in the Left Behind Series by Tim LaHaye and Jerry Jenkins  http://t.co/6bbVrSQSel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am pushing sixty. That is enough exercise for me. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Shelley Fabares  http://t.co/OBLCTEFH9R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Guide to Mountain Biking  http://t.co/nKv0xgzTaR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still love her. But she's retarded, too. Guy Ritchie on Madonna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If a lot of people said what they think, they would be speechless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I have any beliefs about immortality it is that certain dogs I know will go to heaven, and very very few people. - James Thurber]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Pet Insurance  http://t.co/c4Fdmyqj5f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Elvis Presley    http://t.co/rpr1VkYtOP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this very cool bed fan - cools right under the covers! http://t.co/3qRHSaQT9d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eat, drink and be merry, for tomorrow ye diet. - William Gilmore Beymer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of Artemis Fowl By Eoin Colfer  http://t.co/GTeL5unZyj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft: "You've got questions. We've got dancing paperclips."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are 10 types of people in the world: those who understand binary, and those who don't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Future generations will be born free, equal and in debt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids can learn over 20 optical illusions - lots of fun and great learning! http://t.co/DejBd1bKv3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Big-Dog Pet Fountain - Keeps Fresh and Tasty Water for Your Big Dog! http://t.co/xAeHWFbcwa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Sly and the Family Stone  http://t.co/WQpN7vS7rr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometime the best thing to get off your chest is your chin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Little Feat  http://t.co/VbqEVvriCs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only person who is educated is the one who has learned how to learn and change. - Carl Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paparazzi Party Props!!! - thenerdvibe: http://t.co/XUaVA2bk8d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top movies of the 1920s - theband4: Although the emergence of motion pictures began as early as the 1890s,... http://t.co/5zl33tKi9P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Best Tasting Burger - theband4: http://t.co/9YjAj5M8cj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would you say a parachutist is a fall guy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Let's Play: LOTR Ep 1: Meeting the Hobbits  http://t.co/TNCywAzMRc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating history of Wrigley Field!  http://t.co/KJck2uLTWA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Credit card sized took kit with 2-Inch Serrated Knife, can/bottle opener &amp; Flat screwdriver, tweezers &amp; toothpick! http://t.co/knTS3gNBGE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is the transmission of civilization. - Will Durant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Different Types of Beer  http://t.co/f0gIdjNv8r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the shoe fits, it's too expensive. - Adrienne Gusoff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Geek Decision Ball - Picks FAIL, WIN, meh, 404 error, LOL, PWND and More! http://t.co/68xB6jWimF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I started racing my father told me, "˜Cristiano, nobody has three balls but some people have two very good ones. - Cristiano Da Matta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go Big, or Go Home - Eliza Dushku]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The Top 10 European Beers  http://t.co/ENGxgQe2zu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids LOVE Magnets - Check Out Magnet Science - Fun and Educational! http://t.co/eX9onu25wL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bring the best of your authentic self to every opportunity.  John Jantsch - Author of Duct Tape Marketing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Jackson Five  http://t.co/d3SprlUGE9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Linda Ronstadt  http://t.co/OVc1Lf8qCa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is but one game and that game is baseball.  - John McGraw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Kiss  http://t.co/2DyfTUxGSy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gold Glitter Lips - Cool Look!  http://t.co/pFl8kPp1Rw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the way society functions. Aren't you a part of society? - Kramer, Seinfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Blondie  http://t.co/PSJmqqku9i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who think they know everything are especially annoying to those of us who do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever wonder about the history of the coffin?  http://t.co/n4cCF8iscf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Delfonics  http://t.co/M8Xe2m3eee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Clash  http://t.co/wqnUbCIRkM]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>