<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[West Wing Week 08/10/12 or “We Have A Moral, Sacred Duty”: 
	Welcome to the West Wing Week, your guide to everyt... http://t.co/RZR7Grm1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama's Tax Cuts for the Middle Class: 

	Unless th... http://t.co/MkSieW0S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making Forms Simpler: 
	To fulfill its functions, the federal government asks people to fill out a lot of forms.... http://t.co/dKko572q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama's Call with the Prime Minister of India: 

    President Barack Obama talks on the phone wi... http://t.co/DToqbC9J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Report Highlights the Impact of the President’s Agenda on the Hispanic Community: 
	Yesterday I had the plea... http://t.co/NZBTDcw4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch and Engage: PTA Day at the White House: 
	As you may have already heard, this Friday we will welcome over ... http://t.co/vs0fzeil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Empowering Young People to Build a Kinder, Braver World: 
	Yesterday, Cynthia Germanotta and I had the opportuni... http://t.co/bbLxBUi7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Smarter Approach to Regulation: 

	Since taking office, President Obama has been committed to eliminating re... http://t.co/t9wKEWru]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Administration-Wide Response to the Drought: 
	Throughout much of the country, communities are struggling wit... http://t.co/q3rOWhve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding Inspiration in the Champions of Change: 
	Earlier this year, President Obama celebrated the one year ann... http://t.co/hMM8dfSv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vice President Biden Speaks to the Disabled American Veterans: 

    Vice President Joe Biden addresses the... http://t.co/HJHhSsge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Discusses the Shooting in Oak Creek, Wisconsin: 
	Before signing a bill that will better protect... http://t.co/Rx3kIZq4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Signs the Honoring America's Veterans and Caring for Camp Lejeune Families Act of 2012: 

 ... http://t.co/HDS65g2F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Curiosity Takes Us Back to Mars: 
	Ed. Note: This article is crossposted from NASA's blog

    The Mars Sc... http://t.co/Q7zUNr5d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Statement by President Obama on the Shooting in Wisconsin: 
	President Obama today released the following statem... http://t.co/y9OFOMpk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VA Employee and Medal Winning Olympian Natalie Dell on Veterans and Never Giving Up: 
	Ed. Note: This article wa... http://t.co/Ynq7yUI5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday, President Obama: 
	Today, President Obama turns 51. In honor of the occasion, we thought we’d sh... http://t.co/9eD7JQ3u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Address: Celebrating the Summer Olympics and Paralympics: 
	President Obama congratulates all of the Amer... http://t.co/hqqM9bHb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celebrating 3,000,000 @WhiteHouse Twitter Followers: 
	Today, the White House Twitter account reached 3,000,000 ... http://t.co/U4Ywpw0G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Travel and Tourism Industry Vital to Job Creation: 
	Earlier this week I joined Secretary of the Interior Ken Sa... http://t.co/lB7Y1utB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Behind the Scenes: Michelle Obama and the Presidential Olympic Delegation at Let's Move! London: 
	Go behind the... http://t.co/5NaCpcDi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NASA Announces Next Steps in Launching Americans from U.S. Soil: 
	[Editor's Note: This has been cross-posted fr... http://t.co/o2Z6ToJG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Employment Situation in July: 
	While there is more work that remains to be done, today’s employment report ... http://t.co/7AmQlxLQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Wing Week 08/03/12 “98 &amp; 98”: 
	This week, the First Lady brought ‘Let’s Move!’ to the Summer Olympics, the... http://t.co/Hg10qX8z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A New Step Forward to Protect American Wind Energy Jobs: 
	Today, in an overwhelmingly bipartisan vote, the Sena... http://t.co/dB743Gpy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David Plouffe: "President Obama is Talking Taxes Tomorrow": 
	David Plouffe, Senior Advisor to President Obama, ... http://t.co/flWAkerr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beam Signed By President Obama Installed at World Trade Center: 
	Today, the beam signed by President Obama and ... http://t.co/lY8v9vdd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Calls the US Squad: 

    President Barack Obama talks on the phone with members of the U.S... http://t.co/7WjRzEAN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House Office Hours: Preventive Care Benefits for Women: 
	Thanks to the Affordable Care Act, 47 million wo... http://t.co/dIVwlDyl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infographic: The Plan to Help Homeowners Refinance: 
	Congress is currently considering a plan that would help m... http://t.co/RmHc4Tk1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Wing Week: 09/14/12 or "Eleven": 
	Welcome to the West Wing Week, your guide to everything that's happening... http://t.co/1PkmDLUC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honoring Team USA at the White House: 
	Earlier this summer, First Lady Michelle Obama led the American delegati... http://t.co/Flax8hxs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama's Rosh Hashanah Greeting: 
	At sundown this Sunday, the Jewish community here in the United Stat... http://t.co/3AYlvlTy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[50th Anniversary of President Kennedy's Speech at Rice University: 
	Ed. note: This is cross-posted from NASA.go... http://t.co/UYLxJDtr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Welcoming New Citizens to the American Familiy: 
	Yesterday, I had the privilege of speaking at a naturalization... http://t.co/cWXcXcJX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Annual Census Data on Income, Poverty, and Health Insurance for 2011: 
	Today’s report shows that while we have ... http://t.co/KSbLoboc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Discusses the Attack in Benghazi, Libya: 

	Yesterday, four Americans lost their lives after a... http://t.co/hpRUOufp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Health Care Law is Saving Americans Money: 
	Ed. note: This is cross-posted from http://t.co/RQpGmff2.

	The ... http://t.co/RwapwRtt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marking the Eleventh Anniversary of 9/11: 

	Today, President Obama and the First Lady marked the eleventh ann... http://t.co/04dPBCkY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the Archives: September 11, a Day of Service and Remembrance: 

	Today, we honor the lives lost on Septem... http://t.co/muLAUqMm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FAA Commemorates 9/11 with NextGen arrival profiles into National Airport: 
	Ed. note: This is cross-posted from... http://t.co/mi4OTEsd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paying Tribute with Service: 

    President Barack Obama and daughter Malia Obama participate in a service... http://t.co/tdE2QDEv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Address: Coming Together to Remember September 11th: 

	President Obama marks the eleventh anniversary ... http://t.co/pdYVKgLo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Wrap Up: Engage!: 

	Here's a quick glimpse at what happened this week on http://t.co/4TLOL8vz:

	Presid... http://t.co/Wb70dWKg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. Support for Yemen’s Transition: 
	At the Yemen Donor Conference in Riyadh, which I attended on September 4,... http://t.co/hRPOamLR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Employment Situation in August: 
	While there is more work that remains to be done, today’s employment repor... http://t.co/Qd7RSn2K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Wing Week: 09/07/12 or "Engage!": 
	Welcome to the West Wing Week, your guide to everything that's happenin... http://t.co/zXs2sGCR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Office Hours: Inside the White House with Curator William Allman: 
	From day one, the President and First Lady h... http://t.co/hik823SG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Highlights of NFL Champions at the White House: 
	You know summer is at a close and fall is upon us when the NFL... http://t.co/b0n2oS8X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three Ways to Explore the White House...from Home: 
	Ed. Note: Do you have questions about the history of the Wh... http://t.co/6THfPpOo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spending Less, Spending Smarter: 
	
	Under the Administration’s Campaign to Cut Waste, we are scrutinizing every... http://t.co/vCGTthEJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Meets with Victims of Hurricane Isaac: 
	President Obama yesterday made his way to St. John's Pa... http://t.co/SwzqsSMI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We the People: 3 Million Signatures Later: 
	Last year, the White House launched a new tool called We the People... http://t.co/uaQbL8hP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Visiting the White House, "Anytime, Anywhere, and on Any Device": 

      ... http://t.co/SaLutNSn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Labor Day 2012: Honoring the Great American Worker: 
	Ed. note: This is cross-posted from Work in Progress

	On ... http://t.co/MweiOb1u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ale to the Chief: White House Beer Recipe: 
	Ed. Note: There's been a lot of buzz online recently about the reci... http://t.co/De1XWoTG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Address: Honoring Our Nation’s Service Members and Military Families: 
	President Obama marks the second ... http://t.co/yiOhwxDt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Speaks to Troops at Fort Bliss: 
	Two years after his visit to Fort Bliss that marked the end of... http://t.co/mMFFFbi7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Wrap Up: Salute the Troops: 

	Here's a quick glimpse at what happened this week on http://t.co/4TLOL8vz... http://t.co/HXJemdi8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More Than 2.5 Million Records Released: 
	In September 2009, the President announced that—for the first time in ... http://t.co/tF5Aq31L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Improving Access to Mental Health Services for Veterans, Service Members, and Military Families: 
	Ed. note: Tun... http://t.co/LAaDzZxQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Wing Week: 8/31/12 or, "It's Summer Mailbag Time!": 
	Welcome to the West Wing Week, your guide to everythi... http://t.co/CUSH0RtN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Rhodes Ahead: Second Anniversary of the End of the Combat Mission in Iraq: 
	On August 31, 2010, President O... http://t.co/jOrR3ybY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tracking the Response to Isaac: 

    (August 28 - Personnel in the National Guard Command Center in Arling... http://t.co/U1vVLYtL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salute the Troops: Two Years after the End of Combat Missions in Iraq: 
	On August 31st, 2010, President Obama a... http://t.co/RZtlkoOf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Update on Hurricane Isaac: 

    (Department of Homeland Security Secretary Janet Napolitano and FEMA Deput... http://t.co/Fzxr8s1s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Acting Secretary Blank Talks Insourcing and Job Creation at Economic Development Forum: 
	Ed. note: This is cros... http://t.co/rqHHZB4W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Historic Fuel Efficiency Standards for Cars and Light Trucks: 

	Ed. Note: This is cross-posted from The Fast ... http://t.co/ngveF3Cp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Discusses Preparations for Tropical Storm Isaac: 

    President Barack Obama delivers a st... http://t.co/74beRhZz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Preparing for Isaac: 
	As Isaac gathers strength in the Gulf of Mexico, forecasters with the National Weather Ce... http://t.co/vCZ25Syc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Photo Gallery: Remembering Neil Armstrong: 
	
Click here to see the photo gallery. 

	See the full-size galler... http://t.co/U4qzwSQI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House Business Council American Economic Competitiveness forum talks transportation infrastructure: 

			... http://t.co/1evwLQZO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Address: Preserving and Strengthening Medicare: 
	President Obama speaks to the American people about the... http://t.co/mlRYEjsv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Wrap Up: First-Ever Kids’ State Dinner: 

	Here's a quick glimpse at what happened this week on WhiteHo... http://t.co/2TmC46CN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Announcing 125,000 Hires Through Joining Forces: 
	Earlier this week, First Lady Michelle Obama traveled to Nava... http://t.co/oMOIKYGo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First Lady Michelle Obama Visits Sikh Community in Wisconsin: 

    First Lady Michelle Obama greets Kulwan... http://t.co/0L4IbOE5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Engages with Youth with Disabilities: 
	As President Obama has so often said, change in America ... http://t.co/BqQuonLR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Wing Week 08/24/12 or "The Historic, First-Ever Kids' State Dinner Edition!": 
	Welcome to the West Wing We... http://t.co/G584pavV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House Office Hours: #InnovateGov: 
	Today, it was "go time" for the Presidential Innovation Fellows, top i... http://t.co/bE8hGgLP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We the Coders: Open-Sourcing We the People, the White House's Online Petitions System: 
	I'm thrilled to announc... http://t.co/c2cUX50y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday, Bo!: It has been a very busy year for America's First Dog here at 1600 Pennsylvania Avenue. Chec... http://t.co/UNE4EweE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the Archives: Breast Cancer Awareness Month: 

  Click here to see the video. 

October marks Breast Ca... http://t.co/j9UfVOqg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honoring the Memory of My Grandfather, César E. Chávez: Today the President traveled to Keene, California to hon... http://t.co/POVXV0b5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Monument Honors Cesar E. Chavez, an American Civil Rights Leader: Today, I had the privilege of joining Pres... http://t.co/89vTHWVx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Address: Congress Should Keep America Moving Forward: 
In this week’s address, President Obama says that ... http://t.co/vjFL9W6l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What You Missed: WH Office Hours on Empowering Women &amp; Girls Through the Equal Futures Partnership: Today, I joi... http://t.co/aBtuG5OH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Wrap Up: Operation Educate the Educators: Here's a quick glimpse at what happened this week on WhiteHouse... http://t.co/smdLai4h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Employment Situation in September: While there is more work that remains to be done, today’s employment repo... http://t.co/nrkopddy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Wing Week: 09/05/12 or "Operation Educate the Educators": Welcome to the West Wing Week, your guide to ever... http://t.co/HXTK1No7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Office Hours on Equal Futures: Empowering Women and Girls at Home and Abroad: Last week, the U.S., along with 12... http://t.co/vKURDUsX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Launching the Equal Futures Partnership to Expand Women’s Political and Economic Participation: It is no secret ... http://t.co/q1P9ASJS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joining Forces to Train Teachers to Serve Military Children: This afternoon, I was so honored to meet two of our... http://t.co/53eZVXEc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An International Approach to Military Mental Health: Post-Traumatic Stress Disorder has been one of the most sig... http://t.co/I4RWUHX2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vice President Biden Celebrates Achievements of MRAP Task Force: 

    Vice President Joe Biden delivers re... http://t.co/3nyneJL6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House Goes Pink for Breast Cancer Awareness Month: 

    The North Portico exterior of the White Hous... http://t.co/cbgs5stf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Communities Around the Country Mark Domestic Violence Awareness Month: Today marks the beginning of Domestic Vio... http://t.co/EkZgyF8b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Address: It’s Time for Congress to Help Responsible Homeowners: 
In this week’s address, President Obama ... http://t.co/7PZk0R8D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More Than 2.6 Million Records Released: In September 2009, the President announced that—for the first time in hi... http://t.co/rb7BlRAL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Wing Week 09/28/12 or "A Common Heartbeat to Humanity": Welcome to the West Wing Week, your guide to everyt... http://t.co/cb6bIu4K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What You Missed: White House Hangout on Combating Human Trafficking: 
This week, President Obama spoke at the Cl... http://t.co/ACokdlmL]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>