<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About eCommerce E-Tips  http://t.co/Ys4vNs7TkP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Al Green  http://t.co/d8Oep5mBtc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cooking for Geeks: Real Science, Great Hacks, and Good Food  -&gt; http://t.co/zxXvDejChM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing shocks me - I am a scientist. - Indiana Jones, Indiana Jones and the Temple of Doom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overheard when the boss returned from his safari in Africa: "He's the first man the head shrinkers ever failed with."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Videos Games and Fitness with Wii and XBOX  http://t.co/tPgryPsyj6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cinderella is living proof that a pair of shoes can change your life…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Europe – Best Places to Tour  http://t.co/0sS5YzbHac]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A patient man is one who likes slow catsup.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of the animals except for man know that the principle business of life is to enjoy it. - Samuel Butler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A wife doesn't mind seeing a man make a fool out of himself as long as some other woman isn't helping him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Awesome Samurai Sword Chopsticks Set http://t.co/nS5d3HqV5f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one is too big to be kind and courteous, but many are too little]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are inclined to think that if we watch a football game or a baseball game, we have taken part in it. - John F. Kennedy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A twelve-year-old Ben Linus brought me a chicken salad sandwich. How do you think I'm doing? - Sayid Jarrah, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The iPaperPad is not magical or revolutionary. It's a paper pad. A poor man's iPad LOL http://t.co/NC8SCPOS85]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What is Fiverr Exactly and Why All the Buzz?  http://t.co/lhYbv7UZZ7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some of the greatest Hollywood actors are not the award winners, but those congratulating them on their triumph]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every day, in every way, I am getting better and better. - Emilie Coue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The studios have been taken over by marketing people and accountants. - Joe Eszterhas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Flip flops  http://t.co/W0AkoLWfBJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Molly Hatchet  http://t.co/GfRQyxQSRz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Choose a job you love, and you will never have to work a day in your life. - Confucius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like wrestling a gorilla- you don't quit when you're tired, you quit when the gorilla is tired - Robert Strauss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever hear of instant credit? You just add money]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't concentrate in flats! - Victoria Beckham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Wendy's  http://t.co/94FYJl3Qfn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your Attorney Search: Red Flags That Shouldn’t Be Ignored  http://t.co/owPlwJf3xB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Fun - Bumper Water Boats with Water Cannons! http://t.co/kPjpXkUSWV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never make fun of the geeks, one day they will be your boss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The rest of the world lives to eat, while I eat to live. - Socrates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Redrum. -  Danny, The Shining]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bird does not sing because it has an answer...  It sings because it has a song. - Chinese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pair off in threes. - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A wife doesn't mind seeing a man make a fool out of himself as long as some other woman isn't helping him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Very Unusual Hamburgers  http://t.co/C0wiel2wYA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Who Invented the Modern Watch?  http://t.co/4BFEg213m3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The trouble these days is there's no arrest for the wicked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I speak my mind. I never mind what I speak!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Ramones  http://t.co/ZK9stfNNiu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Bangles  http://t.co/WLGBTihnLP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I want to knock a story off the front page, I just change my hairstyle. --&gt; Hillary Rodham Clinton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is not a rock opera. This is not Tommy. I can write songs that emote, and that's it. - John Mellencamp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still have my feet on the ground, I just wear better shoes. - Oprah Winfrey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of David Gates  http://t.co/SdkbKY8s4e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are so many things you can learn about. But you'll miss the best things if you keep your eyes shut. - Dr. Suess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How to Select the Right Technology for Seniors  http://t.co/2G7gxVbyKg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Carlos Santana  http://t.co/5bjLv2iDFO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not wait to strike until the iron is hot; but make it hot by striking - William B. Sprague]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do... or do not. There is no try. - Yoda - The Empire Strikes Back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the history of the Modern Tennis Shoe  http://t.co/4ZBV9h96gh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not anorexic. I'm from Texas. Are there people from Texas that are anorexic? I've never heard of one. And that includes me. Jessica S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A mind once stretched by a new idea never regains its original dimensions. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Matrimony: An Institution of learning in which a man loses his "Bachelor's Degree" and his wife acquires a "Masters"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Commitment leads to action. Action brings your dream closer. - Marcia Wieder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A successful man is one who can lay a firm foundation with the bricks others have thrown at him... David Brinkley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, I think we're the greatest rock 'n' roll band in the world.  - Joey Ramone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I didn't grow up thinking, 'Oh, maybe someday I'm going to have a shoe named after me.' -  Sheryl Swoopes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL - Cool - A Computer Mouse with a Spider in it!   http://t.co/nQvf3TQ6wk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chanel liberated women: Saint Laurent gave them power. - Pierre Berge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't call me a mindless philosopher, you overweight blob of grease! - C3PO, Star Wars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Biking Guide BMX Review  http://t.co/ZCO0SddYLn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any fact facing us is not as important as our attitude toward it, for that determines our success or failure. - Norman Vincent Peale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money, if it does not bring you happiness, will at least help you be miserable in comfort. - Helen Gurley Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome camping t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the camping lovers in your life!   http://t.co/irwD2oyGuB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Hiring a Strategy Consulting Firm  http://t.co/pxLR4Nj0oX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I consider exercise vulgar. It makes people smell. - Alec Yuill Thornton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Successful Alternatives For Link Building  http://t.co/sbsIcNvVvf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The glass is neither half-full nor half-empty: it's twice as big as it needs to be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the Devine RPG Minecraft Mod - http://t.co/bZSqe9HUMK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Temptations  http://t.co/Ww6d3WJmDs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Amazing Big Bag Of Science! http://t.co/zeK2UnMmAb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In 1905 Albert discovered Relativity, in 1906 he invented Rock and Roll.  - Yahoo Serious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Who is The Grass Roots Classic Rock Group?  http://t.co/FaO9BJ8zL5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great History of Johnny Adams  http://t.co/QZH7UNsD9M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only way to prove that you're a good sport is to lose. - Ernie Banks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame Champions: Confused Much?  http://t.co/E8Jg9MBVeP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of Stargate Universe  http://t.co/FK8w7ZRmZy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just think it's great to show a gown that's $8,000 and a shoe that's, like, $25 - but still look fabulous together. - Christian Siriano]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Jay Ferguson  http://t.co/FuDK1mdQxk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The client is not always right. - Enzo Ferrari]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Let's Play: LOTR Ep 1: Meeting the Hobbits  http://t.co/707HVCYpcQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Capital as such is not evil; it is its wrong use that is evil. Capital in some form or other will always be needed.  Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am pushing sixty. That is enough exercise for me. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After the third flip, I lost control - Don Roberts after crashing in the Jade Grenade at New England Dragway in 1975.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If high heels were so wonderful, men would be wearing them. - Sue Grafton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious What Went Wrong T-shirt - Love It!  http://t.co/d9ML9ZdPrM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome baseball t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the baseball lovers in your life!   http://t.co/QUp4ekRItO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only person who is educated is the one who has learned how to learn and change. - Carl Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If a lot of people said what they think, they would be speechless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its better to own the racecourse then the race horse - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I pretty much try to stay in a constant state of confusion just because of the expression it leaves on my face.  Johnny Depp quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is not the most important thing in the world. Love is. Fortunately, I love money. - Jackie Mason]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the Romans had been obliged to learn Latin, they would never have found time to conquer the world. - Heinrich Heine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a way to do it better...find it. - Thomas Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jazz up  your pool or patio with these trendy light cubes - cool!  http://t.co/wQXhlv0PFM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He got brains but the're in cold storage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no psychiatrist in the world like a puppy licking your face. - Ben Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teenagers do everything we did…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Mike Clifford - A One-Hit Wonder  http://t.co/vpGwmeW7f8]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>