<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BeardedGenius: “It was a little tough to watch too much, but I watched as much as I could..." The absolute state of Trump talking about…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@crimesofbrits @OnThisDayPIRA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @crimesofbrits: The British Army went on a rampage in Dublin on this day in 1916. Going door to door shooting and bayoneting Irish civil…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BGinge8: If Liverpool only counted the goals scored by Mohamed Salah this season.... they'd be ahead of Everton on goal difference 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevinKelly1992 Going over for thon final?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CurtisDavidsonn Or a tory]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Seany_FC: You aren't in the same galaxy is that man chief pipe down https://t.co/RVnsmP5LeB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @iresimpsonsfans: The love both campaign release their next poster https://t.co/CtwevR5V0h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KCsixtyseven: Jurgen Klopp's tricolour Liverbird badge for Sean Cox. https://t.co/16TbRcNaOO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mans a nutjob https://t.co/u1TFQs9HQ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @amadoit__: Diego Costa sensing a possible confrontation is like watching a dog react to food dropping off of a table https://t.co/PUWbG…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Sabah07: That’s not Lovren https://t.co/1Bgd0I4dZB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AllezX3: Liverpool have requested the GAA Club Jersey of injured Irish man Sean Cox to hang to in the changing room of Stadio Olimpico…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Lord_Sugar: Eh I don't get this . Can someone explain is she making a statement or what ? https://t.co/C0zBVIcuQs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamieB_1992 It's caused we tanked them imo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ehbenj Stevie knew we'd do our thing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevinKelly1992 Boss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevinKelly1992 Markovic and borini!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @honigstein: Look who sneaked into the game tonight. (photo courtesy of Stefan Osterhaus) #FCBRMA https://t.co/JDXkdNJTi6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @The12thManLpool: If anybody has any contact with sean coxs family or friends i have accomadation above 12th man if they need any were t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @thisisanfield: This lad is all of us. https://t.co/nOznlSwgcc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevinKelly1992 Was it dear? Scandalous right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SportsJOE_UK: James Milner becomes the first person in #UCL history to get 9 assists in a single campaign💥 https://t.co/UAZ7zlWboA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SportsJOE_UK: A familiar face comes back to haunt his own teammates, HERE'S SALAH! https://t.co/uZB0mLWapL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @furmedge78: I don't buy this "you'd have taken 5-2 at the start!" comment. It was 5-0 with 15 minutes to go. The tie was over if we hel…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where im at. https://t.co/dNhAVCFd2D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheSportsman: 🔥🔴 Incredible scenes outside the Arkles at Anfield... 

#LFC

#LIVROM https://t.co/Ly9XKaXA7G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @smurphy2022: 😂😂😂😂 https://t.co/qo7QE4QiT5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kept myself busy today. Played on the range. Went for a long distance run. And it worked. Didn't really think about the game. Till about 15 minutes ago. Arse has fallen off now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lauraw97_ Better not]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sxmmo Off for 3 days now and will most definately be playing at some stage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sxmmo I fucking loath the tories but golf is class]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donegaldarren @MrTimDunn @ELangfordMusic Unreal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ryan3levis: Big Virgil's smiling social media posts are my safe place on the night before a Champions League semi-final... https://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @aadambirmingham: 3rd Muslim PFA Player of the Year in a row. https://t.co/lvZnmeYfWY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rdhwn: *hiding from serial killer*

me: omdz I'm gna get killed if he finds me 

killer: autoglass repair

me: autoglass replace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PrayForPatrick: challenge excepted you big tory @theresa_may https://t.co/asAwq452Zt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sonyalennon @_DHOTYA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobV96 Was flying to Derry once and and a stunner was sat beside me. Asked her where she was from and he replied Londonderry. Saiid never heard of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScalCapone Didn't know about the booze abuse. Poor fella.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScalCapone What happened him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevinKelly1992 Very nice lad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OFalafel: Latest: Arsenal linked with up and coming Italian manager Samuelo Allardiccio. https://t.co/JONJxMswq7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JamieRoss7: Remember when Avicii inexplicably backed Scottish independence while simultaneously giving some guy an absolute bodying? ht…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AYPrivateEye @FirmiSmo Ryanair to the moon and then fly from there be cheaper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRealTekks @BrixTuohy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheRealTekks: Claude to ty https://t.co/l2EeZd7EVd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevinKelly1992 Gonna do the same myself. Until I go mad and go to Kiev.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @wutangklavan: New balance don't give a fuck https://t.co/nJEPch1SEp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlissaNutting @_DHOTYA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wexit!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamieBrysonCPNI talking absolute manure on the radio as per.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevinKelly1992 @Robbie_OR @hipsterscumbag He's better than anything have in midfield]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iresimpsonsfans @DaireBoyle94]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bickerton_neil Selling for profit is dirt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TotalRecoyle Worse than Guantanamo that mate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TotalRecoyle Smithwicks be go to pint in an emergency.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TotalRecoyle 😂😂😂 go you in and do it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donegaldarren @karaweeks_ Haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gav0014 Chartbusters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iantn84 Silly season well and truly alive. Neves is good though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @paddimir: Kenny Miller needs to learn that no one man is bigger than the club.  Older, certainly, but not bigger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevosideways Cheers Stevo. He's on his way home as I write this. Can't wait to get him home.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @theliverpoolway: Harry Kane when he saw that Man City video https://t.co/xYZrFaw6hM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobV96 Horrendously low]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DamianConnor: When you've made up with the doorman and admitted you need to go  home https://t.co/H2yozexUa8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Seany_FC Beats khabib]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Truckerpaddy Lunatic but omg what a player]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nathcun: 5+ hours of waiting only to be told the flight is cancelled. Luckily @flybe were good enough to bless us with  three whole pou…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DavePooky: This is Stephen Whittle, the 97th victim of Hillsborough

Stephen sold his ticket to the match to his friend, who later died…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @iresimpsonsfans: .@jeremycorbyn : but I thought you said there was no magic money tree?
@theresa_may : oh no, I said "let's start world…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NewJohnKnox @d1872l @DWindass10 Aye.  Horrid institution. Like the DUP and sevco. 🇮🇪🇮🇪🇮🇪 ten In a row]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HLNinEngeland Shite mo salah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@d1872l @DWindass10 😂 says the racist loyalist bigot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@d1872l @DWindass10 Gonna win Tomorrow. Again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheStaunchest Rangers were a stain on the Earth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheStaunchest European cup winners. Mate your club was formed 6 years ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheStaunchest Disappearing Just like unionism!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@UpTheReds_ Haha what a cunt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@d1872l @DWindass10 Won't have a say in the matter big lad. Ulster is green. Brexit will deliver it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@d1872l @DWindass10 How mad will you be when Ireland is reunited ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@seathsmark @DWindass10 Sevco are. Dirty Bastards be beat again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bigootsiders @DWindass10 Don't exist mate Rangers are dead thank fuck. Sevco will never win a a league. #herewego10inarow #unitedireland #brexit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DWindass10 Rangers don't exist anymore mate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sean_Lonergan Worst humans on earth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did this earlier. Arsed if you like it or not tbh. I missed Out with city. https://t.co/koKbauNQc2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@misssazz @redbrowny Cheers saz.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@micealbebb Thanks Michael. Means a lot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_DHOTYA @DaireBoyle94]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sampgeoghegan Hope so. Like Brexit though it's the silent ones I fear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobV96 Rodgers came within a whisker of being on banners on the kop for ever. Don't under stand the hate at all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AiddyFriel @TelegraphDucker Home and away]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AiddyFriel @TelegraphDucker #triggered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TelegraphDucker @AiddyFriel money well spent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JimAllister Brexit is like shooting urself in the head. But at least you got to choose the gun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EamonMcGee: "Crystal Swing want you to vote No" should be put on every Yes poster in the country.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AiddyFriel @TotallyMUFC @Evra @DaireBoyle94 😂😂😂😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MrRoyThomas: https://t.co/nPWbKui5or]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_AndyHa @CormacHuzy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blud fam be drinking paint]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>