<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sylwiassta thanks for tweeting! Trying to build up awareness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mva_1000 @wayneford  my favourite photo of them all. 'Tea with five sugars'. That's how he likes it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @wayneford: New blog post: ‘I’ve lived in East London for 85 1/2 years’ by Joseph Markovitch and @MartinUsborne. #photobook http://t. ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just spent the day doing  'make-over' portraits for rescue dogs that can't find a home #yeartohelp http://t.co/5ORuMryo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just rescued dog that was due to be put down and drove him to safe kennels  #yeartohelp http://t.co/dwbHFhqo http://t.co/OPcncjuZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LectorIsmael thanks for watching!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Slightly embarrassing piece on me on german TV here  (go to min 1:00) http://t.co/B911ujiQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New article about my photography in latest edition of hotshoe mag @HotshoeMagazine http://t.co/Fxusm53r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wayneford love this book. great to see you the other day! Stay in touch. best]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just tried to stop man beating his dog in  park. He screamed blue murder at me. Something tells me he's not just angry with dog .... sad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LJArts glad you like. Hope to come to NY soon! new work in the pipeline and the Dogs in Cars book out in October http://t.co/WdgkCVNz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rosie_ann_leigh thanks for this! Do you have a copy? All best, martin and joseph]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[dirty duck update: duck on estate balcony has been rehomed at last!! - according to RSPCA at least. #yeartohelp http://t.co/u5lyDUAn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matscalway although I hope not TOO worthy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matscalway thanks fella!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[getting overwhelmed working out how to help dogs in Europe for #yeartohelp - I googled 'dogs in distress' and got freaked out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#yeartohelp » Sussex wildlife rescue – why Disney got it wrong (part 1). http://t.co/9WlR91ke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMG, this dog is better at rescuing dogs than I am.... it rescued its puppies out of a burning house and took them... http://t.co/vY2uNqMG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been researching what I can do to help dogs in Europe and the internet makes painful reading. Have come across... http://t.co/IFa74GQF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LumleyNews I photographed Joanna recently for CIWF. She was interested in my project spending a year helping animals: http://t.co/dwbHFhqo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My first wildlife rescue &amp;#8211; a bird stuck in a tree? http://t.co/4WsEXssv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rlmcclelland thanks for this! New to twitter so slow reply. Let me know if you need any portrait photography doing! http://t.co/n67XaVmA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katgreenphoto thank you Katherine! Glad you like it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Niamhms23 sorry to upset you Niamh!!!! but glad you liked it! Check out my new blog http://t.co/dwbHFhqo #yeartohelp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am in London for another week or two, if anyone knows of any animals in distress get in touch! @martinusborne #yeartohelp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been chasing up about the poor duck stuck on the council estate balcony  - he's not there any more. I rung... http://t.co/JExxm1Qm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just signed this... http://t.co/5xaTRVlr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was planning on going out to Greece to help dogs but it's been pushed back a few weeks. Anyone have any leads on... http://t.co/10IzHiza]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This story a real inspiration for my animal saving exploits - squirrel rescued from manhole with olive oil. Must... http://t.co/Gcell1So]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[spent day with Debbie McGee and Paul Daniels doing photoshoot. Quite surreal being in Paul's toilet (magic actually), but very nice peeps.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone want to sit on my bookstall in Victoria park this weekend? Beautiful spot, 11-4 daily by cafe,£6.50 p/h + £1 per book sold]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am weighing up the option of rescuing this duck from estate balcony myself if RSPCA don't do anything soon... http://t.co/RRE8IOSI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A friend just seen this baby duck (?) trapped on balcony...am going now..anyone know what it is? baby swan? http://t.co/G8MSS8Ya]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exhausted (emotionally, physically) from helping out the Sussex wildlife rescue team. Check out their incredible work http://t.co/VHir0zZp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deer was alive but very bad attack. Not sure I can do this much more]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Off to rescue another deer that's been attacked by a dog. Vet ambulances not allowed blue flashing lights. Faster,faster !!! #yeartohelp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just rescued seagull trapped on hospital roof. Walked back through intensive care complaining of broken wing. Strange looks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[baby hedgehog rescued from starvation enjoys his new food at the East Sussex rescue centre. http://t.co/zWWURIgm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Went to rescue a baby deer that had been attacked by a dog in East Sussex. Got there too late. V sad. Bambi vs Pluto, not a disney ending]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[just spent 11 hours working in sussex animal wildlife hospital, rescued a crow, saw a hedgehog die, fed baby fox - exhausted #yeartohelp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being filmed for German TV on a shoot - and they are translating it into Arabic - where on earth will I be seen?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have walked 21 hours round London, 3 to go. Feel delirious. Saw sunrise on prim hill, now stumbling through Heath #yeartohelp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After walking 14hr round London have seen/helped/saved fish, terrapin, hedgehog, maggots, seagulls, baby fox, cat- only 8 more hours walking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fotofreak_ thanks for mentioning!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pdnonline @Kehrer_Verlag Thanks for covering this so well!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vickipper @NewPhilanthropy No it was easy! you looked great!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[off to see Joe after heart attack. His book soon to make profit so am buying him new mobile for emergencies. Thanks for supporting project!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vickipper yes, just found you and wrote! Speak soon!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vickipper thanks for shoot yesterday - and for the great tips! Images coming soon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wayneford will do!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kocicenka thanks for supporting with twitter. It means a lot! stay in touch, Martin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jo_WhiteDog thanks for mentioning this Jo! Hi to you and all the dogs!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joseph Markovitch, the old man of hoxton had a heart attack last week. He is still with us and I'm visiting him soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_agatha_a @ayearinapocket glad you like project - did you rescue the ponies?? Well done!! stay in touch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timallenpho Oh no, few other people have said that. We can't seem to pin point the problem. What happened? We can do over phone if u want?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thedogreporter thanks so much for tweeting this. Means a lot to get support from other dog lovers. Will announce a dog-photo comp soon!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jakechurchill good article. Have FBed!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my recent photo book about old man of shoreditch almost sold out in 2 month. thank you! last remaining copies here http://t.co/yqo03VJF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LDNLitProject glad you like! They are virtually sold out but for special edition ones on my site http://t.co/yqo03VJF  thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woman on plane told me off for texting. We rowed.she hoped I would one day contribute to world. I said I help animals. She said didn't count]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessWhite99 autumn 2013 in virginia!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timallenpho you read my mind!! It's friday night and I'm off out with my new look!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessWhite99 yes looking good! How you guys doing?? x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bug, my dog, just ate my wicker hat. Well I suppose it is end of summer. Check out pic http://t.co/tQmpOZhe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AntonioGould will do. thanks very much. Hope all well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am starting a photo campaign to raise awareness for staffies sold on Gumtree - anyone got PR experience? 5 min advice on phone?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BOWOWOWmag hi natasha, can I call you today - how do I reach you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[just gave best man speech at my dad's wedding. Gulp. Seemed to go down ok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[spotted this canine traveler at airport. No doubt off to an important business meeting http://t.co/1FSQ68Cn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dogs In Cars book printed!! Off to the binders next, its out in a few weeks, thanks to all! http://t.co/RF2QGaWv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first page of my new art book Dogs in Cars just come off print press http://t.co/Es6z6HHB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am in Germany overseeing printing of my dogs in cars photo book with Kehrer verlag http://t.co/rCfYaPbj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@the_writer_1966 Hi Rob, hope you get a chance to read it, all the best, Martin and Moose]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BOWOWOWmag great, can you email me your phone number martinusborne@mac.com]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[just broke into an abusive greece dog home under cover of darkness. Scared the life out of me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BOWOWOWmag Thanks for that. Yes, I have heard of them. Is that natasha? Any chance of having a quick chat by phone when I'm back?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank god this rescued Pointer dog in Greece is now eating. Will be sent to Germany for new home in few weeks http://t.co/h40VFlhA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Up at 6am to help abandoned dogs near Kavos, Greece. Not sure these strays need saving http://t.co/1RjMgZd7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am walking rescue dog that has been chained to tree all it's life. He pulls as if I'm a tree too http://t.co/K20YEQAi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am in greece and I reluctantly give my potato dauphinoise to a street dog. He turns his nose up. Is he gluten free?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just met this man in restaurant who proudly showed me his deceased bird (a parrot?) #yeartohelp http://t.co/lDIGipk4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My first day working at Greek dog rescue centre and I fill a bucket full of poop. Lovely dogs tho' http://t.co/h5EqfL4C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vetschooldiary ha! hard to forget i bet...am out in Corfu working with a dog rescue charity called CARE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BOWOWOWmag yes, sounds really interesting, please tell me more!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maighreadsings glad you like it, hi from Joseph and me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Off to greece to help with stray dogs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[rescued this sick pup after going undercover in response to gumtree ad. vets tomorrow #yeartohelp http://t.co/FQEr3NOG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CllrDaisyBenson @kirstenbayes Hey daisy, thanks for spreading the word! Long time!!!! Stay in touch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@virginiawwest Glad you liked the video Virginia. Thanks for tweeting...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ewanjphillips glad you appreciate them Ewan!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alexandraboneuk glad you like them Alexandra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@imogenheap thanks imogen. Very flattered. Love your music too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fatmagenc88 yes, a great response! Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pendreigh yes I know what you mean! and he's retired now too. Shoot was called off last minute as Robbie Williams needed the space. Pah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[thank you, woof woof, beep beep...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SanDraLlorca @LaGuiadelPerro I can't read spanish but thanks for tweet! I'm writing a blog about saving dogs here: http://t.co/dwbHFhqo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Off to photograph Uggie the dog from The Artist tomorrow. Any idea for poses I should ask him to do?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opening night of a group photo show I'm in tomorrow in East London about our relation to animals @AlexGracePhoto  http://t.co/4yD9Kg06]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StudioLegohead thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AlexGracePhoto: 'For Our Pleasure?' Photo Exhibition @HackneyPH featuring AlexGrace, @MartinUsborne, @DanielKukla &amp; Adrien Ehrha ...]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>