<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[A stone-faced Steven Mnuchin explains to President Trump that corporate lobbyists are harmless. Richard Spencer proposes marriage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Jerusalem, Mitch McConnell overhears someone tell President Trump that Nordstroms employees are in on the joke. An ambassador tries hot sauce.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over the holidays, Mike Huckabee announces to President Trump that Alaskans are pro-Trump. Adriana Cohen prints out all the emails.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the locker room, Steve Bannon informs Melania that phone companies are about as dangerous as kittens. God Almighty quotes Scripture.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a playground, Steve Bannon rudely informs Kellyanne Conway that small business owners are withering under excessive regulations. Cthulhu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the season finale, Pete Sessions tries to convince President Trump that teenagers are selling land in National Parks. Vladimir Putin loses an eye.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a lost episode, Jared Kushner admits to Ben Carson that Apple and Microsoft are total winners. David Brooks wears a mask.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An incensed John Kasich politely tells Betsy DeVos that felons are open to dialogue. Larry the Cable Guy learns to knit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before breakfast, Hope Hicks proclaims to President Trump that neoliberals are trying to make ends meet. An obsequious reporter flashes a diplomat's wife.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Moscow, Ted Cruz explains to Melania that small business owners are real. A lovable old man checks out Grindr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A paranoid Sam Brownback tries to convince President Trump that Communists are tying up the phone lines. President Bush collapses in tears.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After a sleepless night, Darrell Issa reluctantly admits to President Trump that Iraqi refugees are human, all too human. Benjamin Netanyahu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While working out, Ryan Zinke proclaims to President Trump that Black Lives Matter activists are special guests. Bill Kristol jumps for joy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breathlessly, Matt Bevin overhears someone tell Ben Carson that reporters are strapped for cash. Chris Christie quotes Dostoyevsky.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Monday, Lamar Alexander tries to persuade Rick Perry that some voters are oppressed by excessive regulations. Scott Walker seeks justice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With gritted teeth, Sean Spicer insists to Kellyanne Conway that ACLU lawyers are clamoring for attention. Rush Limbaugh pretends to be deaf.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A patient Jason Chaffetz politely tells President Trump that the Feds are always strapped. Jeffrey Lord downloads a virus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While swimming, Wilbur Ross reluctantly explains to Jeff Sessions that white women are drains on public coffers. Corey Lewandowski tweets compulsively.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A jealous Louie Gohmert informs Katrina Pierson that prison guards are real. James Woods wins an arm-wrestling contest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a roomful of children, Sean Spicer persuades President Trump that felons are organizing resistance. God Almighty uses the wrong door.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On July 4th, Jason Chaffetz carefully explains to President Trump that Baptists are clamoring for attention. Tucker Carlson gets ready for the Big Night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a bonus episode, Ivanka tries to persuade Kellyanne Conway that Nation of Islam members are patriotic Americans. Scottie Nell Hughes quits smoking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Covered in rashes, Marco Rubio fails to convince President Trump that teenagers are digging holes in the yard. Bill Kristol lies to the press.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In an elevator, Elaine Chao tells Katrina Pierson that the backup dancers are potential donors. Hulk Hogan oozes pus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Camp David, Lamar Alexander convinces Jeff Sessions that Hollywood liberals are selling Girl Scout cookies. Adam Sandler makes a racist joke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the Christmas special, John Kasich explains to Melania that journalists are advocates for secession. The valet hides in the Oval Office.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After dinner, Ted Cruz tries to convince President Trump that ACLU lawyers are human, all too human. Clint Eastwood posts comments on Facebook.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Mar-a-Lago, Scott Pruitt tries to convince President Trump that Black Lives Matter activists are capable of great things. Charles Krauthammer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a lengthy montage, Wilbur Ross tries to persuade President Trump that unicorns are pretty adorable. Eric Trump sacrifices a black cat to Satan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a photo op, David Shulkin insists to President Trump that those girls are fake news. Sean Hannity rides off into the sunset.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While sunbathing, Ryan Zinke announces to Jeff Sessions that leftist college students are ignorant hayseeds. Jesus Christ makes a regrettable bet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The evil twin of Mitch McConnell accidentally convinces President Trump that Californians are filing another lawsuit. Richard Spencer gets an ulcer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over appetizers, Sean Spicer insists to Betsy DeVos that KGB spies are waiting in the green room. Karl Rove quotes the Torah.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smiling serenely, Matt Bevin divulges to Jeff Sessions that Muslim-Americans are hiding in Trump Tower. A local TV anchor pulls a muscle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A tense Jared Kushner admits to President Trump that angry parents are human, all too human. God Almighty tries to make memes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over drinks, Ivanka admits to Melania that NRA members are too turnt. Michael Savage shakes the wrong hand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Friday, Liz Cheney informs President Trump that government employees are enemies of the people. Peggy Noonan tweets compulsively.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While drunk, Jared Kushner accidentally convinces Rick Perry that ABC reporters are waiting in the Lincoln bedroom. The sommelier tweets compulsively.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a wedding, Matt Bevin tells President Trump that skeptics are making America great again. Ted Nugent kisses up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Jerusalem, Roger Stone proclaims to Kellyanne Conway that AARP members are not good with computers. Lou Dobbs jumps for joy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In front of the press, Butch Otter insists to Betsy DeVos that pool reporters are astonishingly successful. Erick Erickson wakes up screaming.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On a three-way call, Jeb Bush patiently explains to Melania that convicts are requesting donations. A mysterious man gets a makeover.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Mar-a-Lago, H.R. McMaster proclaims to Omarosa Manigault that feminist lawyers are too turnt. Tucker Carlson joins the military.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Jerusalem, Ivanka divulges to President Trump that Syrian refugees are enlightened leaders. The maid edits Wikipedia pages.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the men's room, Ivanka reveals to Ben Carson that evangelicals are indebted to Satan. An ex-girlfriend quotes Hegel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a press conference, Jared Kushner fails to persuade Katrina Pierson that poets are still waiting on hold. A White House tourist tries to use street slang.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Marine One, Jeb Bush admits to President Trump that abortion doctors are not that horny. An obsequious reporter ruins Christmas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On a dare, Marco Rubio informs Omarosa Manigault that Trump's in-laws are double agents. Victoria Jackson backs up the server.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While working out, Jason Chaffetz politely tells Rick Perry that Black Lives Matter activists are sitting on vast reserves of oil. Kayleigh McEnany]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a quinceañera, Roger Stone announces to Jeff Sessions that rural youth are part of the lamestream media. An obsequious reporter gets tangled in cords.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A younger version of Stephen Miller announces to Betsy DeVos that tech executives are selling body parts. Adriana Cohen botches an important interview.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Without meaning to, Liz Cheney proclaims to Rick Perry that Nordstroms employees are filing another lawsuit. Melania's bodyguard is torn apart by a mob.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the power goes out, Lamar Smith boldly informs Katrina Pierson that Lyft and Uber are planning something ominous. Larry the Cable Guy confesses a longtime crush.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Los Angeles, Ivanka patiently explains to President Trump that Amazon and Walmart are hiding in Trump Tower. Ivanka's bodyguard pretends to be deaf.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During church, Elaine Chao reveals to Rick Perry that Iraqi refugees are open to dialogue. A "fixer" writes it all down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a flashback, Jeb Bush proclaims to Omarosa Manigault that Republicans are big league. Bill Kristol shocks everyone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a bonus episode, Rick Snyder persuades Rick Perry that Mar-a-Lago members are probably contagious. Jesus Christ kneels before a new master.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While working out, Rand Paul explains to Omarosa Manigault that neo-Nazis are open to dialogue. Tila Tequila goes into mourning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During Christmas, Roger Stone overhears someone tell President Trump that the stars of Friends are not reading Breitbart. Milo Yiannopoulos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Easter, Jeb Bush politely tells Kellyanne Conway that journalists are alcoholics. Vladimir Putin abandons social media.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During church, Jason Chaffetz explains to Katrina Pierson that Mexican immigrants are reading Breitbart. Jeffrey Lord shrieks in terror.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While playing chess, Pete Sessions reluctantly admits to Melania that agnostics are deserving of human rights. Don King tries to make memes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the men's room, Louie Gohmert tries to persuade Jeff Sessions that CIA agents are hoarding Trump steaks. Chris Christie tries yoga.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Without meaning to, Pete Sessions convinces President Trump that teenagers are on point. Trump's bodyguard struggles to speak.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A polite Rex Tillerson calmly tells President Trump that government employees are part of the deep state. Tila Tequila cashes out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sweaty Nikki Haley rudely informs Melania that neoconservatives are waiting at Trump Tower. Stacey Dash loses an eye.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over appetizers, Rick Snyder mistakenly tells President Trump that wealthy executives are potential threats. George Will starts over.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a joke, Matt Bevin announces to Omarosa Manigault that Kentuckians are useful idiots. A White House tourist celebrates diversity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Sunday, Butch Otter decides not to tell Rick Perry that oil executives are spies. Victoria Jackson checks out Tinder.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A stone-faced David Shulkin politely tells Omarosa Manigault that environmental activists are heavily armed. Don King calls a cab.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While flirting, Louie Gohmert divulges to Ben Carson that the interns are not very affluent. The sommelier bores everyone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While sharing a cab, Butch Otter decides not to tell Melania that coal miners are special guests. Alex Jones prints out all the emails.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the phone, Sean Spicer rudely informs Jeff Sessions that Cubans are part of the shadow government. David Brooks dresses as a clown.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a press conference, Reince Preibus calmly tells Katrina Pierson that squirrels are buying up Trump properties. Bill O'Reilly hosts the clip show.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An angry Mitch McConnell informs Melania that black politicians are astonishingly successful. God Almighty flashes a diplomat's wife.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a joke, Wilbur Ross tries to convince President Trump that environmental activists are actually shapeshifting aliens. Karl Rove jumps for joy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the locker room, Ryan Zinke reluctantly admits to Omarosa Manigault that Kremlin officials are not reading Breitbart. Alex Jones fails the Voight-Kampff test.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a bender, VP Pence boldly informs Melania that paleoconservatives are still waiting on hold. Eric Trump violates protocol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While wrestling, Wilbur Ross convinces Kellyanne Conway that Catholics are Rosie O'Donnell fans. Jesus Christ quotes the Torah.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An angry Mitch McConnell mistakenly tells Ben Carson that evangelicals are airing their grievances. Rush Limbaugh proposes marriage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liz Cheney convinces Katrina Pierson that wealthy executives are digging holes in the yard. Ivanka's bodyguard is scared of the dark.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After the two argue, Ted Cruz overhears someone tell Katrina Pierson that iPhone users are phishing .gov email accounts. Willie Robertson quotes Hegel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A younger version of John Kasich accidentally convinces President Trump that coal miners are deserving of human rights. Bobby Jindal stonewalls reporters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the South Lawn, Scott Pruitt boldly informs Rick Perry that Zoroastrians are headed to prison. Rush Limbaugh finds a cursed sword.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A leering Lamar Smith patiently explains to President Trump that Mormons are carrying concealed weapons. Michael Savage loses an eye.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a bender, Pete Sessions tells President Trump that government employees are traitors. Jesus Christ makes a regrettable bet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over the holidays, VP Pence fails to persuade Omarosa Manigault that red state governors are conservative Christians. The butler has a vision.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Covered in rashes, Elaine Chao carefully explains to Katrina Pierson that WSJ reporters are part of the prank. Mike Tyson learns about memes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the power goes out, Ryan Zinke persuades Jeff Sessions that the New England Patriots are hoarding Trump steaks. Bill O'Reilly drinks all the booze.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While playing poker, Steve Scalise overhears someone tell President Trump that Muslims are part of the lamestream media. Alex Jones conceals an illness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A time-traveling Jason Chaffetz calmly tells President Trump that the Bushes are in the Oval Office. A "fixer" leaks to the press.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A grim-faced Lamar Smith politely tells Omarosa Manigault that several dictators are coming for dinner. Tila Tequila is sealed in a casket.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a panic, Matt Bevin proclaims to Katrina Pierson that bisexuals are faithful Republicans. Arnold Schwarzenegger knits a lovely hat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An exhausted Mike Huckabee carefully explains to President Trump that the Clintons are free at last. Bill Kristol shares a joint.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After a rally, Rand Paul boldly informs Katrina Pierson that Iranian immigrants are phishing .gov email accounts. Jesus Christ abandons ship.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over the holidays, Ryan Zinke reveals to Ben Carson that college professors are conservative Christians. Jon Voight redecorates the White House.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a bonus episode, Jared Kushner convinces Kellyanne Conway that white women are vandalizing statues. Vladimir Putin quits smoking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a wedding, Butch Otter admits to Jeff Sessions that FBI agents are phishing .gov email accounts. An ex-girlfriend goes commando.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a diner, Paul LePage reluctantly explains to Omarosa Manigault that Republicans are pro-Trump. Pat Buchanan edits Wikipedia pages.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a ritual, Kevin McCarthy tries to convince Melania that Russian spies are infiltrators. Scott Baio briefly says hello.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>