<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Profanity is a strong way to express a weak mind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the The Burning Bridge by John Flanagan  http://t.co/M4zonWhEmq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am pushing sixty. That is enough exercise for me. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your Attorney Search: Red Flags That Shouldn’t Be Ignored  http://t.co/owPlwJf3xB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's hard to shake hands  with a clenched fist!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If science fiction is the mythology of modern technology, then its myth is tragic. - Ursula K. Le Guin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is what we are, and football is what we have become. - Mary McGrory]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame: Capture the Flag  http://t.co/fqKuvNezo0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[London Weight Loss Salon sign: "We value the pound."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Either write something worth reading or do something worth writing about.  Benjamin Franklin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A toupee is ear to ear carpeting!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd just as soon kiss a wookiee! - Princess Leia, The Empire Strikes Back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best thing about animals is that they don't talk much. - Thornton Wilder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Style is knowing who you are, what you want to say, and not giving a damn --&gt; Orson Welles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Humour. It is a difficult concept - Saavik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Use Twitter in Business  http://t.co/6tEiHzOIYG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Few people SUFFER from egotism. With most of them it's a PLEASURE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of LA Gear  http://t.co/VuHCdYZnUa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious Zombie Family Car Stickers - http://t.co/3S57pLEaNh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oooh right, it's actually quite a funny story once you get past all the tragic elements and the over-riding sense of doom. - Duckman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame Block Hunt: That Guy had a Porcupine Sleep on His Face  http://t.co/0Ohrr0fVRP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Assisted Living in Your Own Home  http://t.co/ILQmjpDYTd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Who is The Grass Roots Classic Rock Group?  http://t.co/WrCEeUJUlC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never wear the same shoe twice. - Dion Sanders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A shoe has so much more to offer than just to walk. - Christian Louboutin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest thing in this world is not so much where we stand, as in what direction we are moving. - Oliver Wendall Holmes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Natalie Cole  http://t.co/0TSpc7kr0a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Creative Writing Degree - Why You Should Consider One  http://t.co/Svcs7ofGsU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the way society functions. Aren't you a part of society? - Kramer, Seinfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Natalie Cole  http://t.co/6ZnkJ9WeWa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You will never change your life until you change something you do daily. - Mike Murdock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Ohio Players    http://t.co/VXwW7ls8mX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's so nervous he keeps coffee awake]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Using Tumblr for Business  http://t.co/0UXLt0rnnm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn Baseball Lingo  http://t.co/Qx6ahvtEEm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I dig science fiction, though it was never really my thing. - Yancy Butler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I believe you are your work. Don't trade the stuff of your life, time, for nothing more than dollars. That's a rotten bargain - Rita  Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft House Showcase: Touring the Winning House  http://t.co/IlCbRxz4PM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometime the best thing to get off your chest is your chin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wait a minute, Doc. Ah --  Are you telling me you built a time machine --  out of a DeLorean? - Marty McFly, Back to the Future]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A philosopher is someone who knows what to do until it happens to him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the Romans had been obliged to learn Latin, they would never have found time to conquer the world. - Heinrich Heine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future belongs to those who believe in the beauty of their dreams. - Eleanor Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[USBCELL AA Rechargeable Batteries work just like rechargeable batteries - simply recharge by any powered USB Port http://t.co/MK3D2uCoQ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Budweiser  http://t.co/a8pCtJPg14]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketing is the devil. - Billy Bob Thornton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Kiss  http://t.co/0tVrVc1uEh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The dog was created especially for children. He is the God of frolic. - Henry Ward Beecher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If high heels were so wonderful, men would be wearing them. - Sue Grafton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Ray Conniff  http://t.co/jPCg0syLnw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I had learned education I would not have had time to learn anything else. - Cornelius Vanderbilt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calling upon my years of experience, I froze at the controls. - Stirling Moss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His pockets always outlast his suits...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gold Glitter Lips - Cool Look!  http://t.co/jzT4WmtSYX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peace Through Superior Firepower "We endanger species"  - Mottos of the marines in Aliens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The absolute fundamental aim is to make money out of satisfying customers. - John Egan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Benefits of iPads for Seniors  http://t.co/bvhGebHYXQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boys, baseball is a game where you gotta have fun. You do that by winning. - Dave Bristol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The difference between a mountain and a molehill is your perspective. - Al Neuharth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are going to turn this team around 360 degrees. Jason Kidd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your Attorney Search: The Advantages of Flat Rates  http://t.co/wkEOA1nPe4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I live in heels. Give me a pair of flip-flops and I'll trip all over myself. - Brenda Song]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion is a form of ugliness so intolerable that we have to alter it every six months. --&gt; Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of the hilarious "I Love Lucy" episode - The Kleptomaniac  http://t.co/u0pOjulhuq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Alice Cooper  http://t.co/2EtiUUV6Ia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Rolling Stones  http://t.co/rWdP5q3Hu8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of the Facebook Game: Miscrits of Sunfall Kingdom  http://t.co/QtNE7NfgIG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We (San Francisco) have football weather during baseball season, and baseball weather during football season. - Herb Caen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So my degree was in political science, which I think was - the closest I could come to marketing is politics. - Steve Case]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am pushing sixty. That is enough exercise for me. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Frustrated at Cleaning Your Keyboards and Other Electronics?  Check Out Cyber Clean - Fast and Simple! http://t.co/nomC4JfZCl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mr. Spock, the women on your planet are logical. That's the only planet in this galaxy that can make that claim. - James T. Kirk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do clever men make good husbands? "No, clever men don't become husbands!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where there is an open mind, there will always be a frontier. - Charles F. Kettering]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame Turf Wars: Such Rage; Much Death  http://t.co/QSuPRuartb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Giant Squids - Hunters of the Deep  http://t.co/YWpbjb0fCq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to J.R.R. Tolkien  http://t.co/eCBo6k1xlm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The safest way to double your money is to fold it over and put it in your pocket. - Kin Hubbard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I didn't have a big fat Greek wedding, but I have a lot of fat Greek friends. Pete Sampras]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Who Invented the Modern Watch?  http://t.co/4BFEg213m3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool Geek Tech - Mini USB Fan - Keep cool at your desk! --&gt; http://t.co/8wRWDZiKs9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So say we all. - Battlestar Galactica]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the star wars lover in your family - Jedi Dressing Gowns - May the force be with you!  http://t.co/M1rVriKW6w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome!  Spongebob Squarepants I Love Nerds Green Juniors T-shirt! http://t.co/RlvbNrLJ0l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may be dumb, but I'm not stupid.  Terry Bradshaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do... or do not. There is no try. - Yoda - The Empire Strikes Back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is what you get from reading the small print in a contract. "experience " is what you get from not reading it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Paul Davis  http://t.co/uw1xl8k3Xz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Invest in Penny Stocks And Earn Huge Profits  http://t.co/zM6i2razRB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is not the man who has too little, but the man who craves more, that is poor.  Seneca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future belongs to those who believe in the beauty of their dreams. - Eleanor Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conceit is a strange disease, it makes everyone sick but the one who has it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagination is more important than knowledge. Knowledge is limited. Imagination encircles the world. - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Mott the Hoople  http://t.co/L0PxwBtZP7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Pat Benatar  http://t.co/EuqPh0MH2E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making money is a hobby that will complement any other hobbies you have, beautifully. Scott Alexander]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Hilarious 60s Comedy – Get Smart  http://t.co/OHJxYBSoD3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're really getting old when your work is less fun and your fun is more work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's like saying Prada's are just shoes, or vodka is just a morning beverage! - Karen, Will &amp; Grace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You never stop earning when you do what you love. - Asha Tyson]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>