<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Finished editing the photos from this morning. Check them out on my Facebook or Tumblr! #photography]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Photoset: SFU in Burnaby. http://t.co/pk6ELiaC7D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Totally forgot to upload and edit some photos I took this morning.. How did I forget to do this....?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for recipes... Getting ready to make something tomorrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can someone mentor me on electronic music production? I could really use some tips...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hopefully I get the things from Shauna soon.. I need some of it to get an idea how to put the vocals in the song.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally back from SFU.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learning a new DAW is so confusing... Thats what happens when im in love with my old one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YoungSavy_xo Here's your hot wings!
http://t.co/HbkK5siVIu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Started off my first day of summer break by waking up at 2pm. Then I decided to bake... why? Cause im huuuungry!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I finally have Ableton! Its great having this DAW but im not sure if im going to make it my primary one. Gunna stay with FL for awhile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JSWPhotography: 5 Composition Tips for Landscape Photography http://t.co/nb9S63kD6u #photography]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well I had my last day of PE yesterday. No more PE for the rest of my high school life!! YAAAY!! Now I need to find a way to stay fit...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its so funny how everyone is complaining about their exams and provincials while im here not caring. Plus my exam is tomorrow morning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @elyonworship: Jeremiah 29:11 For I know the plans I have for you, declares the LORD, plans for welfare and not for evil, to give you a …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Zedlerz Eugene maaan &lt;3 haha #Bromance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Zedlerz did I tell you that Eugene's solo was so sexaay!! &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Zedlerz You already tweeted it? haha I never saw it on my feed. Hold up lemme retweet it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doing nothing in PE class. What to do for an hour....?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My new sounds: Fruit Of The Spirit - Joy http://t.co/W04QuSPmKr on #SoundCloud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ive been working for 4 straight hours on a new song. I wanna sleep... but so early. I still have no idea what to name the song...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Scripture_Truth: Don’t procrastinate — there’s no time to lose. -Proverbs 6:4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Started 2 new projects. A new hip hop remix and some dubstep!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Scripture_Truth: Love is patient, love is kind. It does not envy, it does not boast, it is not proud. -1Corinthians 13:4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think its time to start looking for a job again....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My friend thinks I have a thing for someone... Ohh guuuys! -___________-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not sure if my next song should be an electronic track or a beat making track...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JarridWilson: Matthew 6:34 | Stop worrying about tomorrow. He's got it all under control.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Scripture_Truth: My command is this: Love each other as I have loved you. -John 15:12]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @louiegiglio: We can't be everywhere and do everything, but when we are available to God where we are anything can happen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_itsmigueel Youre in grade 9... You barely have any exams... -______-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guess who has a songwriter and a vocalist?! THIS KIDD!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like I might have someone do some songwriting and vocals for my music! Lets see what happens tomorrow...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @God_Loved: God not only sees where you are, He sees where you can be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Audio: Galations 5:22-23  But the fruit of the Spirit is love, joy, peace, forbearance, kindness, goodness,... http://t.co/JcyWF174fG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My new sounds: Fruit Of The Spirit - Patience http://t.co/SHkpcx2Dzr on #SoundCloud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As iron sharpens iron, so one man sharpens another. -Proverbs 27:17]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A simple "God bless" can change everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great show tonight! Exhausted and ready to sleep...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excited for tomorrow night's show! Show on my buuurfydaay hahah!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unexpectedly got a solo for one of the songs for choir for tomorrows Jazz Night. Well I guess that's what I get when I stay after class. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out some of my photography!! --&gt; http://t.co/2KIfsTQaKu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 hour practice of small ensemble. Exhausted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't sleep....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ive spent about 10-15 hours working on that remix. #GoodJob #Dedicated #Motivated]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out my remix of @CapitalKingsUSA song, "All The Way" --&gt; http://t.co/zjtTWynQF7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Audio: My submission to Capital Kings’ remix contest. Hope you enjoy listening to it!! http://t.co/cwJqtUNlFB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you heard ‘Capital Kings - All The Way (12th Son Of Jacob Remix)’ by @decaiman67 on #SoundCloud? https://t.co/LwpajDP7Vo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My new sounds: Capital Kings - All The Way (12th Son Of Jacob Remix) http://t.co/Y46V1mqbfZ on #SoundCloud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think my remix is ready. Midnight release?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I regret having my drivers license...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I frick'n give up.. help me..... :''(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To get the right sound, play with the effects. #ProducerTips]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JarridWilson: Church is who we are, not where we go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You just cant stop making music if you're having too much fun with it. #ProducerProblems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spend about half the day working on this remix. And Im still working on it...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Capital Kings followed me!! #FanBoyMoment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remix contest! Lets do this!! #AllTheWay @CapitalKingsUSA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone have a pair of Sony earphones I can have? I need some pre' bad... :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@Scripture_Truth: The thief comes only to steal &amp; kill &amp; destroy; I have come that they may have life, &amp; have it to the full. -John 10:10”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Soo I just broke another pair of earphones. Time to get a new pair.. On the bright side, this pair lasted longer than my older ones.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I cant wear snapbacks.. It just doesnt suit me. Im more of a fadora person.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need some inspiration and motivation.... Gotta get back to working on music and less slacking off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PauloApolinar: MSN was the only reason I could type at the speed I can today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need to start talking to some friends again.  Hmmm where's my phone?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give me dove's eyes.
Give me undistracted devotion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bboyvincanity Do you have any tips for learning flares?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can I meet them already? @AndyMineo @lecrae @Tedashii @KB_HGA @TripLee116 @thederekminor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @djofficialdj: I have no clue what GOD is doing but I must follow and let him lead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Photoset: Downtown, Vancouver on Canada Day. http://t.co/LXKcU7i0Kl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out my music --&gt; http://t.co/R2QGljY8XT #Youtube #Soundcloud #music #Electronic #BeatMaking #Remix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I haven't texted anyone in weeks... SOMEONE TEXT ME!!! #Sadlife #NoSocialLife #ForeverAlone #NeverUseMyPhoneAnymore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished watching Despicable Me 2 #GoodMovie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just watched The Hunger Games with the family. #MovieNight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beat Making - All For The King (Intro): http://t.co/svQgDoJAYm via @youtube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beat Making - Dance Like David: http://t.co/rxEEJ146p7 via @youtube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drove for the first time today. Fun stuff xD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The last time I had a decent conversation via texting.... Was June 26... That's sad, I have no social life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goal for this summer: Finish two songs.

One song already done. Just need the lyrics from Shauna to continue on the other song.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pimpin' my iPod out with some new tweaks and a new theme.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Subscribe? http://t.co/R2QGljY8XT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mastering vocals take so much time #ProducerProblems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its weird how everyone got their L today...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So now that I have my learners licence, Its time to find a job..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RNGDancers1: "Great dancers are not great because of their technique, they are great because of their passion." - Martha Graham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@0marhanafi Got my L.... You getting yours yet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MIKEOSONG: dude Christian rap goes off!!! what the heezy... found a super ill rapper with SICK BEATS #unexpectedturnofevents]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Tedashii: If some moments feel like you're walking on water, embrace it. We're supposed to walk by faith.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai Ohhh that kid!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai Can we change up this plan and kill Tommy instead...? #ImTooInnocent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out my Youtube channel, I also put my music up there too! --&gt; http://t.co/R2QGljY8XT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai I would totally expect that from you...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai Deja vu.... The last time I heard you sing, you tried to kill me...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai Ive never seen you dance actually.. (I think) But your singing is AMAZING!! #Sarcasm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 more study days til I take my knowledge test for driving. "L", here I come!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai haha Well, your dancing isnt that bad.. ;) #TryingToBeNice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai I checked out Will's channel and his dance vids make me want to dance again. Theres no way theyre dating, MB is dating JJH.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai So hyped now just because theyre Filipino!! They both dance too..... &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai Did you know Will Pacarro and Megan Batoon are both Filipino?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AndyMineo: Yes, we are all "Children of God." But not all of us have a father-child relationship w Him.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>