<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: The Effect of Cash Transfers to Schools on Voluntary Contributions http://t.co/yYkpQ1GQhG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Investigating the Sensitivity of Household Food Security to Agriculture-related Shocks and the Implicat... http://t.co/tBFGFfi6af]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Benefit in the wake of disaster: Long-run effects of earthquakes on welfare in rural Indonesia http://t.co/Cm2inPqs0Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Can conditional cash transfers improve education and nutrition outcomes for poor children in Bangladesh... http://t.co/fJ8FS0VWeC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Evaluation of the Impact of School Canteen Programs on Internal Efficiency of Schools, Cognitive Acquis... http://t.co/sZRHaOsFDy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JDE: Fertility and Rural Labor Market Inefficiencies: Evidence from India http://t.co/JelIpwzR10]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JDE: Vote Suppression and Insecure Property Rights http://t.co/AdH9LS7fB8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JAE: Beyond Aid: How Much Should African Countries Pay to Borrow? http://t.co/IKzvALV0uL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Does Infrastructure Facilitate Social Capital Accumulation?　Evidence from Natural and Artefactual Field... http://t.co/qpX2gZYa3E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JDE: The role of the informal sector in the early careers of less-educated workers http://t.co/Dn8I40sLo5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JDE: Local intermediate inputs and the shared supplier spillovers of foreign direct investment http://t.co/9Mzf0KFZJq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Determinants of poverty among ethnic minorities in the Northwest region, Vietnam http://t.co/LmgmgxhhiY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Geopolitics, Aid and Growth http://t.co/LVuMrKsNi9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Agricultural Production performance on Small farm holdings: Some Empirical Evidences from Bihar, India http://t.co/JcYqSBYhMa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: To What Extent Does the Adoption of Modern Variety Increase Productivity and Income? A Case Study of th... http://t.co/IdfW5IaHW6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Business training plus for female entrepreneurship? Short And medium-term experimental evidence from Peru http://t.co/9ccSGStoin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Analysing the Effects of Crop Shocks on Child Work: the Case of the Morondava District in Madagascar http://t.co/QGcOllgJjH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Diet quality, child health, and food policies in developing countries http://t.co/MxrsEauHn7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Conspicuous Consumption and Peer Effects among the Poor: Evidence From a Field Experiment http://t.co/YpDqTzamZ8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Ex-post Risk Management Among Rural Filipino Farm Households http://t.co/byRfkJX7PQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Assessing the Political Impacts of a Conditional Cash Transfer: Evidence from a Randomized Policy Exper... http://t.co/01LcySPZKS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Does access to microfinance affect consumption inequality? :evidence from a randomized controlled trial... http://t.co/FpNgDW5sHX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Maintaining Local Public Goods: Evidence from Rural Kenya http://t.co/TlW2QlT1K4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Evaluating CCTs from A Gender Perspective: the Impact of Chile Solidario on Women’s Employment Prospect http://t.co/TT8P61VsOl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NBER: The Road to Redemption: Policy Response to Crises in Latin America -- by Carlos A. Vegh, Guillermo Vuletin http://t.co/PjWMTYlSQb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Is Country-system-based Aid Really Better than Project-based Aid? Evidence from Rural Water Supply Mana... http://t.co/W6fMIglts7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Looking Like an Industry: Supporting Commercial Agriculture in Africa http://t.co/O5H4MLzlnC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Basis Risk and the Welfare Gains from Index Insurance: Evidence from Northern Kenya http://t.co/o0JvRwo4w3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Local government spending and multidimensional poverty in Senegal: insight from the fuzzy approach http://t.co/mGJAHyFLYT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Risk, Infrastructure, and Rural Market Integration: Implications of Infrastructure Provision for Food M... http://t.co/451e7IFRub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Fertility, Household’s size and Poverty in Nepal http://t.co/LoE9R0puzG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World Development: Unintended Consequences of Community-Based Monitoring Systems: Lessons from an HIV Preventi... http://t.co/5cUOqT5erA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JAE: Reverse-Share-Tenancy and Agricultural Efficiency: Farm-Level Evidence from Ethiopia http://t.co/xB1FXmOogc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JDE: Giving Kids a Head Start: The Impact and Mechanisms of Early Commitment of Financial Aid on Poor Students... http://t.co/Ibpycef5Te]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JDE: Don’t Tell on Me: Experimental Evidence of Asymmetric Information in Transnational Households http://t.co/BPx3nk0UY2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JDE: Business training plus for female entrepreneurship? Short and medium-term experimental evidence from peru http://t.co/0bbY6pJeni]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NBER: Federal Reserve Policy and Bretton Woods -- by Michael D. Bordo, Owen F. Humpage http://t.co/oXBZUeuyHK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EJ: Contractual Dualism, Market Power and Informality http://t.co/WlbEnWkZBh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EJ: Financial Literacy And Financial Behaviour: Experimental Evidence From Rural Rwanda http://t.co/pPVI8xaQ1w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Local poverty reduction in Chile and Mexico: The role of food manufacturing growth http://t.co/N65CVwlKy4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: The land certification program and off-farm employment in Ethiopia http://t.co/xTSkZkBybe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: The development push of refugees http://t.co/bgnw286zny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Variable returns to fertilizer use and its relationship to poverty: Experimental and simulation evidenc... http://t.co/VjyMb805Cp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Emergence and evolution of learning gaps across countries: Linked panel evidence from Ethiopia, India, ... http://t.co/gQoE6bFuNh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Resistance to the Regulation of Common Resources in Rural Tunisia http://t.co/BP1LCe6DYu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: The Impact of Displacement on Child Health: Evidence from Colombia's DHS 2010 http://t.co/vUjhTCo01X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Measuring agricultural knowledge and adoption http://t.co/Z0vh4SLut1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: The Impact of Being Poor During Crisis on Child Health and Cognitive Development in Indonesia http://t.co/dQL60kFoPU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Evidence on policies to increase the development impacts of international migration http://t.co/0Oq7W8iR9R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: The Long-Term Effects of the Printing Press in Sub-Saharan Africa http://t.co/y6J0irxnkS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Saving for a (not so) Rainy Day: A Ramdomized Evaluation of Savings Groups in Mali http://t.co/t3f1eqvmGY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JDE: Climate and the slave trade http://t.co/6uTsW6FU94]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JDE: Water Scarcity and Birth Outcomes in the Brazilian Semiarid http://t.co/FT2DrBxZOV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EJ: What Predicts a Successful Life? A Life-course Model of Well-being http://t.co/Am2rCUdzOn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Tools, Fertilizer or Cash? Exchange Asymmetries in Productive Assets http://t.co/sbsLpjHLon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Vitamin A Deficiency and Training to Farmers: Evidence from a Field Experiment in Mozambique http://t.co/vjKCHc70ri]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Agricultural productivity, hired labor, wages and poverty : evidence from Bangladesh http://t.co/9q40syertm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Measures, spatial profile and determinants of dietary diversity: Evidence from India http://t.co/rUOSPEbB0o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: How does contract design affect the uptake of microcredit among the ultra-poor? : experimental evidence... http://t.co/LV3zxBRsUM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: (Measured) Profit is Not Welfare: Evidence from an Experiment on Bundling Microcredit and Insurance http://t.co/Ajw4QpjT62]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Seasonal Credit Constraints and Agricultural Labor Supply: Evidence from Zambia http://t.co/vuPzxvqd38]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Estimating the impact of microcredit on those who take it up: Evidence from a randomized experiment in Morocco http://t.co/5pmEntSD25]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Saving for a (not so) Rainy Day: A Randomized Evaluation of Savings Groups in Mali http://t.co/i1g6Qposp1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Activity Choice in Rural Non-farm Employment (RNFE): Survival versus accumulative strategy http://t.co/VCIwLIXu9R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: African growth miracle or statistical tragedy? Interpreting trends in the data over the past two decades http://t.co/Q72O8vxOVf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Further Evidence on the Link between Pre-Colonial Political Centralization and Comparative Economic Dev... http://t.co/pK2BhWEHSK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Making Progress on Foreign Aid http://t.co/TjVW8p4F0Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Agricultural intensification : the status in six African countries http://t.co/bfhK3MYDk9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Agricultural Employment, Wages and Poverty in Developing Countries http://t.co/O5wKkvN8ma]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: This mine is mine! How minerals fuel conflicts in Africa http://t.co/hSl8CwcOyQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Place and child health : the interaction of population density and sanitation in developing countries http://t.co/csdFxldHWK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: What doesn't kill you makes you poorer : adult wages and the early-life disease environment in India http://t.co/EUWXcGI58b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Macroinsurance for Microenterprises: A Randomized Experiment in Post-Revolution Egypt http://t.co/1pouicBfcY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Gender Differences In Technology Adoption And Welfare Impact Among Nigerian Farming Households http://t.co/Zcy3tN25lQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Agricultural Technology, School Participation and Child Labor in Developing Countries: Cotton Expansion... http://t.co/xW7B3S9BsX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Measured as poor versus feeling poor: Comparing objective and subjective poverty rates in South Africa http://t.co/CkyB7JZDT5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Financing Smallholder Agriculture: An Experiment with Agent-Intermediated Microloans in India http://t.co/9eqsmGA2kP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: How significant is Africa's demographic dividend for its future growth and poverty reduction ? http://t.co/jtQ00Qc4b0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: How far does a big push really push? http://t.co/OFhgJyD8XU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: The impact of conditional cash transfer programmes on household work decisions in Ghana http://t.co/Qyy5FpE6uM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Customary Norms, Inheritance, and Human Capital: Evidence from a Reform of the Matrilineal System in Ghana http://t.co/u2kvMHrIm9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Does ethnic diversity decrease economic interactions? Evidence from exchange networks in rural Gambia http://t.co/TxRFIG8Xip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Preschools and early childhood development in a second best world: Evidence from a scaled-up experiment... http://t.co/Kyyp9UXjUE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Economy-wide effects of input subsidies in Malawi: Market imperfections and household heterogeneity http://t.co/5o1vBfd90j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Teacher Pay and Student Performance: Evidence from the Gambian Hardship Allowance http://t.co/nhpgw7WaBA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Milking the data : measuring income from milk production in extensive livestock systems -- experimental... http://t.co/1wsOhnfavS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Remittances, informal loans, and assets as risk-coping mechanisms: Evidence from agricultural household... http://t.co/xHocuxU8tl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: An African Growth Miracle? http://t.co/09p40LGQAh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JDE: The resource curse: A statistical mirage? http://t.co/u4GNxYSJfe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: The Relative (in)Efficiency of South African Municipalities in Providing Public Health Care http://t.co/RLnweqUqQc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: The role of social networks in an imperfect market for agricultural technology products: Evidence on Bt... http://t.co/fj3Jdm11pn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Social Networks and Health Knowledge in India: Who You Know or Who You Are? http://t.co/b8c4UqiWYW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: The Impact of a One Laptop per Child Program on Learning: Evidence from Uruguay http://t.co/IHSS9UFBD2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Do input subsidies crowd in or crowd out other soil fertility management practices? Evidence from Zambia http://t.co/IsHKtkIkBZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Credit Quality in Developing Economies: Remittances to the Rescue? http://t.co/8wLMWfiN2q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Gender-preferential intergenerational patterns in primary education attainment : a quantitative analysi... http://t.co/9q1BDol8a3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Determinants of Land Allocation in a Multi-Crop Farming System: An Application of the Fractional Multin... http://t.co/vMFDj6O8OO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Public Health Effects of Natural Resource Degradation: Evidence from Indonesia http://t.co/yNQFz97dmd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Market Power &amp; Economic Consequences of Post-Harvest Losses in Rwandan Dry Bean Markets http://t.co/l3WkMS9Qjn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RePEc: Does Development Reduce Migration? http://t.co/7Cqo45x3S4]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>