<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: MetroStar Systems Careers ========================= .Net Developer Web Development Washington, District Of Columbia Apply MetroStar Systems is looking for a results oriented Senior .Net Developer that is passionate about designing and… https://t.co/JjIpcJKCga https://t.co/8hW1behQeK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NETWORK ENGINEER III: Network Engineer III, Sprint Corporation, Overland Park, KS. Research, design, plan, develop and/or evaluate new, advanced network technologies. Apply at https://t.co/E7oEDJ5C5T, Req # 243924BR. Sprint is a background screening,… https://t.co/GbZkXMb09k https://t.co/PMhnqmCsBR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .NET Developer: Senior .NET Developer Salt lake city, Utah – United States Job Start Date – 06/06/18, Posted Date – 06/06/18 Primary Skills.netTax TermsC2COverviewThis is a 6-12 months contract with University of Utah. Phone and Skype. EAD is… https://t.co/wypjD9vzVL https://t.co/olg8dXkE5Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. top court lets states force online retailers to collect sales tax: WASHINGTON (Reuters) - States may force online retailers to collect potentially billions of dollars in sales taxes, the U.S. Supreme Court said in a major ruling on Thursday that… https://t.co/qIxfyKmRFJ https://t.co/zOweZ3pPwu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .NET Developer: Senior .NET Developer for CACI in Quantico, VA 22134(map) Job Description What You’ll Get to Do: CACI International, Inc. (CACI) has an immediate opportunity for a Senior .Net Developer onsite in Quantico, VA supporting the Naval… https://t.co/sE3ZckDJPF https://t.co/H48vZUvHZE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer Ref No.:18-10623 Location: Houston, Ohio Position Type:Contract Start Date: 06/14/2018 Role: .Net Developer Location: Houston, OH Job Type: Contract Roles and responsibilities: – Resource should be strong on C# Design and… https://t.co/DmYtWt1OJr https://t.co/0pe2m6rIcF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager, Engineering Specialty Chemicals, Full-time: Business unit: AMPE About AkzoNobel Industries worldwide rely on our essential chemistry in the manufacture of everyday products such as paper, plastics, building materials, and personal care… https://t.co/dqENGru2YD https://t.co/pptB6gLoIx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft .net Developer: Microsoft .net Developer Ref No.: 18-20706 Location: Washington, District of Columbia Title:- Microsoft .net Developer Location:- Washington DC Contract W2 Role – Candidate should have 5+ years of IT experience – Minimum 2+… https://t.co/cnYylPRN3c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer – .Net: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Fort Worth, TX Job Type: Information Technology Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/7/2018 Job Description Primary Purpose: Responsible for the design, development, testing,… https://t.co/DTSyM4vywT https://t.co/PIaHHVdeej]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: Summary Perform software development of new requirements, support development on existing code base, and optimize a highly complex application built in C# *******. Perform work within an agile development and apply a systematic approach… https://t.co/ec4toUu8bw https://t.co/BwObbsTp7W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .Net, C# Developer: SENIOR .NET DEVELOPER HIGHLIGHTS LOCATIONS: Chandler, AZ JOB TYPE: Contract-to-hire SALARY: BOE JOB SUMMARY GTN is looking for a Senior .NET resource to develop and maintain new or improved software products, procedures and… https://t.co/7n1z7OXgRv https://t.co/uTTJvHZSR4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EU Parliament committee votes for tougher EU copyright rules to rein in tech giants: BRUSSELS (Reuters) - Google , Facebook , Microsoft and other tech giants could face more curbs on their market power after a European Parliament committee voted in favor… https://t.co/u7NX2fSDsK https://t.co/4yADZn442J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering: ENGINEERING: Synaptics, Inc. has multiple openings in San Jose, CA. Software Engineer: build up chained secure flash boot flow on ARM v7/v8 architecture SOC Senior Software Engineer: design multimedia framework incl. AVIN, VPP, VDEC… https://t.co/Ebi0x7Glx9 https://t.co/l3ZIgBBCM0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Winchester, VA Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/8/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management and technology… https://t.co/huTKZ7Zbwa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer: Job Description – .NET Developer Job LocationUS-MD-Rockville | US-IL-Chicago Job ID10268 Job LocationUnited States Alternate locations DC1, IL2 Overview The American Institutes for Research (AIR) is a leading professional services firm… https://t.co/a4Fr91rI0X https://t.co/8ZFEdBPWkp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front End .NET Developer: Buffalo Grove, IL Full-time $90k – $110k Posted Today If you are a Front End Developer with experience, please read on! Based in Buffalo Grove, IL we are an ever growing financial company. Our company cares about our employees… https://t.co/992XF9p1ck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Center Infrastructure Project Manager: TECHNOLOGY SERVICES GROUP (TSG) is the central infrastructure services group with a proven track record of innovating to help BNY Mellon and its customers have most reliable, nimble and cost-effective solutions… https://t.co/WFO8P8ugVl https://t.co/HFisUv8Mpg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .NET Developer: Senior .NET Developer ID 2017-9089 Category Software Development Location US-NY-New York Responsibilities More than 20 years ago, TransPerfect was founded with a mission to help the world's businesses navigate the global… https://t.co/BFQiIaJQEy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer, Junior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Herndon, VA Job Type: Entry Level, Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 5/29/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest… https://t.co/gBUvg00bpQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Military Oprtns Analyst / DoD Human Resources/ Active Clearance / Alexandria VA: Req ID : 437910BR Job Code/Title : E2494:Military Oprtns Analyst Stf Job Description : Develop, prepare, coordinate, and maintain military personnel documentation and… https://t.co/vZrkw38lpJ https://t.co/n1foI5cU72]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/BKeTHRUc7v Developer: POSITION OVERVIEW: Our client located is looking for an ******* Developer with C# experience to support and develop portfolio solutions. The right candidate will be responsible for global proprietary solutions… https://t.co/ukTZnluewz https://t.co/4Pe1cOOns8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Software Developer: .NET Software Developer Ref No.:18-13398 Location: Charlotte, North Carolina Description: Responsibilities . The position requires an experienced developer of components in a distributed, N-tier architecture collection of… https://t.co/mCaYSXiiT5 https://t.co/kveU11dMDA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer: .NET Developer in SeaTac, US-WA, USA | IT Infrastructure at CognizantJob Details | Cognizant – ************* – Industries – – – Services – – – Latest Thinking – – – About Cognizant – Careers Home – Get To Know Us – Our Core Values –… https://t.co/LpGFVNEvwm https://t.co/bHVivZ3rIZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Specialist Developer – https://t.co/BKeTHRUc7v, MVC, C#, SQL Server, SSRS: For BNY Mellon Specialist Developer – *******, MVC, C#, SQL Server, SSRS job – Asset Servicing – Multiple Skip to Main Content – – – – Toggle navigation – Who We Are – What We Do… https://t.co/Wb0PNNMdES https://t.co/nBQJrP0MsM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer Ref No.:18-01046 Location: Irvine, California Position Type:FullTime This opportunity is with a multibillion $ Global giant based in United States, Canada &amp; Mexico, with 16 different delivery centers and Regional offices in… https://t.co/ifnk3pxi32 https://t.co/qcFNGlNvbo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer Ruby on Rails: MAP Digital: MetaMeetings is seeking an experienced full stack Ruby on Rails developer with excellent communication skills to join our team in MetaMeetings, a unique platform for the event industry. You will support us… https://t.co/kdBJZN08jJ https://t.co/En3Pal2uvj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer, Full Stack: Job ID: ********-11060-TL Company Name: Xactware Description: We are looking for someone who has a strong web development or computer science background to join a world-class team building the next generation of Xactware’s… https://t.co/UIjjH4b7BP https://t.co/6QFutuAIMT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer : 18-02186 Ref No.: 18-02186 Location: Folsom, California Akraya is looking for a .Net Developer for one of our clients. If the job description below is a fit, please apply directly or call Viplove Singh at ************. If… https://t.co/ZjKNOOoHdo https://t.co/klrUhX7iNW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET developer: .NET developer Ref No.: 18-25217 Location: Seattle, Washington Position: NET developer Location: Seattle,WA Duration:Contract Note: Need local candidates for F2F interview. Job description: Proven experience with Jquery, JavaScript, CSS… https://t.co/TH118dNm2m https://t.co/98hcJWYThk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Architect with Polygraph: Requisition ID 2018-39863 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Top Secret/SCI with Polygraph Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description Designs and defines system architecture for… https://t.co/qGA7EDhB1h https://t.co/ivLkaeDMZV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer, Senior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Norfolk, VA Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/12/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management and… https://t.co/U3C42vEaaX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer Ref No.:18-10623 Location: Houston, Ohio Position Type:Contract Start Date: 06/14/2018 Role: .Net Developer Location: Houston, OH Job Type: Contract Roles and responsibilities: – Resource should be strong on C# Design and… https://t.co/1uuCx4Xw9l https://t.co/HzAmFmHya4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Developer, SAP PI: Hunter Douglas, Inc. seeks an IT Developer, SAP PI in Broomfield, CO to develop and support eCommerce middleware applications. Design, code, and troubleshoot middleware functions using SAP’s NetWeaver, PI adapters, Java, ABAP, and… https://t.co/uiNV1i4XmC https://t.co/QC1BZliTTd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parts Inspector: General Parts Inspector Eckel Manufacturing Company is looking for a Parts Inspector. Must have experience with parts inspection, assemblies and finished products to drawings and specifications. Perform limited and repetitive visual,… https://t.co/VXJIweFrDx https://t.co/rzGVnk11vT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior C#/.NET Engineer – AWS: Senior C#/.NET Engineer – AWS at Cox Automotive Skip Navigation – Careers Home – Early Career – Tech Careers – Join Our Talent Community – Blog – Manage Your Profile – Cox Enterprises – Cox Communications – Cox Automotive –… https://t.co/kaRtpt4l7u https://t.co/xg5bUItkZ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: MetroStar Systems Careers ========================= .Net Developer Web Development Washington, District Of Columbia MetroStar Systems is looking for a results oriented Senior .Net Developer that is passionate about designing and… https://t.co/FQ3P1U5xou https://t.co/Qk1mzaME4A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer I SurePayroll: Title .NET Developer I – SurePayroll =============================== About the Organization Paychex, Inc. (NASDAQ: PAYX) is a leading provider of integrated human capital management solutions for payroll, HR, retirement, and… https://t.co/vY6B1BlxBO https://t.co/0RPlDDI57u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.net developer: .net developer Ref No.: 18-25237 Location: Mt Laurel, New Jersey Job Title : .Net Developer Location : Mt Laurel NJ Duration : 12 Months Job Description : Net , C sharp skills , MVC Job Title : .Net Developer Location : Mt Laurel NJ… https://t.co/xBWdpxDFIx https://t.co/MY3FoOxIw5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C# .NET Developer: * Must have a Bachelors Degree and high GPA from college.* Dynamic Global Financial Software Firm, located in the Chicago Loop, is currently seeking a C# .NET Developer with strong OO experience. Candidate will join a group a… https://t.co/XAjrra3j49]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. top court mulls Apple's App Store commissions in antitrust case: WASHINGTON (Reuters) - The U.S. Supreme Court on Monday agreed to take up Apple Inc's bid to escape a lawsuit accusing it of breaking federal antitrust laws by monopolizing the market… https://t.co/21Hck4ilzj https://t.co/0pw7o9pwlR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/8jhZIBIKRK Tech Lead: ****** Tech Lead Ref No.:18-03761 Location: Malvern, Pennsylvania Position Type:Contract Start Date: 03/01/2018 ****** Tech Lead Malvern, PA Contract JOB DESCRIPTION: Responsible for ensuring technical quality of… https://t.co/uqNgfbcbna https://t.co/JZ4j4FLsIf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Testing Analyst: Systems Testing Analyst Responsibilities: – Participating in the design phase of projects to ensure that new or modified functions are developed using correct testing methodology – Arranging major activities between the client and… https://t.co/vdQN76CLfk https://t.co/e71Wi8Ortc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google to invest $550 million in Chinese e-commerce giant https://t.co/nXYtO6wdBD: SINGAPORE (Reuters) - Google will invest $550 million in Chinese e-commerce powerhouse https://t.co/nXYtO6wdBD , part of the U.S. internet giant's efforts to expand its… https://t.co/MiHe5si4NL https://t.co/CTMOOaDuIh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Architect – US: Role Technology Architect – US Auto req ID 30221BR Domain Other Domain Skillset IBM IIB Country USA State / Region / Province Connecticut Florida Rhode Island Work Location Cranston, RI Hartford, CT Tampa, FL Company ITL USA… https://t.co/sN75YduInw https://t.co/gjQn2x6V0G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer Ref No.: 18-24808 Location: Dallas, Texas Role: .Net Developer Location: Dallas, TX Duration: Full Time Permanent Skills Required: .NET development (C#.NET, WPF, Entity Framework, *******, *******, MVVM, MVC) .NET Web… https://t.co/C2t6GZcMlg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer: Interested in working for a growing, fast-paced company with diverse projects and technologies? COLAB is looking for talented team members to help shape the companys future. At COLAB, we have a close-knit team with no office politics. You… https://t.co/Y1P0MsWPTl https://t.co/mlpvo908qQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .Net Developer: – Senior .Net Developer Job Locations US-CT-Stamford Req. # 2017-2349Division Financial Guard Position Type Regular Position Overview Legg Mason is currently hiring a .Net Developer and a Senior .Net Developer for our beautiful… https://t.co/bGltl8Ui7i https://t.co/BVR5BkRSJf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front End .Net Developer: Front End .Net Developer Chicago/IL, Illinois – United States Job Start Date – 06/06/18, Posted Date – 06/06/18 Primary SkillsFront End .Net DeveloperTax TermsC2COverview EAD GC Preferred Skype to HIre Front End Developers with… https://t.co/1Dkgj9jN8j https://t.co/tIBuhmFMqY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer Ref No.: 18-22733 Location: Redmond, Washington Position Title : .Net Developer Location : Baltimore, MD Duration : Full Time Permanent Job Description Good Experience in C#, SQL, .NET. Be able to work on a team. Work through https://t.co/ro1UMvOgCf https://t.co/qf0QbgdIDQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C# .NET Developer: * Must have a Bachelors Degree and high GPA from college.* Dynamic Global Financial Software Firm, located in the Chicago Loop, is currently seeking a C# .NET Developer with strong OO experience. Candidate will join a group a… https://t.co/B4kRn4bOc0 https://t.co/FktKG7YRd1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior .NET Developer Intern: Job/Internship Description Junior .NET Developer Intern ABB is a pioneering technology leader that works closely with utility, industry, transportation and infrastructure customers to write the future of industrial… https://t.co/dXi083dDOo https://t.co/28Hdu86dUZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET developer: .NET developer Ref No.: 18-25217 Location: Seattle, Washington Position: NET developer Location: Seattle,WA Duration:Contract Note: Need local candidates for F2F interview. Job description: Proven experience with Jquery, JavaScript, CSS… https://t.co/F43uorwHWD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer Summer Intern: IMPACTFUL WORK. SMART SOLUTIONS. MEANINGFUL CAREERS. Come join a Fortune 500 company that touches the lives of millions in the Health Care Community. If you are interested in Big Data and Health Care, we can provide the… https://t.co/lscdKRSY2I https://t.co/rPkHlLc3rt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net/Sharepoint Developer: Kore 1 Jobs Page ************|************** – Services – Workforce Planning – Software Development – IT Strategy – Staffing Solutions – Technology Staffing – Engineering Staffing – Oil &amp; Gas Staffing – Accounting &amp; Finance… https://t.co/1R3l6BRUKN https://t.co/nXVEj3qOFZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior C#/.NET Engineer – AWS: Senior C#/.NET Engineer – AWS at Cox Automotive Skip Navigation – Careers Home – Early Career – Tech Careers – Join Our Talent Community – Blog – Manage Your Profile – Cox Enterprises – Cox Communications – Cox Automotive –… https://t.co/1UkKkS4fLT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Specialist Systems Engineer/Programmer OS Architecture/Engineering: TECHNOLOGY SERVICES GROUP (TSG) is the central infrastructure services group with a proven track record of innovating to help BNY Mellon and its customers have most reliable,… https://t.co/GuPr5oR74A https://t.co/bhP7QYZHUd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr .Net Developer: Careers | Wilmertech Login Toggle navigation – Services – Application Development – Product Maintenance – Healthcare – Cloud Computing – Mobile First – Service Oriented Architecture – IT Staffing – Our Approach – Technologies – UI/UX –… https://t.co/fW5z5aDBpE https://t.co/L2v4aQPybe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr .Net Developer/Lead: Sr .Net Developer/Lead Ref No.: 18-24951 Location: pittsburgh, Pennsylvania Hello, Hope you are doing great… This isVishalfromEnterprise Solution Inc. and I am writing to you regarding an excellent job opportunity based out of.… https://t.co/dzdMiByveH https://t.co/ItPWt07eA3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .NET Developer SDET: Project Description Our Customer is one of the world’s largest investment management companies. Based in Southern California, our client manages close to $2 trillion in assets. Responsibilities Coordination of the offshore QA… https://t.co/7n0k64OgHc https://t.co/4FGEnaftTy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior .NET Developer: A pioneer in groundbreaking scientific and engineering developments since the 1960’s, TRC is a national engineering, consulting and construction management firm providing integrated services to the energy, environmental and… https://t.co/c66nSMOllT https://t.co/zNT78Juma2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C#/ASP.NET Engineer: About GoDaddy GoDaddy powers the world’s largest cloud platform dedicated to small, independent ventures. With nearly 17 million customers worldwide and over 75 million domain names under management, GoDaddy is the place people come… https://t.co/IJCALg1opW https://t.co/RAa31MvMHv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer: TECHNOLOGY Interested candidates send resume to: Google LLC, PO Box 26184 San Francisco, CA 94126 Attn: V. Murphy. Please reference job # below: Software Engineer positions (Mountain View/Palo Alto/San Bruno, CA) Design, develop, modify, and/or… https://t.co/SobCcq7lGA https://t.co/1fPHzQLbs3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Project Manager Client Services Iselin, New Jersey Medidata’s unified platform, pioneering analytics, and unrivaled expertise power the development of new therapies for over 1,000 pharmaceutical companies, biotech, medical device firms,… https://t.co/D9GEltWdB0 https://t.co/3BPajoDMyT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/itZFk9aFeI developer: ******* developer Charlotte, North Carolina – United States Job Start Date – 07/02/18, Posted Date – 06/13/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview 1. 1. 6-10 years experience developing in ******* 2. MVC, C# 3. SQL 4.… https://t.co/Y3q93UMv8v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/8jhZIBIKRK Applications Developer: POSITION OVERVIEW: Our client, one of Chicago’s Best and Brightest Companies to work for, is currently seeking a talented ****** Applications Developer. This person will work with the technology team on new… https://t.co/fz3e8aSXWv https://t.co/sHbUwaTXx9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer (.NET): Job Location US-DC Job ID 9301 Job Location United States Category Information Technology/Software Overview Be part of something innovative and cutting edge. Join our team of more than a hundred software engineers,… https://t.co/S175qzzPij https://t.co/CFomNHXSyF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer /Developer- Java: Job Description Senior Software Engineer /Developer- Java (*******Z) Carlson Wagonlit Travel is currently seeking a Senior Java Developer to join our team. The Senior Java Developer is responsible for all… https://t.co/xZYmfkkLXJ https://t.co/KWRB0mfXL0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer III – Full Stack .NET: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Milwaukee, WI Job Type: Information Technology Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 7/15/2018 Job Description Primary Purpose: Responsible for the analysis, design, code,… https://t.co/Bu9vGk7EdA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer .NET/C#: Software Engineer .NET/C# Jobs Description at Cox Enterprises Skip to main content Careers Home Our People Locations Join Our Talent Community Blog Manage Your Profile Cox Enterprises Cox Communications Cox Automotive Cox Media… https://t.co/8Bn3CXX9eU https://t.co/L2DWyjvmXy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer – Journeyman: Careers Center | .Net Developer – Journeyman Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome… https://t.co/canWlxK2Qo https://t.co/5vaVzaSfHR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Endoscopy Technician PVH Ctr for GI: Facility: Poudre Valley Hospital Department: PVH Ctr for GI SP Schedule: PRN (FTE must be 0) Shift: 1st Shift – Days Scheduled Days &amp; Hours: Variable day shifts plus on call Requisition number: 76695Summary Provides… https://t.co/KFHAdhRF57 https://t.co/YQmzvPy35r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[202- Java Software Developer: OVERVIEW The Software Engineer develops, maintains, and enhances complex and diverse software systems (e.g., processing-intensive analytics, novel algorithm development, manipulation of extremely large data sets, real-time… https://t.co/TjzB503bNT https://t.co/wmH4KW7BLy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Application Architect: Western Union is changing. Yes, we’re the company that moves money around the world quickly and reliably in 200 countries and territories. We are also present in over 510,000 locations bringing immense distribution convenience… https://t.co/yRHE1MO2gw https://t.co/PCKnAFQLC3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Web Developer/Architect (.NET): Job TitleSr. Web Developer/Architect (.NET) – ID:31845 Duration12 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsBuilds web based applications using *******, MVC, Web API and SQL Server (2012), JavaScript frameworks, Angular JS,… https://t.co/2NlLxgG28j https://t.co/pFTcJfJvY8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer/Sr. Software Developer (.NET) Job: Company Information PACCAR is a Fortune 500 company established in 1905. PACCAR Inc is recognized as a global leader in the commercial vehicle, financial, and customer service fields with… https://t.co/cEmqtO5nLq https://t.co/6Mri1LcJFv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. .Net Developer: Sr. .Net Developer Ref No.:18-11805 Location: Brookfield, Wisconsin Position Type:Contract Start Date: 07/05/2018 Sr. .Net Developer Brookfield, WI Contract Job Description: – Provide technical expertise and guidance for best… https://t.co/7V5ZMylYJW https://t.co/02fQ4WdU7G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer : 18-02612 Ref No.:18-02612 Location: Highlands Ranch, Colorado Akraya is looking for a .Net Developer for one of our clients. If the job description below is a fit, please apply directly or call Somya at ************ If… https://t.co/nlWE1t2S5S https://t.co/sYfIt0RLHt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. .NET Application Developer: Redmond, WA Full-time $100k – $120k Posted Today If you are a Sr. .NET Application Developer with experience, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us Based in Redmond, WA, we are a successful leading technology… https://t.co/7j8gBz5TKg https://t.co/gUSqCxFivL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C# .NET Backend/API Engineer: 7/12/2018 C# .NET Backend/API Engineer Tracking Code 11163 Job Description DataSphere, part of Sinclair Digital Agency, is a leader in mobile marketing, focused on helping local businesses get the most from advertising and… https://t.co/kqnvZjQsVA https://t.co/KjrrAkRuMd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer: Job Title .NET Developer State Texas Description Connection Services has a fantastic opportunity through our technical staffing division in Dallas, TX. We are looking for a Senior IT Security Officer. This is a full time contract… https://t.co/B1plCMbOR5 https://t.co/h7RvkgtzZI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer Skip Navigation Fiserv Menu – Solutions – Industries – About – Careers – Where you fit in – Technology – Accounting &amp; Finance – Contact Center – U.S. Locations – Alpharetta – Brookfield – Dallas/Ft. Worth – Other U.S.… https://t.co/HhtLCMeV1F https://t.co/c6SFgGWPN1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application System Analyst: Application System Analyst ========================== Req #: ******Location: Lawton, OK USJob Category: Information TechnologySecurity Clearance: SecretClearance Status: Must be Obtainable Job Description CACI is seeking for a… https://t.co/YK89Vkbvqs https://t.co/XhhRHOXFzI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Full-Stack Developer: Description How You Can Make An Impact We are looking for a motivated developer who will play a key role in taking our proprietary trading UI components to the next level. The ideal candidate enjoys working with the latest .NET… https://t.co/w6FoWJcWlY https://t.co/behJDWT3jk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (.NET): Software Engineer (.NET) Jobs Description at Cox Enterprises Skip to main content Careers Home Our People Locations Join Our Talent Community Blog Manage Your Profile Cox Enterprises Cox Communications Cox Automotive Cox Media… https://t.co/QWTJvpR4Yl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ANGULAR / UI Developer: ANGULAR / UI Developer Ref No.: 18-30151 Location: Irving, Texas Key Skills – Candidate should have minimum 2 years of IT experience as a front end developer and have experience in HTML5, CSS3 and JavaScript. – The candidate… https://t.co/0tYU8m5G1D https://t.co/1yBSte4pbJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Full Stack .NET Developer: SENIOR FULL STACK .NET DEVELOPER HIGHLIGHTS LOCATION: Plano, TX POSITION TYPE: 6 month Contract to Hire HOURLY/SALARY: BOE! JOB SUMMARY GTN Technical Staffing is currently seeking Senior Software Engineer for a 6 month… https://t.co/a8KDDLjz6K https://t.co/Smb22ix4jG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer Ref No.:18-03095 Location: cary, North Carolina Position Type:Contract Experience in C#, MSSQL, .NET, Angular JS. NLP (Lex, Alexa, DialogFlow, ******, LUIS, BlueMix) required. Exposure to Machine Learning (Google,… https://t.co/nofOmwhRMh https://t.co/FsuuaC7OK3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C#.NET Developer: Our direct fortune 500 client is in need of C#.NET programmers to join their dynamic team. Contract and Contract-to-Hire positions available. Required: – 5+ years C#.NET experience – 3+ years SQL programming experience – 3+ years SQL… https://t.co/v1gfOZwTRm https://t.co/xF6cZHaWxj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developers, Sr: The Senior Web Application Developer (‘Developer’) is responsible for most internally and externally facing web applications and tools. The Developer’s role is to help design and create solutions that support both the mission of the… https://t.co/pG84deINzW https://t.co/EdWPBM2Z3b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It: IT HCL America, Inc. has the following openings in Sunnyvale, CA. Travel &amp; work @ various unanticipated client sites as assigned: Business Analysts: Transform business requirements into functional specifications, focusing on workflow analysis &amp;… https://t.co/BrCv9knYXH https://t.co/ipBpYE7SU1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unix System Admin: 15881BR Job Description and Requirements The candidate is responsible for: Managing Business Applications Infrastructure(SAP, Oracle, etc.) in a highly available environment. Managing Oracle and MySQL databases. Establishing operation… https://t.co/COrqUtfdAF https://t.co/x94pyE8ISn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Application Developer (C#, https://t.co/itZFk9aFeI): Senior Application Developer (C#, https://t.co/itZFk9aFeI) Posted Date 2 weeks ago(6/6/2018 3:35 PM) ID 2018-31637 Job Location USA-MD-Hanover Required Clearance TS/SCI with Polygraph Category… https://t.co/Ykscr84P08 https://t.co/sUJb0mb756]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Software Engineer: This position services as an expert technical and industry resource to management, clients and development staff in new uses of information technology in all phases of major system and subsystem development. Provides consultation… https://t.co/t434cmqfbA https://t.co/0RT7Ll5Do3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Web Developer: Beacon Hill Technologies has an opportunity for a .NET Web Developer with our client located in Strongsville, Ohio. This is a 6 month contract to start and can extend. REQUIRED DEVELOPMENT SKILLS INCLUDE: * C#, .NET 4.0 (or earlier) *… https://t.co/tFQiOSkbBl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Software Developer – Corptax: Employer, a CSC company, is transforming the business of tax through technology and business process expertise. Offering the first and only single platform solution on the market, Employer handles an unlimited range of… https://t.co/JaFuBoXlNf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Configuration Analyst 3:   Job Description – Configuration Analyst 3 (18014352) Configuration Analyst 3 Requisition ID : 18014352 Location : United States-California-Edwards AFB US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation Assistance:… https://t.co/35hIHbfJaV https://t.co/El3l4PY3rf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Washington, DC Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 7/2/2018 Job Description Job Number: R******* .NET Developer The Challenge: Are you looking for an opportunity to not just… https://t.co/RvhVYr9lRK https://t.co/8hl8227NhK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net/ Angular JS Developer: .Net/ Angular JS Developer Ref No.: 18-29140 Location: Charlotte, North Carolina Position: .Net/ Angular JS Developer Job Location: Charlotte, NC Job Title: Full time permanent Excellent organizational skills as changes for… https://t.co/o84DikSDB5 https://t.co/GfUo4A5zSb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Comcast concedes to Disney in bidding war for Fox assets: Comcast Corp dropped its $66 billion bid for Twenty-First Century Fox Inc's entertainment assets on Thursday but said it would still try to expand its international footprint by acquiring 61… https://t.co/eA7xMXWt28 https://t.co/S0EogJe3Tb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NETWORK ENGINEER III: Network Engineer III, Sprint Corporation, Overland Park, KS. Serve as a Microwave Engineer for the cellular/ wireless telecommunications system. Remote work is authorized. Apply at https://t.co/E7oEDJ5C5T, Req # 245305BR. Sprint is… https://t.co/9Yf0XmCToP https://t.co/Ehg9SV9fhj]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>