<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @theScore: Peyton and the Broncos win the Manning Bowl while all Eli can do is be sent to his room without supper.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeymanHustle stay alive wanna see you at #Battleground next month!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amanda_bykiv111 def got it from me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleeyywatt123 perfect slu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Raymondraws lmfao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @iMax2021: 80's and 90's movies soooo much better then anything now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[About time Kadri]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hilarylocks sweet deal. Ill see you tomorrow! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bensanity_15 yea it was crazy in the arena :p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hilarylocks wed as in tomorrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hilarylocks I dunno but are you workin wed? I'm coming to the store with David]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mon Night Raw was fun. Daniel Bryan and the yes chants were over like crazy #Raw @WWE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TSNBobMcKenzie: UFA F Mason Raymond will be attending TOR's training camp on a PTO.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RC_Survivor I heard of the unfortunate circumstances involving you being on Survivor. Hope your dad is better. I woulda had you winning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CP24: Wrestling has been reinstated for the 2020 Olympics, according to the Canadian Press.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amanda_bykiv111 samee -_-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chellatamby91 any money is good money]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleeyywatt123 my reflexes and speed void that punch. â˜ðŸ‘ŸðŸ’¨ðŸš€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleeyywatt123 hahaha Yeaaaa ok ðŸ˜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleeyywatt123 hardcore music = METALLICA!!!!!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hilarylocks guilty as charged]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sarahjcourte but I don't remember which one or what was goin on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sarahjcourte ill def check it out and let you know what I think. Now that you told me the premise I'm pretty sure I saw an ep randomly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sarahjcourte what's it about?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sarahjcourte lol will do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sarahjcourte that's amazing! I have to watch that show I hear my wife Allison Brie is on it!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sarahjcourte is already awesome but if she could pull this off she will go into the upper echelons of awesomeness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sarahjcourte lucky lucky girl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sarahjcourte sadly it's hard to obtain :( maybe we can convince @JeffProbst to sponsor me lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sarahjcourte me me me me me me me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hilarylocks because I am mad at you. You better start smartening up woman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vanessa_orz @999virginTO help this girl out!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People that chew with their mouth open, slurp their drinks and make weird noises when eating learn how to fucking eat your not toddlers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Ssnyder1835: still my favorite cosplay ever http://t.co/PlHOTtcAlV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeffProbst anything survivor is amazing, no one should have any doubts. Long time fan since season 1!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WRESTLEZONEcom crying over punching another wrestler, face or not that was the worst segment iv seen in awhile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WRESTLEZONEcom later they will try to have us believe he's unstoppable and has no remorse for anyone. I mean think about it a wrestler..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WRESTLEZONEcom it makes me sick that WWE insults our intelligence by having Show cry about the punch to Bryan. Meanwhile 3 months...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hilarylocks Miss you too tho &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hilarylocks whoa whoa whoa I don't take demands I give them. You come visit me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hilarylocks :p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hilarylocks *not]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Sarahjcourte: I want beer in me #cometomommy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lmfao not even the #Bills want #Tebow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleeyywatt123 kidding but you fucked up leaving the dog outside we came home and he smelt like poo and dug up the yard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleeyywatt123 shattup ðŸ˜” where were you guys today I came over. Everyone partied we ordered hookers to the house you missed out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sarahjcourte catching up with you! Preseason pick is gervais straight from season 1. Ill keep in touch :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sarahjcourte oo la la I love to travel! you gotta hook me up when you run things! Alright Sarah my bed is long overdue it was nice...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sarahjcourte that's awesome! at least you'll be in your comfort zone anyway, what program are you taking?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sarahjcourte it's awesome. Changed my life :) you must be anxious to get back to school, I'm sure your lovin being home tho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sarahjcourte I won't be full time for a billion years but its good pay and I have pension and in the union so it all balances out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sarahjcourte I work in food services at the Brampton civic hospital. Was very fortunate my friend got me in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleeyywatt123 of course, I'm bringing paperback.. (Cheesy JT line since he's over again)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sarahjcourte except a Sarah Jessica Parker variety hour special if they ever had one. Then I would lose faith in the amphitheatre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sarahjcourte yea completely agree, it's nice to be up close but the lawns are perfect. Good summer scene for any show]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleeyywatt123 way better than the movies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleeyywatt123 you should read the Michael Crichton masterpieces Jurassic Park and The Lost World you shall not be disappointed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sarahjcourte it to a private company? I'm not in the loop..isn't Ontario place closed already? I'm so confused]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sarahjcourte wow cheapos..wait aren't they closing down Ontario place? Whatever will they do with the amphitheatre? Did they already sell..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sarahjcourte lol no deal but I got your back on the Survivor tip tho!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sarahjcourte how's your other job treatin you? Have you been able to get ahold of good seats for concerts and ish]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sarahjcourte oh I was just discussing Satc with Jon lmao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sarahjcourte haha nice, yea I can def see that in her character. Time out tomorrow you'll be like what did I do at 2:11am...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sarahjcourte 1st one ðŸ‘ŒðŸ˜”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sarahjcourte yea very naive and foolish of me. Tbh I think I fell asleep during.. Have you seen it yet? Or are you still powering thru ep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sarahjcourte what do I know tho iv never seen an episode just wasted 2 hours watching the movie blah blah blah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sarahjcourte advantage of men meanwhile in irony men prob just laughed at how dumb and ugly she is lol!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sarahjcourte 1. She's ugly 2. She portrayed a slu on tv and set bad examples for women trying to show they were empowering by taking...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sarahjcourte and no disrespect to my boy Matthew Broderick but SJP looks like her face got hit by train then dragged on for a couple km]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sarahjcourte Sex in the City is trash. Your a smart girl, why do you watch that garbage lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thomasinaysmith I'm in it - yeezy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sarahjcourte should be interesting for a few weeks. He won't last long]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NikoKetsilis YEEEESSSSS! Submitted for the approval by the midnight society I call this story...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HacksawJDuggan: Happy Thanksgiving to The Mountie and all you other Canadian tough guys! http://t.co/Lhw6E2aQc7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleeyywatt123 fair enough I agree. I was watching it on my iPad when they came over and she told me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleeyywatt123 nice try I religiously watched the first 2 seasons so I watched it. Also I stopped cuz Quinn left]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleeyywatt123 relax. It wasn't that bad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bensanity_15 what do u think of it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @theScore: The Giants are 0-6, or as the NFC East calls it, right in the thick of things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleeyywatt123 CM Punk?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bensanity_15 I actually do for kanye too...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sarahjcourte @JeffProbst wish my friend good luck on her mid terms tomorrow or be banished from Emmy nominations forever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wondering if @Sarahjcourte is ready for #Survivor tonight hosted by @JeffProbst]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kaitlyn_Rooth @ashleeyywatt123 arms it's your birthday today? Happy bday! I'm coming over tonight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bensanity_15 we were on tv all night Sunday for the ppv lmao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bensanity_15 http://t.co/b1XDQNSXel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bensanity_15 also look http://t.co/IAqvIFuzHV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bensanity_15 fuck j.cole I got VIP floors for Yeezy and Kendrick Lamar next month :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @steveaustinBSR: Just watched my first couple episodes of #breakingbad. Better late than never. #hooked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amanda_bykiv111 crop the photo first]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleeyywatt123 lmao I told you i was on tv the whole night you should have told me I woulda made a sign]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buffalo today for WWE Battleground!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Chellatamby91 yesss stay the night and come to the ppv with us tomorrow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bensanity_15 1-0 Toronto son]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LexiWatt19 @ashleeyywatt123 hell ya!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleeyywatt123 he's got jobber tattoos with a 10 year olds body]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bensanity_15 that's cuz it's not time for ball, it's time for hockey...GO LEAFS GO!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gingerjess_ blocked and deleted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck yea Simpsons tapped out Halloween update today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amanda_bykiv111 I know I'm stoked I just dropped the new song today.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>