<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: We currently have an opening for an IT Project Manager in our PRS IT team. The IT Project Manager will have responsibility for the management and coordination of multiple concurrent projects within the PRS Product portfolio. IT projects… https://t.co/stqam7ONpD https://t.co/BBfbjRmEco]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master (SR775) Job: Date: Mar 15, 2018 Location: Albuquerque, NM, US Company: SAIC Scrum Master (SR775) (Job Number:434149) Description: SAIC is looking for an experienced Scrum Master. Job Description: You will work in a highly collaborative and… https://t.co/26frZirbTc https://t.co/NAQLFAbdwT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Lead- QA: Technical Lead- QA Indianapolis, Indiana Fulltime position Job Description: * Written Unit tests * Used version control * Database experience with writing, reading stored procedures and complex SQL * Ability and experience… https://t.co/6m64X3iX44 https://t.co/cpheHOZGFV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: Infosys- Retail, CPG &amp; Logistics Technology Lead US – User Interface Lead Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to create and execute strategies for their… https://t.co/HXwfH0ik5E https://t.co/9LEB2Gs6E3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director – IT Project Management: DIRECTOR – IT PROJECT MANAGEMENT FULL TIME PERMANENT POSITION – No H1B LOCATION: ATLANTA, GA SALARY: up to $110k/yr DIRECTOR – IT PROJECT MANAGEMENT SUMMARY This position is responsible for leading cross functional teams… https://t.co/7It9SWnzAQ https://t.co/dUqDVnXDCe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Angry Birds' maker Rovio cuts boardroom pay after profit warning: HELSINKI (Reuters) - "Angry Birds" maker Rovio proposed cutting the pay of its chairman and vice chairman following a drop in the Finnish mobile game studio's market value and a media… https://t.co/Uu2l72I06h https://t.co/qyy29lId4Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master Mayfield Heights, OH Full Time Position Job Description: Should have strong experience in C++ As a Sr. Scrum Master, the candidate is expected to be a Practitioner of agile-lean practices and processes at the team level with… https://t.co/4XzN2ye34V https://t.co/nzW6uHeU93]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Engineer-Infrastructure Team: At Ad Hoc we build government digital services that are fast, efficient, and usable by everyone. Ad Hoc brings small teams of highly skilled professionals from the private sector to build government software right… https://t.co/blncbqYdL7 https://t.co/LBWeprM6bj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master Bentonville, AR Full Time/Contract Position Job Description: Should have strong experience in C++ As a Sr. Scrum Master, the candidate is expected to be a Practitioner of agile-lean practices and processes at the team level… https://t.co/ZnvBF9Mk9L https://t.co/xFeWGDMi2K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[User Interface Engineer II, Partner Solutions: User Interface Engineer II, Partner Solutions at Cox Automotive Skip Navigation – Careers Home – Early Career – Join Our Talent Community – Blog – Manage Your Profile – Cox Enterprises – Cox Communications –… https://t.co/h6HbRKyIkU https://t.co/4OXGwxMz4t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master Responsibilities: Facilitate all scrum ceremonies: Sprint Planning: help the team commit to a sprint goal with your product owner and decompose all stories and defect work into tasks with owners and estimates. Daily Standup:… https://t.co/C3IEudK1K9 https://t.co/Mxpax1nr54]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master / Website Development Project Manager: Other agencies may call this job Project Manager or Account Manager, but we don’t like using the M-word. Rather, we do our web design and software development work in 5-person teams, with each member of… https://t.co/eShYOoIQxv https://t.co/QotChlV52h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: We currently have an opening for an IT Project Manager in our PRS IT team. The IT Project Manager will have responsibility for the management and coordination of multiple concurrent projects within the PRS Product portfolio. IT projects… https://t.co/MTGmQJP4Mj https://t.co/2ha8ObYwBE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Category: Project Management City: Herndon, Virginia, United States Position ID: J0318-1586 Employment Type: Full Time Meet our professionals CGI: An employer of choice Position Description: CGI has an immediate need for a Scrum Master to… https://t.co/rozdV6t2S0 https://t.co/J2tG7Jbp2I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BA / Scrum Master: Position Overview: The Scrum Master leads the Agile process for one or more Scrum teams, ensuring predictable delivery of software releases within scope. This position is also responsible for the ongoing development of the team within… https://t.co/ENobGlGeYg https://t.co/aerqNE4oCC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/l0kR7LZYHV Architect/Developer: Trustwave helps businesses fight cybercrime, protect data and reduce security risk. With cloud and managed security services, integrated technologies and a team of security experts, ethical hackers and… https://t.co/OeZoXOV6rp https://t.co/s9PN7G92zy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Scrum Master: Job TitleSr. Scrum Master – ID:30316 Duration6 Months Start DateASAP Job Skills6 – 9 YOE Skills: Required DCC DATA MANAGEMENT MASTER DATA MANAGEMENT LocationDenver, CO Date Posted03/13/2018 Scrum Master II Responsible for leading one or… https://t.co/OU8DpImhd4 https://t.co/7DOXDkpZIx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon wins grocery foothold in France through Monoprix deal: PARIS (Reuters) - Monoprix, one of France's biggest grocery store chains, said on Monday it will start selling its products to customers in Paris through Amazon's Prime Now service this year,… https://t.co/b9UdzdVrvo https://t.co/jq6xEFUhlH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer: As a Senior Software Developer at Ascensus, you will be working in a high-energy team, writing beautiful code by using the best engineering practices in the industry today (e.g. unit testing, source control, continuous integration,… https://t.co/g2MBqWvZXi https://t.co/A416YQq9o2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer, Android: As an Android-focused software engineer at Grio youll be focused on building Android applications using the latest SDKs and industry best practices. You will be able to work on a variety of projects and experience new… https://t.co/MUvZ5NikeO https://t.co/Lji0eSHZsG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Software Developer: Overview Software Developer IV (SDIV) will be part of a team of some of the best and brightest in the industry who are focused on developing scalable web and responsive applications that touch our growing customer base every… https://t.co/6L6ziRMlWr https://t.co/tOQWHmC7Qh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – US: Infosys Retail, CPG &amp; Logistics Project Manager Java, Agile Scrum Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to create and execute strategies for their digital… https://t.co/4ljirp7wCF https://t.co/oaNgYdeoAd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital Commerce Project Manager (US): Zaelab, based in USA is a dedicated team of focused, agile and innovative consultants who work to bridge the gap from vision to delivery of B2B commerce technology projects. Our commitment to evolving commerce… https://t.co/VTAUwINj6a https://t.co/wqEaYbFTS4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: O3 World is seeking a DevOps Engineer with a passion for building great tools and compelling experiences like the projects listed in the WORK section of our site… https://t.co/AkKeIat5s1 https://t.co/krziC1tGjv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Description QGenda is a fast growing Atlanta-based healthcare software company, with an amazing corporate culture, where we strive to be the best place to be a customer. Our software is used by thousands of hospital departments… https://t.co/ntStjluBZu https://t.co/OdPsop244X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Full Stack Software Engineer: Job Details Level Experienced Job Location Fortior Solutions Corporate – Hillsboro, OR Position Type Full Time Education Level 4 Year Degree Salary Range Undisclosed Travel Percentage Negligible Job Shift Any Job… https://t.co/rtAMozNQSq https://t.co/M9nfxmD6Gl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Test Engineer – Automation: Job Description Section 1: Position Summary The Software Test Engineer position is a hands-on role that contributes to the success at Ascensus by designing and developing automated tests, scripts and tools to champion… https://t.co/r6pRE69XOR https://t.co/79Y3lT4WpT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agile Scrum Master: Key Required Skills: Hands on Agile Scrum Master, training, Agile implementation experience using Scrum, Kanban, Lean, etc., customer engagement, communication, project management MUST be US Citizen or green card holder. Prefer local… https://t.co/UTq4SBhkbQ https://t.co/XgHmwtTdgI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: Infosys- Retail, CPG &amp; Logistics Technology Lead US – User Interface Lead Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to create and execute strategies for their… https://t.co/imA85yoM2B https://t.co/z9xYNlzg1J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber sells Southeast Asia business to Grab after costly battle: SINGAPORE/SAN FRANCISCO (Reuters) - Ride-hailing firm Uber Technologies Inc [UBER.UL] has agreed to sell its Southeast Asian business to bigger regional rival Grab, the firms said on Monday,… https://t.co/aH2GWI7gtE https://t.co/RC7j1Wyqd2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Job TitleScrum Master – ID:25428 Duration6 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsExposure to various business intelligence applications and architecture such as Cognos, Tableau and data warehousing LocationVernon Hills, IL Date Posted03/06/2018… https://t.co/ru9ovxVlF0 https://t.co/8iCYdxNdbo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SFDC Marketing Cloud – Sr. Consultant – FT role – (Top Management Consulting): Sr. Consultant Level * 5+ years of consulting experience and/or Marketing project implementation experience. No Contractors or Job Hoppers! * 2+ full life cycle projects with… https://t.co/HCCTUzWYQw https://t.co/zt7OvSFldv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: OVERVIEW Responsible for design, development and maintenance of software and firmware for electronic control systems deployed in the rail industry. This includes developing software requirements specifications, functional… https://t.co/JSmu40cUZ4 https://t.co/cIEYvK7L1K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Business Analyst (eLearning Application Analyst Developer): ReliSource | IT Business Analyst (eLearning Application Analyst &amp; Developer) – About – Company – Leadership – Vision – Services – Data Management – Embedded Engineering – Qualification &amp;… https://t.co/u6CWqpyLAc https://t.co/hgoKqoSH1W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Business Analyst: Requisition # TITLE: SENIOR BUSINESS ANALYST Location: Phoenix, AZ Duration: 12 months INTERVIEW TYPE: IN-PERSON INTERVIEW (LOCAL CANDIDATES PREFERRED) JOB SUMMARY Analyze, document and validate business requirements. Document… https://t.co/NdKwrdNkY4 https://t.co/fStKOAJGlw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master/Coach: Job TitleScrum Master/Coach – ID:31104 Duration12 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsFirst level Scrum Master certification (CSM, PSM I) LocationPlan0, TX Date Posted02/26/2018 FOR IMMEDIATE DETAILS ABOUT THIS POSITION, contact ANY of us… https://t.co/GWidx64QGM https://t.co/8MCtlmX52y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UI Developer: AmpThink is looking to hire a full-time UI Developer who can build beautiful, responsive front-end web applications based on existing design patterns. The ideal candidate will have a passion for front-end development and work closely with… https://t.co/l1pCyk6Dkx https://t.co/SVbk2mQsUW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Quality Assurance Engineer: QA Engineer Responsibilities: Review quality specifications and technical design documents to provide timely and meaningful feedback Creating detailed, comprehensive and well-structured test plans and test cases… https://t.co/xUw1DpMHvh https://t.co/kuiH7Q2X42]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Job TitleScrum Master – ID:29933 DurationPermanent Start DateASAP Job SkillsA minimum of four years of related project management. A minimum of two years of scrum master experience. Kanban methodology knowledge and experience is a plus.… https://t.co/yQ5v4vSB08 https://t.co/dshUIrScMf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fullscreen – Senior Ruby Engineer: The Senior Ruby on Rails Software Developer within Fullscreen Engineering team supports the architecture, design, development, and deployment of applications, API services, and client integrations for Fullscreens Brands… https://t.co/4qNaRJfu0Y https://t.co/93o6UUviqG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Test Lead – US: InfosysIVS-Financial Services- Technical Test Lead Automation Testing Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to create and execute strategies for their… https://t.co/RBszUB5Uad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK investigators search London office of firm at center of Facebook data storm: LONDON (Reuters) - Investigators from Britain's data watchdog searched the London offices of Cambridge Analytica, the data analytics firm at the center of a storm over… https://t.co/qovQvyL2Nu https://t.co/k2QnRtLwAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Requisition Number 18-0533 Post Date 3/8/2018 Title Software Engineer City Santa Ana State CA Description Designs, modifies, develops, writes and implements software programming applications/operating systems. Also, coordinates work… https://t.co/8sitZU9DGE https://t.co/zfvmviWHXz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce Sales Architect (SE): Company Overview Do you want to be part of a fast-paced environment, supporting the growth of cutting edge technology in cloud computing? Silverline employees are passionate about what they do. Were a diverse group of… https://t.co/om2i3dXCLQ https://t.co/sFMVQVbxZi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce Sales Architect (SE): Company Overview Do you want to be part of a fast-paced environment, supporting the growth of cutting edge technology in cloud computing? Silverline employees are passionate about what they do. Were a diverse group of… https://t.co/vbIAfWUJ3c https://t.co/SVuWsh5CTw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer III – Birmingham, UK: Job Title: Software Engineer Location: Birmingham, UK Hours: ~40 Travel: 5% About the Role As a Software Engineer on our Aprimo R&amp;D team, you’ll be building web applications that make our customers more productive.… https://t.co/JTdnyddND3 https://t.co/RkL8H8qse2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer/Scrum Master: BRIGHTREE HOME Healthcare &amp; Hospice (Morrisville, NC) seeks Software Developer/Scrum Master – Develop, create, &amp; modify general computer applications software or specialized utility programs. Req. M.S. in Engg, Info.… https://t.co/PuD0Rqm3qA https://t.co/D6MqLurzrR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Software Engineer (Java): The Lead Software Engineer (Java) is responsible for development activities for FanThreeSixtys back-end RESTful web services and data integration application, collaborating with Product Development, Mobile and Web… https://t.co/l2LRAHStab https://t.co/BZ1zq0hUzu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior, IT Development Manager: Requisition Number 17-1748 Post Date 11/20/2017 Title Senior, IT Development Manager City Bridgeton State MO Description On March 1, 2017 McKesson Corporation (NYSE MCK) and Change Healthcare Holdings, Inc., formed a new… https://t.co/1aqFuMA4jO https://t.co/L5HeUxCnz8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer I, Applications: Sysco Associate Apply – Click Here Company: CORP Enclave Location: US-TX-Houston Zip Code: 77077 Minimum Level of Education: Bachelor’s Degree Minimum Years of Experience: 1 Position Type: Exempt Travel Percentage: 0 More… https://t.co/n8LM1TSMQV https://t.co/99sUybuwnQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Agile Coach: Title: Senior Agile Coach Location: Bellevue, WA Duration: 6+ Months Contract There is an opening for a regular agile coach and another one for Senior agile coach. Required: * For both coaches, at least 3 agile related certifications,… https://t.co/Lhor6tdoJd https://t.co/LUKqRgwJVc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager/Scrum Master: JOB DESCRIPTION: Resource 1 is in need of a Project Manager/Scrum Master for a 8-12- month contract in Rosemont, Illinois. Client is open to either long-term contract or conversion to permanent. Individual should have at… https://t.co/BMWIIRL2Qx https://t.co/YxMKlZHCtM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer (Front End): Adaptive Software is one of the fastest growing parts of the DRG family. Broadly, Adaptive sells workflow and business process software tools to health plans and Pharmacy Benefit Managers (PBMs), the organizations that… https://t.co/oMrXiPAu7x https://t.co/u5244nGPtR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[India queries Cambridge Analytica over alleged Facebook data breach: NEW DELHI (Reuters) - India has set a March 31 deadline for London-based political consultancy Cambridge Analytica to respond to a query on whether it was engaged to improperly harvest… https://t.co/YFVCO3JOfK https://t.co/SV2im5Z176]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager (Certified Scrum Master) for HP Inc.: Paradigm is looking for an experienced Project Manager to support our client, HP Inc., in San Diego, CA. The individual were seeking is skilled in managing technical design projects from initiation,… https://t.co/iMYf6RBj5O https://t.co/3Jdl9YdaA0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master Job: Scrum MasterLocation: Bloomfield, CTDuration : 6+ months?Scrum Master CertificationPMP certification is a plus, agile?Raeela ******************************************?? – provided by Dice Scrum Master Certification – ID#:… https://t.co/WTYkU6xs6B https://t.co/POF7dk5a6j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Scrum Master: Job Title: Senior Scrum Master Location: Chicago, IL Duration- 6 Months Roles &amp; Responsibility Guiding the team and organization on how to use Agile/Scrum practices and values to delight customers – Guiding the team on how to get the… https://t.co/Sm1JM4X2sl https://t.co/CwsIIilb3e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer, Core Technology Group (Big Data and Cloud): Our Team The Core Technology Group (CTG) is the innovation hub within Informatica that is responsible for delivering an extensible, reliable and scalable platform that provides the… https://t.co/jOJdZNUu1K https://t.co/oWvUOXrbUR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer/Cloud Engineer: 7+ years engineering experience with Agile/Scrum methodologies. Solid understanding of algorithm complexity, parallel/distributed systems, advanced data structures, computer networking, operating systems and cloud… https://t.co/ueEzat3IsS https://t.co/OGlUAwsACs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test Automation Engineer: Test Automation Engineer (C++/Python) Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Responsibilities: Implement automation solution for BIOS validation test cases through Python programming Debug the test failures in… https://t.co/JHmWRrQtyO https://t.co/1pMxCjl3fZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer: Adaptive Software is one of the fastest growing parts of the DRG family. Broadly, Adaptive sells workflow and business process software tools to health plans and Pharmacy Benefit Managers (PBMs), the organizations that… https://t.co/vJWCKCxFE7 https://t.co/hE8KlHVtQa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mobile Game Artist: Funkitron is the creator and developer of the top grossing Cascade game published by Big Fish Games. We are looking for talented and experienced Mobile Game Artists with experience working in Unity3d for an upcoming project. Looking… https://t.co/eHAIVhU9Rj https://t.co/6y0hYlSjxS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Integration Test Lead: Sr. Integration Test Lead – (1800004E) Description JOB SUMMARY: The Senior Integration/Test Lead will be responsible for systems integration, test plan, design and support technical activities related to CRM/ERP integration for… https://t.co/r6ORKX1SIl https://t.co/M2svHP5qVt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software QA Specialist: We are seeking an experienced Senior Quality Assurance Specialist to add to our Software team. The individual will perform manual and automated testing of new software releases to ensure all business requirements are met… https://t.co/Nfedypxo2j https://t.co/t1qwQXGZGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Scrum Master / Agile Coach: Promotes the agile mindset in agile teams, challenging and removing organizational and cultural impediments. They are constantly guiding teams in discovery and learning. The Scrum Master also helps a team through… https://t.co/zVOnBltIp4 https://t.co/Ufajw2OdXX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer: Why join Irdeto? Every industry has to come to grips with the ramifications of being in an increasingly connected world. From cars, to heavy vehicles, to fleets, to industrial equipment, today’s vehicles increasingly run on… https://t.co/48FD3fD9QY https://t.co/NmNVfKtofB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. lawmakers formally ask Facebook CEO to testify on user data: WASHINGTON (Reuters) - U.S. lawmakers on Friday formally asked Facebook Inc's Mark Zuckerberg to explain at a congressional hearing how 50 million users' data got into the hands of… https://t.co/AwipVFwqAU https://t.co/lSMKoeuiM2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer (Jr. to Sr.): Welcome to DataFinch Technologies! With the autism prevalence rate jumping as high as 1 in 42 live births, clinicians, parents and teachers are relying on technology to streamline effective treatments and in turn are helping… https://t.co/f3FSiUw1Kf https://t.co/mjItA8M2Ch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Architect, Point-of-Sale Solutions: As the POS Architect, you will play an important role in the evolution of our global point-of-sale solutions that sell millions of tickets each year. You will be responsible for collaborating with fellow architects and… https://t.co/SiZzLzilEQ https://t.co/YfSkPVyiJ5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack .NET Developer: Saturno is hiring a full stack .NET developer to help us with a variety of web-based projects, including mid to large size websites and implementation of our industry-leading software. Our ideal candidate is a self-directed,… https://t.co/eVozSgLcYL https://t.co/6jlan9UQlC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager: JOB TITLE: Senior Project Manager JOB LOCATION: Deerfield, IL JOB SUMMARY: Senior Project Manager is responsible for leading teams to deliver project(s) that span across one or more business units. Manage resources, schedules,… https://t.co/pEyL4ar3Kl https://t.co/CoE9tuEq4U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Tax Analyst – Software: Equus Software is a growing global mobility software provider in downtown Denver! We are looking for a Senior Tax Analyst to help ensure we stay at the top of our game with respect to our clients, software and tax modules.… https://t.co/DZRRCiHVU5 https://t.co/x7NctlDEM0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. .Net Developer (local): Company Description US IT Solution provides full-service staffing solutions to help your business to deliver better in a dynamic market environment. With over a decade of recruitment and staffing expertise in the Asian and… https://t.co/6cU8hpZm2Q https://t.co/1QFDCa5GEx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cassandra DBA: We practice Agile/Scrum methodology and we program in a variety of languages such as Python, C/C++, &amp; Java. We are building a large scale and high-performance cloud based networking service platform that will deliver the next generation of… https://t.co/rWTUV8kK4C https://t.co/kxTCDa5T3D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (PHP): Akkadian Labs focuses exclusively on creating collaboration inspired software that maximizes business results by improving the way people communicate and work together. Our solutions include turnkey applications and custom… https://t.co/7jr6Z69WEJ https://t.co/n7GmGnm6xp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CW Scrum Master: CW Scrum Master (******) Georgetown, Kentucky – United States Job Start Date – 03/15/18, Posted Date – 03/15/18 Primary SkillsScrumTax TermsC2C,W-2,1099Overview Dear, I am Mohammed Dastagir with Saxon Global Inc wanted to let you know… https://t.co/uBjheIS45G https://t.co/Li2LxFpWDO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer Software 2: At Northrop Grumman, our employees have incredible opportunities to work on revolutionary systems in air and space that impact people’s lives around the world today, and for generations to come. Our work preserves freedom and… https://t.co/u30s9jrZOc https://t.co/RNpCD4af1o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software QA Analyst: The IT Team at Wayside Publishing is expanding and seeking new talent! Through our custom learning management system, the Learning Site, Wayside delivers interactive digital content developed using the most modern pedagogical… https://t.co/DNpcj0vZr3 https://t.co/Z8bsBgtYpR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automakers launch online tool to look up car recall: (Reuters) - Automakers have launched an online tool that will allow U.S. car owners, insurers and regulators search for open recalls, an auto trade group said on Friday. https://t.co/pHPYTxQUbs https://t.co/3He0DX12DN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Category: Project Management City: Chattanooga, Tennessee, United States Position ID: J0218-1797 Employment Type: Full Time Meet our professionals CGI: An employer of choice Position Description: Dynamic and innovative information… https://t.co/yaHBg4zUtX https://t.co/NrZIom8q3w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Scrum Master: Job TitleSr. Scrum Master – ID:30316 Duration6 Months Start DateASAP Job Skills6 – 9 YOE Skills: Required DCC DATA MANAGEMENT MASTER DATA MANAGEMENT LocationDenver, CO Date Posted03/13/2018 Scrum Master II Responsible for leading one or… https://t.co/Qbdp9ooOog https://t.co/bT47SbbDXu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Job TitleScrum Master – ID:25428 Duration6 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsExposure to various business intelligence applications and architecture such as Cognos, Tableau and data warehousing LocationVernon Hills, IL Date Posted03/06/2018… https://t.co/9K5CkQzxqC https://t.co/gNWDZhcruF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SENIOR BUSINESS ANALYST: Georgia-Pacific Who is Georgia-Pacific?Watch to find out! Georgia-Pacific (GP) is among the world’s leading manufacturers of bath tissue, paper towels, napkins, tableware, paper-based packaging, office papers, cellulose,… https://t.co/sjDnnCmIjX https://t.co/oVCWooY5D2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, Lead: Job Description Summary: CACI National and Cyber Solutions is looking for an experienced, innovative, and eager Software Engineer to help lead a team of developers employing modern, web-based software technologies for building… https://t.co/xYGPKZ6T0S https://t.co/a5KOMjnWMD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer (Java): Trustwave helps businesses fight cybercrime, protect data and reduce security risks. With cloud and managed security services, integrated technologies and a team of security experts, ethical hackers and researchers,… https://t.co/4jB9FqPiFe https://t.co/C1TwPIuxCg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Test Lead – US: InfosysIVS-Financial Services- Technical Test Lead Automation Testing Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to create and execute strategies for their… https://t.co/0uaaTDd5Q3 https://t.co/93dNwm0WZM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Product Generalist: About Cobalt Cobalt is a growing software development company and Microsoft Dynamics 365 (formerly Microsoft Dynamics CRM) partner with a track record of providing quality custom software solutions to our clients. Cobalt… https://t.co/1LT6t0VBcU https://t.co/mtjNgZ5EYR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Full Stack Developer: Description: THE COMPANY Are you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing… https://t.co/12uaPd5lrY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master/Coach: Job TitleScrum Master/Coach – ID:31104 Duration12 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsFirst level Scrum Master certification (CSM, PSM I) LocationPlan0, TX Date Posted02/26/2018 FOR IMMEDIATE DETAILS ABOUT THIS POSITION, contact ANY of us… https://t.co/Gq9eEefbCi https://t.co/7k7xJ6rkjv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dropbox shares close up 35 percent in biggest tech debut since Snap: (Reuters) - Dropbox Inc's shares closed at $28.42, up more than 35 percent in their first day of trading on Friday, as investors rushed to buy into the biggest technology initial public… https://t.co/k8gbF55D1H https://t.co/zRccM0Bq4q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UI/UX Designer: Aristotle is looking for a UI/UX Designer (with some JS development experience) that believe those companies that champion a design-centric approach to their product interfaces are the ones that rise above the rest. You live and breathe… https://t.co/a7JaUOwq9z https://t.co/He3tCbkPt6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Full Stack Application Engineer: Primary Responsibilities: Advance the state of the art in building services products with React.js, Node.js, Ruby on Rails and AngularJS, Java, PHP and mobile (Android/iOS) frameworks. Full stack development for… https://t.co/lJGVAvOtZZ https://t.co/cL88N9yRjs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: Infosys Energy, Communication &amp; Services Technology Lead US Java/J2EE(Spring Ecosystem, Spring Boot and Soap/Rest Web Services) Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50… https://t.co/bz4yHRvIKR https://t.co/ufotvvZfiv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Automation Engineer: The QA Automation Engineer will be a member of the Software Engineering team and will report to the Manager, Quality Assurance. The primary duties of the QA Automation Engineer require the exercise of discretion and independent… https://t.co/0gT4vch4Xe https://t.co/fJtixpjOTb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master – Application Delivery Manager: Client Reference Code: 214532JOB SUMMARY Our team manages the software delivery process for the Service Activation department by leading cross-functional, iterative, scrum-style software delivery teams. We… https://t.co/Egy9Xq58RX https://t.co/Vqw88OvVC8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager, Provisioning: CenturyLink (NYSE: CTL) is a global communications and IT services company focused on connecting its customers to the power of the digital world. CenturyLink offers network and data systems management, big data analytics,… https://t.co/4gr3ONZpng https://t.co/EUuyMOTdJs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Software Engineer: Job Description CACI National and Cyber Solutions is looking for an experienced, innovative, and eager Software Engineer to employ modern, web-based software technologies for building secure, Agile, cloud-enabled… https://t.co/bbEfZ13UYf https://t.co/tbCbKjOUu9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CW Scrum Master: CW Scrum Master (******) Georgetown, Kentucky – United States Job Start Date – 03/15/18, Posted Date – 03/15/18 Primary SkillsScrumTax TermsC2C,W-2,1099Overview Dear, I am Mohammed Dastagir with Saxon Global Inc wanted to let you know… https://t.co/DRD8WCRtD7 https://t.co/rRXnMKqBXw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Concur – Sr. IT Project Manager: SAP Concur – Sr. IT Project Manager Job Close By continuing to use and navigate this website, you are agreeing to the use of cookies. Accept – SAP employees – Join our talent community Search by Keyword Search by… https://t.co/Z8jOtSV8ND https://t.co/BE2dquuNI5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China gives Baidu go-ahead for self-driving tests after U.S. crash: SHANGHAI/BEIJING (Reuters) - China's capital city has given the green light to tech giant Baidu Inc to test self-driving cars on city streets, indicating strong support for the budding… https://t.co/ZURO8uVmqy https://t.co/KAFksZVzMy]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>