<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[New @slaw_dot_ca - 25 Tips from the Best in Legal Marketing: http://t.co/6klE4Srlg5 -- @LMA_ANNUAL_CONF #bclaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your Legal Mktg ROI: Take It to the Next Level  http://t.co/a2qDe93UpK (article)  #bclegal #lawfirm @slaw_dot_ca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maximize Legal Mktg ROI: What strategies can you add?  http://t.co/a2qDe93UpK (article)  #bclegal #lawfirm @slaw_dot_ca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JournalistsLike: We need to do a public service campaign that if you're going to record news on your iPhone, turn it sideways for cryin…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's hoping #boston + especially it's police force, is tucked in and fast asleep. Tomorrow will be a brighter day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ewwww...gross! Keep them apart! "@News1130radio: Notice more #spiders in #Vancouver? It’s their mating season! http://t.co/J2b3G0fDqr"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome! "@cbanatmag: Local lawyers plan to offer free legal advice to the poor http://t.co/T9RXYsLK9T"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @thriveorg: How to be a really good listener.  Are you hearing them right? http://t.co/lkce8E2ADB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tla_bc Oh, go on... Tell us! Give us a clue!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Legal Mktg and Social Media: When to invest. http://t.co/dSLpkS3ckA [Article]  #bclaw @slaw_dot_ca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strategic Social Media Mkting: Not an Oxymoron. http://t.co/dSLpkS3ckA [Article]  #bclegal #lawfirm @slaw_dot_ca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Legal Mktg with Social Media? Plan for investment. http://t.co/dSLpkS3ckA [Article]  #lawmarketing @slaw_dot_ca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you chasing shiny baubles? Social Media can do that to you. http://t.co/JrSEwGltKz [Article]  #bclaw @slaw_dot_ca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the Library: "Write like a journalist [ahem…not like a lawyer]" http://t.co/ZG0UD1wGBg --- #bclegal @slaw_dot_ca ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tip 3 -- Legal Mktg and Social Media: Be selective. http://t.co/JrSEwGltKz [Article]  #bclegal #lawfirm @slaw_dot_ca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Legal Mktg: Where does your Social Media fit? http://t.co/JrSEwGltKz [Article]  #bclegal #legalmarketing @slaw_dot_ca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Legal Mktg: Know your content for Social Media success. http://t.co/JrSEwGltKz [Article]  #lawmarketing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Legal Social Media Mktg: Know where your audience is. http://t.co/JrSEwGltKz [Article]  #lawmarketing @slaw_dot_ca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Legal Mktg: Where do Facebook, LinkedIn and Twitter fit? http://t.co/JrSEwGltKz [Article]  #bclaw @slaw_dot_ca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the Library: "Focus on your rainmakers first" -Legal Mktg ROI http://t.co/LR9alysh4t (article)  #bclegal @slaw_dot_ca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strategic Social Media Marketing: How to start. http://t.co/JrSEwGltKz [Article]  #bclegal @slaw_dot_ca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Legal Social Media Mktg: 6 Tips to Stay Effective. http://t.co/JrSEwGltKz [Article]  #lawmarketing @slaw_dot_ca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Legal Mktg with Social Media: Stop! Now is the time. http://t.co/JrSEwGltKz [Article]  #bclegal @slaw_dot_ca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New @slaw_dot_ca - Social Media: Shiny Bauble or Strategic Tool? http://t.co/JrSEwGltKz ---   #bclaw #bclegal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cybelenegris: Telus donating $1 for every social media mention of #vansunkids Vancouver Sun Children's Fund http://t.co/vjDxPkBeNr pls …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful msg, produced perfectlyl! RT @BlakesLaw: Wishing you all the best for a wonderful holiday season http://t.co/E1dSaEC9F2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WOW! MT @RoyalColumbian: Thanking @McQuarrieHunter. As part of Donation Day, they announced $10K in support towards the MPIS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PinkBakery: Beaming with pride right now. Thank you @NewWestChamber @McQuarrieHunter and everyone else involved #PlatinumAwards http://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome! Just STOP and watch this 5 min heartwarming @westjet prank + PR lesson http://t.co/COixeVnq3L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nicely done! Helpful + informative. "@papercliplaw: Buying property the @papercliplaw way - the ABCs. http://t.co/hUAOqPkAex"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TristinHopper Me thinks the bigger story is that Red Deer has a house listed for $1 mill! #justsayin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @walkerparkmedia: 2 cancellations mean we are desperate for makeup artists  at Help Portrait in #mapleridge this Sat 1-8  Anyone? RT's a…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@erindermer LOL! Your own personal clipping service!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HomaAzad @ArticlingWomen @slaw_dot_ca thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @strombo: Broadcast opportunity: @CBCSaskatoon is looking for a Reporter-Editor (TV/Radio/Online)... http://t.co/Dkhog9moqs #CanadianTal…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CindyZheng: @McQuarrieHunter e-Alerts- if you missed them, you can find them here: http://t.co/UCfGDuVDsW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Legal Marketing Tip 5 of 10: Get invited! http://t.co/SIJJ62jbgW #lawmarketing #lawfirm @slaw_dot_ca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LMAVancouver @BullHousser @FSVancouver Thanks, BH! Hope you're settling well into your new (temp) digs!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LMAVancouver Thanks for the plug, guys!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Legal Social Media Mktg: Leave your footprint online http://t.co/SIJJ62jbgW #lawmarketing @slaw_dot_ca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Legal Marketing: Build your dream team and reach your goals http://t.co/SIJJ62jbgW #bclaw @slaw_dot_ca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tip 3: Be Selective - manage social media, don't let it manage you! http://t.co/qBSGdH4UGg #legalmarketing @slaw_dot_ca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you started your pipeline of hope? http://t.co/SIJJ62jbgW #bclegal @slaw_dot_ca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Miss604: MT @CKNW: City of Vancouver asking ppl to check their catch basins for leaves 2 prevent roads flooding - up to 70mm of rain ex…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Legal Marketing: On the fast track? Update your bio as you go http://t.co/SIJJ62jbgW #bclegal @slaw_dot_ca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@globebooks Ok, so are u asking yet? Go on, ask us!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @globebooks: We’re thrilled to start #globereads, where each week we'll ask you, our followers, a question, &amp; print our favourite answer…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DyeDurham: RT @david_bilinsky: Pacific #Legal Tech Conf accredited 6.25 professionalism hours by #LSUC. Attend Oct 4 via web. #PLTC13...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@papercliplaw Sunny fall day in one of the most beautiful cities! What's not to love?! Must be beautiful on North Shore today!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FaskenMartineau: New WCB Bullying and Harassment Policies Take Effect November 1, 2013 http://t.co/UEKzJ35S1U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TLA members: MT"@tla_bc: Join us at the #TLABC offices for sips &amp; snacks - at the Annual Fall Membership Reception: http://t.co/oyNEqndS1L"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Simple + true!"@papercliplaw: Let @papercliplaw create your contracts so you can go about building your business. http://t.co/141zMHFu2F"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @McQuarrieHunter: Free Family Law Seminar, WEDNESDAY, October 9th.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DisneyInstitute: #INFOGRAPHIC: 80% of companies believe they deliver superior service, you won't believe what percent of customers do: …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @UBCLaw: RT @myfutureinlaw: Good luck to the UBC 2nd year law students who are attending On Campus Interviews today!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nhouseinsight thank you!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tip 1: Building a great reputation starts now http://t.co/SIJJ62jbgW #lawmarketing @slaw_dot_ca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think of social media as a pillar of your strategic marketing plan http://t.co/qBSGdH4UGg #legalmarketing @slaw_dot_ca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Legal Marketing: Build your profile online http://t.co/SIJJ62jbgW #bclegal #legalmarketing @slaw_dot_ca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I loooove my dog ... Even if she looks like a cartoon character in this pic! http://t.co/amQN0VPzTk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh no! "@globeandmail: In Pictures: Via train collides with bus http://t.co/rxUzhaPsks"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RoyalColumbian: We've been sharing health tips on RJ1200 AM Radio weekdays between 10AM &amp; 12PM. Here is our "Preventing Falls" tip: htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MAHHfew: "There is no reason why the core values of a company can't include doing something good for society." @ariannahuff #TheArtOf #…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Movin' on up! MT "@BullHousser: BH says goodbye to Royal Centre; address as of Sept. 23: Suite 900 - 900 Howe Street, Vancouver V6Z 2M4"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Luv it! MT "@HolmesandKing: 100% organic, free-range legal services. No additives, preservatives or pesticides. Just good, practical advice"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RidgeRCMP: Please slow down and drive carefully. Some reports of black ice on our roads this morning. Road crews are working... http://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is for some of our clients MT"@JaffePR: Outsourcing social media for lawyers (or firms) - Is it right for you? &gt; http://t.co/RMeibqFVGD"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DB_Legal500: What lawyers put in their website bios versus What clients want to see in lawyer bios http://t.co/lcFm1ZGJxe #2014MPF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Client service excellence is a team sport. Your 5 basic tips http://t.co/6hgVlqO3UY #bclegal # bclaw @slaw_dot_ca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MillerThomson Vancouver will arguably be best-dressed law firm w office move above Nordstrom's in 2015.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tx! "@slaw_dot_ca: Comment on How Your Assistant Can Help With Your Legal Marketing Efforts by Susan Van Dyke http://t.co/pxEUNSYvkB"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ontraccoach: New @lawyersweeklyca - Short term savings may mean long term losses http://t.co/UuunAxgpdv #canadaslawyercoach #lawfirm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks @samtaracollier!  So glad the article gave you a boost in some way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SlawTips indeed ... Thx for the clarification (blush)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tx! "@LuluIslandWild: several cool tweets you might have not noticed via @PieterDorsman @EdTechEmpowers @lawyerPR http://t.co/LOCy2JNKId"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samtaracollier yes, so sad to lose a great man so young. So great that yer donating to @NSRescue. Nice piece in @VancouverSun today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thx @samtaracollier! Glad u enjoyed my @SlawTips article. That'll make @fodden smile -if his avatar can read this w/out specs on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LOL! MT"Via @harmlessscience: How 2013 newsmakers would make a peanut butter and jelly sandwich http://t.co/0NMID34jZB via @macleansmag"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wendy_Stueck @NSRescue @BCSARAssoc #nsrescue My 1000th tweet - I just donated to both orgs in memory of Tim. Pls RT + donate today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was happy for u too!"@papercliplaw: @lawyerPR that's what we love to hear!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@papercliplaw met a happy corporate client of yours on Friday!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wendy_Stueck Excellent Wendy -  thx for spreading the word. I'm donating today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tributes for hero Tim Jones @NSRescue pouring in. Heartbreaking - only 57 yrs old.  How best to honour a life-saver?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This was imp + successful client retention strategy for 1 of my clients "@LAWPRO: I won’t make clients wait in reception #legaltips"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fodden! You're not looking quite yourself lately ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shocked MT"@CKNW: Remembering a hero - @JonMcComb980 on loss of #NSSR Spokesperson Tim Jones http://t.co/rrhFwqpK4N http://t.co/4HESwX3kE0"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True! MT"@ArleneDickinson: Wrking w football in bckgrnd = entrepreneurs idea of wknd relaxing. http://t.co/mz0kQpbjYL. You aren't alone!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnaleaWayne @PattyMC22 Milestones at English Bay in Vancouver. Beautiful day!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PattyMC22 great to see you today! Forgot to officially toast your QC, my *young* friend! #cbaab]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Garin: "If opportunity doesn't knock, build a door." ~Milton Berle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ianmulgrew: Ikea monkey 'mom' ordered to pay $83K in legal costs to sanctuary she sued http://t.co/pAohOOEdcD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@RoyalColumbian: We're looking for a Communications Specialist! Details here: http://t.co/rRyQhP2pQ6 #Jobs #Careers #NewWestminster #YVR"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your assistant can improve the client experience (+ client loyalty) http://t.co/6hgVlqO3UY #bclegal #lawfirm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @northshorebar: Judges' Dinner Next Week! on Tuesday, January 28, 2014 - http://t.co/iRKd9VuZli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@clebc love it + sentiment: "Ravens teach us to be creative for the common good" (art credit: M.Johnny Jr.) http://t.co/43bBFVxAaB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you for the wonderful speaker's gift that just arrived @clebc! So thoughtful! So CLE!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 Tips to increase your legal marketing efforts http://t.co/F0RYcRee9i #bclegal #lawfirm @slaw_dot_ca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loads of personality + humour! "@CBCVancouver: Who's behind those tribute tweets @kingsgatemall? http://t.co/iw1yOMCSZ5"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @erindermer: “@erinireland: it's coffee o'clock. a list of vancouver's most trusted spots for a solid cup http://t.co/fSstaRoUz1” @mojac…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New @slaw_dot_ca How your assistant can help with legal marketing http://t.co/6hgVlqO3UY #bclegal #legalmarketing]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>