<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint/Web Developer: Job Description Job Description Job Number: R******* Booz Allen Hamilton has been at the forefront of strategy and technology for more than 100 years. Today, the firm provides management and technology consulting and engineering… https://t.co/ukevzXDV1v https://t.co/uC9mbP5dBe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint SME: SharePoint SME Location: Washington, DC Job Code: 3265 # of openings: 1 Description Bay State Computers, Inc. is a professional services firm and a leading provider of Information Technology (IT) services and products to the U.S. Federal… https://t.co/JnTybLpJLp https://t.co/xzblhqG7DU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Nintex Developer: Prestigious Enterprise Company is currently seeking a Developer with SharePoint and ****** experience, as well as some Nintex exposure. Candidate will be responsible for end-user computing development using the Microsoft… https://t.co/nHUQJBBzwn https://t.co/AogM3NVhZU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sharepoint Administrator UNIX/Linux Administrator (Multiple Positions): Point Administrator Atlanta, GA 15 Months Job Summary: Under broad supervision, installs, configures, and supports the client Point-based infrastructure and associated applications.… https://t.co/QD1wig0NK1 https://t.co/TiHNUWhjQy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solutions Architect – SharePoint Online Job: Company Information PACCAR is a Fortune 500 company established in 1905. PACCAR Inc is recognized as a global leader in the commercial vehicle, financial, and customer service fields with internationally… https://t.co/WLdgJ90ik8 https://t.co/glBUfnEc50]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Lead Solutions Engineer/Architect: SharePoint Lead Solutions Engineer/Architect Ref No.:18-00145 Category: ************* Location: Washington, District of Columbia Position Type:Contingent Experience Level: 7 Years Start Date: 04/09/2018 Job… https://t.co/BESgkRRehq https://t.co/PFx760sDEY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer, .Net / Sharepoint: The St Louis Fed is one of 12 Reserve Banks serving all or parts of Missouri, Illinois, Indiana, Kentucky, Tennessee, Mississippi and Arkansas with branches in Little Rock, Louisville and Memphis. The St. Louis Feds most… https://t.co/gwOHo1iohl https://t.co/fE1zTZzZKu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sharepoint developer: Sharepoint developer boston, Massachusetts &amp;#8211; United States Job Start Date &amp;#8211; 04/09/18, Posted Date &amp;#8211; 04/09/18 Primary SkillsSharepointTax TermsC2COverviewface to face any visa Sharepoint Developer in Boston. Must be… https://t.co/yOB3IcSzR0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer, Mid: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Coronado, CA Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 4/15/2018 Job Description Job Number: R******* Booz Allen Hamilton has been at the forefront of strategy and… https://t.co/sG8PIiFv0B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solutions Architect – SharePoint Online Job: Company Information PACCAR is a Fortune 500 company established in 1905. PACCAR Inc is recognized as a global leader in the commercial vehicle, financial, and customer service fields with internationally… https://t.co/Ek4HOScUQK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sharepoint Developer: point Developer Ref No.:18-09221 Location: pittsburgh, Pennsylvania Position Type:Direct Placement Start Date: 05/18/2018 Role: point Developer Location: Pittsburgh PA Type: Full Time Role: Point Developer/Senior Developer Skill… https://t.co/V9LZxGy8fH https://t.co/zWteBHccYE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Solution Architect: Imaginet is your trusted software technology partner who turns your business innovation ideas into reality. As a 10-time Microsoft Gold Partner, Imaginet specializes in SharePoint Consulting and Managed Services,… https://t.co/YoUB9pZRvA https://t.co/V8awF5ma3a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: Requisition ID ******* Job Family US-MD-Owings Mills Posting Description Aon Is Looking For An Operations and Technical Specialist II As part of an industry-leading team, you will help empower results for our clients by delivering… https://t.co/9lMJC3gCPC https://t.co/h9t5TvNot2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sharepoint Web Developer – Top Secret Clearance SCI Eligible: point Web Developer &amp;#8211; Top Secret Clearance SCI Eligible at DXC U.S. Public Sector Skip Navigation Menu &amp;#8211; Home &amp;#8211; Military Thrive on change We are technology independent. Our… https://t.co/kvV5dha7k4 https://t.co/AoL1bmEFmZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: SharePoint Developer ==================== Req #: ******Location: Alexandria, VA USJob Category: Information TechnologySecurity Clearance: SecretClearance Status: Must Be Current Job Description Responsibilities: * Helps to develop… https://t.co/okJ6hRUz1G https://t.co/EqyEkYedyA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: Job Title SharePoint Developer Education Bachelor&amp;#8217;s Degree Location BETHESDA, MD 20810 US (Primary) Job Description Futrend Technology is looking for a SharePoint Developer who wil l be responsible to initiate new application… https://t.co/a7uoncU3Ma https://t.co/t6ssDPtwIm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: SharePoint Developer ==================== Req #: ******Location: Arlington, VA USJob Category: Information TechnologySecurity Clearance: SecretClearance Status: Must be Obtainable Job Description Program Overview CACI is currently… https://t.co/hA0KROJ22b https://t.co/YxRUzAvKnn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager Sharepoint amp; collaboration: * worked on medium &amp;#8211; large size projects ($1 million +) * managed a team of 5-10 members or more * worked on a project that required them managing multiple workstreams concurrently PROJECT SPECIFICS:… https://t.co/ZaWV8sEmxC https://t.co/2g5m6fzzYu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: Company Description For over 10 years, ABSc has provided world class consulting services with a fresh perspective. Our focused solutions are designed to meet the mission critical needs of our clients. We bring innovation and proven… https://t.co/v9LRuaLLnX https://t.co/VM43eWlojM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sharepoint Developer: point Developer Ref No.:18-09221 Location: pittsburgh, Pennsylvania Position Type:Direct Placement Start Date: 05/18/2018 Role: point Developer Location: Pittsburgh PA Type: Full Time Role: Point Developer/Senior Developer Skill… https://t.co/i5eNcjQWeG https://t.co/FTQUqaI8u4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[o365 / SharePoint Collaboration Tools Specialist: Fivesky is looking for a highly motivated and talented Collaboration Tools Specialist to join a fast-paced, dynamic, and challenging environment. The ideal candidate must have a background of working with… https://t.co/huDbYA4Ad7 https://t.co/FrUIj3Bt1f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Is GDPR and Why Should You Care?: Yes, they mainly affect those who live inside the EU. But non-Europeans should pay attention too. https://t.co/Y1KKR2tvzs https://t.co/bMfMbIXLZx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: SharePoint Developer ==================== Req #: ******Location: Alexandria, VA USJob Category: Information TechnologySecurity Clearance: SecretClearance Status: Must Be Current Job Description Responsibilities: * Helps to develop… https://t.co/z5TpD8sr5N https://t.co/V0SF8e2nXN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: MetroStar Systems Careers ========================= SharePoint Developer Web Development Reston, Virginia Apply MetroStar Systems is looking for a SharePoint Developer that is passionate about the hands on delivery and development… https://t.co/5nQfUG2xds https://t.co/IEzx0HpwRS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: Job Title SharePoint Developer Education Bachelor&amp;#8217;s Degree Location Atlanta, GA 30301 US (Primary) Job Description Futrend Technology is looking for SharePoint Developers who will be responsible for creating technical design… https://t.co/TGg97Bq5oX https://t.co/0IhcUddEHD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint / Web developer: POSITION: Web Developer SUMMIT TECHNOLOGIES has a position for a WEB DEVELOPER to join our team. You will be responsible for enhancing websites and web-based applications. This on-site position is located at FT. LEE, VA and… https://t.co/Nv1gP264uO https://t.co/G3cclRMofR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Lead Solutions Engineer/Architect: SharePoint Lead Solutions Engineer/Architect Ref No.:18-00145 Category: ************* Location: Washington, District of Columbia Position Type:Contingent Experience Level: 7 Years Start Date: 04/09/2018 Job… https://t.co/W6CTyDA5G9 https://t.co/HgpxSpMjl3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Sharepoint Developer: Title Senior Sharepoint Developer =========================== EOE Statement We are an equal employment opportunity employer. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color,… https://t.co/hkdxN7CCOD https://t.co/P399LDWjq2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: MetroStar Systems Careers ========================= SharePoint Developer Web Development Reston, Virginia Apply MetroStar Systems is looking for a SharePoint Developer that is passionate about the hands on delivery and development… https://t.co/BHuGA2sxWC https://t.co/PuA5jVKhWm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Online Developer: We are currently seeking a motivated, career and customer service oriented Point Online Developer to join our team in Alexandria, VA to begin an exciting and challenging career with Unisys Federal Systems. In this role, you… https://t.co/voahC1rDcD https://t.co/ho4lxDD7Bf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Administrator: Req ID 97846BR Business Title SharePoint Administrator Group CORP Location USA VIRGINIA Herndon Clearance Level Needed None Category Information Technology Job Duties and Responsibilities ManTech is seeking a highly motivated… https://t.co/5ZjTJiqmdb https://t.co/wOTiRty6Cg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: DESCRIPTION: Employer is seeking a SharePoint Developer to support a customer site in Springfield VA. Active TS/SCI clearance is required. The successful candidate will provide web development and technical support to the customer… https://t.co/HRHHJFFNb8 https://t.co/qgvilAPiBO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Nintex Developer: Prestigious Enterprise Company is currently seeking a Developer with SharePoint and ****** experience, as well as some Nintex exposure. Candidate will be responsible for end-user computing development using the Microsoft… https://t.co/hS0NWYMpq8 https://t.co/5x1pml8pqZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Business Analyst w/ Office 365 &amp; SharePoint Experience: The Senior Business Analyst is responsible for ensuring the operational efficacy and excellence of the company. The business analyst documents processes and captures requirements in various… https://t.co/oVPuPxHnId https://t.co/Wy7O4DG205]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid level Sharepoint Developer: Title Mid level Sharepoint Developer ============================== EOE Statement We are an equal employment opportunity employer. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race,… https://t.co/zBQ2FbaYLk https://t.co/umVEW4Cq5k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: Job Title SharePoint Developer Education Bachelor&amp;#8217;s Degree Location Atlanta, GA 30301 US (Primary) Job Description Futrend Technology is looking for SharePoint Developers who will be responsible for creating technical design… https://t.co/1AHS5QKFyn https://t.co/OblExoFs97]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sharepoint Developer: Sharepoint Developer Ref No.: 18-18152 Location: NYC, New York Required Skills: [-] Strong C#, ******* &amp;#038; PowerShell skills [-] Ability demo SharePoint features; to provide specialized consulting services with regards to out of… https://t.co/eDDtCCnRMl https://t.co/bhABIMe3H7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Knowledge Research Analyst – SharePoint: Req ID 97320BR Business Title Knowledge Research Analyst &amp;#8211; SharePoint Group MCIS Location USA MARYLAND Fort Meade Clearance Level Needed TS/SCI Category Intelligence Job Duties and Responsibilities… https://t.co/iW4hpAEkIY https://t.co/42jN7Rmyrp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager with Sharepoint: Project Manager with Sharepoint Ref No.: 18-21572 Location: Redmonds, Washington Project Manager with Sharepoint Redmond, WA 12 Months contract Job Description: Taking requirements from customer and stakeholders,… https://t.co/UIpshfIgvV https://t.co/1bmBpqZFa1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: Company Description For over 10 years, ABSc has provided world class consulting services with a fresh perspective. Our focused solutions are designed to meet the mission critical needs of our clients. We bring innovation and proven… https://t.co/u02tcvMASa https://t.co/YfTFeoTmUN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer, Mid: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Lexington Park, MD Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 4/25/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients&amp;#8217; toughest… https://t.co/yOrLj14vq4 https://t.co/mHhd0H8VXG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: Job Title SharePoint Developer Education Bachelor&amp;#8217;s Degree Location BETHESDA, MD 20810 US (Primary) Job Description Futrend Technology is looking for a SharePoint Developer who wil l be responsible to initiate new application… https://t.co/WblrZwNnZs https://t.co/3xgkwUX1fE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Support Analyst: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Millington, TN Job Type: Strategy &amp;#8211; Planning Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 5/13/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients&amp;#8217;… https://t.co/COeffjmJ3c https://t.co/6ETjo5D31C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: Point Developer in Arlington, VA &amp;#124; CACI International &amp;#8211; Small Business &amp;#124; &amp;#8211; Suppliers &amp;#8211; About Us &amp;#8211; &amp;#124; &amp;#8211; What We Do &amp;#8211; &amp;#124; &amp;#8211; Media &amp;#038; Events &amp;#8211; &amp;#124; &amp;#8211;… https://t.co/SZcNF1UBMW https://t.co/15cZp4efCb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: Discover Technologies, LLC provides SharePoint professional services in both the commercial and public sectors to ensure effective delivery of contracted services to customers world-wide. In this role, Discover Technologies… https://t.co/k725uEgJt5 https://t.co/21IqlZh6Pv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: SharePoint Developer Ref No.: 18-18258 Location: Plano, Texas Job Title : SharePoint Developer Location : Plano, TX Duration : 12 Months Job Description : Responsible for specific architecture and technology decisions such as… https://t.co/GbFUwDplVJ https://t.co/xvCezJtsxn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: SharePoint Developer Ref No.: 18-20192 Location: Santa Clara, California &amp;#8211; Minimum 10 years of SP development experience &amp;#8211; Excellent programming skills in SP platform (*******, Javascript, JQuery, CSS) &amp;#8211; Highly… https://t.co/Z6apvibeAt https://t.co/zpjIC90C2O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: Point Developer in Chantilly, VA &amp;#124; CACI International &amp;#8211; Small Business &amp;#124; &amp;#8211; Suppliers &amp;#8211; About Us &amp;#8211; &amp;#124; &amp;#8211; What We Do &amp;#8211; &amp;#124; &amp;#8211; Media &amp;#038; Events &amp;#8211; &amp;#124; &amp;#8211;… https://t.co/kpfCsEKejc https://t.co/uMfh8bjIJX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: Point Developer Enter job title or location Search menu open clear text Search jobs Recent Searches &amp;#8211; Deloitte home &amp;#8211; About Deloitte &amp;#8211; Job cart &amp;#8211; Location: United States &amp;#8211; Global (English) English… https://t.co/VWIkT9H6DJ https://t.co/yUeaIOdqzu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sharepoint developer: Sharepoint developer Ref No.: 18-19985 Location: Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania Job Title: Sharepoint developer Onsite Work Location: Pittsburgh, PA Duration: Permanent Note: No Remote Work, No C2C/C2H, No Visa Transfer, No Sponsorship… https://t.co/Izke2Axoc0 https://t.co/kJ696tBdTw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: SharePoint Developer ==================== Req #: ******Location: Arlington, VA USJob Category: Information TechnologySecurity Clearance: SecretClearance Status: Must be Obtainable Job Description Program Overview CACI is currently… https://t.co/GMVWl6si1E https://t.co/QTK4utBCdn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: Point Developer in Chantilly, VA &amp;#124; CACI International &amp;#8211; Small Business &amp;#124; &amp;#8211; Suppliers &amp;#8211; About Us &amp;#8211; &amp;#124; &amp;#8211; What We Do &amp;#8211; &amp;#124; &amp;#8211; Media &amp;#038; Events &amp;#8211; &amp;#124; &amp;#8211;… https://t.co/MnqPWrkyS8 https://t.co/SGNEWKHJLR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Web Developer (.Net/SharePoint): Sr. Web Developer (.Net, Point) &amp;#8211; V3Main ************** &amp;#8211; Home &amp;#8211; About &amp;#8211; Mission, Vision, &amp;#038; Values &amp;#8211; Leadership &amp;#8211; Government &amp;#8211; Cybersecurity &amp;#8211; News &amp;#8211; Services… https://t.co/UFX7lGAX2f https://t.co/3kFM4yDDmq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: Point Developer Enter job title or location Search menu open clear text Search jobs Recent Searches &amp;#8211; Deloitte home &amp;#8211; About Deloitte &amp;#8211; Job cart &amp;#8211; Location: United States &amp;#8211; Global (English) English… https://t.co/qgtzzRK7V0 https://t.co/EJ0iXzODgK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid level Sharepoint Developer: Job Information: Mid level point Developer Job Email Opening Title Mid level point Developer EOE StatementWe are an equal employment opportunity employer. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment… https://t.co/M3N46j5dh2 https://t.co/dfWEeikDRK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer/Designer, Mid: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Dayton, OH Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 4/25/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients&amp;#8217; toughest… https://t.co/ce3QVPCpY3 https://t.co/wy8FuoszHB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: Company Description For over 10 years, ABSc has provided world class consulting services with a fresh perspective. Our focused solutions are designed to meet the mission critical needs of our clients. We bring innovation and proven… https://t.co/OqfSxp33vQ https://t.co/3qgXFBC1wg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sharepoint Developer, Secret Clearance, Kittery ME: point Developer, Secret Clearance, Kittery ME in Kittery, ME &amp;#124; CACI International &amp;#8211; Small Business &amp;#124; &amp;#8211; Suppliers &amp;#8211; About Us &amp;#8211; &amp;#124; &amp;#8211; What We Do &amp;#8211; &amp;#124;… https://t.co/cftGnGEAyh https://t.co/wVmoqvJVJw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer, Mid: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Joint Base Pearl Harbor-Hickam, HI Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 4/26/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our… https://t.co/T9HxwGw12M https://t.co/yr3RN2UgiP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: Imaginet is your trusted software technology partner who turns your business innovation ideas into reality. As a 10-time Microsoft Gold Partner, Imaginet specializes in SharePoint Consulting and Managed Services, Application… https://t.co/gllMvEVCP1 https://t.co/iGrhAN0qYX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: Job Title SharePoint Developer Education Bachelor&amp;#8217;s Degree Location BETHESDA, MD 20810 US (Primary) Job Description Futrend Technology is looking for a SharePoint Developer who wil l be responsible to initiate new application… https://t.co/i1QYNTzJD8 https://t.co/X7iizuJmSb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer Mid Level: Job Title SharePoint Developer Mid Level Education Bachelor&amp;#8217;s Degree Location Rockville &amp;#8211; Rockville, MD 20850 US (Primary) Job Description Futrend Technology is looking for a SharePoint Developer who will be… https://t.co/3gBClBboHE https://t.co/msv2L7SGdE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft Sharepoint Developer: Microsoft point Developer in Washington, DC &amp;#124; CACI International &amp;#8211; Small Business &amp;#124; &amp;#8211; Suppliers &amp;#8211; About Us &amp;#8211; &amp;#124; &amp;#8211; What We Do &amp;#8211; &amp;#124; &amp;#8211; Media &amp;#038; Events &amp;#8211;… https://t.co/GgSGm5ywjX https://t.co/EcuSmLoxH8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: MetroStar Systems Careers ========================= SharePoint Developer Web Development Reston, Virginia Apply MetroStar Systems is looking for a SharePoint Developer that is passionate about the hands on delivery and development… https://t.co/Mz9MAWOnIO https://t.co/ZRfdQ5vWld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: Job Title SharePoint Developer Education Bachelor&amp;#8217;s Degree Location Atlanta, GA 30301 US (Primary) Job Description Futrend Technology is looking for SharePoint Developers who will be responsible for creating technical design… https://t.co/sEKJI2y9z5 https://t.co/oN5o5kNkfg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sharepoint Developer: Sharepoint Developer Ref No.: 18-18152 Location: NYC, New York Required Skills: [-] Strong C#, ******* &amp;#038; PowerShell skills [-] Ability demo SharePoint features; to provide specialized consulting services with regards to out of… https://t.co/EDm3CcR6G3 https://t.co/VUV4JRQ9pd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sharepoint Developer: point Developer Ref No.:18-07176 Location: Rockville, Maryland Position Type:Contract Start Date: 04/18/2018 &amp;#8211; Candidate should have 6+ years of IT experience in Development and migration projects &amp;#8211; Candidate must have… https://t.co/fTYQBwfnMX https://t.co/Z00NroEz7k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: Point Developer Ref No.:18-06971 Location: Resmond, Washington Position Type:Contract Experience Level: 5 Years Start Date: 04/16/2018 Role: Point Developer Location : Redmond, WA Duration 8-12 months Experience: 6-8 Year Primary… https://t.co/OAGNuiG2h0 https://t.co/DK1Imd4X5I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer/Architect: POSITION TITLE: SharePoint Developer/Architect TYPE: Perm SCOPE:enhancements, technical leadership, and making the best use of their current SharePoint Farm. MOST IMPORTANT QUALIFICATIONS &amp;#038; WHY: * Must have solid C#… https://t.co/AVyZ3MHEn1 https://t.co/b6sGajv3VA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sharepoint developer: Sharepoint developer Ref No.: 18-19985 Location: Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania Job Title: Sharepoint developer Onsite Work Location: Pittsburgh, PA Duration: Permanent Note: No Remote Work, No C2C/C2H, No Visa Transfer, No Sponsorship… https://t.co/cAZ0oxwCmc https://t.co/YGcaOMIv4P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer and Administrator: Chicago, IL The individual in this role will play a critical part in building, supporting and maintaining our Firm Intranet SharePoint environment to help lawyers and staff access information on demands or per… https://t.co/06iLJOQmOi https://t.co/DkImRUQuxN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer/Engineer: Point Developer/Engineer &amp;#8211; Spalding Consulting, Inc. ************** *************** &amp;#8211; Home &amp;#8211; About &amp;#8211; Solutions &amp;#8211; Careers &amp;#8211; Contracts &amp;#8211; Contact &amp;#8211; My Account Job Openings &gt;&gt;… https://t.co/lwrC1n6uyc https://t.co/2TyDSyha7f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Provider Data Consultant – US Telecommute: Expanding access to affordable, high quality health care starts here. This is where some of the most innovative ideas in health care are created every day. This is where bold people with big ideas are writing… https://t.co/aAS87jRnBn https://t.co/G6JZx14xMT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Risk Solutions Lead Analyst: Primary Location: United States,Texas,Irving Education: Bachelor&amp;#8217;s Degree Job Function: Finance Schedule: Full-time Shift: Day Job Employee Status: Regular Travel Time: Yes, 10 % of the Time Job ID: 18010339 Description… https://t.co/o02XJB7s7Y https://t.co/PxQnz4VGRY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: DESCRIPTION: Employer is seeking a SharePoint Developer to support a customer site in Springfield VA. Active TS/SCI clearance is required. The successful candidate will provide web development and technical support to the customer… https://t.co/jo0KbDDZou https://t.co/M5o3w0MBLt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer, Mid: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Joint Base Pearl Harbor-Hickam, HI Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 4/26/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our… https://t.co/DPFcWgx6DH https://t.co/qBFkhPAiBH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: SharePoint Developer Ref No.: 18-18258 Location: Plano, Texas Job Title : SharePoint Developer Location : Plano, TX Duration : 12 Months Job Description : Responsible for specific architecture and technology decisions such as… https://t.co/rUcTztrNWw https://t.co/MhvhvvDZbO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint / Web developer: SUMMIT TECHNOLOGIES has a short-term position for a WEB DEVELOPER to join our team. You will be responsible for enhancing websites and web-based applications. This on-site position is located at FT. LEE, VA and requires a… https://t.co/YwpnAwTy70 https://t.co/QTrVO2Dojd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: SharePoint Developer Ref No.: 18-20192 Location: Santa Clara, California &amp;#8211; Minimum 10 years of SP development experience &amp;#8211; Excellent programming skills in SP platform (*******, Javascript, JQuery, CSS) &amp;#8211; Highly… https://t.co/Q6NOIqonkY https://t.co/Zk2M3xJM97]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Configuration Management Analyst: Description: The job of the Configuration Management (CM) Analyst is to perform the necessary functions to maintain configuration control of aircraft system hardware and software configurations. PRIMARY… https://t.co/Slk5Ru8eDY https://t.co/YucdpZ8IQY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Configuration Analyst: Description:The Leidos Defense &amp;#038; Intelligence Group is searching for a Configuration Analyst in support of our SS-AISR program located in Huntsville, AL. JOB SUMMARY:As the Configuration Analyst, you will track and maintain… https://t.co/YUWEKVKUXv https://t.co/bl2szzoMF6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sharepoint developer: Sharepoint developer Ref No.: 18-19985 Location: Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania Job Title: Sharepoint developer Onsite Work Location: Pittsburgh, PA Duration: Permanent Note: No Remote Work, No C2C/C2H, No Visa Transfer, No Sponsorship… https://t.co/kHMHL6Y7Pp https://t.co/gTYJXzoFX9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: DESCRIPTION: Employer is seeking a SharePoint Developer to support a customer site in Springfield VA. Active TS/SCI clearance is required. The successful candidate will provide web development and technical support to the customer… https://t.co/q6HMfLk62B https://t.co/D43DFYXSnx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer/SharePoint Consultant, Junior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Troy, MI Job Type: Entry Level, Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 5/7/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our… https://t.co/OYBrGmI3KY https://t.co/ATGSEZJ4fA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer, Senior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Washington, DC Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 5/6/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients&amp;#8217; toughest… https://t.co/T4VnRlZuRc https://t.co/ESMulhGdzP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer, Mid: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Lexington Park, MD Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 4/25/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients&amp;#8217; toughest… https://t.co/cuDxGG5D8S https://t.co/ZCA5TLkjhl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Web Developer: PRIMARY PURPOSE: Under minimum supervision, this position is responsible for assisting in the discovery, development, implementation, and support of software applications across BSI, its affiliates and business units. Responsible for… https://t.co/z9FE0bauvQ https://t.co/i0yBRPFB0d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: Company Description For over 10 years, ABSc has provided world class consulting services with a fresh perspective. Our focused solutions are designed to meet the mission critical needs of our clients. We bring innovation and proven… https://t.co/kx52YGVfQd https://t.co/fyk6EPVsE5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Cloud Specialist: We are currently seeking a motivated, career and customer oriented O365/Point Cloud Specialist to join our team in Washington, DC to begin an exciting and challenging career with Unisys Federal Systems. The O365/Point Cloud… https://t.co/rGctAHeDbu https://t.co/Bngq2rRmXT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: SharePoint Developer Ref No.: 18-20192 Location: Santa Clara, California &amp;#8211; Minimum 10 years of SP development experience &amp;#8211; Excellent programming skills in SP platform (*******, Javascript, JQuery, CSS) &amp;#8211; Highly… https://t.co/cawKJxOYgh https://t.co/w2IqbgZVqH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: Imaginet is your trusted software technology partner who turns your business innovation ideas into reality. As a 10-time Microsoft Gold Partner, Imaginet specializes in SharePoint Consulting and Managed Services, Application… https://t.co/xk3fOuzZo3 https://t.co/vVCja2n6pg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager (SharePoint): Job Description PSI Title: Project Manager (SharePoint) Work Location: VA &amp;#8211; Arlington Description Essential Functions: Serves as the project manager for the task order and shall assist the Government Program Manager in… https://t.co/nX6XOEzNjZ https://t.co/9ZV8wLgxeE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer: PRIMARY PURPOSE: Under minimum supervision, this position is responsible for assisting in the discovery, development, implementation, and support of software applications across BSI, its affiliates and business units. Responsible for full… https://t.co/8gXRBzBx7C https://t.co/BsKIkJ7bzI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Specialist: *We are unable to sponsor for this permanent Full time role* Prestigious Global Firm is currently seeking a SharePoint Professional with both administration and development skills. Candidate will be building, supporting and… https://t.co/n29AHneFxK https://t.co/0DdX5ML7ux]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: SharePoint Developer Ref No.: 18-18258 Location: Plano, Texas Job Title : SharePoint Developer Location : Plano, TX Duration : 12 Months Job Description : Responsible for specific architecture and technology decisions such as… https://t.co/YTcXRBUcCR https://t.co/hrK6BDni2p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sharepoint Web Developer I: point Web Developer I Description at Advocate Health Care Skip Navigation Menu Jobs By City &amp;#8211; Algonquin Jobs &amp;#8211; Arlington Heights Jobs &amp;#8211; Aurora Jobs &amp;#8211; Barrington Jobs &amp;#8211; Bartlett Jobs &amp;#8211;… https://t.co/JhPaxRNPq4 https://t.co/LceA1rIkOo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sharepoint developer: Sharepoint developer Ref No.: 18-19985 Location: Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania Job Title: Sharepoint developer Onsite Work Location: Pittsburgh, PA Duration: Permanent Note: No Remote Work, No C2C/C2H, No Visa Transfer, No Sponsorship… https://t.co/BBbIVJ65g8 https://t.co/pAfFcud1lT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer/SharePoint Consultant, Junior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Troy, MI Job Type: Entry Level, Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 5/7/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our… https://t.co/iSEneSpMCI https://t.co/v3pa87nKGH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer, Mid: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Lexington Park, MD Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 4/25/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients&amp;#8217; toughest… https://t.co/TC0wq9OzgA https://t.co/LWFnb6Ju2t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Web Developer: SharePoint Web Developer ======================== Req #: ******Location: Washington, DC USJob Category: Information TechnologySecurity Clearance: SecretClearance Status: Must Be Current Job Description CACI is seeking a… https://t.co/7FBjgLTYRK https://t.co/7UHi4mZCY7]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>