<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Kinds of Strategy Consulting Firms to Avoid  http://t.co/pnkZtpmc2h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you wish to grow thinner, diminish your dinner. - Henry Sambrooke Leigh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We thought you was a toad! - Delmar, O Brother Where Art Thou?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Matrimony: An Institution of learning in which a man loses his "Bachelor's Degree" and his wife acquires a "Masters"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Who is The Grass Roots Classic Rock Group?  http://t.co/xJrbmgsvsJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Mountain Climbing - Best Mountains to Climb in the World!  http://t.co/4D7CD6aifL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fantasy is the impossible made probable. Science fiction is the improbable made possible.  - Rod Serling, creator of The Twilight Zone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome gardening t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the gardening lovers in your life!   http://t.co/GupT4IXh7x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one really knows who created Bitcoin - read about the fascinating history of Satoshi Nakamoto... http://t.co/NkMaoJR8gp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome ping pong t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the table tennis lovers in your life!   http://t.co/ikRGqi0ElG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn the Keys to Using LinkedIn for Your Company  http://t.co/qXcGm9w0he]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Men of lofty genius when they are doing the least work are most active. - Leonardo da Vinci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A college is a place where pebbles are polished and diamonds dimmed. - Robert Ingersoll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is the mark of an educated mind to be able to entertain a thought without accepting it. - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The probable reason some people get lost in thought is because it is unfamiliar territory to them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blow off some steam, or rather, shoot some smoke rings. The Zero Fog Blaster is a ray gun - totally cool!  http://t.co/4zTmj6srpk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SEO and Web Marketing – Harness the Power of Google Analytics  http://t.co/EFws88ipyQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take your time...don't live too fast, troubles will come and they will pass. - Simple Man - Lynyrd Skynyrd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What fun is it being cool if you can't wear a sombrero? --&gt; Bill Watterson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How To Grow Your Business With Twitter  http://t.co/1erJKMROtV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone can steer the ship when the sea is calm. - Publilius Syrus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helpful Tips for Web Marketing  http://t.co/84dzytrKm9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I had learned education I would not have had time to learn anything else. - Cornelius Vanderbilt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flattery, like perfume, should be smelled, not swallowed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to that hilarious sit-com Three’s Company - http://t.co/MjRNJRZIFN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conceit is a strange disease, it makes everyone sick but the one who has it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Tools for Finding Good Keywords  http://t.co/4ClZtwpYwY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Clash  http://t.co/JkcBMiuTC1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Habit is habit and not to be flung out of the window by any man, but coaxed downstairs a step at a time. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the history of the Modern Tennis Shoe  http://t.co/4oatSxZfEM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You gotta love the 80s and there was nothing better than the crazy fitness trends - http://t.co/fFZ6vueWJO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool just found these 25 Original Unopened Packs of Vintage Baseball Cards (80s-90s) - can find some value in there!  http://t.co/mX8VdD1luZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Joey Dee and the Starliters  http://t.co/ITQChOYQdS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For 45 cents, Americans deserve a postage stamp which tastes better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A little smile adds a good deal to a faces value]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pop culture is not about depth. It's about marketing, supply and demand, consumerism. - Trevor Dunn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The longer you're not taking action the more money you're losing - Carrie Wilkerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the math geek in your life - the math clock... http://t.co/qELJKi7WdM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow these Steps to Clean Your Credit  http://t.co/TfDcKBSWCg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I want to knock a story off the front page, I just change my hairstyle. --&gt; Hillary Rodham Clinton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Babysitter: a teenager who acts like a Grownup while grownups are acting like teenagers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must be the change you wish to see in the world. - Mahatma Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fascinating history of solar power - read on!  http://t.co/tKbB0w5pQO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome tennis t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the tennis lovers in your life!   http://t.co/Ttqy7ibWru]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction To http://t.co/RsYh4MByPY  http://t.co/GZMGG8UNYW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the History of the Hamburger  http://t.co/kpLnHBjlsn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Benefits of Going Green As A Business – Get Certified!  http://t.co/GPUQfBRfIX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What you don't know won't hurt you but it provides a lot amusement for other people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was born in 1950 and watched science fiction and horror movies on TV and was always really fascinated by them. - Rick Baker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What is Chronic Lyme Disease?  http://t.co/7hQAtEItHa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you wish to grow thinner, diminish your dinner. - Henry Sambrooke Leigh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of White Castle  http://t.co/kBEJY4LLKt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never realized how boring this game was.  - Homer Simpson while watching baseball while sober]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 11 - Waiting  http://t.co/jeS429GiBR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I had learned education I would not have had time to learn anything else. - Cornelius Vanderbilt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harness The Power of Twitter for Business to Business Internet Marketing  http://t.co/rXP8stmLqk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Evolution of the Wooden Clog  http://t.co/Q5rSWzUuI2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Selecting a Strategy Consulting Firm  http://t.co/Q08k56zeh1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for great resources on Beer?  Check out our top 10... http://t.co/DFwbQh6Gjc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Jackson Five  http://t.co/ITzvmTobFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a meat-eating world, wearing leather for shoes and even clothes, the discussion of fur is childish. --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His head is getting too big for his toupee...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Animals are such agreeable friends - they ask no questions, they pass no criticisms. - George Elliot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out Crimson Mine’s awesome Tumblr page... http://t.co/OWoCDqnOdi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome kayaking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the paddling lovers in your life!  http://t.co/leCzHFYx51]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I accidentally forgot to graduate from college.  - Anne Lamott]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing shocks me - I am a scientist. - Indiana Jones, Indiana Jones and the Temple of Doom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool Geek Tech - Mini USB Fan - Keep cool at your desk! --&gt; http://t.co/ZPj9u2QAy5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pessimist: A man who thinks that all woman are bad Optimist: A man who hopes so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's hard to win a pennant, but it's harder losing one. - Chuck Tanner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 7 - No Luck!  http://t.co/oAoujWhGw1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Habit is habit and not to be flung out of the window by any man, but coaxed downstairs a step at a time. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Meat Loaf  http://t.co/iNgW5Y7omd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 2 - Road Trip!!!  http://t.co/BgmK2o91MR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Breaking News - New Michael Jackson Song  http://t.co/A4VAgX3jc2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Donna Summer  http://t.co/RLwWV4dOrT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If man is a little lower than angels, then angels should reform.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't concentrate in flats! - Victoria Beckham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still have my feet on the ground, I just wear better shoes. - Oprah Winfrey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the Dos XX Most Interesting Man In the World - Top Quotes!  http://t.co/ZizXPLepXA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is like a poker game, nobody wants to quit when he's losing: nobody wants you to quit when you're ahead. - Jackie Robinson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like wrestling a gorilla- you don't quit when you're tired, you quit when the gorilla is tired - Robert Strauss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yo, dudes. Got a new tourney lined up. We're playing for the last of the deodorant sticks. Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greetings, programs! - Flynn, TRON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Kansas  http://t.co/vZVQgtp3XG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is not the most important thing in the world. Love is. Fortunately, I love money. - Jackie Mason]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The bird of paradise alights only upon the hand that does not grasp. - John Berry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dress shabbily and they remember the dress; dress impeccably and they remember the woman. --&gt; Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Little Richard  http://t.co/5jZnGO8TIj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep you can keep your devices charged via solar power - find out here - http://t.co/c8RMB6cY5w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He had a forward spring... And an early fall...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft: "You've got questions. We've got dancing paperclips."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gin and Titonic Ice Cube Tray - Add the Titanic To Your Drinks http://t.co/fZEeXgXNIX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Donna Summer  http://t.co/XTyipcaFZJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excuse me, miss, a little bit of your face is showing around your makeup - you might want to take care of that!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn Baseball Lingo  http://t.co/ebkvNgLMVi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have heard of Bitcoin?  Read these 10 important things you should know... http://t.co/ewZG7fObu0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A baseball game is simply a nervous breakdown divided into nine innings. - Earl Wilson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Evolution of the Wooden Clog  http://t.co/Q5rSWzUuI2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These Yoda Lights Must You Have!  Wonderful Geek Gear! http://t.co/qfVfEinQOX]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>