<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Business has only two functions - marketing and innovation. - Milan Kundera]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Rufus  http://t.co/RECIuToccI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the history of the Modern Tennis Shoe  http://t.co/hHNIXADtdc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Paul McCartney and Wings  http://t.co/GcxmWlrc59]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The crashes people remember, but drivers remember the near misses. - Mario Andretti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'll forgive me, Madam President, if I don't wish to be executed based solely on your... gut feeling. - Doctor Gaius Baltar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Courage is not the absence of fear, but rather the judgment that something else is more important than fear - Ambrose Redmoon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bird does not sing because it has an answer...  It sings because it has a song. - Chinese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give a girl the right shoes, and she can conquer the world. - Marilyn Monroe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the The Early History of Beer  http://t.co/Tc7C90CYBz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, I'm from Iowa. I only work in outer space. - Kirk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We broke something, I think it was traction --  - Carl Edwards after getting spun out by Dale Jr. at Michigan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I want to knock a story off the front page, I just change my hairstyle. --&gt; Hillary Rodham Clinton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this very cool bed fan - cools right under the covers! http://t.co/5qhCZpg7UH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Some Very Interesting and Unusual Beers  http://t.co/6qtfsM7wRc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Powerful Tools For Your Internet Marketing Program    http://t.co/5JU6YOQpYD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's hard to shake hands  with a clenched fist!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need to be able to rock out.  - Bryan Adams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Management is nothing more than motivating other people. - Le Iacocca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My dad is a marketing mastermind. - Serena Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caring For Your New Garage Floors  http://t.co/ShS6NxBEH2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Genesis  http://t.co/WQpwxqaRpt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Great Tips from Web Marketing Experts  http://t.co/Bj2xiDpWOy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's recording techniques would have been regarded as science fiction forty years ago. - Tony Visconti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame Quakecraft: FAILURE IS AN OPTION!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! http://t.co/Oc7jaNN8BA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 2 - Road Trip!!!  http://t.co/e1nRXzGXSr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can a guy win a game if you don't give him any runs? - Robert Bo Belinsky after Losing 15 - 0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space Invaders Video Game - Men's Silk Necktie - Cool! http://t.co/xMxs3bIvB6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Major Shoe Retailers  http://t.co/GSxyy6tp7i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science fiction is no more written for scientists than ghost stories are written for ghosts. - Brian W. Aldiss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Star Trek Enterprise Pizza Cutter! http://t.co/wDyuxHkMCg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't preach a boy about his problems. Just remind him that you, too , were a Nincompoop at his age.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How to Select Best Climbing Equipment  http://t.co/z4Gg1uRPph]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I'm not back in five minutes, just wait longer. - Ace Ventura, Ace ventura, Pet Detective]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Jackson Browne  http://t.co/kZDbjLp4px]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helpful Hints for Web Building from the Experts  http://t.co/e7f5hJlMNt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Jimmy Choo  http://t.co/A6EnPxkheE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The key to wisdom is a knowledge of our own ignorance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You maniacs! You blew it up! Oh, damn you! Damn you all to hell! - Taylor, Planet of the Apes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool 14' Iceberg For Your Pool or the Lake! http://t.co/tB77V7MV01]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a world without fences and walls, who needs Gates and Windows?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To achieve anything in this game you must be prepare to dabble in the boundary of disaster. - Sterling Moss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Barbara Mason  http://t.co/5S8rm8aVM8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Sword Umbrella - Eye Catching http://t.co/YbwhgnpdDC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Chilled Stones to Keep Your Drink Cool - Milled in Vermont http://t.co/NgbnTLWD44]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yah! I'm on the "Starts tomorrow" diet!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strikeouts are boring - besides that, they're fascist. Throw some ground balls. More democratic. - Bull Durham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Mountain Biking – A Real Adventure  http://t.co/yp2KzXDH6y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Little by little does the trick. - Aesop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The client is not always right. - Enzo Ferrari]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am convinced that every boy, in his heart, would rather steal second base than an automobile. - Thomas Campbell Clark]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money was never a big motivation for me, except as a way to keep score. The real excitement is playing the game. - Donald Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love making money, but you can't live your life waiting to get rich in a job that no longer feeds you artistically. Julianna Margulies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A shoe without sex appeal is as barren as a tree without leaves. - Rita De Acosta Lydig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool Batman Comfy Throw - Stay Warm and Cool :&gt;)  http://t.co/LiqjWyWfEX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I didn't have a big fat Greek wedding, but I have a lot of fat Greek friends. Pete Sampras]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flattery, like perfume, should be smelled, not swallowed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The designated hitter rule is like letting someone else take Wilt Chamberlain's free throws. - Rick Wise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of Little House on The Prairie Episode - "In the Big Inning"  http://t.co/KrlylqPmdN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of the animals except for man know that the principle business of life is to enjoy it. - Samuel Butler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My name is Inigo Montoya. You killed my father. Prepare to die! - Inigo, The Princess Bride]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm on a 90-day wonder diet. Thus far, I've lost 45 days. - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Foreigner  http://t.co/IN1x8JT7Vj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel like punching the boss' jaw again  "Did you say again?" "Yes, I felt like doing it once before today!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are 10 types of people in the world: those who understand binary, and those who don't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Egotism is the Knack of seeing desirable qualities in yourself that others can't see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriousness is stupidity sent to college. P. J. O'Rourke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Locate Your Garage Space Before Installation Of Cabinets  http://t.co/pYuZwwKGQe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Little House on the Prairie – An American Classic TV Series  http://t.co/w9ZwFwlxK1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good introduction to Minecraft Mods - http://t.co/Ol6SrLHuft]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the parents of a Little Leaguer, a baseball game is simply a nervous breakdown into innings. - Earl Wilson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fool and his money are never without friends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the shoe fits... buy it in every color.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone has a rock bottom.  - Prince]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sorry. You are right. Those pants don't make you look fat. - Jin-Soo Kwon  The only three things a woman needs to hear! - Sawyer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The process of growing old is a question of mind over matter. If you don't mind, it doesn't matter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read The History of the Beau Brummels  http://t.co/S4DQpUaBUa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People who enjoy what they are doing invariably do it well. - Joe Gibbs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who wish to sing, always find a song. - Swedish Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Magic texting glove with conductive yarn finger tips for iPhone, iPad and all touch screen devices - 4 colors  --&gt; http://t.co/HJjSEO8qke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blow off some steam, or rather, shoot some smoke rings. The Zero Fog Blaster is a ray gun - totally cool!  http://t.co/tMnpP6kKwU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man has never really tested his strength until he tries to lift a mortgage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Cascades  http://t.co/MkanswifdS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science fiction is not predictive; it is descriptive. - Ursula K. LeGuin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't care half so much about making money as I do about making my point, and coming out ahead. Cornelius Vanderbilt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Battleship Memorial Park – Mobile Alabama – A Great Historical Experience  http://t.co/UmYIqc2ETo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The right man is the one who seizes the moment. - Johann Wolfgang von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The law gives a man the right to open his wife's mail, but not the nerve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Samsung Galaxy Gear Watch  http://t.co/9nLqBSusAP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating Famous and Historical Watches  http://t.co/tvcfwNoqmX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Genesis  http://t.co/WQpwxqaRpt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only those who risk going too far can possibly find out how far one can go. - T.S. Eliot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With four pairs of shoes I can travel the world. - Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Leapy Lee the Classic Rock Artist?  http://t.co/YRtXKYJczt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Libby: How'd you get shot, anyway? Sawyer: With a gun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope I didn't bore you too much with my life story.  - Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For 45 cents, Americans deserve a postage stamp which tastes better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I led the league in Go get 'em next time." - Bob Uecker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A philosopher is someone who knows what to do until it happens to him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Pat Benatar  http://t.co/nJwBEVleSu]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>