<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is beautiful. Love is wonderful. Love is everything. Do you agree? –Ray in "Princess and the Frog"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's just our luck we're stuck together. Nobody else but you. – Goofy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look at the world, so close, and I'm halfway to it. Look at it all, so big, do I even dare? –Rapunzel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/7k7z45Numi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes friends are family too. –Snow White in Disney Hallmark]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's so cute http://t.co/OzYNqnz6Ry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's because I like you, I don't want to be with you. It's a complicated emotion. –Marlin (Finding Nemo)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/fQZnHZanqy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't be so hard on yourself. Everyone makes mistakes. –Belle in "Belle's Magical World"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give him something from your heart. It will be more precious than anything you could buy. –Fairy Godmother in "Princess Stories"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your heart will lead you where you belong. Your heart will lead you home. –Tigger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow my friends @ladopeshop badass Fashion &amp; accessories Made in USA, LOS ANGELES CA. have you read your labels? Is it made in the #USA ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don’t want that to go that way. I don’t want to forget. –Dory (Finding Nemo)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life without worry? You seek hakuna matata. –Rafiki (The Lion King 1½)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m so hungry. I could eat a whole elephant. –Rolly (101 Dalmatians)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The way you laugh is just the best. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An act of true love will thaw a frozen heart. –Olaf (Frozen)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't you understand, Tink? You mean more to me than anything in this whole world. –Peter Pan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/BChQZ6G9ch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lara_mullen I'd love to! Lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/sLjIt4nyBq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I choose you, Aladdin. –Jasmine in "Aladdin"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only way to achieve the impossible is to believe it is possible. –Charles in "Alice in Wonderland"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You’ll love me at once, the way you did once upon a dream. –Aurora in "Sleeping Beauty"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd get over losing anything, but I'll never get over losing you. –Toy Story 1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop taking everything so seriously. –Mother Gothel (Tangled)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fake reputation is all a man has. –Flynn Rider (Tangled)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fantasy and reality often overlap. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things are not as bad as they seem. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As you go through life you'll see, there is so much that we don't understand. –Simba (The Lion King II)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'll be alright. We're together now. Everything's going to be fine. You'll see. –Belle (Beauty and the Beast)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/ioZ9Ywqwis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/enrD60K7RW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/h9vnzsI9hP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once you love someone, they stay in your heart forever. –Nita  in "Brother Bear 2"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing can go wrong if everything is right, and everything is right somehow. – Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a world of laughter, a world of tears. It's a world of hopes, and a world of fears. – It’s A Small World "]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You know how men are. They think that "No" means "Yes" and "Get lost" means "Take me, I'm yours". –Megara in "Hercules"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I listened earlier, I wouldn't be here. But that's just the trouble with me. –Alice in "Alice in Wonderland"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don’t be the monster they fear you are. –Hans in  "Frozen"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goodbye? Oh, no, please. Can’t we go back to page one and do it all over again? –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you keep on believing, the dreams that you wish will come true. –Cinderella]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ladopeshop: Handcrafted in Los Angeles. #madeinusa http://t.co/nbFwLfGcGh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can’t give you anything but love. –Minnie Mouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Without trust, there can be no relationship. –Mushu in "Mulan II"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friends stick to you like honey. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't run away from your troubles. There ain't no place that far. –Uncle Remus in "Song of the South"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That’s the real trouble with the world. Too many people grow up. They forget. - Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is my reflection someone I don't know? –Mulan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing’s too good for a friend. –Tigger in"Book of Pooh"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's the circle of life, and it moves us all through despair and hope, through faith and love. –The Lion King]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey, let’s play a game. It’s called “see who can be quiet the longest.” Carl in " Up"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When we work together, things are always better. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes the smallest thing can make the biggest changes of all. –Plio  in "Dinosaur"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/VRAsNsXDeh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bambi: “I'll never forget any of you.” 

Thumper: “Of course not. Can't forget your bestest friend.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes a little thing can be quite important. –Mary Poppins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never met someone who thinks so much like me. –Anna "Frozen"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buzz Lightyear: “Whatever happens, at least we’ll be together.”
Woody: “For infinity and beyond.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you are what you eat, then I only want to eat the good stuff. –Remy in "Ratatouille"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When life gets you down, you know what you gotta do? Just keep swimming, just keep swimming. –Dory "Finding Nemo"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Miracles are real but they need someone to believe, so they can happen. – Disney Fairies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I were truly to be myself, I would break my family's heart. – Mulan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of my favorite villains! http://t.co/EpqfCHFJD6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We LOVE her! #tinkerbell http://t.co/i5lc08kukc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/5KHl7qSqXw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cinderellas dress http://t.co/AX9xPbndwb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bambi! http://t.co/sfsZg3j0mz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ariel: “You’ve gotta get away from here.” | Prince Eric: “No, I won’t leave you.” –The Little Mermaid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/dmim3Ui9xK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You've stolen me. And I'm here to take meself back. –Jack Sparrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No owner means no heartbreak. –Lotso in "Toy Story 3"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I shouldn't ask for more. I've got so many things I should be thankful for. –Rapunzel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dreams are stronger than doubts, courage is my more powerful than fear, and nothing is greater than love. –Ariel in "Princess Stories"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you truly believe that you write the tale of your own life, then the end is up to you. – Mickey Mouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eat, drink and be merry, and tomorrow we diet. – Goofy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't undo what's been done. It's done. –Innoko in "Brother Bear 2"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What you give is what you get. –Tiana in "Princess and the Frog"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't care, as long as I'm with you. –Mowgli in "The Jungle Book"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you can’t say something nice, don’t say nothing at all. –Thumper in Bambi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christopher: “Forever and ever is a very long time.” 
Pooh: “Forever isn't long at all when I’m with you.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm wishing for the one I love to find me today. I'm hoping and I'm dreaming of the nice things he'll say. –Snow White]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/A0JaAGRQWj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can get it if you really want, but you must try, try, and try. You’ll succeed at last. –Sebastian in The Little Mermaid Series]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/TOrUFsvyM8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/wReDJ8KAvp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[aww! we do! http://t.co/jUZeQLw3Ux]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[oh but i already am! http://t.co/YmgaSeGhWv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/MJ5WRCrho2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[so they say... http://t.co/IwpGRaArxn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where one thing falls, another grows. Maybe not what was there before, but something new and wonderful all the same. –  Bambi’s Mother]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/HwauouQ8xa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your lips say “I don't care”, but your eyes say “I do care”. –Tawni (Sonny with a Chance)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[❤❤❤ http://t.co/ceciDEMz8a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anna: “Can I just say something crazy?? ” - Hans: “I love crazy!” –Frozen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/hAyFWl2rNv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know, I am so romantic. Sometimes I think I should just marry myself. –Mike in "Monster Inc"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/YrdIS7C64W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're dead if you aim only for kids. Adults are only kids grown up, anyway. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Buzz his crazy.. http://t.co/JqOL8yOfhV]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>