<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Javascript Engineer: Santa Monica, CA Full-time $140k – $175k Posted Today Are you a Senior Javascript Engineer who believes that "being healthy" is achievable for every US household? If so, read on… We are a team of serial social entrepreneurs &amp;… https://t.co/OXwOXcyuxL https://t.co/sKu5KZR4JZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best photos from the Tonys red carpet: See what celebrities wore at this year's Tony Awards in New York. https://t.co/D8jrAXdr63 https://t.co/pkPZzuYI98]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Drools Developer: Java Drools Developer Ref No.: 18-21594 Location: troy, Michigan Hello, Hope you are doing great… This is Vishal from Enterprise Solution Inc. and I am writing to you regarding an excellent job opportunity based out of. Position:… https://t.co/D3aH617iL3 https://t.co/Ao4mtVsosE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Software Engineer: Java Software Engineer Enter job title or location Search menu open clear text Search jobs Recent Searches – Deloitte home – About Deloitte – Job cart – Location: United States – Global (English) English Available in 145 locations… https://t.co/Blg71VxfKr https://t.co/dLZtVz1uYo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Fool Trade': Trump continues to rip G7 in tweetstorm: US President Donald Trump continued to excoriate his Group of 7 summit allies in a series of tweets from Singapore, where he is due to meet North Korean leader Kim Jong Un in a historic summit Tuesday. https://t.co/tpnm4fCvrz https://t.co/LYxLtDpdDo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NEW DEV! – Senior Lead Java Software Engineer – AMAZON ALEXA Machine Learning Te: Job Description NEW DEV! – Senior Lead Java Software Engineer – AMAZON ALEXA Machine Learning Team – ************************** Job ID ****** Location US-MA-Cambridge… https://t.co/jfNQKSUHFL https://t.co/3cfG6zIj4M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Lead/ Architect: Java Lead/ Architect Ref No.: 18-25313 Location: Minneapolis, Minnesota Position: Java Lead/ Architect Location: Minneapolis, MN SDLC Backend Development Coach description notes: – Hands on Architect/Lead Developer to focus on the… https://t.co/RHp0J1RRVH https://t.co/lu9vig37D4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java: Java Ref No.: 18-21535 Location: Sunnyvale, California Experience with programming in Java Experience developing front end technologies Proficient in J2EE, Struts 2.0, Spring, Hibernate, JQuery.Excellent knowledge of Relational Databases, SQL and… https://t.co/34TOzrtyn6 https://t.co/XIl7oSJbaA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Developer – Full Stack Java: Do you have what it takes to become part of a winning team that strives for pushing boundaries? We highly promote creative thinking that helps all involved get to the solution. We offer a trendy productive environment… https://t.co/YAsAwAVu2Y https://t.co/EI6Jd9x8se]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From real estate to diplomacy, Trump chases the ultimate deal: Donald Trump had made up his mind. https://t.co/KyUFRKwdRu https://t.co/R3cX4PVGZq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Command &amp; Conquer' mobile game wants in on that 'Clash of Clans' money: If you were looking for a full-scale return of the Command &amp; Conquer franchise, this probably isn't it. During the EA Play presentation at E3, the publisher revealed the new mobile… https://t.co/ikW6k5Kx0t https://t.co/pCzN6DM9KT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Software Engineer, Senior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Herndon, VA Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 5/16/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management… https://t.co/NfIH2zHQKb https://t.co/bgkfzJA8G6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java-Developer: Java Developer Populus Group seeks a Java Developer in Columbus, OH to design, develop, test, and maintain enterprise software applications for the financial industry utilizing object oriented design, Java, GitHub, Maven, Jenkins, JSON,… https://t.co/voAY5adibk https://t.co/GnMfKTwVjn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer (Java Spring) – Detroit: ABOUT US TribalScale is an innovation firm that brings organizations – from the startup to the enterprise – into the future. We build digital products, transform teams, and grow startups. Were… https://t.co/1CHFfZ03RF https://t.co/3lQPkAY2yG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tech Lead Full Stack Java: Responsibilities * Partner with Product Owners and Scrum Masters to optimize implementation of agile practices on client projects * Serve as the primary technical point of contact for multiple full stack development teams *… https://t.co/cz9e3m9iMh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[APPLICATIONS ENGINEER – JAVA: APPLICATIONS ENGINEER – JAVA ============================ Req #: ******Location: Fort Meade, MD USJob Category: EngineeringSecurity Clearance: TS/SCI with PolygraphClearance Status: Must Be Current Job Description As a… https://t.co/0V3lftcMkF https://t.co/vY4xmZ31YX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Specialist Developer – File Transfer Services (Java/Python): TECHNOLOGY SERVICES GROUP (TSG) is the central infrastructure services group with a proven track record of innovating to help BNY Mellon and its customers have most reliable, nimble and… https://t.co/Xmxnfh76Hr https://t.co/6uCxqxB1Zw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook reportedly sold user data to businesses in secret deals: Contrary to Facebook's claims that it cut off developer access to its user data back in 2015, the Wall Street Journal has discovered that the company has allowed certain third party… https://t.co/6Dcu1FORnp https://t.co/oXa0tutFR4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone paid $28 million for this chair: On June 20, Christie's New York will offer a wood-and-brass armchair upholstered with calfskin at its summer design auction. The 90-year-old "Transat" armchair, designed by the late Irish architect and designer… https://t.co/Wf91Hdos2f https://t.co/6PVCLz2bf3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TIME magazine cover depicts Trump as a king: Panelists discuss the latest Time magazine cover, which features an illustration of President Donald Trump gazing at a reflection of himself in which he's dressed up as a monarch, complete with a jeweled crown… https://t.co/pPMePrgaC4 https://t.co/OSfq4TLcY1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Software Engineer – Cyber Security Computer Software Company: SENIOR JAVA SOFTWARE ENGINEER Austin, TX Currently seeking an Austin based Senior Software Engineer to work with a profitable computer software company specialized in IT security… https://t.co/xEMq87ag77 https://t.co/f5fUcrOYg2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Application Developer: Job Title : Java Application Developer Job ID : ******BR Location : IL – Buffalo Grove Street Address : 2100 E. Lake Cook Rd. Category : Information Systems Description : Job Description As a Java Application Developer, you… https://t.co/rT9Oyb9HmP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JAVA DEVELOPER: JAVA DEVELOPER for BAE SYSTEMS in Reston, VA(map) Senior Java Software Engineer with a minimum of nine (9) years experience. Require competence in business applications design, database management, and use of programming languages. The… https://t.co/espOEnPhwj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Java Developer Spring, REST API, Unix, RDBMS, Maven): Critical, highly visible opportunity for a talented developer with strong product sensibilities and lead mindset / capabilities to drive the design of new platform for Enterprise Financial… https://t.co/4lDrVayVXY https://t.co/VGbC7jXcPI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Java Tech Lead: Albertsons-Safeway Company is one of the largest food and drug retailers with 2,300+ stores. The Albertsons-Safeway family of brands includes some of the most prominent brands in food retailing, with a growing base of loyal shoppers.… https://t.co/xasSq69G8A https://t.co/fL3dVuY7nA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Java /JS Developer (Application Development): Candidate will support agile based application development activities including creating technical design from business requirements and test driven development for eligibility &amp; enrollment and… https://t.co/yKEASmAAEK https://t.co/AXwTq2Y87e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump is dressed as a king on the new Time magazine cover https://t.co/wRYWxHAb1e https://t.co/E084xKFBQU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chip and Joanna Gaines' company fined by EPA: The Environmental Protection Agency is taking issue with the stars of a hit HGTV show after noticing issues with lead paint in some episodes. https://t.co/7ULDKYzX62 https://t.co/gHPFqDGAsY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer II/III – Java (contract): The client requires candidates to be a US Permanent Resident or have US citizenship. Individuals who require employment sponsorship will not be considered due to the nature of their industry. Current client,… https://t.co/450YBQYP8Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Angular Developer: The selected candidate will gain experience designing, developing, and maintaining software applications, data integration services, and proof of concepts. The selected candidate will be working on a large-scale, software… https://t.co/KumxcvLTMy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Dancing doctor' defends music videos, says patients asked for them: An Atlanta-area dermatologist is defending her appearance singing and dancing in videos during surgical procedures, saying the videos were recorded at her patients' requests to… https://t.co/1spHE6gvrx https://t.co/RPi0xl7GrJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some questions for the guy selling more than 20,000 films for $1 million: Who does this, who has the time? How did eBay seller Adam "kilamad" Malik manage the stunning feat of collecting some 21,000 rare, out of print, 4K, Blu-ray, HD-DVD, DVD,… https://t.co/3UrSrwXVvL https://t.co/w3hkD6QZNb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Fullstack Developer: Java Fullstack Developer Ref No.: 18-24001 Location: ATLANTA, Georgia Hi, Hope you are doing well Enterprise Solution Inc. is currently looking to fill urgent full-time permanent job positions as Java Fullstack Developer with… https://t.co/0PWTMUYJi7 https://t.co/f0qwBGfXYk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: MetroStar Systems Careers ========================= Java Developer Web Development Bethesda, Maryland Apply MetroStar Systems is looking for a Senior Software Developer that is passionate about building procurement and financial… https://t.co/FUCqxktyfw https://t.co/3tszcfv67H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer III: Job Description Employee Perks Why You Will Love Being Part of the Navy Federal Team: *Competitive compensation with opportunities for annual raises, promotions, and bonus potential *Best-in-Class Benefits! (7% 401k match / Pension… https://t.co/4BHKaNOvZk https://t.co/Pz2L3zSFb2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Self-driving cars. Scooters. The future of commuting to work is here https://t.co/WfevK07ePL https://t.co/gRrHxQqxX6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: To provide senior level system analysis, design, development, and implementation of applications and databases for mainframe-, client/server-, Web-, and/or PC-based systems for Investment Systems. Technology Stack: Must haves: Java… https://t.co/MYyhBUQ8Q8 https://t.co/hyb4zwc3a9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FULL STACK JAVA DEVELOPER: Job TitleFULL STACK JAVA DEVELOPER – ID:30696 Duration6 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsFULL STACK JAVA DEVELOPER LocationNew Jersey, NJ Date Posted01/04/2018 FULL STACK JAVA DEVELOPER Location: New Jersey, NJ 07059 Duration:… https://t.co/pIOhZq7Vzn https://t.co/FpPKe3l7kh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America may soon face its biggest labor strike in decades https://t.co/UtpQji4eTM https://t.co/Ksa578woIZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Software Engineer I/II ( C++, Java, Unix): Sr Software Engineer I/II ( C++, Java, Unix) Skip Navigation Raytheon – Cyber – News – What We Do – Who We Are – Global – Investors – Careers – Visit:Cyber – Who We Are – Leaders – Businesses – Corporate… https://t.co/VkZLn87UDF https://t.co/hQfAGSTTQI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer/Engineer: OUR COMPANY Employer Corporation is the worlds number one independent provider of data integration software. Thousands of enterprises worldwide depend on Employer data integration, data quality, and big data solutions to… https://t.co/LmImNNfHzb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jake Tapper: Trump lied about the Eagles: CNN's Jake Tapper breaks down President Donald Trump's decision to cancel the White House visit for the NFL Super Bowl champion, the Philadelphia Eagles. https://t.co/bjlnKSVItB https://t.co/SihVEpMhgn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Orange is the New Black’ season six will debut July 27th: Netflix announced today that Orange is the New Black will return for its sixth season on July 27th. In a teaser for the season, which you can watch below, we see Litchfield Penitentiary in a… https://t.co/y6LgrSnjvK https://t.co/KMfAPZ1dVg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Java Engineer: Job Description Our Team: Technology drives our business. Our team is made up of talented software engineers, infrastructure engineers, leaders and UX professionals. We care about technology as a craft and a differentiator. We bring… https://t.co/eVj03NSvTU https://t.co/0wkPBMhBSp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Full Stack Developer: Java Full Stack Developer Ref No.: 18-20249 Location: NYC, New York Position: Java Full Stack Developer Location: NYC, NY Duration : Full-time/Perm No C2C/C2H, No Sponsorship, No Remote/Telecommute Job Description: – 4 years’… https://t.co/mB8FHWVdeH https://t.co/yAl44GuIi2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fox News ripped for misleading photos of Eagles players kneeling https://t.co/52eGYuKGUJ https://t.co/BssJI4Q90f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Engineer – C++/Java: Job Description Software Development Engineer – C++/Java (15826) Introduction: We are seeking a Software Development Engineer to join a close-knit prototyping team developing capabilities that enable warfighters… https://t.co/mBe1MMVp6N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Java Developer: Washington, DC Full-time $120k – $160k Posted Today If you are a Java Developer with experience and a TS/SCI Security Clearance, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us – Fast-paced, challenging, and innovative environment… https://t.co/NKmTR8gR5k https://t.co/CtwmURucyH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Careers Center | Java Developer Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome page Returning Candidate?… https://t.co/JEynvEvpBl https://t.co/hovDlh27qL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former DIA officer charged with attempting to send national defense information to China: A former Defense Intelligence Agency officer is being charged with allegedly attempting to send national defense information to China. https://t.co/SzIW57O6zC https://t.co/SFs0KXkYl8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple's Podcasts app is coming to watchOS: If you love Serial or This American Life, good news: Apple is bringing its homegrown podcasts app to watchOS. That means if you're cycling, or out on a run, you can stay safe and control everything from your… https://t.co/tDAoPd1Owz https://t.co/hfGAbAB5Qw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supreme Court wipes away ruling about undocumented teen's access to abortion: A unanimous Supreme Court issued an order Monday that attempts to diffuse a controversial issue concerning an undocumented teen in US custody who sought an abortion last fall. https://t.co/H5mQPrBEEA https://t.co/LzeedTmSQW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[iOS 12 lets parents limit kids’ screen time: Amid attention that kids are spending more and more time on screens, cutely termed "smartphone addiction, Apple made parental controls a priority this year. In March, the company launched a website containing… https://t.co/wjScntNIus https://t.co/OkgjdjU7a4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JAVA DEVELOPER: JAVA DEVELOPER Ref No.: 18-20476 Location: Mountain View, Illinois Job Description: https://t.co/sw9i1UAjyZ developer – JAX-RS – Java API for RESTful Web Services -Wilmington – Delaware 2. core java developer – SQL Server- Mc Lean –… https://t.co/dTEcp4Ufqx https://t.co/BK0JOge6HU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer 2 (Java): The Asurion’s Back Office Gateway IT team has created critical enterprise applications to support Asurion global billing, tax calculations and other functions, which are essential for business innovations and customer… https://t.co/yRUOUrCv7s https://t.co/Ctwn7UXNhw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, JavaScript (Node.js): Who You Are: You’re an upbeat, creative, fun loving engineer looking for an opportunity in an exciting, fast paced, growing startup. You like working in teams but are also excellent at working on your own. You… https://t.co/y4RTROiyLF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tech Lead Full Stack Java: Responsibilities * Partner with Product Owners and Scrum Masters to optimize implementation of agile practices on client projects * Serve as the primary technical point of contact for multiple full stack development teams *… https://t.co/TPgE0305Cx https://t.co/AQSNXymGvJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Cloud Dockers Consultant: Java Cloud Dockers Consultant Ref No.: 18-20306 Location: San Jose, California Job Title: Senior Java Cloud Dockers Consultant Location: San Jose, CA Duration: Fulltime / Permanent (or) Contract Job Description: – Java… https://t.co/4OfE3jz2dL https://t.co/8loW6wCF1b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Assoc Engineer, Software (Java, Open Source, and Network Mgmt.): Job Description Job Description Assoc Engineer, Software (Java, Open Source, and Network Mgmt.) Description The Technology Software Engineer will work with a team of other software… https://t.co/yMh3xKbiMe https://t.co/xxyQiPU8A1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: UNABLE TO WORK WITH 3RD PARTY AGENCIES LOCAL CANDIDATES ONLY UNABLE TO SPONSOR H1BS AT THIS TIME We are looking for a full stack engineer who feels strongly about delivering good software but also about running software in the real world.… https://t.co/aZ91ktjjuA https://t.co/xYGfS9zVVe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[java Developer: java Developer Ref No.: 18-20285 Location: FLORHAM PARK, New Jersey PPosition: java Developer Location: FLORHAM PARK, NJ Essential Skills, Experience with Spring, Spring MVC, Hibernate, web services – REST/SOAP, JMS, JPA, MDB, CXF,… https://t.co/RkqrfDbKik https://t.co/YTwEvbKWGs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Engineer – C++/Java: Job Description Software Development Engineer – C++/Java (15826) Introduction: We are seeking a Software Development Engineer to join a close-knit prototyping team developing capabilities that enable warfighters… https://t.co/G5tyRxUsZk https://t.co/iwrRVaIMMW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Selenium Engineer with Java: Selenium Engineer with Java Ref No.: 18-20614 Location: Jersey City, New Jersey Position :Selenium Engineer with Java Duration : Full Time Permanent Location : Blue Ash, OH Description: Mandatory Technical / Functional Skills… https://t.co/gJ0sXzkdYH https://t.co/WUpY9M1BAv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Barista, Java Del Mar, Part Time: Greets, prepares, services, and takes guests’ orders for beverages and/or food in a friendly, courteous, professional and timely manner to ensure total guest satisfaction. Upsells additional items to enhance… https://t.co/9XFHFS4AY9 https://t.co/GdTeKTZvXQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jr. Java Developer: – At least 3 years of experience working in Java, J2EE, Java Script – Strong communication skill is must – Experience with Agile Scrum Methodology Job Type: Full-time Experience: – Java: 3 years 2 hours ago – save job Please review… https://t.co/6JKGpljeFg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[java developer: java developer Ref No.:18-09540 Location: Dear born, Michigan Start Date: 05/24/2018 Title: Java Developer Location: Dearborn – MI Type Of Employment- Contract Must Have Skills: – Spring Boot; Java (Spring) – Experience building… https://t.co/AVGLfDEcbg https://t.co/84EHugEJAt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why working from home could increase your tax bill https://t.co/7kcza11cDv https://t.co/dFWbdvAWuW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Java/MicroServices: Your user session will timeout in 5 minutes. Please click OK to continue with your application. Sr. Java/MicroServices Tracking Code 121-****** Job Description Position Highlights: – Recognized leader: Rated #1 Prepaid Wireless… https://t.co/S7HzVLGDSv https://t.co/SuOqzSHGb5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: Software Developers at Redflex are part of a community that design and create leading edge solutions that make our cities and our lives more green, safer and smarter. We take a whole team approach to software quality, following… https://t.co/AJqas6Syfi https://t.co/0mnmDJySGl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Ref No.: 18-20267 Location: Phoenix, Arizona Position: Java Developer Location: Phoenix AZ Duration: Long Term Contract Job Description: Need strong experience in Java Development with Spring, Rest services https://t.co/LG5I28RzJZ https://t.co/rhJ4quc9RP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 'insanely good' food of Hong Kong: Anthony Bourdain indulges in Hong Kong's unique and inviting cuisine. Watch Parts Unknown Sundays at 9PM ET/PT on CNN. https://t.co/02TX3GkEHG https://t.co/ZkRFG3zvQU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java/PHP Developer: SUNDIAL SOFTWARE IS CURRENTLY RECRUITING FOR A JAVA/PHP DEVELOPER FOR A DIRECT-HIRE OPPORTUNITY. SENIOR DEVELOPER / ANALYST DESCRIPTION Our client is seeking to fill the position of Senior Developer/Analyst. The Senior… https://t.co/fflXVXRtl6 https://t.co/JRuvYDSwa2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China's NetEase invests $100 million in Bungie to make new games: Bungie, the studio behind hits like Halo, Myth and Destiny, has announced a new deal with Chinese online gaming company NetEase to "build new worlds and invite players, new and old, to… https://t.co/izvibLLQwQ https://t.co/f7o0wbFZDo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Java Engineer – Atlanta, GA: Back to search results Search by Keyword or Job ID More Search Options Search by Location or Country Search by Postal Code (US ONLY) Search by Location or Country Search by Postal Code (US ONLY) Distance Search by Postal… https://t.co/fbtqwE4KE3 https://t.co/aVGiVYHy2M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Development Team Lead (Java): Job Description PSI Title: Development Team Lead (Java) Work Location: DC – Washington Description Essential Functions and Job Responsibilities: The successful candidate’s core responsibilities will include, but not to be… https://t.co/BIshEirtBN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java-Software-Engineer: We are currently seeking a motivated, career and customer service orientedSoftwareEngineerto join our team in Springfield, VA, to begin an exciting and challenging career with Unisys Federal Systems. Position Summary /… https://t.co/SLo0ypyOak https://t.co/VAun384PDK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AWS Develp with java: Java Microservices – Developer Ref No.: 18-23245 Location: RTP, North Carolina Job title: Java Microservices – Developer Location: RTP, NC Duration: 12 months. Strong understanding of Microservices architectures Prior hands-on… https://t.co/QE9pb7ISuP https://t.co/aGu0IYVYUG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NextGen Platform Java Developer: Gen Platform Java Developer Enter job title or location Search menu open clear text Search jobs Recent Searches – Deloitte home – About Deloitte – Job cart – Location: United States – Global (English) English Available in… https://t.co/U6hTDVHe8O https://t.co/3viBUanxlN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CNN anchor calls out double standard: CNN's Anderson Cooper points out the hypocrisy of President Trump tweeting about Samantha Bee's vulgar language, but remaining silent about Roseanne Barr's racist remarks. https://t.co/MurauJra6M https://t.co/46S19qk4BC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[# ColdFusion developer w Java – Cherry Hill, NJ: TITILE: Senior ColdFusion Developer Type: Contract Duration: 6+ Months Location: Cherry Hill, NJ Key Skills: ColdFusion with Java backend Requirements * BS in Computer Science or related field of study. *… https://t.co/ZrCJBNFff9 https://t.co/peTszkiMdP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Pasadena, CA Full-time $150k – $175k Posted Today If you are a Senior Back-End Developer / Platform Engineer with experience increasing scaling and performance in a JAVA environment, please read on… Do you want to join a growth mode… https://t.co/JWJxBvB9wZ https://t.co/2rTq3h76Kn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tennis player crushes ball boy at French Open https://t.co/4AXKY52JQH https://t.co/O2JmoUupMH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Java Developer: Denver, CO Full-time $120k – $160k Posted Today If you are a Java Developer with experience and a TS/SCI Security Clearance, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us – Fast-paced, challenging, and innovative environment working… https://t.co/pH5PWVYNy9 https://t.co/K9Wev3s2Pt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (Java): WHO WE ARE _accesso_ is a world-wide software company delivering industry leading virtual queuing, eCommerce and ticketing solutions for the attractions, cultural and leisure industries. The _accesso Passport_ ticketing suite… https://t.co/FlOTU4kwqR https://t.co/L9bA7sqKvh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google's military AI drone program may be more lucrative than it said: Google's Project Maven program for AI-based military drone image recognition program could net the company up to $250 million per year, according to internal memos seen by The… https://t.co/OMftON13xC https://t.co/WsRq2QdFjO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meghan's other new title: The Duchess of Sussex has been named by the UK edition of Vogue magazine as one of the most influential women working in Britain. https://t.co/VZfpImAZeZ https://t.co/jJNvY8fgtu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Ref No.:18-09258 Location: Ashburn, Virginia Position Type:Contract Start Date: 05/21/2018 AVA/J2EE, Spring Core, Spring ORM/Hibernate, REST, Spring Boot, Spring Integration, Hands on in Java/J2EE Design patterns ,… https://t.co/jj5ocdmaf9 https://t.co/z6M5Qp6K9q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer – Polygraph: Researches, designs, develops and/or modifies enterprise-wide systems and/or applications software. 1. Designs, develops, codes, tests and debugs highly complex new software products or makes significant enhancements to… https://t.co/NXjsBCAXvE https://t.co/28sAdpoDo9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer- Innovative Company!: Irvine, CA Full-time $100k – $160k Posted Today If you are a Senior Java Developer with experience, please read on! Are you a Senior Java developer that is looking for something new and exciting? Do you want… https://t.co/2ORsMdmRqj https://t.co/Xez4RYkytK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mom asked to prove biracial son is hers: Lindsay Gottlieb says, "because he has a different skin color," Southwest Airlines asked to prove she was the mother of her son https://t.co/SziGSCoI24 https://t.co/BxJxq20pnL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Software Engineer I/II ( C++, Java, Unix): 109879BR Sr Software Engineer I/II ( C++, Java, Unix) MA – Woburn 109879BR Job Description: An opportunity exists for a Senior Software Engineer I within the Missile Defense Radar Software Department in… https://t.co/LBNhlA6jdH https://t.co/MwwP15zoGf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Online dating lowers self-esteem: Before there were smartphones, singles would often go to bars or clubs and try to meet "the One," or at least the one for that night. Alcohol-induced courage and a steep bar tab later, singles were on top of their game… https://t.co/MfXNfYiKwb https://t.co/F9RnX0FaPV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid Java Frontend Developer – Engineer Software 3:   Job Description – Mid Java Frontend Developer – Engineer Software 3 (18005018) Mid Java Frontend Developer – Engineer Software 3 Requisition ID : 18005018 Location : United States-Virginia-Lorton US… https://t.co/ktTElzSzoW https://t.co/UMcny9kJzM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google's AR drawing app lets Android and iOS users collab on doodles: You no longer need an Android phone to try Google's take on augmented reality drawing. The tech giant has released an iOS version of Just a Line that brings the same three-dimensional… https://t.co/IPYlDj3dSA https://t.co/NKZk2r9cBy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Des Moines, Iowa – United States Job Start Date – 05/03/18, Posted Date – 05/03/18 Primary SkillsJavaTax TermsC2COverviewsubmit a solid 10+ year H1B consultant from IT SERVE skype Technical Stack 1. Java 2. Tomcat Apache 3.… https://t.co/S9F4jvCUSF https://t.co/DDohjejkIR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Application Lead, Java:   Job Description – Senior Application Lead, Java (00019908) Job Description  Senior Application Lead, Java – (00019908) Description   Gartner is looking for a Sr Application Lead who will direct a multi-disciplinary… https://t.co/qR4PSqZZBm https://t.co/0ZgYxuizbx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staged 'murder' of Russian journalist is costly https://t.co/dNGWD4a8TT https://t.co/WBvpsI6koB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jave Full stack developer, Java JDBC, Web services, Spring MVC, Hibernate RTP-NC: Jave Full stack developer, Java/J2EE, JDBC, Web services, Spring MVC, Hibernate RTP-NC Ref No.: 18-22740 Location: RTP, North Carolina Jave Full stack developer, Java/J2EE,… https://t.co/rU2ZYNnVag https://t.co/Z1nT7Edysb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many military injuries in Iraq, Afghanistan weren't from battle: Car accidents, falls, equipment mishaps and other nonbattle incidents caused about a third of all injuries sustained by nearly 30,000 US service members during three military operations in… https://t.co/YwozZJ9Ggq https://t.co/hcsYgN8Ulr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[java developer: java developer Ref No.:18-09313 Location: Columbus, Ohio Position Type:Full Time/Contract Start Date: 05/22/2018 Position: Java Developer Location: Columbus, OH Duration: Full Time Job Description: o Bachelor’s Degree in Computer… https://t.co/hDTWIsmZGL https://t.co/VxdAKOMXYx]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>