<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Redrum. -  Danny, The Shining]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was sad because I had no shoes, until I met a man who had no feet. So I said, Got any shoes you're not using? --&gt; Steven Wright]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gluten Free Recipes - Making a Gluten-Free Gravy  http://t.co/K02JbhRDQx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Advanced Weight Scales and Body Monitoring – Keeping Track of your Body Weight  http://t.co/Kw0zK40Tiy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sam Cooke was the king of soul - read his history - http://t.co/IGFHjtTmhR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rule your mind or it will rule you. - Horace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Redrum. -  Danny, The Shining]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of B.B. King  http://t.co/J4pNihPS5W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can an EMP really wipe us out?  http://t.co/FeyA3nV4ou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[End Of Line - The MCP, TRON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I want to knock a story off the front page, I just change my hairstyle. --&gt; Hillary Rodham Clinton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to ABBA  http://t.co/i8FGx9vNWv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is what you get from reading the small print in a contract. "experience " is what you get from not reading it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What is Fiverr Exactly and Why All the Buzz?  http://t.co/SX8kHkDPhD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And God took a handful of southernly wind, blew His breath over it and created the horse. - Bedouin Legend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Wonderful Canadian Rockies Tour  http://t.co/6aYG60oHqg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Neil Diamond  http://t.co/p5f1eW4Ryp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today’s Top Women’s Shoe Designers  http://t.co/RxmsN4COeZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Classic Cassette Silicone Case for Your iPhone! http://t.co/JxWYYJrrMu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Trouble with a kitten is that eventually it becomes a Cat - Ogden Nash]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you know how hard it is to maintain cover while dancing the salsa in three-inch heels? - Syndey, Alias]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like my money right where I can see it -- hanging in my closet. - Carrie Bradshaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we knew what it was we were doing, it would not be called research, would it? - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm shooting a commercial for safe sex. How ironic. Because I don't have that.   Tila Tequila]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Natalie Cole  http://t.co/yRYuJmPHji]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to win at golf:  cheat!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of State Farm Insurance  http://t.co/k3Ux1N9l1s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never wear the same shoe twice. - Dion Sanders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only those who risk going too far can possibly find out how far one can go. - T.S. Eliot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I get to go to a lot of overseas places, like Canada.  Britney Spears]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The easiest way to stay out of hot water is to keep a cool head]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think education is expensive, try ignorance - Derek Bok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We didn't lose the game; we just ran out of time. - Vince Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Assisted Living - Some Things to Consider  http://t.co/La7lxSZFx2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rule your mind or it will rule you. - Horace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It gets late early out there. - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to know what a man is really like, take notice of how he acts when he loses money.  Simone Weil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Heineken Phone Case --&gt; http://t.co/JE50ERlDLJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Rod Stewart  http://t.co/JICAN9AKAm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only place where success comes before work is in the dictionary. - Vidal Sassoon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the Hillbilly 10 Commandments ROFL - http://t.co/UmlDyXR61c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1f u c4n r34d th1s u r34lly n33d t0 g37 l41d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Biking Guide BMX Review  http://t.co/urzluOBTcf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space is the stature of God. - Joseph Joubert]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes make me happy. - Actress Lauren Conrad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's one small step for [a] man; one giant leap for mankind. - Neil A. Armstrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opera in English is, in the main, just about as sensible as baseball in Italian. - Henry Louis Mencken]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Isley Brothers  http://t.co/zpzbNTTTE2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ginger Rogers did everything Fred Astaire did, backwards and on high heels - Faith Whittlesey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dogs come when they're called; cats take a message and get back to you later. - Mary Bly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Are the Major Kinds of Insurance?  http://t.co/jzcFChpSD7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You've got to say, I think that if I keep working at this and want it badly enough I can have it. It's called perseverance. - Lee Iacocca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Strategy Consulting Firms to Avoid  http://t.co/37r8HPeBDo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you drag your shoe a bit those plastic spikes or rubber spikes can be almost as bad as metal spikes. - Bernhard Langer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's easier to ask forgiveness than it is to get permission - Grace Hopper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If man is a little lower than angels, then angels should reform.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The scenery was very beautiful. But I did not see the Great Wall. - Yang Liwei, China's first astronaut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really love this Han Solo iPhone case - may the force be with you! http://t.co/HbB1jZVQp8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spock, where the hell's the power you promised?" - Kirk  "One damn minute, admiral" - Spock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To achieve anything in this game you must be prepare to dabble in the boundary of disaster. - Sterling Moss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read about the Emerging Threats From An Electromagnetic Pulse Attack  http://t.co/FeyA3nV4ou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Geek Decision Ball - Picks FAIL, WIN, meh, 404 error, LOL, PWND and More! http://t.co/LP2rY5yoR6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sawyer: Son of a . . .! What's a head doing back here? Hurley: Oh, that's just Roger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the Hillbilly 10 Commandments ROFL - http://t.co/UmlDyXR61c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't sweep if you don't win the first game, and it's tougher to win two out of three if you lose the first one. - Todd Helton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Very Cool Hand Juicer http://t.co/3RNO5dKkyB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Trade School Programs  http://t.co/ytJBnqAWPu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If having a soul means being able to feel love and loyalty and gratitude, then animals are better off than a lot of humans - James Herriot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You want to fall in love with a shoe go ahead. A shoe can't love you back, a shoe can't hurt you too deeply either. - Allan Sherman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are seven winners of the Monaco Grand Prix on the starting line today, and four of them are Michael Schumacher. - Murray Walker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bird does not sing because it has an answer...  It sings because it has a song. - Chinese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I live in heels. Give me a pair of flip-flops and I'll trip all over myself. - Brenda Song]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Doobie Brothers  http://t.co/C8t33OIryZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life begins when we first realize how soon it ends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[E.T. phone home - E.T.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The trouble with most people today is that they're too fond of people that agree with them and with food that doesn't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do clever men make good husbands? "No, clever men don't become husbands!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is like a poker game, nobody wants to quit when he's losing: nobody wants you to quit when you're ahead. - Jackie Robinson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is not the filling of a pail, but the lighting of a fire. - William Butler Yeats]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you tried to give rock and roll another name, you might call it 'Chuck Berry'. - John Lennon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone can steer the ship when the sea is calm. - Publilius Syrus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make it so! - Engage! - Captain Picard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Peter Cetera  http://t.co/qgjsnSZmYe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learning Styles - Learn About Teaching so They Can Learn  http://t.co/hJEwuQe9TY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the Romans had been obliged to learn Latin, they would never have found time to conquer the world. - Heinrich Heine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your Business Guide for Small Business Internet Marketing  http://t.co/E7BBPk6Ti1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have never let my schooling interfere with my education. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Tips from Web Building Experts  http://t.co/Ir4Rxux523]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Industry is the soul of business and the keystone of prosperity. -Charles Dickens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Genesis  http://t.co/fcjiFOSo6S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to focus on my salad.  Martha Stewart when asked about her stock dealings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes make me happy. - Actress Lauren Conrad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You call the driver of a car a motorist, until he comes just little too close.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is a Creative Writing Degree for You?  http://t.co/FqZvr61VyN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spock, where the hell's the power you promised?" - Kirk  "One damn minute, admiral" - Spock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cooking - A Simple Way To Bond With Kids  http://t.co/cZQadsxN5C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing worthwhile comes easily. Work, continuous work and hard work, is the only way to accomplish results that last. - Hamilton Holt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL A Toilet Mug for your Coffee!  http://t.co/AHr0dvDxvd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we can't live together, then we're going to die alone. - Jack Shephard, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd walk through hell in a gasoline suit to play baseball. -  Pete Rose]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>