<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Net Developer with Angular: Net Developer with Angular Ref No.: 18-31534 Location: Cleveland, Ohio PFB details: Title: .Net Developer with Angular Max – 98K + Benefits Location: Cleveland, OH Non visa holders Job Description- Proven experience as a .NET… https://t.co/n6fJDTC4RR https://t.co/rL6zL1qeRH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US military commander: On North Korea, the lack of trust is the enemy: The top US military commander on the Korean peninsula said Friday that even as the United States and North Korea work on easing tensions and working toward denuclearization, diplomacy… https://t.co/8ucIYD0rqf https://t.co/cpr2Fchu9s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Systems Administrator: Company Name: MarkWest Energy Partners, L.P. Location Name: Denver, CO Location Address: 1515 Araphaoe St Twr1 Ste 1600, Denver, CO, United States (US), 80202 Education Level: Bachelor’s Required Relevant Experience Level: Mid… https://t.co/58fCoH0fEl https://t.co/b712xvIX0L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java-MuleSoft Lead: Java-MuleSoft Lead Ref No.: 18-29162 Location: Columbus, Ohio Technical Lead Web Technologies : Java Rest web services, Digital : MuleSoft – Expertise in ESB Mulesoft – Experience is working with the large integration/transformation… https://t.co/NrzwGVcv47 https://t.co/vbevX10sEe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Los Angeles police report possible hostage situation at Trader Joe's: Los Angeles police reported a possible hostage situation at a Trader Joe's grocery store Saturday. https://t.co/H7mcGqm42A https://t.co/PRkB85RsDW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer Level 1: Software Engineer Level 1 Honeywell Careers Chinese (Simplified)Czech (Czech Republic)Dutch (The Netherlands)English (US)French (Canada)French (France)German (Germany)Portuguese (Brazil)Spanish (Spain)Create a Profile|Log In… https://t.co/8wtReoXnaT https://t.co/JqDjzU8wi5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tiger Woods poised for Open strike as Jordan Spieth relishes battle: Tiger Woods is in contention for fourth Open title, first major for 10 years and 15th major in all. https://t.co/zNh9YqNQJX https://t.co/a4QYTxwgma]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sergio Marchionne stepping down as CEO of Fiat Chrysler: Replacing him will be the be the former boss of FCA's Ram and Jeep brands, Mike Manley. https://t.co/Db93fGczig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump says 'inconceivable' that Cohen recorded conversation about ex-Playmate payment: President Donald Trump lashed out Saturday morning at his former personal lawyer Michael Cohen and mischaracterized the government's April raid of Cohen's home and… https://t.co/rtJZfvaYcC https://t.co/GzRZ1snefP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's right: Britain IS in turmoil: Theresa May could be forgiven for thinking that the forthcoming summer break, when the UK Parliament does not sit for six weeks, has not come soon enough. https://t.co/JaQ6KotZoz https://t.co/kdjS0yWl0W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is kompromat?: Russia has denied gathering compromising information about US President-elect Donald Trump -- so what exactly is "kompromat" and how has it been used previously? https://t.co/7NoBqM4sFW https://t.co/05tM2ckS3G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Analyst: Project Analyst Business Group Architecture and Software No. of Positions 1 Requisition Number 77744BR Job Category Engineering and Technicians Position Type Full Time Relocation Eligible No Position Summary The role will report to the… https://t.co/rcH2Vyxabv https://t.co/NtEFMNSJWE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Security Consultant: Network &amp; Security Consultant Business Group Control Products and Solutions No. of Positions 1 Requisition Number 78087BR Job Category Sales, Services, and Solutions Position Type Full Time Relocation Eligible No Position… https://t.co/ZommZ5nnWK https://t.co/r1bxGsQwYX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Financial Integrations and Systems Analyst: Multi-Color Corporation is hiring a Senior Financial Integrations &amp; Systems Analyst! If you are looking to join a growing organization, look no further! Multi-Color Corporation located in Batavia, Ohio –… https://t.co/ALGODXOJYu https://t.co/CLfc3SCeLe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior C# Developer – Full Stack Developer: Our Fortune 500 direct client has an exciting opportunity for an experienced full stack developer with experience working in C#, HTML5, CSS3. SQL Server, etc. Angular experience and/or training is strongly… https://t.co/kCwHgVkj2x https://t.co/HflRXoWOS8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Entry Level IT Systems Engineer: Job Postings | Reyrey.comReynolds and Reynolds LogoFacebookLinkedInTwitterYouTubeInstagram Skip to main content [RR – Careers] Careers Super Navigation Careers Menu #ReyReyLife Search Jobs Main navigation [RR – Careers]… https://t.co/h7wtmmJv0F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Duck boat disaster: Tragedy strikes a country playground: Touring people around on amphibious vehicles of the kind used in WWII has long been a way of making a living in an area where a new lake turned a financially challenged region into a family… https://t.co/iHZAS4xoXd https://t.co/GVtWkwPZf1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Entry Level Software Developer: Job Postings | Reyrey.comReynolds and Reynolds LogoFacebookLinkedInTwitterYouTubeInstagram Skip to main content [RR – Careers] Careers Super Navigation Careers Menu #ReyReyLife Search Jobs Main navigation [RR – Careers]… https://t.co/18dm5xT53K https://t.co/Qp5j7mcueG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right-wing media called him a leftist terrorist. He appears to be a pro-gun conservative: Headlines from a variety of right-leaning outlets asserted that Einerwold was a member of "Antifa." https://t.co/YCMYoyxzql https://t.co/XazWYJMeXi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Engineer in Test: Our direct client is seeking to hire a software developer in test for a long-term contract position. We are looking for individuals familiar with planning and executing test engineering activities across the… https://t.co/kLDxv4v3bW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Mark Sanford met Maria Butina: Rep. Mark Sanford, the South Carolina Republican and frequent critic of President Donald Trump, had his own run-in with accused Russian spy Maria Butina at his family farm last year. https://t.co/2ZmDgmjOOM https://t.co/YerUMFR4RY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Large Programs Project Manager: Location: Cincinnati Job type: Permanent Sector: Operations Category: Senior Manager Jobs Position Description The Program Manager is responsible for the successful industrialization of major programs per the contractual… https://t.co/5JFeYynaI1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deadly duck boat crash in Missouri: At least 13 people are dead after a duck boat capsized in Missouri. Follow here for the latest. https://t.co/q2MuP7c8g0 https://t.co/NMWJ1JBO90]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nigeria's former minister of finance Ngozi Okonjo-Iweala joins Twitter board: Twitter has named Nigeria's former finance minister, Dr. Ngozi Okonjo-Iweala to its board. https://t.co/nwOvPHMlTg https://t.co/ujmqywbqgz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior XML Modeler/ XSLT Developer: Location US-OH-Cincinnati Posted Date 3 days ago(6/18/2018 3:18 PM) Job ID 23720 # Positions 2 Category Technology Position Type Full Time Overview Be Here. Be Great. Working for a leader in the insurance industry… https://t.co/rsbHXfH7zp https://t.co/Le5vi9F6JL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Valtteri Bottas signs contract extension at Mercedes: Mercedes has locked down its options for next season's starting grid by securing the signature of Valtteri Bottas https://t.co/9NlORZ8ToP https://t.co/SKBu57Q5en]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Risk Systems Specialist: The Risk Management Specialist in the Operational Risk Management Group will be responsible for supporting Archer which is the Enterprise Risk Management System (ERMS). The primary responsibilities of this position are to lead… https://t.co/TJzyDCnrxM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Software Developer: Java Software Developer – Diverse Lynx – Blue Ash, OH | ********** Loading…Server error, please try again laterSorry! It looks like you are in private browsing mode, which is not supported. Please switch your browser mode. Java… https://t.co/XXFAkmI4LU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pompeo: Russia 'will try to undermine Western democracy' in 2018, 2020: US Secretary of State Mike Pompeo said Thursday he believes that Russia will try to undermine democracies around the world for the foreseeable future. https://t.co/U8RWS4HGnE https://t.co/xIuwAowgQ7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer | -Come join our product development team in a hands-on technical role where you-ll be involved in th: Software Developer | Come join our product development team in a hands-on technical role where you’ll be involved in the end-to-end… https://t.co/cchknaujuC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world's oldest fighter pilot retires at 66: The world's oldest active fighter pilot, a grandfather of four, has retired and taken his last flight at the age of 66. https://t.co/A7B4TnLPSv https://t.co/wM1x3dXyBZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump administration: 1,606 parents possibly eligible for reunification with kids: Facing a looming deadline to reunite of hundreds of migrant families by next week, the Trump administration said Thursday it had found at least 1,606 parents potentially… https://t.co/nrbQJ1yQN9 https://t.co/FQzHZz1VRH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tiger Woods fights for legacy -- great or greatest?: From the minute he swept into view, you knew something was different. https://t.co/uGg7N2Synl https://t.co/z2hexZQFUU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Pega Developer: Location US-OH-Cincinnati Posted Date 7 days ago(6/25/2018 2:10 PM) Job ID 23158 # Positions 1 Category Technology Position Type Full Time Overview Be Here. Be Great. Working for a leader in the insurance industry means opportunity… https://t.co/D6gHMmCbkg https://t.co/EQHqLcyE8i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House says Trump 'disagrees' with Putin suggestion to interrogate Americans: President Donald Trump now disagrees with a proposal raised by his Russian counterpart to interrogate Americans in exchange for assistance in the US-Russia probe, the… https://t.co/A5oetiUYtL https://t.co/GaH9rV26kB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla Model 3 cancellations outpace deposits, analyst says: Tesla's stock is dropping nearly 3% after an analyst warned of a problems. https://t.co/RRGbTw983z https://t.co/hTPjSkGQSM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Net Developer: Net Developer Ref No.: 18-29228 Location: Cincinnati, Ohio Role: .Net Developer Location: Cincinnati, OH, Denver, CO Duration: Full Time Permanent Note: NO C2C, NO C2H, NOOPT, NO H1B TRANSFER, NO REMOTE Job Summary Skills Required: .NET… https://t.co/gDaZbBYadN https://t.co/kgZ75sinG7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DESKTOP SUPPORT: DESKTOP SUPPORT Ref No.: 18-29473 Location: Sharonville, Ohio The IT Service Desk Analyst – Level 1 will provide first line technical support in a 24x7x365 environment. – Act as a single point of contact for phone calls, chat and emails… https://t.co/P6ZzHGq7pY https://t.co/9MuvaWlUKt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager II – Higher Ed: Job Description Tracking Code 5158-244 Job Description At Gilbane we’re building more than buildings, we’re helping create schools, hospitals, laboratories and other facilities across the United States and throughout the… https://t.co/4fgkK4n1y4 https://t.co/0IDyaSZoEz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China's yuan plunges again. Is a currency war coming?: The Chinese yuan weakened almost 1% against the US dollar on Thursday to hit its lowest level in a year. How low can the currency go? https://t.co/SDNRSHDD1N https://t.co/fzEnbZkPnb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer, Software Engineering (SAP Order to Cash – Pricing) (P-Mod): At Cardinal Health, we are developing the innovative products and services that make healthcare safer and more productive. Join a growing, global company genuinely… https://t.co/NsJcFp0afb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Modern slavery in developed countries more common than thought: A report on modern slavery around the world has found that the number of slaves in developed nations, including the United States and United Kingdom, is much higher than previously thought. https://t.co/D2X99KaEQC https://t.co/QdVGPUBvm9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master Ref No.: 18-30028 Location: BlueAsh, Ohio Mandatory Technical / Functional Skills – 8+ years of experience in the field of IT Projects and Project Management – 3+ years of experience as a Scrum Master and should possess a… https://t.co/XUqmGlscdn https://t.co/dF1rSv9eej]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canadian police investigate beating of Muslim man as hate crime: Two brothers from Ontario who allegedly assaulted several people, including one man who reportedly remains in intensive care, are the subjects of a hate crime investigation, Canadian police… https://t.co/xEJbq1pvxz https://t.co/6QmShmH9oj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Job ID 2018-9179 Overview Insituform Technologies, LLC is looking for an experienced Project Manager to be based in our Columbus, OH office. Insituform Technologies LLC, a subsidiary of Aegion Corporation, is a leading worldwide provider… https://t.co/GPxmSiP7hV https://t.co/LgLkdxhBY8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ESPYS posthumously honors Parkland coaches: The ESPYS on Wednesday posthumously honored three coaches killed in the mass shooting at Marjory Stoneman Douglas High School. https://t.co/ntFb3ooRJd https://t.co/eG72yDHBZm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Security tightened as Pakistan braces for more election violence: Pakistan is due to vote next week in general elections overshadowed by deadly terrorist attacks, hundreds of arrests and accusations of widespread interference by the military. https://t.co/H0YvMxr3nu https://t.co/rp28tvggOs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Serial stowaway' Marilyn Hartman will have to wear an ankle monitor as she awaits trial: Marilyn Hartman, the 66-year-old woman who has been accused of sneaking onto commercial airline flights, is mentally fit to stand trial, a Chicago judge has ruled. https://t.co/PrOxtlzNfz https://t.co/CCXniaPlUJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master Ref No.: 18-29278 Location: Cincinnati, Ohio Position Title : Scrum Master Location : Cincinnati, OH Duration : Full Time Permanent Note: NO C2C, NO C2H, NOOPT, NO H1B TRANSFER, NO REMOTE Roles &amp; Responsibilities Knowledge of… https://t.co/1IPxZMN5YS https://t.co/P0aVT3z4Yz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Comic-Con kicks off amid period showing off fandom's ugly side: Comic-Con, we have a problem. https://t.co/suX71DYq5K https://t.co/T2AWBQiakV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce Developer: Salesforce Developer Ref No.: 18-28040 Location: Cincinnati, Ohio Job Title: Salesforce Developer Job Location: Cincinnati, OH Duration: Fulltime Permanent Hire Compensation: Base Salary + Benefits NO C2C/C2H, No Sponsorship, No… https://t.co/Tl9dtIQ8mB https://t.co/vb34FSVF5X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Europe has fined Google $5 billion. But that won't hurt it: Europe has slapped Google with another record fine. But the company's dominant position in Europe's mobile market is unlikely to be dented. https://t.co/cBr0qSle0W https://t.co/K4BfV2wyqr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First it was Pfizer. Now Novartis has frozen drug prices in the US: Novartis is holding off on hiking drug prices in the United States, days after President Donald Trump called on other companies to follow Pfizer's lead in rolling back price hikes. https://t.co/VNJAHBy5Bo https://t.co/Bg41XqVuQC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google's punishment; Elon Musk apologizes; Morgan Stanley earnings: Here's what you need to know about the markets before you start your business day. https://t.co/1VZFULpOo4 https://t.co/ZEQryee6Kv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The family behind the decades-old photos in a projector at Goodwill has been found: Kristie Baeumert bought a projector in Georgia and unearthed decades-old family slides. In an unexpected ending, she's found the owners. https://t.co/NpZpt6B7ER https://t.co/PCi2fMXRIu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Hosting System Administrator: Location US-OH-Cincinnati Posted Date 1 month ago(6/13/2018 3:35 PM) Job ID 23709 # Positions 1 Category Technology Position Type Full Time Overview Be Here. Be Great. Working for a leader in the insurance industry… https://t.co/T0T0qhGqbQ https://t.co/1tGYNoJF7t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embedded Developer (Device Connectivity): Our direct client located in Twinsburg is looking for an Embedded Developer (Device Connectivity).. Desired skills include 2+ years of experience with C/C++, Linux OS, Embedded systems development, JavaScript,… https://t.co/kSMGZgp8GO https://t.co/NWEjeSwSPE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst: The data analyst’s primary objective is to ensure that consumers of data-sets and reports receive agreed outputs, and that these outputs meet the relevant quality, governance and timetable requirements. The key accountabilities for the Data… https://t.co/nZ0pxFpM38 https://t.co/duRfMrvypc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michelle Williams reveals she sought help for mental health issues: Former Destiny's Child singer Michelle Williams has revealed she's now happy and healthy after recently seeking medical help for mental health issues. https://t.co/NagqHGHzPi https://t.co/Dq90wfw1Di]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UX Designer Consultant (UX Researcher): Detailed Description: – Collaborate with designers, product managers, brand managers, analytics teams and leadership to identify knowledge gaps and propose methods to gain needed insights – Participate in… https://t.co/FBWmaYxVxN https://t.co/5WLiCq3W4x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US expects first group of remains to be returned July 27 from North Korea: The United States is expecting North Korea to return the first group of possible US service member remains on July 27, according to a US official. https://t.co/cCePrsLMuh https://t.co/zrvPBpwQ5y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US and UK intelligence agencies concerned Russia is readying to ramp up aggression after World Cup lull: Russian intelligence agencies are planning to ramp up operations targeting western countries now that the World Cup and the Trump-Putin Helsinki… https://t.co/vU3RK3MD3m https://t.co/hnK1yamXvn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge vacates order requiring Los Angeles Times to alter published story: The judge's decision came only days after he had ordered the Times to remove details from a story regarding a police officer who pleaded guilty to charges that he lied to federal… https://t.co/HGy6npRDST https://t.co/5ePSmkTuul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Front End Developer $120k: Cincinnati, OH Full-time $110k – $140k Posted Today If you are a Lead Front End Developer with experience, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us We are one of the fastest growing companies in the country that invest… https://t.co/eAVxOjkLn7 https://t.co/O4ZPsdrdgC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ADHD study links teens' symptoms with digital media use: A new study on teens suggests that ADHD symptoms might be associated with engaging frequently in digital media activities, such as streaming video or using social media. The association was… https://t.co/yrNuZMUr8P https://t.co/4n5Y3kOopw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israel tightens Gaza restrictions amid heightened tensions: Israel says it is halting fuel shipments and restricting the fishing zone off Gaza from Tuesday amid heightened tensions with militants . https://t.co/pAbE9fbZ7E https://t.co/YsVfJ1Xv6K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jean Van de Velde: Frenchman forever linked with sporting disaster: It was as heart-breaking as it was excruciating to see a man slowly lose his grip on a childhood dream. https://t.co/ydp7n8VEGr https://t.co/KHyBNzJPAS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Analyst-System Analysis and Programming: Job Description What you’ll be doing. The National Customer Service Operations Team works with key leaders, stakeholders, field partners and business partners. This position is a Sr Analyst-level developer… https://t.co/pkMS1m7Hey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's been over two months since Hawaii's Kilauea volcano started erupting, and the lava's still flowing: Since Hawaii's Kilauea volcano erupted in May, the Big Island has weathered thousands of earthquakes, a stream of eruptions, and lava engulfing homes. https://t.co/3Rua6K0Psm https://t.co/WV8i0OmYN7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Admin: Network Admin in Columbus, Ohio, United States | IT Infrastructure at CognizantJob Details | Cognizant – ************* – Industries – – – Services – – – Latest Thinking – – – About Cognizant – – Careers Home – Get To Know Us – Our Core… https://t.co/jxU8yCCkpj https://t.co/TwotQJxEvO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dotnet Developer with MES support: Dotnet Developer with MES support Ref No.: 18-30770 Location: Harrisburg, Ohio Position: Dotnet Developer with MES support Location: Harrisburg, OH Duration: Fulltime Position Job Description 6-8 Years’ Experience in… https://t.co/h6M121ScKi https://t.co/pxMvSDcrWE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Blue Ash, Ohio – United States Job Start Date – 07/23/18, Posted Date – 06/18/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview Job Description Video Screening Process: Once submitted, your candidate will receive a link to complete… https://t.co/nVXRgjCpEp https://t.co/d1ddUYI0WW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst/Scientist, Senior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Beavercreek, OH Job Type: Strategy – Planning Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 7/11/2018 Job Description Job Number: R******* Data Analyst/Scientist, Senior Key Role: Perform as a… https://t.co/MDtKiPk2QF https://t.co/nHloo1jf7N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House issues talking points to curtail damage from Russia summit: The White House sent talking points to Republican surrogates and members of Congress on Monday as aides dealt with the fallout of the summit between President Donald Trump and… https://t.co/OtsLycJTuz https://t.co/4OkTRCX3F1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Data Modeler, Business Intelligence Analytics (P: At Cardinal Health, were developing the innovative products and services that make healthcare safer and more productive. Join a growing, global company genuinely committed to making a difference… https://t.co/3exXejarBJ https://t.co/PLhM8nRj34]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hillary Clinton was exactly right about Trump being Putin's puppet: Hillary Clinton's tweet, ahead of Trump's summit with Putin, asking which team Trump plays for, seemed to foretell his display of trust in Putin over his own intelligence community,… https://t.co/GfOjJphg4n https://t.co/q3VfR8WEFZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. .Net Developer: Sr. .Net Developer Johnston, Iowa – United States Job Start Date – 06/25/18, Posted Date – 06/25/18 Primary SkillsHTML,CSS,.net,Java ScriptTax TermsC2COverview Sr. .Net Developer Location: Johnston, IA 50131 Duration: 1 year contract… https://t.co/jXiKmQNaEC https://t.co/b9a6zqlm1Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['How bad was that?': Even Trump aides question damage done: President Donald Trump hoped his hotly anticipated summit talks with Russian counterpart Vladimir Putin would amount to a triumphant television event. Instead, he returns to Washington facing… https://t.co/MQRAaR4OaC https://t.co/IJsAGOSwMu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineering #180057176: Software Engineering Columbus, OH Job #180057176. Job Description: Duties: Participate in end-to-end application development lifecycle activities, including design, coding, testing, and deployment. Collaborate to develop… https://t.co/GMf3AQlrNi https://t.co/28XA7lOeop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How much more can Netflix grow?: Netflix is expected to announce it added 5.5 million subscribers in the second quarter. It reports earnings Monday. https://t.co/VHkXn9TcFW https://t.co/QQDwABKGd2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer, Software Engineering (SAP MDG Master Data): At Cardinal Health, were developing the innovative products and services that make healthcare safer and more productive. Join a growing, global company genuinely committed to making a difference for… https://t.co/UtbUgIXU7J https://t.co/NK0KlGNGjQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineering #180057151: Software Engineering Columbus, OH. Job #180057151. Job Description: Duties: Design, develop, and maintain Android mobile application. Perform entire application life cycle: concept, design, build, deploy, test, product… https://t.co/w1Lp0lKRO2 https://t.co/0VNDaYbonp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hadoop Developer: Hadoop Developer Ref No.: 18-28402 Location: Strongsville, Ohio Position: Hadoop Developer Location: Strongsville, OH Duration: 12 Months 8 to 10 years of work experience as Hadoop Technical lead with significant knowledge of different… https://t.co/bFqBj1mlpI https://t.co/a5xenP4VNf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US signals it would consider some exemptions on Iranian oil: The Trump administration signaled for the first time it might consider exemptions from US sanctions for countries as they reduce their dependency on Iranian oil. https://t.co/AkBSEMrtED https://t.co/quhggxK8hm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Desktop Support Intern: Job/Internship Description Desktop Support Intern Job Title Desktop Support Intern Requisition ID ******** Duration Location Mansfield, OH 44903 Other Location Description Desktop Support Intern – Are you ready to make a… https://t.co/uz8SlFXr96 https://t.co/qjU5hTBWLR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Engineer: Make your mark in Broadcasting and Digital Media. Sinclair Broadcast Group and Sinclair Digital Solutions are dedicated to making Sinclair a communications powerhouse! We are the largest and most diversified television broadcasting company… https://t.co/MCXz8poYIp https://t.co/iUOfd89Uo3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mob in Indonesia slaughters 300 crocodiles in revenge killing: Nearly 300 crocodiles were slaughtered in revenge killings by a mob in Indonesia over the weekend. https://t.co/eA5Ko0ZUnT https://t.co/dQ89NIcXzp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[British rescuer considers legal action against Musk over 'pedo' tweet: British rescuer Vern Unsworth says he is considering legal action against US billionaire Elon Musk after he made an unfounded and disparaging claim he was a "pedo", or pedophile, in a… https://t.co/GbIqcvpY4z https://t.co/nTuNQxppZs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Lead – Product Review Engineer: Company The Boeing Company Job ID ********** Date posted 06/26/2018 Location Heath Ohio United States Job Description The Boeing Defense, Space &amp; Security (BDS) organization is seeking an experienced Technical… https://t.co/Pw2hIDJgH3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Japan floods: Heat wave adds to misery in devastated areas: A heat wave in southern Japan has killed at least eight people, dealing another blow to a country still recovering from the worst flooding in decades. https://t.co/Qu4VMfHu9E https://t.co/IHNNw2i64z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Ref No.: 18-29433 Location: BlueAsh, Ohio Position: Java Developer Job Location: BlueAsh, OH Job Title: Full time permanent Mandatory Technical/ Functional Skills: – 4+ (8+ years for senior level) years experience with Java… https://t.co/0DM2wChaNy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prince Louis' christening photos show grinning Prince George: Kensington Palace has released the first official photographs from the christening of Prince Louis, the third child of the Duke and Duchess of Cambridge. https://t.co/pxCvqlcSLm https://t.co/VgfELprYXq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elon Musk makes unfounded accusation against Thai cave rescuer: A British diver who was called an integral part of the rescue mission at a Thai cave earlier this month criticized billionaire Elon Musk's plan to build a "mini-sub" to help with the effort.… https://t.co/8s1dEg5BLF https://t.co/XQbg29gD9X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Analyst: Location US-OH-Cincinnati Posted Date 19 hours ago(6/18/2018 3:22 PM) Job ID 23724 # Positions 1 Category Technology Position Type Full Time Overview Be Here. Be Great. Working for a leader in the insurance industry means opportunity… https://t.co/nRVaTiNdCe https://t.co/qTUbfsFeuB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Formula E: Jean-Eric Vergne sets seal on title triumph as Audi Sport takes team crown: Jean Eric-Vergne capped a triumphant day for France by winning the final round of the Formula E championship in New York Sunday to set the seal on his title-winning… https://t.co/Yijirqbmu2 https://t.co/R6NXIFnQxU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Expedite Coordinator (Supply Chain Operations Analyst I): Job Description CEVA Logistics, one of the world’s leading supply chain companies, designs and implements industry leading solutions for large and medium-size national and multinational companies.… https://t.co/mve8gLJTIV https://t.co/WsAxDk09kE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manager, IT Program Project Management: At Cardinal Health, we’re developing the innovative products and services that make healthcare safer and more productive. Join a growing, global company genuinely committed to making a difference for our customers… https://t.co/PiF81MWj7O https://t.co/LMAdflUtaQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To Putin, Trump insists he'll be 'different': Vladimir Putin has stood the test of time through four American presidents, but from Donald Trump he is looking for one thing in particular: to be elevated on the world stage, away from global isolation. https://t.co/g7fuWDZnB6 https://t.co/eOedZLA4Cf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer Student Co-op (PES, PP): For Siemens Software Engineer Student Co-op (PES, PP) job – Internal Services – Milford, Ohio Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard – Toggle navigation – My Dashboard – Our Stories –… https://t.co/WsLLQ43PNf https://t.co/71KFA4eQG7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul: Asking for Russian hackers' extradition a 'moot point': Republican Sen. Rand Paul says asking for the extradition of the Russian intelligence agents indicted Friday for interfering in the 2016 election would be a "moot point." https://t.co/EISm62lOn5 https://t.co/SgiFt4dm8d]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>