<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people are like angels - always harping on something!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The difference between try and triumph is just a little umph! - Marvin Phillips]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overview of Social Bookmarking Sites  http://t.co/goAcE3Zst6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest lie you can make is to lie to yourself. - Matt Zotti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marriage lets you annoy and aggravate one special person for the rest of your life.  What a joy LOL!!  :&gt;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Boston  http://t.co/qc5dxkxCVc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Jay Ferguson  http://t.co/s2i94cgITj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take twice as long to eat half as much. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Orleans  http://t.co/fLINlECN69]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Interesting Burger Facts and History  http://t.co/vwGEjbUvLm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any government big enough to give you everything you want is big enough to take it away from you, too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Awesome BookBook for iPhone- Combine Wallet and Phone and Style  http://t.co/FlNbYSW9BW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hops Holster 12 Can Ammo Pack - Beer Anywhere!  http://t.co/rgNi71zS55]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Five Guys Burgers and Fries  http://t.co/OL4o5qfuHV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why does a girl with the least principle draw the most interest?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I prefer the company of peasants because they have not been educated sufficiently to reason incorrectly. - Michel de Montaigne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still love her. But she's retarded, too. Guy Ritchie on Madonna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Choosing To Use Solar Power  http://t.co/PhWfKxyE4I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Geek Decision Ball - Picks FAIL, WIN, meh, 404 error, LOL, PWND and More! http://t.co/xNAFnTDP1v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never wear the same shoe twice. - Dion Sanders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Earth, Wind and Fire  http://t.co/LSLzH7WBRN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the Little House on the Prairie Episode The Nephews  http://t.co/vyZ3dZZaSB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A girl should be two things: classy and fabulous. - Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone who lives within their means suffers from a lack of imagination. - Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids LOVE Magnets - Check Out Magnet Science - Fun and Educational! http://t.co/RzQk0k2igL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter Can be an Invaluable Business Tool  http://t.co/ggcxDdK6vG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always laugh heartily at your boss' jokes - he may be giving you a loyalty check.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you ever walk into a room and forget why you walked in? I think that is how dogs spend their lives. - Sue Murphy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money, if it does not bring you happiness, will at least help you be miserable in comfort. - Helen Gurley Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I have a machine gun. Ho ho ho. - John McClane - Die Hard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't compare me to my father. Our similarities are different. -  Dale Berra about his father Yogi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Hilarious 60s Comedy – Get Smart  http://t.co/iJ6y6fHBKR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One deer to another:  "I wish I had his doe"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to that hilarious sit-com Three’s Company - http://t.co/jjgd0aJOx2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Creative Writing Degree - Why You Should Consider One  http://t.co/rzLEpSIX6X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's an edge to real rock 'n' roll. It's all that matters. - Neil Young]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is but one game and that game is baseball.  - John McGraw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really wish I had invented the flipflop. I love flipflops. Its the one style of shoe I would be so proud of inventing. Christian Louboutin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are peaks and valleys in this game. We're in a valley - Death Valley. - Kirby Puckett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A little smile adds a good deal to a faces value]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The universe, as far as we can observe it, is a wonderful and immense engine. - George Santayana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I started racing my father told me, "˜Cristiano, nobody has three balls but some people have two very good ones. - Cristiano Da Matta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn the Best Spots for Mountain Climbing  http://t.co/f4FcgEyqRr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adornment, what a science! Beauty, what a weapon! Modesty, what elegance! Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Harmless Version Of the Original Russian Roulette - Great for Parties! http://t.co/yl9Ca2Y7Oj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Heart  http://t.co/3S4PqVDc61]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Little Richard  http://t.co/bWCUQHm85B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China has blocked Twitter!!  Now 2 billion people will have no idea what I'm having for lunch.  Bummer!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goonies never say die. - Mike, The Goonies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still love her. But she's retarded, too. Guy Ritchie on Madonna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Genesis  http://t.co/aKOhSCya5o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman's dress should be a like a barbed-wire fence: serving its purpose without obstructing the view. - Sophia Loren]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Gardening Fall Flowers  http://t.co/krLG0xzFi9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hold fast to dreams, for if dreams die, life is a broken winged bird that cannot fly. - Langston Hughes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some of the greatest Hollywood actors are not the award winners, but those congratulating them on their triumph]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Play is the only way the highest intelligence of humankind can unfold. - Joseph Chilton Pearce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I see a pair of shoes I adore, and it doesn't matter if they have them in my size. I buy them anyway. - Keira Knightley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't pay good wages because I have a lot of money; I have a lot of money because I pay good wages. - Robert Bosch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very "COOL" Titanic Ice Cube mold - http://t.co/A9pOjv0P9b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overheard when the boss returned from his safari in Africa: "He's the first man the head shrinkers ever failed with."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sky is no longer the limit. - Richard M. Nixon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you think, your mouth is closed, but your mind keeps on talking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the top science fiction movies of all time!  http://t.co/NNc32hKT1Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hating the (New York) Yankees is as American as pizza pie, unwed mothers, and cheating on your income tax. - Mike Royko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our health always seems much more valuable after we lose it. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read How to Use LinkedIn for Your Company   http://t.co/E3sdhARR0B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Bert Kaempfert  http://t.co/o9Fc6aYJyp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My own mother told me I didn't have a shot in hell of winning tonight.  A shocked Katherine Heigl upon winning an Emmy for Grey's Anatomy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really love this Han Solo iPhone case - may the force be with you! http://t.co/5bCoreU85D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana’s Lyme Journey - Part 5 - Test Results In!  http://t.co/JbW1vy85PT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Major Shoe Retailers  http://t.co/48jJJSlcw3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Adam Faith  http://t.co/8WcqVDu1Ni]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this gallery of the top 10 European beers!  http://t.co/TScwpBFQAR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I went through baseball as a player to be named later." - Joe Garagiola]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the Devine RPG Minecraft Mod - http://t.co/RXUzv9DWeY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The rest of the world lives to eat, while I eat to live. - Socrates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am alive and well and unconcerned about the rumors of my death. But if I were dead, I would be the last to know. - Paul McCartney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What is Facebook Gaming?  http://t.co/V9f789qkEQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like my money right where I can see it -- hanging in my closet. - Carrie Bradshaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn the Keys to Using LinkedIn for Your Company  http://t.co/KdIQVHSvbZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Blue Origin - A Profile of This Emerging Space Company  http://t.co/zJGZq0gP9w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supporting Adopted Students: Parents and Teachers Working Together  http://t.co/0fXz5wf00A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good introduction to Minecraft Mods - http://t.co/pFXMRQ2WD0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 14 - Doctor Decides to Discontinue IV Treatment  http://t.co/h3EVp2y4vQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Reviews By Children Affect a Product’s Sale  http://t.co/aqRFix3i1v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Organizing Garage Cabinets and Storage  http://t.co/jZqrA5k0gT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is not the strongest of the species that survive, nor the most intelligent, but the one most responsive to change. - Charles Darwin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Evolution of the Wooden Clog  http://t.co/8wqkFTohld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Favorite Things for Kids to Review  http://t.co/B5c3ZRXh44]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who likes not his business, his business likes not him. - William Hazlitt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Manolo Blahnik  http://t.co/w0no45dzWB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got hit in the head pretty hard. My clock ran backwards for two years. - Buddy Baker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Underwater Scooter - How Cool! http://t.co/HLdNvSmBpI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Humble Pie  http://t.co/akeCqGsjJq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the star wars lover in your family - Jedi Dressing Gowns - May the force be with you!  http://t.co/YrSishZxYL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only those who risk going too far can possibly find out how far one can go. - T.S. Eliot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence is no match for Natural Stupidity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really &amp; truly you can never have 2 many pairs of shoes. You need a pair for every mood &amp; everyone knows women have lots of moods. Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When a subject becomes totally obsolete we make it a required course. - Peter Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is that which discloses to the wise and disguises from the foolish their lack of understanding. - Ambrose Bierce]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>