<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager (IT Security)- PMP: Project Manager (Security)- PMP Location: Detroit, MI Interview Mode: In-person preferred after telephonic round Project Duration: 12+ months * 10+ Years in project management or involvement on projects * Client needs… https://t.co/SpowiscVnA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior SharePoint Developer: Senior SharePoint Developer McLean, VA $120-125K Prestigious Organization is seeking a Senior SharePoint Developer. The Corporate Systems team is responsible for supporting application delivery and support for several… https://t.co/HxrTCT46zk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: Jobs Toggle navigation * Sign In * Sign Up * Help Career Portal * Failure Message Cannot parse, seems some issue with the profile, please create the profile manually Alert Message Job Post has been updated successfully * Position… https://t.co/R0atenNfXP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer Systems Analyst Subject Matter Expert 16496: Technical Solutions Description Huntington Ingalls Industries &amp;#8211; Technical Solutions Division, Integrated Mission Solutions Group (Camber Corporation) provides mission-critical engineering and… https://t.co/7RLWVfEeQF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Target Development Network Analyst 16094: Description Huntington Ingalls Industries &amp;#8211; Technical Solutions Division, Integrated Mission Solutions Group (Camber Corporation) provides mission-critical engineering and technical service to Information… https://t.co/HuFFhUT9EZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Developer/Architect SharePoint/Office 365/Angular: Portal Solutions (now part of the Withum Team) Microsoft Solutions and Service practice helps organizations share what they know and find what they need by connecting people, data, and content. We… https://t.co/no8W3L00Gg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Developer – JavaScript SharePoint: Title Senior Developer &amp;#8211; JavaScript &amp;#038; SharePoint ========================================== EOE Statement We are an equal employment opportunity employer. All… https://t.co/QPBlgvC4jB 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See the Bike Cyclist Lael Wilcox Uses to Ride 20,000 Miles a Year: Lael Wilcox pedals a distance nearly equal to a trip around the globe every 12 months. https://t.co/Rygow7Avro https://t.co/qFYTUwB9u1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Project Manager (CMDB)- Contract: Configuration Management Project Manager. Need a strong PM who knows what to do (minimal hand-holding) and knows when to escalate. Strengths include removing roadblocks,… https://t.co/UqLM9tkcCu 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Nintex Developer: Prestigious Enterprise Company is currently seeking a Developer with SharePoint and ****** experience, as well as some Nintex exposure. Candidate will be responsible for end-user computing development using the Microsoft… https://t.co/ng6SCRwZfa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle Web Center Developer: ODClogo-horizontal 200&amp;#215;38.jpg ************************** Position Function: This role will be primarily responsible for designing, building, modifying, testing, maintaining, and… https://t.co/SDf7Tgmt3g 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior SharePoint Developer: Senior SharePoint Developer McLean, VA $120-125K Prestigious Organization is seeking a Senior SharePoint Developer. The Corporate Systems team is responsible for supporting application delivery and support for several… https://t.co/7DVN4lgjEN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer/Engineer/Admin: JOB TITLE: SHAREPOINT DEVELOPER/ENGINEER/ADMIN LOCATION: COLUMBIA, SC DURATION: 12 MONTHS REQUIRED SKILLS: * Experience working with core Microsoft technologies including SQL Server and IIS. * Experience with… https://t.co/iEBbEHT5ed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Nintex Developer: Prestigious Enterprise Company is currently seeking a Developer with SharePoint and ****** experience, as well as some Nintex exposure. Candidate will be responsible for end-user… https://t.co/t72QZpzYkv 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: If you are creative; a self-starter who enjoys working with a collaborative team; have a passion to learn and work with new technologies; desire great job benefits; and require work / life… https://t.co/St1diU6qco 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Applications Systems Analyst (OBIEE): The Enterprise Business Systems department is responsible for development, maintenance and support of close to 150 administrative and financial applications including those… https://t.co/7uC2Y7Z0W0 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Linux/Java Software Engineers for Cognitive Search/Artificial Intelligence: Be in on the ground level of establishing the U.S. office for this fast-growing, leading global (European)provider of appliances and cloud… https://t.co/9Ypi9CNQLo 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid level Developer – JavaScript Sharepoint: Title Mid level Developer &amp;#8211; JavaScript &amp;#038; Sharepoint ============================================= EOE Statement We are an equal employment opportunity… https://t.co/v2L0n3Yphq 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Securities Operations Senior: Position Overview The group is responsible for assisting with work and projects related to securities operations of all mortgage backed securities issued by Freddie Mac. In addition,… https://t.co/yPl6PoipZC 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer – Office 365: Irvine Technology Corporation (ITC) is a leading provider of technology and staffing solutions for IT, Security, Engineering, and Interactive Design disciplines servicing startups… https://t.co/B6cLKQelZF 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Email System Administrator: Why Join Altec? If you&amp;#8217;re considering a career with Altec, Inc., there&amp;#8217;s never been a better time to join us! Our Company was founded based upon values that place the customer first, and view people as our greatest… https://t.co/NRrFofGyCJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Systems Administrator: JOB TITLE: SHAREPOINT SYSTEMS ADMINISTRATOR LOCATION: PEACHTREE CITY, GEORGIA CLEARANCE: ACTIVE SECRET CLEARANCE CITIZENSHIP: US CITIZEN POSITION OVERVIEW: Swingtech is seeking a talented SharePoint Systems Administrator… https://t.co/qFJpDD4VwJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Solutions Architect – Supervision Group: Job Summary Technology developer, designer, and innovator with a strong business orientation to create business-driven applications using SharePoint, Nintex and… https://t.co/s7eskn01pd 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CND Analyst (Network Senior) – 16399: Description Huntington Ingalls Industries &amp;#8211; Technical Solutions Division, Integrated Mission Solutions Group (Camber Corporation) provides mission-critical engineering… https://t.co/NIDNKhPtB7 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Developer/Architect SharePoint/Office 365/Angular: Portal Solutions (now part of the Withum Team) Microsoft Solutions and Service practice helps organizations share what they know and find what they need by… https://t.co/xtK4ViUPaR 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Securities Operations Prf: Position Overview The Payment &amp;#038; Disclosure group is responsible for the bond administration of all mortgage backed securities issued by Freddie Mac. This includes calculating monthly payments &amp;#038; disclosure data,… https://t.co/DYxgjlvtmk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Sharepoint &amp; collaboration: * worked on medium &amp;#8211; large size projects ($1 million +) * managed a team of 5-10 members or more * worked on a project that required them managing multiple… https://t.co/z9qT2g30fA 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Technologist-Applications: MicroVision is a dynamic company which is partnering with some of the world’s most recognized companies to bring solutions to the market which allow people to visually experience and share information in entirely… https://t.co/KXEqthCe2p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Help Desk Analyst: Associate Help Desk Analyst Why Work For Credit Acceptance? Credit Acceptance is rapidly-expanding our IT department with a variety of dynamic opportunities. Our culture has landed us… https://t.co/A5LvbpVgVA 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Development Requirements Analyst Job: Date: Feb 26, 2018 Location: Washington, DC, US Company: SAIC SharePoint Development Requirements Analyst (Job Number:434441) Description: Job Description &amp;#8211; This contract position is a key member of… https://t.co/GZk4euLfgr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Project Manager II: CenturyLink (NYSE: CTL) is a global communications and IT services company focused on connecting its customers to the power of the digital world. CenturyLink offers network and data systems management, big data analytics,… https://t.co/Ycvp3fXvFl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Management Specialist 15385: Camber Corporation is seeking a Database Programming and Data AnalysisSpecialistto join our diverse, team-oriented company that is customer focused &amp;#8211; employee driven. The successful candidate will join our team… https://t.co/a6MU9yTWNU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leica CL: Snap Candids in Style With This Discreet New Camera: While potential photographic subjects would shy away from a DSLR-wielding tourist, barely a soul would notice a box as compact as Leica’s CL. https://t.co/5jtIG7AZ4b #Gear #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/SQpJGWKpJh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Nintex Developer: Prestigious Enterprise Company is currently seeking a Developer with SharePoint and ****** experience, as well as some Nintex exposure. Candidate will be responsible for end-user computing development using the Microsoft… https://t.co/Vnz1FnIU7l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tier 3 UC Application Engineer – Microsoft: Company Description Arkadin is focused on bringing businesses into the future by delivering Cloud Communication services that drive productivity and provide a seamless… https://t.co/0GGFzKOYYX 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: If you are creative; a self-starter who enjoys working with a collaborative team; have a passion to learn and work with new technologies; desire great job benefits; and require work / life balance &amp;#8211; we are looking for YOU! The… https://t.co/ie71KgF2u0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Nintex Developer: Prestigious Enterprise Company is currently seeking a Developer with SharePoint and ****** experience, as well as some Nintex exposure. Candidate will be responsible for end-user… https://t.co/CXMm6mT4rY 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Assurance Systems Engineer Level 2- 15870: Camber Corporation has an opening for a Cybersecurity Systems Engineer Level2 located inVirginia Beach, VA. The Cybersecurity Systems Engineer-Level2 will provide cybersecurity engineering supportto… https://t.co/fdLSbZ3RMf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Developer/Architect SharePoint/Office 365/Angular: Portal Solutions (now part of the Withum Team) Microsoft Solutions and Service practice helps organizations share what they know and find what they need by… https://t.co/wn4PN7xqd9 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Development Requirements Analyst Job: Date: Feb 26, 2018 Location: Washington, DC, US Company: SAIC SharePoint Development Requirements Analyst (Job Number:434441) Description: Job Description &amp;#8211;… https://t.co/ZwwRw34KaK 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Administrator/Developer: JOB DESCRIPTION: Resource 1 is seeking a SharePoint Administrator/Developer for a 6-month contract-for-hire opportunity in Chicago, IL. The selected candidate should have experience in Microsoft Technologies,… https://t.co/MgY1oTYLeW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead, Network Operations Engineer: Job Description Position Summary Network Operations Lead will be responsible for overseeing the day-to-day management and operations of the data and voice networks… https://t.co/Cc7Mu9ozyH 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer Sr.: Responsible for the design, deployment, maintenance, configuration, availability, monitoring, troubleshooting of a SharePoint Farm within a multi-site Data Center internal application portfolio… https://t.co/peUk3fRtrC 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Project Manager (CMDB)- Contract: Configuration Management Project Manager. Need a strong PM who knows what to do (minimal hand-holding) and knows when to escalate. Strengths include removing roadblocks, identifying priorities, and moving the… https://t.co/Dn1MVYdXqg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Block Calls and Texts on iPhone in iOS 11: Unwanted calls and messages arriving on your iPhone? Block 'em all with our guide. https://t.co/qLUC747knQ #Gear #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/ygHkNVWx2Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Consultant – Analyst/Developer/Administrator: CRI Advantage is looking for a SharePoint consultant to work with our federal client based out of Boise, Idaho. There will be some Pacific Northwest travel on a monthly basis to service satellite… https://t.co/ZYx9lQftGP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Security – Senior Developer: Supports the development, configuration, testing and deployment and integration of PeopleSoft/OIAM Application Security for the IPPS-A project. Provides support for systems… https://t.co/LhIbFoa1Yj 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Team Lead Job: Date: Mar 9, 2018 Location: Washington, DC, US Company: SAIC SharePoint Team Lead (Job Number:432851) Description: Job Description This contract position is the lead member of a SharePoint… https://t.co/FNPtjAFV3R 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Systems Administrator: JOB TITLE: SHAREPOINT SYSTEMS ADMINISTRATOR LOCATION: PEACHTREE CITY, GEORGIA CLEARANCE: ACTIVE SECRET CLEARANCE CITIZENSHIP: US CITIZEN POSITION OVERVIEW: Swingtech is seeking a… https://t.co/bOnZOCMqHY 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator – Honolulu: System Administrators at Intech are the foundation of our team. They are our customer champions, the fixer of all things broken, and the jacks of all trades. They are the heros… https://t.co/6h8vm9k1u3 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Systems Analyst – Division of Supervision and Regulation: The Information Systems Analyst is responsible for the design, implementation, and support of complex automated distributed systems essential to… https://t.co/NNRZfe8TK3 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Email System Administrator: Why Join Altec? If you&amp;#8217;re considering a career with Altec, Inc., there&amp;#8217;s never been a better time to join us! Our Company was founded based upon values that place the… https://t.co/KYZVKFSEpr 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Contract Developer: _Come help us write great software._ Polaris is looking for software contract developers to work for 6 &amp;#8211; 9 months. We are looking for strong and passionate individuals who are ready for a… https://t.co/LRlfoQJaX1 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ET Developer – SharePoint/.NET: Requisition Number 18-0535 Post Date 3/12/2018 Title ET Developer &amp;#8211; SharePoint/.NET Part Time? No City Memphis State TN Description The ET Developer – SharePoint is a web… https://t.co/68Ix1qAJuB 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior SharePoint Technical Developer Lead: Companyhas an excellent opportunity for a hands-on Senior SharePoint Developer to oversee a Development Team. This person will be directing a team of highly skilled… https://t.co/K0CC5pajzr 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Help Desk Technician: The Helpdesk Technician manages and monitors the IT helpdesk and handles direct support requests from IT operations support program client end users. Helpdesk technician work will generally… https://t.co/qibbysVeXZ 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Architect – Chicago, IL: Job Type:PermanentDate Posted:12th February 2018Location:Chicago, IllinoisContact Name:Christopher CriscuoloTelephone:Reference:NFI272018CC2 Salary:$100000 &amp;#8211; $120000 per… https://t.co/TXZBO79z4Y 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Solutions Architect – Supervision Group: Job Summary Technology developer, designer, and innovator with a strong business orientation to create business-driven applications using SharePoint, Nintex and… https://t.co/JMCbFm3Mgz 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer Systems Analyst Subject Matter Expert 16496: Technical Solutions Description Huntington Ingalls Industries &amp;#8211; Technical Solutions Division, Integrated Mission Solutions Group (Camber Corporation)… https://t.co/VFgQGcCWCu 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Applications Software Engineer III: Overview Do you excel in an environment that values exploration and discovery? We have a universe of opportunities waiting for you! The Jet Propulsion Laboratory (JPL)… https://t.co/MiUf2XBb9T 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Manager: Are you a problem solver? Do you strive to make a positive difference? Do you enjoy being a contributor to a world class team? Summit Technical Solutions (STS) is seeking a Database Manager to… https://t.co/ZtFhVvDDNX 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer – Office 365: Irvine Technology Corporation (ITC) is a leading provider of technology and staffing solutions for IT, Security, Engineering, and Interactive Design disciplines servicing startups… https://t.co/WABkN9V8sV 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Systems Engineer: Req ID 1267BR Recruiter Matthew Jones Industry Job Title Sr Systems Engineer Internal Position Title Sr. Systems Engineer Employment Status Regular Full-time Location Colorado Springs, CO… https://t.co/Jf7wA9gkve 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Development Requirements Analyst Job: Date: Feb 26, 2018 Location: Washington, DC, US Company: SAIC SharePoint Development Requirements Analyst (Job Number:434441) Description: Job Description &amp;#8211;… https://t.co/tP0NIrCNyB 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint and O365 Developer: Description: THE COMPANY Are you interested in helping solve today&amp;#8217;s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work… https://t.co/9WW9cVNhzN 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid level Developer – JavaScript Sharepoint: Title Mid level Developer &amp;#8211; JavaScript &amp;#038; Sharepoint ============================================= EOE Statement We are an equal employment opportunity… https://t.co/PxnsNtwKEh 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Admininistrator / Developer: SharePoint Admininistrator / Developer Location: Herndon, VA Job Code: 3200 # of openings: 1 Description Bay State Computers, Inc. is a professional services firm and a… https://t.co/jaCdE3yYyo 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: Jobs Toggle navigation * Sign In * Sign Up * Help Career Portal * Failure Message Cannot parse, seems some issue with the profile, please create the profile manually Alert Message Job Post has… https://t.co/jgl1nRRH60 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: Kore 1 Jobs Page ************&amp;#124;************** &amp;#8211; Services &amp;#8211; Workforce Planning &amp;#8211; Software Development &amp;#8211; IT Strategy &amp;#8211; Staffing Solutions &amp;#8211; Technology… https://t.co/vvzmOPh5zP 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HTC Vive Gets $100 Price Cut, Vive Pro Launches For $799: The HTC Vive VR system is finally getting affordable as the new Vive Pro goes up for preorder. https://t.co/Hj5cCjzbKp #Gear #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/DM76D3lFm3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spectrum ETL Analyst: Client Reference Code: 214068JOB SUMMARYResponsible for successful development, maintenance, and delivery of data-driven financial and sales reporting and data analysis for the Sales… https://t.co/5wew17kU6D 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Sharepoint &amp; collaboration: * worked on medium &amp;#8211; large size projects ($1 million +) * managed a team of 5-10 members or more * worked on a project that required them managing multiple… https://t.co/ShH5mbXNKw 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Architect: Enterprise Content Management Consultants We are currently seeking experienced Microsoft SharePoint Developers, Architects and ECM/RM Consultants with exceptional consulting skills and the… https://t.co/wBdwcadlAC 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior IT Specialist: Company Description Wi-Tronix provides products and services to wirelessly monitor high-value mobile assets such as locomotives, industrial equipment, and marine vessels. Mobile assets of this… https://t.co/dN6y7vyPud 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer TS/SCI: Point Developer TS/SCI &amp;#8211; SBG Technology Solutions Menu &amp;#8211; About &amp;#8211; &amp;#8211; About &amp;#8211; Message From CEO &amp;#8211; Leadership Team &amp;#8211; Corporate Responsibility… https://t.co/girN5X3sXV 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. SharePoint Specialist: Job Location: Little Creek, VA Job Title: Senior SharePoint Specialist Position Summary DRS Seeks a full time Senior SharePoint Specialist (SPS) to support the Enterprise Knowledge… https://t.co/3BJ0WwQFhr 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT System Management Capability Lead: Job Number: R0020261 Booz Allen Hamilton has been at the forefront of strategy and technology for more than 100 years. Today, the firm provides management and technology… https://t.co/bM36QMWpCz 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Team Lead Job: Date: Mar 9, 2018 Location: Washington, DC, US Company: SAIC SharePoint Team Lead (Job Number:432851) Description: Job Description This contract position is the lead member of a SharePoint… https://t.co/4XD9np9tyK 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Solutions Architect – Supervision Group: Job Summary Technology developer, designer, and innovator with a strong business orientation to create business-driven applications using SharePoint, Nintex and… https://t.co/SamvGHsCIT 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Specialist, Order Implementation – Spectrum Enterprise: Client Reference Code: 214427 About Spectrum Enterprise Spectrum Enterprise, a part of Charter Communications, is a national provider of scalable,… https://t.co/H2MqnhODTx 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Sharepoint Architect: Requisition Number 18-0077 Post Date 2/16/2018 Title Senior Sharepoint Architect City Houston State TX Description Founded in 1886, Buckeye Partners has a proven track record of… https://t.co/1QVkE9548h 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ET Developer – SharePoint/.NET: Requisition Number 18-0535 Post Date 3/12/2018 Title ET Developer &amp;#8211; SharePoint/.NET Part Time? No City Memphis State TN Description The ET Developer – SharePoint is a web… https://t.co/sgNHHqGsPW 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Consultant – Analyst/Developer/Administrator: CRI Advantage is looking for a SharePoint consultant to work with our federal client based out of Boise, Idaho. There will be some Pacific Northwest travel… https://t.co/6aW0dhvskX 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Development, Senior (SharePoint): Position Overview The Single-Family SharePoint Team is seeking a SharePoint Development Senior to assist in SharePoint 2013 Projects by analyzing the business needs and translating… https://t.co/4UPtKvhi1y 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior IT Specialist: Company Description Wi-Tronix provides products and services to wirelessly monitor high-value mobile assets such as locomotives, industrial equipment, and marine vessels. Mobile assets of this… https://t.co/VkBdWeA06c 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Sec Controls Administrator (IT): Does this sound like you? Are you ambitious? Want to make a difference in how your company operates? Are you a change leader? Do you thrive in an environment that leverages… https://t.co/LHonceLFx3 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: Jobs Toggle navigation * Sign In * Sign Up * Help Career Portal * Failure Message Cannot parse, seems some issue with the profile, please create the profile manually Alert Message Job Post has… https://t.co/VxPpRWKUj0 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developers: JOB DESCRIPTION Software Developers, Systems Software (work in Northville, MI &amp;#038; various unanticipated locations throughout US) to research, design, develop and test software using 1 or… https://t.co/RMtrUd9J8e 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Solutions Architect – Supervision Group: Job Summary Technology developer, designer, and innovator with a strong business orientation to create business-driven applications using SharePoint, Nintex and… https://t.co/yBmJLHXLZW 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Architect – Chicago, IL: Job Type:PermanentDate Posted:12th February 2018Location:Chicago, IllinoisContact Name:Christopher CriscuoloTelephone:Reference:NFI272018CC2 Salary:$100000 &amp;#8211; $120000 per… https://t.co/dM5m3lpF2z 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Nintex Developer: Prestigious Enterprise Company is currently seeking a Developer with SharePoint and ****** experience, as well as some Nintex exposure. Candidate will be responsible for end-user… https://t.co/Agc0pU32Ye 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: Kore 1 Jobs Page ************&amp;#124;************** &amp;#8211; Services &amp;#8211; Workforce Planning &amp;#8211; Software Development &amp;#8211; IT Strategy &amp;#8211; Staffing Solutions &amp;#8211; Technology… https://t.co/4JvSLQCyYe 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Specialist II/Sr (JAVA) (2 positions): IT Specialist II/Sr (JAVA) (2 positions) Job Number: 1600620 Description This position is responsible for providing leadership and technical deliverables in the design,… https://t.co/bybRYjCSx8 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Architect: Send This Job to a Friend LinkedIn Google+ Facebook Twitter Email Department CCHS Information Services Schedule Full-Time Shift Days Req Number 39067 Job Details Summary: The Software Architect… https://t.co/7pwnywJ3EP 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Online Developer Job: Date: Mar 2, 2018 Location: Washington, DC, US Company: SAIC SharePoint Online Developer (Job Number:434597) Description: Job Description: &amp;#8211; This contract position is a member… https://t.co/1rHI66Urwx 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer Analyst(SSRS): JOB DESCRIPTION We are looking for a SharePoint / SSRS Report Developer. This person will work closely with our Business stakeholders and IT team members to develop solutions and enhance… https://t.co/BcLs1rCUyJ 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[systems engineer: Company Description Commvault is the world&amp;#8217;s most powerful backup and recovery software in the cloud and on any infrastructure, helping companies transform their data into a powerful… https://t.co/qwGBFyhBe4 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT ERP Help Desk Support Specialist: The Business Systems Support Specialist – Technical’s primary responsibility is to provide business system technical help desk support. Creates, evaluates and tests new… https://t.co/82vgQ5oo50 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Nintex Developer: Prestigious Enterprise Company is currently seeking a Developer with SharePoint and ****** experience, as well as some Nintex exposure. Candidate will be responsible for end-user… https://t.co/LEd4fKKRFV 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer – Office 365: Irvine Technology Corporation (ITC) is a leading provider of technology and staffing solutions for IT, Security, Engineering, and Interactive Design disciplines servicing startups… https://t.co/C6ODHnuC7Q 👈#sharepoint #job #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>