<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes as much energy to wish as it does to plan!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The difference between try and triumph is just a little umph! - Marvin Phillips]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Andy Gibb  http://t.co/nGGK2jv4ED]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wanted to make the lightest shoe possible, but still be able to perform at the same time. - Carmelo Anthony]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adversity causes some men to break; others to break records. - William A. Ward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science fiction, outside of poetry, is the only literary field which has no limits, no parameters whatsoever. - Theodore Sturgeon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In order to break the ice --  crack a smile]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best augury of a man's success in his profession is that he thinks it the finest in the world. - George Eliot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Barbara Mason  http://t.co/E6pKsa3CrI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fall seven times, stand up eight. - Japanese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would be more frightened as a writer if people thought my movies were like science fiction. - Neil LaBute]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn The Importance of a Good Pitching Repertoire for Young Pitchers  http://t.co/aj5ds4qqgk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is the only major sport that appears backward in a mirror. - George Carlin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Great Book - The Majestic Tree of Life  http://t.co/qSmogX0MlW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of James Brown  http://t.co/sMwt0Zdf9B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do women want? Shoes. --&gt; Mimi Pond]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Fun - Bumper Water Boats with Water Cannons! http://t.co/guEer6fW8I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Ray Conniff  http://t.co/tJRY7ppmOi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every boy should have two things: a dog, and a mother willing to let him have one - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laverne and Shirley is an American sitcom classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/CROYJ7xd8H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Play is the only way the highest intelligence of humankind can unfold. - Joseph Chilton Pearce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Tips on Using Other Websites for Link Building  http://t.co/glsH1cEG3s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Top Science and Tech Websites  http://t.co/4aYqd4gsgd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating history of Wrigley Field!  http://t.co/pNy8eOWcLd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its Real - You Can Print Shoes with a 3D Printer!  http://t.co/agyaqCzZRx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Grand Slam in Tennis – what's the big deal?  http://t.co/iaj0ONxDBp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't preach a boy about his problems. Just remind him that you, too , were a Nincompoop at his age.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't be melancholy in fashion because people don't respond to it. - Isaac Mizrahi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We thought you was a toad! - Delmar, O Brother Where Art Thou?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Bobby Darin    http://t.co/PnvPMM8QRD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He looks like a girl.  Marlon Brando on Leonardo DiCaprio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jin Kwon: Good... to see... you. Sawyer: Well look at that! Somebody's hooked on phonics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A philosopher is someone who knows what to do until it happens to him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Julius LaRosa  http://t.co/kw0YFD8Dfe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips for Using Facebook Pages for Your Business  http://t.co/eNbYyjE9d8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Rolling Stones  http://t.co/yitgIbkyNw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blogging Lost – Season 1  http://t.co/CeLB432GkR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Using Instagram for Web Marketing  http://t.co/VHPz0xZDMM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the American Hamburger  http://t.co/bt7Tdahb83]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome cooking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the cooking lovers in your life!   http://t.co/1RqbMvp8Zs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need to be able to rock out.  - Bryan Adams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow the whiskey.  - Kid Rock, who arrived with "Redneck Woman" singer Gretchen Wilson, on his plans after the Country Music Awards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hops Holster 12 Can Ammo Pack - Beer Anywhere!  http://t.co/HRrkqu1Z0b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must remain focused on your journey to greatness. - Les Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Modern Homesteading  http://t.co/5UZqgL0pX1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Blue Origin - A Profile of This Emerging Space Company  http://t.co/1ZxoHPhzFh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Carlos Santana  http://t.co/gJWzCHh2Y6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My life is an open book. With illustrations.  Hugh Hefner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The kindness planned for tomorrow doesn't count for today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Bonnie Lou  http://t.co/4CpDNjdgMk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Petula Clark  http://t.co/a95zepGVTO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't be afraid to get creative and experiment with your marketing.  Mike Volpe - CMO - Hubspot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellence is to do a common thing in an uncommon way. - Booker T. Washington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball has the great advantage over cricket of being sooner ended. - George Bernard Shaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really &amp; truly you can never have 2 many pairs of shoes. You need a pair for every mood &amp; everyone knows women have lots of moods. Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's recording techniques would have been regarded as science fiction forty years ago. - Tony Visconti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you love James Bond?  Check out these cool t-shirts, hats, stickers and more --&gt;  http://t.co/yo2ViWY3cK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The key to wisdom is a knowledge of our own ignorance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Blue Oyster Cult   http://t.co/yhhS70kl5w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Parliament  http://t.co/zD6M8HFx46]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education ... has produced a vast population able to read but unable to distinguish what is worth reading. - G. M. Trevelyan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 7 - No Luck!  http://t.co/Ch063MTVkS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plastic surgeons can do almost anything with a nose these days, except keep it out of other people's business]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If my uniform doesn't get dirty, I haven't done anything in the baseball game - Rickey Henderson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Michael Jordan Shoes  http://t.co/xLkYdWFpg4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Rose Royce  http://t.co/UBdXwZ0Etx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Mike Clifford - A One-Hit Wonder  http://t.co/tKfAlbvqa2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of George Harrison  http://t.co/0Cv6SFvQzz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adults are always asking little kids what they want to be when they grow up because they're looking for ideas... Paula Poundstone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Product Reviews Through the Eyes of a Child  http://t.co/ryehC5JYXp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think MTV should consider using subtitles. Half the time, even I can't understand what the **** I'm talking about.  Ozzy Osbourne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You’ve got to give us Americans a lot of credit.  How else could we buy a new car every year?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Brady Bunch is an American sitcom classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/eLfm0QMCZ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The Best of ABBA  http://t.co/l8fhQyGLxT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Increasingly, the mass marketing is turning into a mass of niches - Christ Anderson Author of The Long Tail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tantrums, Sick Days, and Being a Patient Mommy  http://t.co/I87reHlBWq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Best Tips Given for Facebook Pages Geared for Business  http://t.co/6CcG743RnP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am for conversations.  But you need to have a message.  Rennee Blodgett - President Blodgett Communications]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's face it: The teeth are getting more and more British every day. I look in the mirror and see Austin Powers staring at me.  Hugh Grant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yum! Even MORE Brownie's Edge In This Baker's Edge Nonstick Pan  http://t.co/lBV3cWmgIq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out Crimson Mine’s awesome Tumblr page... http://t.co/slQB4Y8I3g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If high heels were so wonderful, men would be wearing them. - Sue Grafton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future is always beginning now. - Mark Strand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 9 - Appointment With Another LLMD  http://t.co/VKO78I3eJq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All arguments have two sides, but some have no ends.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About why Kids Love to Read and Review  http://t.co/HUIjwRvw3c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Mary Hopkin  http://t.co/4NkOCUtzwV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to Tumblr Blogging  http://t.co/dXG65771xB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Profanity is a strong way to express a weak mind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I went to college for four years. - Kim Kardashian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Brownsville Station  http://t.co/owKC5jqx7e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't realize how strong a person really is until you see them at their weakest moment. - Unknown Author]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your attitude determines your altitude! - Denis Waitley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding the Right Fitness Gadgets  http://t.co/bMzGngVFpg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't go into details, I've already told you  more than I overheard myself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I won't be a rock star. I will be a legend. - Freddie Mercury]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Adam Faith  http://t.co/QPSv6yA9Cz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pair off in threes. - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Canada - Just Across the border and Beautiful! http://t.co/OZekMN9AHt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Kim Carnes  http://t.co/5iWoA3Zhhj]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>