<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GiBillRights: Important news article out this morning from @AmericanBanker_ on why #veterans #military and @DeptofDefense oppose @CFPB…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SarahSpain: “A Star Is Born.” Shit. 

Lived up to the hype. Gutting. Amazing performances. Beautiful, beautiful music.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AshleeMPreston: Welp...it’s official...Kim Kardashian finally decided to divorce Kanye West... https://t.co/C2p25mxWJO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GiBillRights: Read the Veterans Education Success report on @ACICSaccredits here: https://t.co/4cKYqsQ4VF https://t.co/p1B88QRNuc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GiBillRights: Our analysis found:

❌70% of students at ACICS-approved colleges earn no more than a high school graduate https://t.co/72…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DaHalperin: Latest @BetsyDeVos @usedgov effort to stack deck in #4profit #highered rulemaking meetings: Eliminating seats at the table…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoa! Federal data shows #ACICS students are worse off than when it was terminated in 2016, and vast majority are left worse off than if they'd never attended - just as political appointees at @usedgov want to override career staff to resurrect it.  
https://t.co/7sOHlBhq6p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nikkiwentling: A new lawsuit alleges the VA is unlawfully withholding records that would show the extent of influence 3 Mar-a-Lago memb…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Bob_Shireman: It appears to be an implementation of the @hlcommission requirement that colleges identify their important constituencies…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Bob_Shireman: What is this boring, legalistic advertisement that appeared in the print edition of the Sacramento Bee? It asks for input…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BillKristol: Putin’s killing people in the U.K., the Chinese regime has created a massive Uighur gulag, and the Saudis have murdered a…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MotherJones: USA Today published a remarkably dishonest op-ed by Donald Trump today, wherein the president completely misrepresents his…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Policy: At Twitter, we believe privacy is a fundamental right, not a privilege. Learn more about our privacy policy here: https://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CREWcrew: “They buy apartments from me. They spend $40 million, $50 million. Am I supposed to dislike them?” - @realDonaldTrump on the…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NBCNightlyNews: USA Today criticized for printing Trump op-ed despite alleged inaccuracies. https://t.co/tkq2Z64Sn4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SenBlumenthal: We need to do more to make sure the public service loan forgiveness program is working for all who utilize it. Navient s…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LeoShane: VA leaders won't turn over documents to Congress related to Mar-a-Lago businessmen influencing department policy. https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A leading theology professor attests he heard about #Kavanaugh pushing his penis in Ramirez's face at the time it happened. https://t.co/ziUNIe3HWL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jenniferweiner: “Emotional women, loud women, angry women get ignored. Emotional, loud, angry men get to sit on the Supreme Court. They…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CarlosMonjeJr: Twitter teams up with local broadcasters to livestream select debates https://t.co/02lYL0khkK via @usatoday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nytimes: With tears welling in her eyes, Heidi Heitkamp stared intently at a reporter and said: “And I want you to put this in there, i…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GiBillRights: .@DeptofDefense just launched a new career pathway exploration and planning tool called Career Path #DECIDE. Check it out…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EduBenM: These aren't ringing letters of endorsement--they're the equivalent of verifying employment. In fact, ED career staff looked a…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EduBenM: The only agency that appears to have looked at ACICS's standards and approved them is ARRTS. And it isn't recognized by ED. I'…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EduBenM: But let's look at these 5 agencies listed now. Here are screenshots of those for ACOTE, CAPTE, ACEN, and ABHES. Only one of th…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EduBenM: Here's the original text (with the highlights) and the suggested replacement. What stands out? Only 1 of the 9 agencies shows…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EduBenM: As @mstratford reported last night, ED got caught fabricating the endorsements of major accreditation agencies for ACICS and b…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ColinCrowell: Climate report details what to expect from climate change, and how to limit it - CNN https://t.co/j7GJAa6hcK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Acosta: Experts say only drastic, immediate change can save us from the dangers of climate change
https://t.co/CYfxDZ9SOb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TwitterMoments: Taylor Swift has broken her silence about her political views, endorsing Democratic candidates for the midterm election…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmericanAir Can u please have someone from HQ confirm that you will institute a policy at @AmericanAir to inform passengers immediately of a flight cancellation?  Passengers deserve transparency]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmericanAir American Air gate agents tell me there is no policy requiring them to announce a flight cancellation.  

Are you serious?  

Please tell me you will widely distribute clear instructions to gate agents on how to handle a cancellation and on basic politeness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@AmericanAir yet another cancellation for mechanical failure, followed by terrible customer service. Fix your planes!  And teach your gate agents some basic courtesy!  You need to clean up your act!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Important fact-check https://t.co/OgVQpk0gZ5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RadioFreeTom: You're not surprised, I know, but here it is. | "The Republican Party...is now the party of situational ethics and moral…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Nate_Cohn: Probably relatedly, this is also the pattern in our polls. Dems have comfortably led enough of our polls to be at +18. There…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Evan_McMullin: .@RadioFreeTom: “The Republican Party, which controls all three branches of government and yet is addicted to whining ab…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jwgop: This from the Russia Today correspondent. Need I say more? https://t.co/Xgtod5kDN9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nbcsnl: The FBI investigation into Brett Kavanaugh got a little help from #SVU's Benson and Fin. #SNL https://t.co/yNku7wUUvp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nbcsnl: "We couldn't have done it without Susan Collins." — Sen. Lindsey Graham #SNL https://t.co/m1hfjgoWI4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nbcsnl: Sen. Lindsey Graham from inside the GOP locker room after the Kavanaugh confirmation. #SNL https://t.co/PMHU3AjeYY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nbcsnl: Sen. Mitch McConnell on the Kavanaugh confirmation. #SNL https://t.co/rafJZuJTh2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nbcsnl: We take you live inside the GOP locker room, where the mood is nothing short of euphoric. #SNL https://t.co/Z3uMNjss86]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nytimes: Our investigation revealed that Donald Trump received the equivalent today of at least $413 million from his father’s real est…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MotherJones: Impeaching Brett Kavanaugh is a liberal fantasy. Give it up. https://t.co/Z1XstJkJcm https://t.co/uIwIafcIfm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PostBaron: Turkey concludes that prominent journalist Jamal Khashoggi was killed in Saudi consulate, two people familiar with the probe…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RogerPielkeJr: Fixing procedures &amp; restoring norms no easy task but not impossible. 
Consider: 3D Blue Dog Senators &amp; 3R Main Street Se…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @gelles: Supreme Court Nominations Senate Votes:

Gorsuch  54-45
Garland  n/a
Kagan 63-37
Sotomayor 68-31
Alito 58-42
Miers n/a
Roberts…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CarolLeonnig: EXCLUSIVE Chief Justice Roberts has received many misconduct complaints against Kavanaugh from a fellow judge based on Se…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@realDonaldTrump's leadership  at work https://t.co/1jGTDmKbhW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ChuckModi1: Thought he’d just focus on Kavanaugh. Instead he gave best response on rape culture I’ve ever heard from a man! 
I aspire t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the public had turned out in force like this for #MerrickGarland, they might have forced the Senate to hold a hearing and a vote, rather than ignoring him for 300 + days #SCOTUS #KavanaughVote https://t.co/YwmbGbkV6m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HeidiPrzybyla: .@NBC exclusive:
Kavanaugh Yale classmates ignored by the FBI speak out, reveal new text message about Kavanaugh advisin…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @costareports: Sen. Flake, heading into chamber, tells me the Senate has “hit bottom.”

I ask why so many lawmakers keep using that spec…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JoeNBC: 2001: Bush inherits $155 billion surplus
2009: Bush leaves $1 trillion deficit and doubles the debt

Trump Republicans are on p…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such a cop out. Either you have something to say prior to the vote, or you don't.  #ABA https://t.co/vQkgjSvBb0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FailStateMovie: It's with great pride to share news almost six years in the making. Today @THR announced that #FailStateMovie will be r…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lisamurkowski: Tonight I spoke on the Senate floor on my decision to oppose the nomination of Judge Brett Kavanaugh to serve on the Uni…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/JvMsSoDXRW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @johnrobertsFox: .@WhiteHouse sources tell @FoxNews Manchin called this morning to inform them he was a "yes" on Kavanaugh.  That was lo…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nobel Peace Prize goes to a rape victim who spoke out https://t.co/3LEWTo20vv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is bad. They need to stop the partisan attacks. https://t.co/6wPUQVcrYQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RVAwonk: WH Deputy Press Secretary Raj Shah just told @CNN that Kavanaugh doesn't known Deborah Ramirez and has never spoken to her.

.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MarkHertling: Is it me or is it strange that the Kremlin/Putin are even taking the time to express an opinion on who the US is putting…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mikeitzkowitz: However, when @mstratford reached out to those accreditors, most of them said, nope, we did not submit anything. This me…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mikeitzkowitz: ERROR IN @USEDGOV JUSTIFICATION RECOMMENDING #ACICS FOR APPROVAL.

Dian Auer Jones stated to DeVos that #ACICS had recei…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mstratford: The @usedgov report last wk cited “letters of support” for ACICS from nine other accreditors, but many of those other accre…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mstratford: Trump administration's report recommending federal approval of for-profit college accreditor ACICS cited a series of endors…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EduBenM: This especially matters because both the 2016 ED analysis and the 2018 draft staff report raised concerns about lack of suppor…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EduBenM: Here's where ED claims that 9 agencies endorsed ACICS on page 24 of Diane Auer Jone's decision. It's not just a list. ED itsel…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kavanaugh's drinking buddies: "No one should be able to lie their way onto the Supreme Court. Honesty is the glue that holds together a society of laws. Lies are the solvent that dissolves those bonds." https://t.co/HxOy9G2SXb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I believe that an independent and impartial judiciary is essential to our constitutional republic. If confirmed by the Senate to serve on the Supreme Court, I will keep an open mind in every case and always strive to preserve the Constitution and the American rule of law."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AP: BREAKING: Supreme Court nominee Brett Kavanaugh is acknowledging he "might have been too emotional" in Senate testimony but says he…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Important from #Kavanaugh tonight:  He apologizes for the partisan outburst and commits to being a nonpartisan impartial judge.  He's got the votes.  This is key for the legitimacy of the SCt #SCOTUS 
https://t.co/Pq9gcv9x5r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @landpsychology: Every bunny was kung-fu fighting https://t.co/3fRH9ug9G6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CarolLeonnig: This is scalding https://t.co/Nc1D0zwAQR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PaulRieckhoff: Asking for help is a sign of strength, not weakness. Jason Kander is what a leader looks like. “KS mayoral candidate wit…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/CUiMyGmzMn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kylegriffin1: Current and former FBI officials confirmed to NBC News that dozens of witnesses have come forward to FBI field offices wh…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PaulRieckhoff: This is what a hero looks like. @IAVA #VetsRising https://t.co/hvRSKu8iIc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NormEisen: The “Bart” signature also is evidence that Kav is the “Bart O’Kavanaugh” depicted in Mark Judge’s book. https://t.co/c76ZrNk…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @samstein: One risk being run by GOPers here is that the FBI doesn’t interview these 20-40 witnesses that apparently want to be intervie…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @iava: We’re still out here on the @NationalMallNPS as the 5,520 flags stand representing the veteran and military deaths by suicide to…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kingWTOP: Flags on the Nat’l Mall to raise awareness about veteran suicides. @IAVA Iraq and Afghanistan Veterans of America works for v…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kingWTOP: 5,420 flags represent vets lost to suicide. @IAVA Iraq and Afghanistan Veterans of America is here on the Natl Mall to raise…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @iava: In our 2017 member survey, 65% of respondents know a post-9/11 veteran who has attempted suicide. 58% know a post-9/11 veteran th…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ConnectingVets: @iava placed 5,520 flags on the @NationalMallNPS to represent the number of veterans and active duty personnel that hav…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @iava: Our National Mall Activation around Veteran Suicide is underway. Volunteers, allies, and Stormers from our Fall #StormTheHill are…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BCAppelbaum: Do you know how high the bar is for the NYT to directly accuse someone, let alone a sitting president, of tax fraud, which…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @davidfrum: Worth noting that Trump also inherited the growing US economy he keeps boasting about]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ncweaver: And a timeline:
3 weeks ago @benjaminwittes strongly endorsed Kavanaugh.

A week and a half ago he gave advice on how Kavanau…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BBCJonSopel: Longstanding #BrettKavanaugh colleague says he's not fit to be on #SCOTUS: "I cannot condone the partisanship—which was ra…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ericmbudd: Brett Kavanaugh's opening statement "was an unprecedentedly partisan outburst of emotion from a would-be justice"

https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @andreagonram: A compelling essay by @benjaminwittes, who publicly supported Brett Kavanaugh but is now grappling with the aftermath of…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jbendery: Ben Wittes, editor-in-chief of Lawfare: I Know Brett Kavanaugh, but I Wouldn’t Confirm Him

"This is an article I never imagi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheAtlantic: "I have a long relationship with Kavanaugh and I have always liked him," writes @benjaminwittes, "but I wouldn't confirm h…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LeoShane: .@JasonKander: "I’m done hiding this from myself and from the world. When I wrote in my book that I was lucky to not have PTS…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mitchellreports: https://t.co/DTdCdjHkLY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @joshscampbell: Yikes. WaPo's @GregPMiller describes a tense moment from 2016 involving a CIA director trying to sound the alarm on Russ…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SenMarkey: In 2015, Brett #Kavanaugh delivered a speech at Catholic University titled “The Judge As Umpire,” outlining what he believes…]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>