<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Fifty per cent of rock is having a good time. - Roger Daltrey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Rufus Thomas  http://t.co/xZmREPDbnn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A comparison and History of Game Consoles  http://t.co/TkPuzIS0KU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome camping t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the camping lovers in your life!  http://t.co/RxRfUlU8Pm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A college is a place where pebbles are polished and diamonds dimmed. - Robert Ingersoll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read How Customer Connects Mount-Up with Social Media Sites  http://t.co/odyO9592qX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Foghat  http://t.co/Z6YccJrbHU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Joe Simon  http://t.co/CTEkvbrICW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So exactly how did the modern Garage evolve into its current form?  Very interesting... http://t.co/xuCiwafsaN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The needs of the many outweigh ... the needs of the few... Or the one. - Kirk and Spock - Star Trek II: The Wrath of Khan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I learned law so well, the day I graduated I sued the college, won the case, and got my tuition back. - Fred Allen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah Robe You Must Have - Star Wars Master Yoda Bathrobe! http://t.co/daaxhhA5yp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gluttony is an emotional escape, a sign something is eating us. - Peter De Vries]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the top science fiction books of all time!  http://t.co/GeMtqWgwAf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our Review of Amazon’s Popular Kindle Reader  http://t.co/wXM394clPP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be successful, the first thing to do is fall in love with your work. - Sister Mary Lauretta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one really knows who created Bitcoin - read about the fascinating history of Satoshi Nakamoto... http://t.co/0GquoAft73]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So say we all. - Battlestar Galactica]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction To http://t.co/mTAb3m6YKC  http://t.co/6QruNv8Spj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's human nature to stretch, to go, to see, to understand. Exploration is not a choice, really; it's an imperative. - Michael Collins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't be melancholy in fashion because people don't respond to it. - Isaac Mizrahi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must remain focused on your journey to greatness. - Les Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips for Using Facebook Pages for Your Business  http://t.co/u34GOFSsLj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good teaching is one-fourth preparation and three-fourths pure theatre. - Gail Godwin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Don Henley  http://t.co/KnjWAId9qQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't preach a boy about his problems. Just remind him that you, too , were a Nincompoop at his age.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the darkness of the world cannot put out the light on one small candle. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read about the Emerging Private Space Industry  http://t.co/mO8BgYV7lo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very very cool SpyHawk RC Plane with 3.5 inch LCD Monitor/Controller &amp; video recording &amp; auto-pilot system - HOT - http://t.co/piiLgqFCfm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't go into details, I've already told you  more than I overheard myself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids LOVE These Volcano Making Kit!  Fun and Educational! http://t.co/bqFymL75mr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Twilight Zone is a scifi TV classic - read its fascinating history here - http://t.co/VSizUpUWBu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't tell you what I had for breakfast, but I can sing every single word of rock and roll. - Patty Duke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the fascinating history of the Boston Red Sox - http://t.co/jyb6gC9wwl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fall seven times, stand up eight. - Japanese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I'm hungry, I eat. When I'm thirsty, I drink. When I feel like saying something, I say it. Madonna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overheard in hollywood: "You said their marriage wouldn't last! They left the church together, didn't they?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A mosquito is just like a child, when it stops making noise, you know it's getting into something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't call me a mindless philosopher, you overweight blob of grease! - C3PO, Star Wars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read a Review of Heaven is For Real  http://t.co/hDPRn2Gwda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Organizing Garage Cabinets and Storage  http://t.co/zZLgr2JjUD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gary US Bonds was an amazing musician and rocker - read his history - http://t.co/Nbtx0Zw9pp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to WordTracker SEO Tools http://t.co/pCMapiki34]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the The Early History of Beer  http://t.co/TPrff4qmWn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, give us the man who sings at his work. - Thomas Carlyle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still love her. But she's retarded, too. Guy Ritchie on Madonna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are no oaths that make many perjurers as the vows of love]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winners take time to relish their work, knowing that scaling the mountain is what makes the view from the top so exhilarating. Denis Waitley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Air Supply  http://t.co/RJy4rdvtER]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10-Light Star Wars Plastic Yoda Light Set - may the force be with you! http://t.co/FcIvpoSrzR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But I'm a rock 'n' roll singer; that's my livelihood, my occupation.  - Little Richard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Billy Joel  http://t.co/uPFTg4nJf5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Rolling Stones  http://t.co/YAuakkcFht]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poets are like baseball pitchers. Both have their moments. The intervals are the tough things. - Robert Frost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are 10 types of people in the world: those who understand binary, and those who don't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I want to knock a story off the front page, I just change my hairstyle. --&gt; Hillary Rodham Clinton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who think they know everything are especially annoying to those of us who do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give a girl the right shoes, and she can conquer the world. - Marilyn Monroe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's rough to go through life with your contents looking as if they settled during shipping. - Milton Berle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am alive and well and unconcerned about the rumors of my death. But if I were dead, I would be the last to know. - Paul McCartney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn Marketing Secrets for eCommerce Business  http://t.co/S1RvHdybFu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marvel's The Avengers - ALL FOUR Movies in one Collection - including The Avengers - VERY COOL!!!! http://t.co/XPsCut5TNf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What is Eating Paleo?  http://t.co/TY83RpWBet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge a man by how much he does when he doesn't need to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For Real!?!? - this is AWESOME - a Redneck Beer and Soda Can Holster! http://t.co/yjtqnY2fA6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About The Beginning Of Christian Religion  http://t.co/aFP586e1se]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're a very expensive group; we break a lot of rules. It's unheard of to combine opera with a rock theme, my dear. - Freddie Mercury]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jin Kwon: Good... to see... you. Sawyer: Well look at that! Somebody's hooked on phonics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Canada - Just Across the border and Beautiful! http://t.co/Ennhr87t5i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's an edge to real rock 'n' roll. It's all that matters. - Neil Young]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Locate Your Garage Space Before Installation Of Cabinets  http://t.co/QI4XeTPPLp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One family that practices population control:  the mafia!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a world without fences and walls, who needs Gates and Windows?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, I think we're the greatest rock 'n' roll band in the world.  - Joey Ramone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I raced a car last it was at a time when sex was safe and racing was dangerous. Now, it's the other way round. - Hans Stuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Mike Clifford - A One-Hit Wonder  http://t.co/cJRE0VYPUT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the top science fiction books of all time!  http://t.co/GeMtqWgwAf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I live by a simple philosophy: Wear fine shoes and enjoy the best luck. - Qiana Markham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Schnauzers  http://t.co/LF64DWUgAK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We thought you was a toad! - Delmar, O Brother Where Art Thou?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tantrums, Sick Days, and Being a Patient Mommy  http://t.co/KSj32rPp68]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yo, dudes. Got a new tourney lined up. We're playing for the last of the deodorant sticks. Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We didn't lose the game; we just ran out of time. - Vince Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Media is a Helpful Tool in Connecting with Customers  http://t.co/gKVQxRzR0x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With four pairs of shoes I can travel the world. - Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful Women Prefer Nerds! A Real Man's Guide on How to Find, Date, and Romance the Perfect Woman! http://t.co/5erTxxH7Yo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Billy J. Kramer and the Dakotas  http://t.co/YFTiOQrz0v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Book... The Shapeshifter  http://t.co/NHG0lQTCgR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Different Types of Major League Pitches  http://t.co/h6ev86sUfr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Humour. It is a difficult concept - Saavik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are so many emotions involved that I would like to wait until I know I'm with the right person &amp; married. Britney on virginity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having Fine Wine with Dinner - learn more! http://t.co/6V8uEba1aF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of the Inheritance Series Third Volume – Brisingr  http://t.co/MJPCrW6g3l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Maxine Brown  http://t.co/8lzSBUnLJE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attitude: It is our best friend or our worst enemy. - John C. Maxwell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think about it... Mistakes are just small steps to perfection...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read Great Outdoor Camping Equipment Tips  http://t.co/XEg1wq2zHn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women should look like women. A piece of cardboard has no sexuality. - Alexander McQueen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read The Life and Music of Rupert Holmes  http://t.co/SMiwblDHTP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The quickest way to get a doctor today is to turn on your television set. . .]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>