<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How Small Business Can Grow with Social Media Sites  http://t.co/vfRvxuAcTj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In order to break the ice --  crack a smile]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Transformer Autobot Cufflinks! http://t.co/QJQu4hbdmo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Lesley Gore  http://t.co/7yqE8bs3P5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The earth is the cradle of humankind, but one cannot live in the cradle forever. - Konstantin Tsiolkovsky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Green Acres is an American sitcom classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/qHupkOPrDC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow the whiskey.  - Kid Rock, who arrived with "Redneck Woman" singer Gretchen Wilson, on his plans after the Country Music Awards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What becomes of the broken-hearted? They buy shoes. - Mimi Pond]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame Quakecraft: FAILURE IS AN OPTION!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! http://t.co/fpsizqr8IQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So cool - German Beer Steins - check out their history - http://t.co/ng01CTXuKd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it bleeds, we can kill it.  - Predator]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is like a sixth sense - and you can't make use of the other five without it. - William Somerset Maugham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In any contest between power and patience -- bet on patience]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space Invaders Taito Astronaut Video Game T-Shirt Tee  http://t.co/psHBEKhTnE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating History of American Idol   http://t.co/XlAZMpXHwD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I could walk a mile in ur shoes but I already know they are just as uncomfortable as mine. Lets walk next to each other instead Lynda Meyers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips To Draw More Traffic With Quality Link Building  http://t.co/mD0NtWYTm3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep you can keep your devices charged via solar power - find out here - http://t.co/OAo6hKdxmH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Future of Blackberry  http://t.co/PS8Kph6Ql9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of McDonald's  http://t.co/2WBXSY0Thd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Donna Summer  http://t.co/4MzGl5FJSs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada has Great Tourism Just Across the Border  http://t.co/IUDKpGEjVl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't do fashion. I am fashion. - Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overview of Social Bookmarking Sites  http://t.co/RM64YgaJnq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to be the Cecil B. DeMille of science fiction. - Steven Spielberg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Rod Stewart  http://t.co/VJ1iGbyRAw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I am become Death, the destroyer of worlds - J. Robert Oppenheimer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Gloria Gaynor - The Queen of Disco  http://t.co/2VXppus3Qv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter Can be an Invaluable Business Tool  http://t.co/vXYUaKsocB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Star Trek Enterprise Pizza Cutter! http://t.co/sbO0En0EWY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Customer:  "Could I try on that suit in the window?"  Clerk:  "We'd rather you do that in the dressing room."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Top 10 Asian Beers  http://t.co/yYR9idPr9k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you know how hard it is to maintain cover while dancing the salsa in three-inch heels? - Syndey, Alias]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winners never quit and quitters never win. - Vince Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes are the quickest way for women to achieve instant metamorphosis - Manolo Blahnik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing Like Nerdy Babes and Nerdy Stuff --&gt;  http://t.co/qtq21vxkgL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gary US Bonds was an amazing musician and rocker - read his history - http://t.co/OnSCMIa8wM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Old age means realizing you will never own all the dogs you wanted to. - Joe Gores]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Steve Miller Band  http://t.co/QAXrA2awZz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man with a lot of money may be a bad egg, but folks seldom take offense until he is broke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Building an Effective Company Blog  http://t.co/y4mZzweomJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kate Austen: So what, I'm your prisoner? James 'Sawyer' Ford: If that sort of thing turns you on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caring For Your New Garage Floors  http://t.co/OGzDmuOo9s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is like a poker game, nobody wants to quit when he's losing: nobody wants you to quit when you're ahead. - Jackie Robinson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blow off some steam, or rather, shoot some smoke rings. The Zero Fog Blaster is a ray gun - totally cool!  http://t.co/8ByMclzIyV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I prefer the company of peasants because they have not been educated sufficiently to reason incorrectly. - Michel de Montaigne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL A Toilet Mug for your Coffee!  http://t.co/QUc0FLGLbX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A theory is a hunch with a college education]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money cant buy happiness, but it sure makes misery easier 2 live with!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does Food Dye Cause Hyperactive Behavior in Children?  http://t.co/PJCLmxDbnS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fascinating history of solar power - read on!  http://t.co/A8YeugB2Vn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A twelve-year-old Ben Linus brought me a chicken salad sandwich. How do you think I'm doing? - Sayid Jarrah, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The pessimist sees difficulty in every opportunity. The optimist sees opportunity in every difficulty. - Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Interesting Burger Facts and History  http://t.co/da3tfW5NMv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Gary Lewis and the Playboys  http://t.co/wh6jzW8WuF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some of the greatest Hollywood actors are not the award winners, but those congratulating them on their triumph]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Christians Making a Profession of their Religion  http://t.co/vZETn9kI9t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What is Chronic Lyme Disease?  http://t.co/IfFQrSKhI2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Tools for Finding Good Keywords  http://t.co/bdojIQysrw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read The Story of the Dramatics Classic Rock Group http://t.co/cT1TCwBa0K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The kindness planned for tomorrow doesn't count for today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The main part of intellectual education is not the acquisition of facts but learning how to make facts live." - Oliver Wendell Holmes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You gotta love the 80s and there was nothing better than the crazy fitness trends - http://t.co/S5nzn9ASrQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Budget: A domestic quarrel!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Using Instagram for Web Marketing  http://t.co/xuxb2peVQw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the Chitika Ad Network - An Alternate to Google AdSense  http://t.co/pM1MV8o8Yd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to John D. Loudermilk  http://t.co/wHbc52AwoK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wear my sort of clothes to save me the trouble of deciding which clothes to wear. - Katherine Hepburn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Power of Solar Power - Get Plugged In!  http://t.co/YXAKJk9Kaj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Trini Lopez    http://t.co/af2jYX25AS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Mike Clifford - A One-Hit Wonder  http://t.co/gsLlAfIIyI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bird does not sing because it has an answer...  It sings because it has a song. - Chinese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoot your co-workers with this Miniature Ballista Kit - Wooden Desktop Warfare Ballista - ROFL -  http://t.co/vKQULzS0z2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Johnnie Tayor  http://t.co/Ehufa6m8uU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One thing you get for more of your money these days is bills.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Monopoly Money Extra Long Tie - Fun! http://t.co/lcYzbhVPnO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How Small Business Can Grow with Social Media Sites  http://t.co/vfRvxuAcTj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I believe you are your work. Don't trade the stuff of your life, time, for nothing more than dollars. That's a rotten bargain - Rita  Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Auto racing, bull fighting, and mountain climbing are the only real sports --  all the others are games. - Ernest Hemingway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The man who is old enough to know better is always looking for a girl who is not quite old.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One Person’s Musings on Elvis  http://t.co/lAEnugMjz1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just in time for winter - Touch Screen Texting Gloves  - http://t.co/DUpIld3oEJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the animals: God has given them the rudiments of thought and joy untroubled - Fyodor Dostoyevsky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nolan Ryan is pitching much better now that he has his curve ball straightened out. - Joe Garagiola]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 4 - Supplements and Herbs  http://t.co/AwowEC6FCP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Harmless Version Of the Original Russian Roulette - Great for Parties! http://t.co/GWvG4bkeSS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The reality of science is that it takes 40 years to get to Jupiter, and that's a dull show. - Glen Morgan, "Space: Above and Beyond"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool Batman Comfy Throw - Stay Warm and Cool :&gt;)  http://t.co/VKASBgoKNE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Don Henley  http://t.co/cL53dLrf2S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[London Weight Loss Salon sign: "We value the pound."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In any contest between power and patience -- bet on patience]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Top 10 fitness gyms  http://t.co/ePqN51hZPA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Firefighters recently rescued two people from an industrial clothes dryer. They were listed in stable condition but missing one sock!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When money talks these days, it's probably asking what happened]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't fix stupid - Larry Morgan, NHRA Pro Stock driver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very cool 23 mile range walkie talkies!  Stay connected!  http://t.co/S0azKaFQiR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must be the change you wish to see in the world. - Mahatma Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to WordTracker SEO Tools http://t.co/JVVppJpkED]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Danger Will Robinson! Danger! - Robbie the Robot, Lost in Space]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overheard:  "I don't mind going to work.  It's that long wait to go home that bothers me."]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>