<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[That's 'The Waste Land' https://t.co/TofpkkMjaO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eliot (by Patrick Heron) and Pound (by Wyndham Lewis) in Journeys with 'The Waste Land' at Turner Contemporary https://t.co/B8hcC3MKuz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Margate https://t.co/ZRYkZOS2im]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EdwardGLuce: "Mueller’s report hints at more dramatic possibilities by further corroborating contents of the Steele dossier". Me on tod…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's the best of the @FinancialTimes' commentary this week on South Africa after Zuma in one place https://t.co/6vHjtdA0y3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Person in the news: @muradahmed on Richard Scudamore, English football's dealmaker in chief https://t.co/QQCp9yaKaO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DougHenwood: Fresh audio product: @maxbsawicky on Trump’s budget, @EdwardGLuce on the crisis in the American class system https://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@davidpilling on how Zuma's luck ran out https://t.co/MjH9Fs0y0R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@mthombothi explains why South Africa is pinning its hopes on Ramaphosa https://t.co/IUYQ7ViMJ7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the Republicans learned to love the deficit. Whatever happened to the Tea Party, asks @EdwardGLuce https://t.co/a0gwDNqMbS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating reporting by @AndyBounds on Britain's emerging east-west divide https://t.co/f41i4IooEh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't forget to sign up for the @FinancialTimes' daily opinion email if you haven't already done so https://t.co/fXFYZJ9MLM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It is impossible to determine which ... instruments are played at any given moment" - Rahsaan Roland Kirk, 1971 https://t.co/Mg0DyHL7D3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picked this up at the wonderful Crocojazz in Paris. Holland and Rivers can make a bass and tenor/soprano sound positively symphonic https://t.co/SJqdU8jSDf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KCMANC My favourite of yours of MES.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DuncanWeldon He's been reading JS Mill, clearly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jazzonthisday: Art Blakey and the Jazz Messengers recorded Free For All for Blue Note Records  #onthisday in 1964. The album includes p…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daveweeden I don't think so. That's the Canal St Martin rather than the Seine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Homeless encampment, Quai de Valmy https://t.co/8cZu1FzTAW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oscar Niemeyer's French Communist Party HQ https://t.co/FyrmWG1KWh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PCollinsTimes Paris, rue des Ecoles, 5eme.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Paris à mon coeur dès mon enfance ..."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Montaigne https://t.co/9da2f8lhBQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snow - Paris, 5eme https://t.co/CIqUeGoCEM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picardie in the snow https://t.co/BZ1Mn9MFTY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paris-bound to interview the splendid @LaurentBinetH for the @FinancialTimes Books Café. Facebook Live at 10am, London time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From last year: @gideonrachman on the "global sickness" of "Soros hatred" https://t.co/iFP6C526lL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonathanshainin It really is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've always thought that Foucault's reporting from Iran in '78 was much less breathlessly credulous than is often argued https://t.co/CqTdUfS1ZB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Macron trying to have it both (all?) ways in this speech on Corsica https://t.co/hvBetYOfRr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The discreet terror of the American bourgeoisie - @EdwardGLuce on Trump and the cognitive elite https://t.co/iYw0s0z2r0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stefanstern @rafaelbehr Yes, Jenkins, who was an avuncular confidant of Blair's at the time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rwilliams1947: Here's a piece about the debut album from @nubya_garcia, one of a large number of gifted @women currently correcting the…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheosElizabeth @DawnHFoster @neilgriffiths @sacred_podcast Thanks Elizabeth. Enjoyed that immensely.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jan Gross for @ftcomment on the Polish government's attempts to falsify history https://t.co/xO1XpWN04V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@olivialanguage @VivGroskop So looking forward to this having followed its gestation in real time on Twitter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@sarahoconnor_ on digital Taylorism https://t.co/hWE3nTJMnP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnthonyBarnett I said "most", Anthony!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a very important point systematically overlooked in most diagnoses of the Brexit vote https://t.co/Hy0OZcfhoo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Seize the memes of production" - very nice skyline on tomorrow's @FinancialTimes front page https://t.co/iaeJeUI4gw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to dipping into this, @AgnesCPoirier https://t.co/SyO93cRLDt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social media users of the world unite! Excellent column by @johnthornhillft on data-as-capital vs data-as-labour https://t.co/QcItwFAlHw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GeorgeWParker: Theresa May might be ruling out "a customs union" but we're still none the wiser on what will be put in its place. Big r…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@JananGanesh on Rees-Mogg and a Tory party ripe for capture https://t.co/hpsHJMpx3F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jan Gross wrote for @FT back in 2016 on how PiS is instrumentalising the history of Holocaust &amp; WWII. Still relevant https://t.co/1ViiJ9Q1ib]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hosted the @FT politics podcast this week. I was joined by @Laura_K_Hughes, @PickardJE, @JKynge &amp; @DyerGeoff https://t.co/vozUb364tJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MADarbyshire Missing the District Line?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now that's record post to come home to: @tenderlonious22 and @brownswood's We Out Here compilation https://t.co/ygItvcOfOh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ftcomment: Obituary: Henry Brooke, barrister and judge, 1936-2018 https://t.co/LNjnsm9xRj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If a lion could talk, we would not understand him" - @pilitaclark channels Wittgenstein in this column on Wikie the "talking" killer whale https://t.co/il0jhcG9Cr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A choir of strangers accompanies David Byrne singing David Bowie’s 'Heroes'. H/t @questingvole  https://t.co/Y2IZlhSQdE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Many Primes of Muriel Spark: wonderful documentary presented and narrated by Kirsty Wark https://t.co/m0QInmGdtm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JayElwes: Hear the audio of that @prospect_uk event with @CER_Grant here: https://t.co/7gnOYl4vaO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lovely account of the life and times of @MondedesLivres, which is 50 this week https://t.co/2c869ntgPS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NickCohen4 @_coltseavers Oi!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think economics has a forecasting problem? Think again, says @ChrisGiles_ https://t.co/mzQXRa9I3K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MalcolmMoore: I present the...err...quarterback of news @SpiegelPeter https://t.co/CGJ4C0X65f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JeanBirnbaum: La voici donc, la une de ce numéro spécial qui fête les 50 ans du @MondedesLivres. Avec, notamment, un grand récit signé…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@philipstephens anatomises Brexit Britain's nervous breakdown https://t.co/9Nt1m5OJ3i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GrahamTAllison: Well said, @gideonrachman: "This new combination of a protectionist and nationalist America, and an assertive and natio…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EliPhilippe: Deux Français dans la liste, mais la concurrence est rude (Munoz Molina, Krasznahorkai ou Javier Cercas par exemple) https…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JosephineCumbo: BREAKING: Agreement has been reached in #USS dispute.

Statements to follow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mette Frederiksen, leader of the Danish Social Democrats, for @ftcomment on how to save Europe's centre left https://t.co/fvW8HrqV4F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@parabasis Ha, ha!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joelgombin Ah, ok. Another time, I hope.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How's that 'dédiabolisation' going, Marine? https://t.co/CjAyfIkQvP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joelgombin Would you be interested in writing something là-dessus fo the FT?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent @libe front page https://t.co/HG9TKphkof]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quite a band: Peacock, DeJohnette, Stanko and Garbarek - for ECM, 1982 https://t.co/HEljU3xO6Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @henrikenderlein: French „Front National“ changes its name to „Rassemblement National“. There already was a party with that name in Fran…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Herbie Hancock collaborates with Kendrick Lamar, Flying Lotus on new LP https://t.co/g3xaOv12n9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Philip_de_Bary: Ever been bored in a lecture on Immanuel Kant's logic? One contemporary  student drew this cartoon inside an interleave…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a very subtle column on America’s gun fixation by @rbrtrmstrng  https://t.co/fkqcrtebuz https://t.co/BaZY5NPq2H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last call for my @FTLifeArts books essay: whatever happened to radical Paris?  https://t.co/x0j2bjBCKI https://t.co/GZ0cgFm1J3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Following Cobb in my rather antiquated plan de Paris https://t.co/z0djS8B5aE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GroomB That is the work of the splendid @beePencil.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The VIme has been lost beyond hope ..." Richard Cobb, 1980.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can China save the global trading system? Great piece for @ftcomment by @Princeton's Christina Davis https://t.co/xDBNdiEqmB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidEdmonds100 Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Assuming this scrawled dedication in my copy of Richard Cobb's The Streets of Paris is from the author to Asa Briggs https://t.co/5xccprPjKr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can the centre hold? The best of the @FinancialTimes' commentary this week on the travails of European social democracy https://t.co/iynI4dQuL5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lovely piece by @GroomB on what the GKN-Melrose saga tells us about the history of British capitalism and current attitudes towards the free market https://t.co/3O4Row6rZ4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DavidMarkHerman @FTLifeArts @AgnesCPoirier I allude to Sartre et al's philo-Sovietism when I refer to Koestler.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanielKatz6 Have emailed you a "gift" article!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whatever happened to radical Paris? My essay for @FTLifeArts on books by @AgnesCPoirier, Eric Hazan and others https://t.co/x0j2bjBCKI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @YanniKouts: 'The Syriza party is undermining democracy in #Greece - The Tsipras government has mounted an attack on the rule of law' --…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[St James the Great in Clapton - wonderful venue for @nubya_garcia's show tonight https://t.co/N3IczO3673]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smart piece by @TomHale_ on universities, capital markets and the future of state funding for higher education https://t.co/TYAiUALESf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @joswinson: This kind of nuanced, insightful journalism is exactly what we need to make the most of gender pay gap reporting and use it…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Britain, Ireland and The Politics of Nomenclature. Fascinating  https://t.co/b6BhFLCIZc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@olivialanguage Huge congratulations!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChassNews Cough https://t.co/0pXWDJ4vW9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@JackPittBrooke's reporting of the @DulwichHamletFC story has been exemplary. Here's his latest https://t.co/HMvyv40QYL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DulwichHamletFC: FT:

What a response from this team, after everything that’s been thrown at us, we beat @BTFC 3-1 and move top of the…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@martinwolf_ on how protectionism begets more protectionism https://t.co/Mw0z38nmbY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Il n'ya pas d'explication. C'est football." Roy Hodgson, en français https://t.co/6l0GuTGZJX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KuperSimon @ESPNFC Great piece. This is when Zidane first registered for me: https://t.co/X3sgfbFJDA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A useful reminder from @gideonrachman that Europe faces some difficult choices on Brexit too https://t.co/4vl6YTDWID]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@TonyBarber8's piece on the decline of the European centre left from last week is worth re-reading this morning https://t.co/F1D73vsKXc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adwooldridge What do you make of Buruma's NYRB? Or is it too soon to say?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>