<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Inaugural - all welcome https://t.co/ihKfH1Sd52]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DrDaveOBrien: This week’s highlight from our new Handbook of Global Cultural Policy is part 1 https://t.co/zLsfLB9MNE (ebook now just £…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jeffreysharkey: Culture for everyone - @RCStweets and throughout Scotland https://t.co/KHzHfO79Qs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SGSAH_: We are delighted to launch the SGSAH AHRC Doctoral Training Partnership Studentship. Fully funded PhD and much more! https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SCOmusic: Not long now 'til our Season Opener in #Edinburgh -  #RobinTicciati #MitsukoUchida @theusherhall 7.30pm #mySCO https://t.co/J…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BPSOfficial: Do you know a psychology technician who deserves recognition? We make two awards in this field https://t.co/0VNIPCJrUl htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KatieCebula: Beautifully written, so full of love, &amp; endlessly sad. Should be read by everyone working with young people with LD @Justi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoyed hosting @ShashiTharoor 's public lecture @EdinburghUni India Day celebration. He liked the location (#McEwanHall) and great turnout! https://t.co/t3XQzho38o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BarbaraBompani: Don’t forget that we are hiring! A 3-year career development post in support of our distance learning teaching https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jrsmith73: Career Development Fellow in @africanstudies @EdinburghUni Three weeks to apply! Please share https://t.co/kyLQ9a4ZKz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Creative_Fed: New report on changing uses and impact of technology in arts and cultural organisations .@ace_national .@nesta_uk https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonderful to spend the afternoon congratulating staff on their contributions and achievements #CAHSS @EdinburghUni https://t.co/byttvsmbth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @drvickyw: Please help my super PhD Miki with her survey; mental wellbeing in music students. Important project, real impact https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @IASH_Edinburgh: Playwrights: applications now open for 2018 IASH-Traverse Creative Fellow!
* £10,000
* Private office for 6-10 mths
htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @UK_Music: We are setting up &amp; nearly ready to find out from our expert panel, what #Brexit means for music at #LAB2017 @UKLabour #brigh…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @REF_2021: Updates published to the REF #openaccess Policy FAQs to reflect the #REF2021 initial decisions: https://t.co/ubYHuzCJxT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations Claudia! Richly deserved https://t.co/Qsm0LufQcb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EdinUniCAHSSres #REF2021 workshop kicks off... nostalgia for @joshaw ?! https://t.co/aH76n6bOp8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @StCeciliasHall: Tickets still available. After the premiere of this #performance in #Scotland we host Q&amp;A with Prof Deary &amp; Dr Overy fr…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SGSAH_: ICYMI we have a funded PhD starting in 2018, collaborative with industry and looking at 21st century Scottish Folk Drama. @Scot…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KatieCebula: Great to hear from so many, but still seeking families with children w. Williams syndrome for this research study - gratef…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HoneybHighton: Our Edinburgh resources for schools https://t.co/XbUXESyMIQ  downloaded 1,165 times by teachers  #ukoer @OpenEdEdinburgh…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now there's a plan! https://t.co/ll1btbzcQo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DanGoodley: https://t.co/jkaFdjifrt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sbayne: Beyond "edtech is the new fintech": TechCrunch article on edtech investment and values #dfled #mscde  https://t.co/xyJGlwno28]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RosaMurr: UoE National Returning to teaching programme launches online today,blended learning and rich content.first cohort,https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @StellaWYChan: Come and work with me on adolescent depression research. Postdoc application deadline Friday 29th. Apply here: https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BPSOfficial: Do you know a psychology technician who deserves recognition? We make two awards in this field https://t.co/0VNIPCJrUl htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ScottishDocInst: BFI Unveils £20 Million Plan to Attract 10,000 New Workers to UK Film  https://t.co/R5ZOnYHvoi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ahrcpress: Our Creative Economy Champion Andrew Chitty has written an opinion piece in response to @PeterBazalgette #BazReview https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheBookbag: Forgetfulness: Making the Modern Culture of Amnesia by Francis O'Gorman: push your mind into dusty corners: https://t.co/t5…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @scottishbktrust: Can you write a 50-word story that features a bridge? Enter our #flashfiction competition by 30 September: https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ahrcpress: #CreativeIndustries Clusters Programme launched by @GregClarkMP today at the #bazreview by @PeterBazalgette https://t.co/HkP…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @samwetherell: Research appeal! Does anyone live in, or know anyone who lives in, a private block of flats built before 2000 in UK? (RTs…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HoneybHighton: Edinburgh Phd students: Could you be our Equality Images Intern? https://t.co/WvAqeAxaR7  @UoEIS @EdUniMainLib @CRC_EdUn…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SGSAH_: We have added two more paid internships from @BBCScotland as part of our internship call. Apply by 2/10. https://t.co/W4Bycu3c9…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Creative_Fed: 2/2 Building talent pipeline for creative workforce is crucial to continue success. Our full response to #BazReview https…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SAGEsociology: Special issue from @culsoc Producing and Consuming Inequality: A Cultural Sociology of the Cultural Industries https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ScottishOpera: We're delighted to be participating in #OperaPassion live day on 19 Oct. Find out more about our contribution here: http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sbayne: Help design the future of digital education @EdinburghUni - https://t.co/0M9SF1z0l2 @NearFutureTeach #mscde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DeirdreHeddon: I highly recommend this event by one of our PhD interns with RSPB. @SGSAH_ @ahrcpress @ScotFundCouncil https://t.co/b7rQ…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LizDobsonUoH https://t.co/KPbTx5O1ID]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CulturalKings: What does the digital age mean for patterns of music consumption? #CultureCase https://t.co/vYv0TfbZSK https://t.co/A6Ks…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations @MorayHouseHoS !! https://t.co/EoieLQTMtF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @UoEArtColl: One of Edinburgh’s 101 Objects: 
The Golden Boy by John Hutchison 1888. Here he is getting new coat of gilt bronze #Edinbur…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CRC_EdUni: Our latest @wellcometrust project - lots of exciting things to come! https://t.co/LR2yvESd0A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sgsahblog: Fancy writing an article for @SGSAH_ ? We are looking for guest bloggers! Get in touch if you're interested! #phdchat #phdad…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ProfArno: these are so cool. and beautiful. and inspiring. i'll be RTing over and over on Saturday... https://t.co/8SJ8tzBmAp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EdinburghUni: Acclaimed Nigerian author Chimamanda Ngozi Adichie was awarded an honorary degree. See her full acceptance speech: https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ahrcpress: We're investing millions in universities and #creativeindustries collaboration. Find out more at our October events.
https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ProjectSoothe: Can you support our research by rating our most recent photosets? Takes around ten minutes. #CitizenScience

https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some views of #futures are more reliable than others! @UoEFuturesInst https://t.co/ulip3atLJW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EdiArtHistory: ‘Culture is a meritocracy’ - an article by @DrDaveOBrien &amp; @markrt on creative workers reinforcing social inequality htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GlobalJusticeEd: Our Changing World Lecture - Redrawing boundaries: religion, violence and the search for peace. Edinburgh, 26 Sept htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @onlytherhythm: If it's on the @eca_edinburgh website, then it must be officially happening https://t.co/ZHKVDxlqqq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @UoWPsych: If you're not a @BPSOfficial member, here's your chance to see what you're missing with the brilliant @psychmag https://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JoCliffordPlays: There is a serious attempt to ban one of my plays in Brazil. Please retweet if you care about freedom of speech https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @royalsociety: Congratulations to Cordelia Fine – our 2017 @InsightInvestIM #scibooks winner https://t.co/Z2oRNePsCc https://t.co/WX5Lav…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @suchprettyeyes: Fabulous looking new stuff! Library of Congress Labs just launched and has a pile of digital goodies to play with! http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Example to #Edinburgh?! https://t.co/KkyUiaUWYt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CreativeSDS: Love this - visitors to @philamuseum find their doppelgängers in art https://t.co/yw3c1BMWpx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @uoe_online: Tartan-clad heroes, espionage, rebellion. Not only in #Outlander but also in our free online course: sign up now! https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll have music therapists on standby! https://t.co/DTVd6sOKpt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take it from me, they're only interested in the grandkids! #granniesrule https://t.co/GuHPUIY5H4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't imagine what you'll need by Friday! https://t.co/iNq1gU5mHi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations! https://t.co/Ra8APmTs3b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DeirdreHeddon: Doctoral internships with BBC Scotland. Tempted? https://t.co/6PCPn3yRL9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sbayne: Knowledge and skills needs in the Social Sciences: call for evidence from the UK @esrc https://t.co/zyH3ubBWQt @UoEFuturesInst…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SchoolofPPLS: Explore some of @EdinburghUni 's most interesting buildings this weekend #DoorsOpenDay https://t.co/w4uvLTkGO4 https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tomstafford: Question: Which concepts do psych students have the most difficulty with? Interested to hear from people teaching *or* lea…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SGSAH_: SGSAH wins £1m @ahrcpress funding for National Productivity Investment Fund Studentships.
https://t.co/rL2yj1yLJ8 https://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sbayne: We are recruiting a researcher to work on data analytics and libraries with the fabulous @philshe https://t.co/nuvRV55nQ2 #dere…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @UoE_IICR: Book your ticket for a workshop with @deboraspar on 4 October, with Joanna Baker, managing director of @edintfest  https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Creative_Fed: Be sure to pick up your copy of the @ftweekend with Fed Founder Sir John Sorrell - A blueprint for creative living https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tomstafford: researchers - you can and should do all of these https://t.co/PST0wKtGSY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blimey you've got me taped!! https://t.co/lJ3EK9A6Mw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BBCRadio3: 🎶 Music lovers! Take part in our online experiment, run with Dr @CathLoveday of  @UniWestminster. More info here 👇 https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @skape_ed: Check out details of our seminars coming up over the next academic year: https://t.co/SAwbyCQmzP #sociology #socialpolicy #ST…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoyVamvakari https://t.co/EOiF9igokU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @alwaleed_centre: The British Ambassador to Iran, @NicholasHopton, is coming to @EdinburghUni to deliver a talk on 6 Oct. More info: htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @openculture: Watch a Musician Improvise on a 500-Year-Old Music Instrument, The Carillon https://t.co/XBZt2G1URK https://t.co/nrYomkRcdJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great welcome to new #elite #sports students today @UoE_Sport_Exer https://t.co/2rlDKUN6RF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EdinburghUni: University Principal Professor Sir Timothy O’Shea is to receive the city of Edinburgh's biggest annual accolade https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me too! https://t.co/8E3oxUrwpo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @IASH_Edinburgh: We are excited to launch #genderED, a digital hub showcasing research and teaching in gender and sexuality studies http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tmcphers: Arrived in the mail.  Many thanks to the @anvcscalar and Vectors team for years of inspiration and collaboration. https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DrImogenTyler: Yes this: cultural political economy (or what Stuart Hall called cultural studies but with a bit more critical attention…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @uni_scot: Academic freedom is a fundamental right in a democratic society and should not be challenged or censored in any way. https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @IASH_Edinburgh: Just a week to go 'til the 3rd Enlightenment Lecture: Philanthropy &amp; Education in Scotland. Free tickets: https://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @IASH_Edinburgh: Join us on Wednesday for the launch of #genderED, showcasing teaching and research in gender and sexuality studies http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @litlong: 'Exploring Edinburgh's Literary Landscape' events with @litlong as part of #beinghumanfest17. Book your place soon! https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SGSAH_: You have one week to apply for a place on this writing retreat. Listen to the experiences of others who attended at https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're hiring - great opportunity! https://t.co/jfyfzvhl48 Please RT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sbayne: Write the future of education - come to our Future Fictions workshop led by @jlwpoetry https://t.co/peBGQ4NqGz @NearFutureTeach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EdiPhilOnline: Heads up, part 3 of @Eidyn1's intellectual humility course in launching about November 20th! https://t.co/bhe9rfx8K2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @utafrith: Essi Viding's lecture is up now. Not to be missed. https://t.co/nUdFPU3Qvi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hurry up-you need to be in the office tomorrow 😃 https://t.co/GWyIKOHzfu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loved #cockpit @lyceumtheatre especially being in the midst of the action on stage! https://t.co/po3YMMcBRi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DangerousWomen_: Come and celebrate the launch of the #genderED research and teaching hub at the #mothership @IASH_Edinburgh this comin…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @UoECounsandPsyc: Centre for Creative-Relational inquiry and @CPASS First Thursday seminar series - next one 2 November. Join us! https:…]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>