<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The Koch brothers saw a big defeat tonight. Justin Trudeau is the new Prime Minister of Canada. His dad would be so happy. #LiberalMajority]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canadians, you are free from a dark four years. Now you have permission to be Canadian again. #LibertyMajority]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi, owen. This Darren's dad. We're thrilled w/ results. Oh happy days. Hope all is well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[33 million Canadians wake up tomorrow with new hope. There is good in the world. No more fear, bullying. Canada you get your country back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeahWestMusic Happy!!!! I remember 2011. It's been a long four years living under a bully.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shanakassa Of course I remember.  Who could forget you? Are you interested in having a coffee soon? write me on michael.shandrick@gmail.com]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/AyOWX3Fom2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/ziwYC5Wr8G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks Frank. I'll try it. http://t.co/eyKwlbU8GT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday, Chuck. When I was 18 I was a roadie for a rock &amp; roll back-up band on tour with Chuck through... http://t.co/4zrP6qAxOi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need more of emmylou harris in my day http://t.co/MZNTWAVkTY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every now &amp; then I have to play this heartbreaking song about Amy lou losing Grahm Parson to drugs and his... http://t.co/EIrB3HIchl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trust Harper? http://t.co/hiwOehwrAZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing talents singing this Crosby, Stills &amp; Nash tune. So good... http://t.co/32WiHpkA1b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/Gh9Y12JEu8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I flew with Chuck Yeager ...on a flight from San Francisco to Vancouver. Two hours to ask the General questions.... http://t.co/w8faStGIhz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/l316a4QTR8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@miretrodriguez My ex-girlfriend is an artist living in Paris. She is now a full-time artist living in Paris. You look quite at home there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@datehackme whose hacking who, for starters?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/ba3qUOU5ao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gimme Shelter is another great song selecting street musicians from around the world by Jimmy Buffett's Playing... http://t.co/u52c0qCL6b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/UW3i2DuHiL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/RUxnWWR0Np]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/zhGfV56utJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shut the fuck up Donny... http://t.co/JlBeXHt9As]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you did not vote in the last general election... Please at least do the math. http://t.co/q6gF5Yjejz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dude! Peace out. http://t.co/Z2Fm12MX3O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Bells turn the buzz to silence. http://t.co/UGzmZrUN87]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marg Brings Change http://t.co/OvJCpqQG3J #margbringschange via @mightypop #bringsomecentstoHarper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[El Nino is now a threat to become permanent. http://t.co/5STIauWU3P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the only woman Harper actually fears. http://t.co/OtlVzyeeaY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first time I broke up with FB. http://t.co/8DPx7Fq19c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More reasons to dump fear-baiting Harper from a woman he fears the most. http://t.co/nrFFnPf6pQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The pace does rapid fall on the lame. http://t.co/pLCB8NUxlA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Spectrum Bliss: The Secret to an Oxytocin-Based Sexual Connection http://t.co/H4yTfqUFVo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chinese trafficking kingpin busted for killing thousands of elephants. http://t.co/S8JQjBJS5O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear mr. zukerberg, what is this? http://t.co/KmorOE8O8O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An effective strategic how-to vote in this all-too-important election. 

Pass along to your neighbors, voting age... http://t.co/vi3bphUlwR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@miretrodriguez Miret, I want to know if you are safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/wa3DtYJdJM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/vFnlpCuRQX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/nqDTKF0QJc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And winter has just begun. Aaachooo! https://t.co/bsgRFEtgSr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In my home town of Colorado Springs, Colorado the people made a tribute of solidarity with the citizens of Paris.... https://t.co/TTstPSwj9Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/uVAgBlYAdF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/8tvsBjQIhy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/p7fzomVOTM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/xWryJtmsbo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/uB1K0Yt5bb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/mQO2EtQhVK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/BbvpVXdhj1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/BIgg2Kgp5a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/6CeGC6vBIV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/TKmkcp6vMi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/lU0TBn9FNR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/luWBQ8lwBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/jJgkkCQoP5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/kgIKWk8Atu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/8kBRihzYVW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/AeZRWUM4oG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@miretrodriguez Know that your angels are surely with you on this terrible day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the doubts are waiting for you by the door as you near the finish line. https://t.co/a8PFZYdY1S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazingly, I see that friends in Mexico are sharing posts with friends in Spain about dogs being sentient in... https://t.co/YRqUoDJREh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Molly. She sat in my in box to get my attention. She made me laugh. https://t.co/9bEMIEkWbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bolivia, once the playground of nihilist capitalism, is now in the hands of the people. Che lives! https://t.co/eLizDvpn9S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bien sûr pourquoi pas? https://t.co/sNtmq0nKr6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Rio, Pacification Without Peace https://t.co/MPux3UC0S6 via @nytvideo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In 2008 it was statistically safer for people in the slums of Rio when traffickers controlled the slums. Police... https://t.co/Y40XeN4KU1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The armies of the north and south refused the support of people in Missouri, so vile and violent they were.https://t.co/qmKES7A1Gx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[100 years ago the great armies faced each other expecting a quick victory. Millions died over the next four years... https://t.co/b5BDEK0Fx8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My alma mater, University of Colorado, Boulder. https://t.co/6vBw2nIDoa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christian Watson on Instagram: “If you hate @starbucks because of their cups, unfollow me. If... https://t.co/7gzY9hULsD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He claims his ancient ancestors appear to give him advice on occasion. https://t.co/kA4p1eI1fA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carson Hopes Debate Will Focus on Lost City of Atlantis https://t.co/kUl4czqsFd via @BorowitzReport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/P2LXj5MY2Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love this bit ..Christians get it wrong every time. https://t.co/xy8BrkgI0h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/WvBeizsVPq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is well documented in Michael Harris' best-selling book, "Party of One". https://t.co/DXKAufvUFd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/CMsKyDQEz3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Removing bias from creativity. https://t.co/hlpYxHccKB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infographic: The Ideal Length of Everything Online, From Tweets to YouTube Videos | Adweek https://t.co/8qhXTs1N8x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @billmaher: Did Jeb Bush really answer the question "Would U kill baby Hitler?"? Yes, he did. Why do ppl get mad at me for saying its a …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Less is more in brand content. https://t.co/uFzo27znVE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some Viking wisdom. https://t.co/1vfdmtZ5LM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conference Proposals that Don’t Suck https://t.co/BKDhljAkK1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@miretrodriguez Delma Godoy. It would be awesome if you two met. She lives in metro Paris.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheInSneider @JordanPeele @blumhouse It will be cheeky, irreverent and pushing the limits.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@miretrodriguez Her name Delma Godoy. Very talented and amazing. I will finish the book I wrote about our time together. She is legend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But only for a minute, then you'd find a lot of people making you into a godess. https://t.co/TNiBGegGi9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JordanPeele I'm all in. 
 Droid sex, mixed race and dwarves. Hey, sounds like the GOP colonizes Saturn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama gave a death blow to Keystone pipeline and scientists across Canada had their gag order removed with the departure of its former PM.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FionaQuinnBooks @MaggieToussaint Today scientists across Canada are no longer gagged and bound with the departure of its former PM.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@benaroberts America today is a large country filled with small minds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LoveValerieee: Some people just don't deserve a reaction from me! 😌👌]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheTumblrgirl_ done. I'm yours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheHappyWriters You're everywhere Joey. Admit it, you hired a stunt double.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have avoided becoming a trope...so far. https://t.co/jV5qN9wjZS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama 's dirty deal unveiled. https://t.co/ExfNxyjbLE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This amazing panoramic photo was taken on the flanks of Pumori shows the Everest basin. (My humble photos were... https://t.co/vDWMe7HV85]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Z8VGZ0RGnS]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>