<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @InvestForRights: If you missed our last #bizhumanrights webinar on @RankBHR New Results, you can access the recording here: https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @globalvoices: #NetizenReport: Tanzania’s crackdown on free speech targets media advocates from CPJ https://t.co/cEef8k8FCb https://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @globalvoices: Welcome to the ‘New Turkey': Five years after #Gezi park, protesters face new threats of arrest https://t.co/KO2LfU0p1z h…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @globalvoices: We are #thankful for each of your donations! They help us maintain our independence and sustain our projects @GVlingua @r…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @katestarbird: This is turning my stomach. Around the same time I was invited to Facebook to give a presentation on online disinformatio…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Ethical_Corp: .@sara__blackwell of @shiftproject says #companies have been slow to grasp the truly #positive results of working to addr…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Info_Activism: Silicon Valley’s Chinese Dream - Tech elites, weary of democracy, look to the East "For Google, China represents both co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @hoofnagle: Surprise surprise...Elliot Schrage hired Definers. And takes the fall for Sheryl. “Thanks for sharing this, Elliot.” Mark pr…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pressfreedom: Join CPJ in its #JusticeForJamal campaign. Share why journalism matters to you on social media using the hashtag. #JamalK…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Info_Activism: Facebook policy chief admits hiring PR firm to attack George Soros https://t.co/a7LFYaCrxT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Info_Activism: Study: It only takes a few seconds for bots to spread misinformation - Just six percent of bots on Twitter accounted for…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @zararah: Sick to my stomach reading this. The women human rights defenders who fought for the right to drive in Saudi Arabia have been…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MarechalPhD: Excellent analysis by ⁦@anildash⁩, on what a scam the internet economy all is https://t.co/h1bCXomd6f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jason_kint: Facebook FFS: 

11/21/18 Thxgiving eve
Soros memo dump

11/5/18 Election eve
Myanmar Report

12/22/17 Fri before Xmas
launc…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jason_kint: If Schrage is going to take the fall then let him. Put him under oath, also ask him about Cambridge Analytica dates, Joe Ch…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Info_Activism: The Snowden Legacy, part one: What’s changed, really? In our two-part series, Ars looks at what Snowden's disclosures ha…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RonDeibert: A haunting example of the type of tactics a huge, powerful social media company can wield without proper public accountabil…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @zararah: Come and work with me and a bunch of wonderful people @EngnRoom! We're looking for a Tech Team Manager, a Senior Researcher an…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @natashanyt: further to social credit scoring: 
American Airlines monitors Twitter for complaints and analyzes users’ bios, their number…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kuminaidoo: I've written to @antonioguterres today on behalf of more than 170,000 @amnesty supporters, urging him to set up a UN invest…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @davidakaye: good to see this from @kuminaidoo @amnesty - see also our letter yesterday: https://t.co/mA2JIKSaGy #JamalKhashoggi https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @connectedrights: Could online advertising maybe become less creepy? https://t.co/sgDXw9cpI9 https://t.co/937td9PsDT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check it out! https://t.co/9xBy6NHa17]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you and thanks to our hard working @rankingrights team who made this possible!! https://t.co/8cyUklkaQx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Gizmodo: With Facebook's Portal devices, you have to ask yourself: Am I ready to invite Facebook into my home? 
https://t.co/0c8QorTolM…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @davidakaye: this is seriously messed up. fb should admit that the soros reference echoed what authoritarians &amp; anti-semites are doing w…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cis_india: CIS is hosting the Global Citizen debate on the Future of Internet. The event is on the 7th of December in Bangalore.
Thousa…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kfahim: In addition to the beatings and electric shocks, at least one prisoner was hung from the ceiling during an interrogation. Anoth…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pressfreedom: “Rappler -- and [@mariaressa] -- stood up to #Duterte. They showed how he weaponized the internet -- unleashing fake news…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @davidakaye: in light of Trump’s statement today, what Fred Ryan called a “betrayal,” sharing letter I, @AgnesCallamard and UN Working G…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rankingrights: Are you at @SMEX's #breadandnet conference in Beirut today?

Don't miss RDR's @Afaf_TN on:
▶ ​Approaches to involving co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @courtneyr: This is why CPJ is so concerned about the use of the term "#FakeNews" by @POTUS @realDonaldTrump https://t.co/3nSRXA4JSR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jimsciutto: How are dissidents in Saudi Arabia, Russia, China &amp; beyond to take these words at this moment? The US Secretary of State di…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @davidakaye: trump goes through hoops of nonsense to justify avoiding any serious consequences for what appears to be state-sanctioned m…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rankingrights: Today is Day 1 of #breadandnet organized by @SMEX and featuring @rankingrights @article19org @accessnow @Wikimedia @Mada…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pressfreedom: "If you boil the White House statement down to its essence, President Trump has just asserted that if you do enough busin…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rasmus_kleis: Want to play a leading role at @risj_oxford and join us in exploring the future of journalism worldwide through debate, e…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EFF: It’s here! 

EFF and McSweeney’s have teamed up to bring you "The End of Trust" (@mcsweeneys 54), the first all-nonfiction McSween…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @InterwebzNani: International Media Support (IMS) is looking for a Programme Manager in #Tunisia. Application deadline is 2 December: ht…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rankingrights: Surveillance capitalism and targeted advertising have become the norm on the internet, and it's hurting all of us, write…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KevinBankston: Just one reason why transparency reports need to break down requests by product/service--a single number for an entire c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EFF: EFF fights surveillance… and we do so in 11 languages in our educational resource, Surveillance Self-Defense. https://t.co/77mCeFi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @irenepoet: "Proposed #cybersecurity law in #Thailand would give a new government agency sweeping powers to spy on internet traffic, ord…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RonDeibert: Why it's important to study how "cybersecurity" ends up being implement and practiced at regional and national levels. Incr…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @hunterw: Peak New York: Amazon is being given land in Queens that was supposed to go for affordable housing. Now 1,500 homes are off th…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jason_kint: I could create an entire twitter feed of things Facebook has tried to cover up since 2015. Where do you want to start, Mark…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NewYorker: Newly surfaced e-mails show that Steve Bannon and Cambridge Analytica were simultaneously incubating both the Trump campaign…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KevinBankston: Ford's CEO just said on NPR that the future of profitability for the company is all the data from its 100 million vehicl…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RonDeibert: If so, why doesn’t the Trudeau govt do something concrete about the fact that a Canadian company provides autocratic regime…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @freedomonthenet: The research is clear: There is no evidence that internet shutdowns work #KeepItOn @apargupta84 @tame_wildcard  https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EFF: Instead of trying to figure out which messenger provides the best “security” features by certain technical standards, think about…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ElCalavero: @kevinroose @KurtWagner8 Hi Kevin, there are many known cases of Facebook suspending services temporarily at the request of…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ChristopherJM: Journalist @ColborneMichael took punch to face, sustained cut &amp; had glasses broken by far-right radicals while covering…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @amyyqin: This week it’s all about CHINA. The New York Times has just dropped the first part in a weeklong series examining China’s rise…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @riptari: "A good guide for how to tame Facebook comes from America’s long experience with AT&amp;T, the telephone corporation that dominate…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats to you and @panphil and everybody else involved in this. Look forward to digging in. https://t.co/7sRpMwwCtk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just joined The Correspondent, a movement for #unbreakingnews. Will you join me? https://t.co/q5TTityc8B #thecorrespondent via @The_Corres]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great piece by my colleague @MarechalPhD ! https://t.co/BE3e4dXiXV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FrankPasquale: “Zuckerberg is unlikely to be ousted as CEO — he is both the majority shareholder and the chairman of the board. As a re…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @davidakaye: kindly reminder that the killing of #JamalKhashoggi was a crime w/int’l dimensions. globally, don’t expect reliance on what…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HaifaDia: Second that! @JustinVaisse ‘s outstanding leadership and the work he enabled with @marcreverdin heading a committed + compete…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ParisPeaceForum: What was your favourite article written about #ParisPeaceForum? Share it with us here! #StandforPeace https://t.co/FXY…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @josemurilo: “'we’re building a #dystopia just to make people click on ads.'
#Zuckerberg emphasized that his company doesn’t sell user d…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MarechalPhD: @zizip @michaelzimmer The action research I'm doing for @rankingrights aims to evaluate the impact that companies througho…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @s_kakade14: Journalists across India share their testimony on the deteriorating state of media — and vow to fight back https://t.co/Q81…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @IFEX: Hong Kong: "If people can no longer speak their mind, what place is there for press freedom?" https://t.co/EucA7MukEY @HongKongFP…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EFF: The EU has spent months trying to fix the #CopyrightDirective, but leaks show they're failing. https://t.co/RVieu5V7FI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EFF: Encryption is not a privacy and security cure-all, but it is still the best existing technology we have to protect information fro…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FrankPasquale: Oligarchs enjoy a “borderless world with a pick-and-mix of rights, loopholes and laws. Inhabitants can choose Maltese pa…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great piece by @MarechalPhD https://t.co/kBEIPv3qf8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @soledadobrien: This is actually untrue and reporters should say so: https://t.co/g7gTGu4BZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exactly. https://t.co/f36RkzUvmP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MarechalPhD: My latest, with insights from @zeynep @shoshanazuboff @tim_libert @BostonJoan @safiyanoble @ghoshd7 #itsthebusinessmodelst…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks! You guys blazed the trail with your ranking of countries! https://t.co/7l1cnMszCd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rankingrights: Dear Mark Zuckerberg,
The World's Freedom of Expression is in Your Hands

@rankingrights joined with @EFF @article19org…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @zeynep: The apology tour is no longer a viable strategy for Facebook. https://t.co/VFRDOI3knN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarechalPhD Depends on what medium they are using]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating and thought provoking thread. https://t.co/iJprNzqWQ7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sheeraf: Facebook has issued a response to our story. Read for yourself: https://t.co/FGvyu77SnP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rasmus_kleis: Voice systems are-through speakers and phones-rapidly becoming more popular, but what does this mean for news? New @risj_…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh my. https://t.co/sJ7VutE76M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you @RoyaPak for all your hard work and enthusiasm!! It was a real pleasure. https://t.co/0U5GKdgWU7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @karenkornbluh: The reaction to the piece is grounded in the fact that we need more from “the platform that has become [the] heart of pu…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Info_Activism: Facebook reportedly discredited critics by linking them to George Soros - Facing a string of crises, Facebook hired a PR…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MediaGFMD: Bonjour from the @mozilla Paris office where we are joining @CIMA_Media, @tanja_maksic, and many others for an event on #AI…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RianThum: Big news: In rare coordinated move, 15 Western envoys seek meeting on Xinjiang concerns. https://t.co/zbGQX6FdD2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @craigmfagan: When dealing with the #InternetOfThings - a must have in today’s #digital world to protect your #privacy https://t.co/K6G4…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AABerwick: Today @Reuters published my investigation into how Chinese telecoms giant ZTE is helping Venezuela build a system that monit…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @craigmfagan: This is why people need to rethink #digital identity and put clear global rules in place to govern it. https://t.co/GhXl0y…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jodikantor: I’ve never seen Facebook cracked open like this. We’re in a new stage of the conversation now. I hope these sources keep ta…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @freedomonthenet: What can governments, civil society, and the private sector do to advance #netfreedom globally? See our recommendation…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you!! We are thrilled! https://t.co/H8N5sHCWWR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EDRi Awards 2018 - EDRi This year’s cranial fracture facepalm Award goes to…surprise… Facebook! https://t.co/FiM7ArOsCS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @anxiaostudio: “In any industry, the companies that will succeed over time and weather change are those that are aligned on the problems…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mattblaze: Over time, the probability that any entity holding a large store of sensitive private data will remain both competent enough…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @theGNI: With elections approaching in #DRCongo and #Bangladesh, see the report from @theGNI/@UNESCO event on ICTs and elections [https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @privacyint: Today, PI, @aclu and @UB_LawClinics filed a US FOIA lawsuit demanding US law government disclose rules for when it hacks fo…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @davidakaye: platforms may be improving but they are often opaque to users whose accounts are suspended or posts hidden from view, esp w…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KhurramParvez: UN Special Rapporteur @davidakaye  has written a letter to Twitter CEO about blocking of Twitter handles &amp; Tweets of Kas…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Joelcpj: We are very excited to be part of this celebration. Many thanks to @TimesSquareNYC for this recognition. https://t.co/wpPgIPC0…]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>