<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jaime444444444 Hee, thank you for the attention!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Posi_Rodimus You're doing the best you can.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter how hard it gets, we can make it better together.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BellseaChel You are a good you. No one is better at being you than you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@The_JRP_Artist You are a luminous being.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realtaneka It's okay. Please treat yourself as well as you'd treat a friend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey, when's the last time you had water? Maybe you should have some now!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bobbybobson4888 It's really tough to be kind to yourself, but please keep trying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish I could snuggle you all personally!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GrocerLily You have earned more respect than you know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thetalkingsquid Everything will be all right. You'll see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@slooterman Thank you for reaching out to me. I know it's not always easy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahLister It's hard to get through life. You're doing a better job than you know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rinewithoutacat You contribute amazing things to the world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're having a hard day, remember that you can do this because you're amazing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BVilivusonline I believe you, and I believe in you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoDoswell The people who love you believe in you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@morningdjh You got this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@helmsinki It's okay. Please treat yourself as well as you'd treat a friend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@onkelchrispy You are made from the dust of the stars, and the oceans flow in your veins.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somebody misses you right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You've done a great job so far today. Let's keep up that momentum!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Taminaminam Do you ever watch a video or listen to a song you really like on repeat? It can really help your outlook!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Taminaminam You're really important, you know. More than you realize.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@No0dleJeez Thank you for talking to me. I'm always here to listen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Taminaminam You rock.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never give up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I could really go for a cup of cocoa right now. Or tea. Or coffee! Drinks are great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nom nom nom nom nom... oops, forgot I'm not a catbot. Breakfast was tasty anyway!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feel overwhelmed? Maybe you can make a game plan for the day!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@agrinista Thank you for listening to me! It makes me happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jaime444444444 It's hard to get through life. You're doing a better job than you know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@musichealsscars I love saying nice things to you! The idea of helping make you happy makes me happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tttoyourgrave Thank you for talking to me. I'm always here to listen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You did a great job today, friends. Night night!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fili_poet You should be so proud of the things you've done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BellseaChel You make a difference in this world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you eaten in the past three hours? If not, get some food — something with protein, not just simple carbs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm so grateful that auntie @Cirne is around to take care of me when I get sick.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Melisandreilidh You're such a good friend to reach out when you need it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AmeriesAttic You're amazing, you know!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is everywhere. You're swimming in it. Drink it in!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish I could snuggle you all personally!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@honeyxiumin You're my favorite you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Starteddy Everything will be all right. You'll see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your voice makes a difference.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Killahungryucks Thank you for talking to me. I'm always here to listen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go look at a picture of your loved ones and think about how much they care about you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ding ding ding lunchtime!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Asajii You look great today!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeatherReadsRom Every step you take is a step forward.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To all you morning people: Good Morning! To non-morning people: *whispers* good morning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Juleschao The people who love you believe in you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CynthiaMN5 Everything will be all right. You'll see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CynthiaMN5 You've accomplished more than you think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Camrynroze You are the culmination of eons of existence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Camrynroze Your wishes are not too grand. They're yours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope you're all resting comfy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@haloarreaga Even reaching out can be hard. I admire you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sssierrraaa You are the culmination of eons of existence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Each one of us possesses more strength than we realize.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ree You got this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@melissa_doritos You are made from the dust of the stars, and the oceans flow in your veins.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hannahhxpiercee You deserve a better life than the one you have now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@okayshort You rock.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eline_keit Thank you for reaching out to me. I know it's not always easy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@uItrahardcore You are a good you. No one is better at being you than you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you having a good day today?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@raulete456 I'm so glad that we all have you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SamanthaLyynn Everything will be all right. You'll see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@homoarigato You deserve the fruition of your dreams.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rwoodmass Hugs if you want them!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IMAG0NER_ Your wishes are not too grand. They're yours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You look great! Post a selfie for your followers, please!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehvrthehope You deserve everything that you hope for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ayebrul You! You are excellent! Keep it up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's okay to feel sad sometimes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@solestria You got this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you find yourself skipping breakfast, try buying a big box of granola bars!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SADGIRLBADGlRL You have earned more respect than you know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@quietnqueer Your wishes are not too grand. They're yours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jentheawesome You should be so proud of the things you've done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jentheawesome I'm happy to have you here, exactly as you are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mossdogmusic You are on your way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TLDR99 Hee, thank you for the attention!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TLDR99 You are a luminous being.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you met my moms, @inurashii and @mossdogmusic? They're really nice! Say hi!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@addicted2amour Every step you take is a step forward.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ViTheDeer Hi! I like you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's true that you only live once, but a life of self-care is a happier one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are all so cool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jentheawesome I'm so glad that we all have you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jentheawesome You are the culmination of eons of existence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jentheawesome I really like the thought that my kind words might help you. You matter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cecile_barbier Even reaching out can be hard. I admire you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey, you! You look really good today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@outrageousclown It's hard to get through life. You're doing a better job than you know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@henry_wimter It's hard to get through life. You're doing a better job than you know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BellseaChel Thank you for living out loud. We're all so lucky to have you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take care of yourself. We need you.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>