<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA["You have to jump into disaster with both feet." - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There are worse things you can do to the people you love than kill them. The regular way is just to watch the world do it." - Lullaby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You could chop her head off and put it on blue velvet in the window of Tiffany's and somebody would buy it for a million dollars." - I.M.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Every woman is just a different kind of problem." - Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We come from a generation of people who need their TV or stereo playing all the time... These soundaholics, these quietophobics." - Lullaby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If a tree falls in the forrest and nobody is there to hear it, doesn't it just lie there and rot?" - Survivor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @claudia_artusi: @methadrone13 @chuckpalahniuk quote http://t.co/k8dO0Cri]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you haven't read Chuck's infamous short story "Guts" that's made hundreds faint at readings, do it now! Please RT... http://t.co/0ALLd2Ew]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's all mirror, mirror on the wall because beauty is power, the same way money is power, the same way a gun is power." -Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fertility Hollis quote from Survivor... #ChuckPalahniuk http://t.co/Cl7ckIlt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["People fall so in love with their pain, they can't leave it behind. The same as the stories they tell. We trap ourselves." - Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Your whole life is about discovering who you already were." - Diary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The whole world consists of nothing but vultures and hyenas waiting to take a bite out of you." - Tell-All]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's stunning how having nothing to lose will build your self-confidence." - Damned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I have to know that I can love somebody. Completely and totally, permanently and without hope of reward, just as an act of will." - I.M.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What if reality is nothing but some disease?" - Rant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Let's just not pretend. I don't have fuck for a heart. You people are not going to make me feel anything." - Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Our real discoveries come from chaos, from going to the place that looks wrong and stupid and foolish." - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["After long enough, everyone in the world will be your enemy." - Lullaby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I moved through the days like a severed head that finishes a sentence." - Amy Hempel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If we can leave all of our stories behind. Our being villains or victims. Only then can we maybe rescue the world." - Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FightClub Poster... http://t.co/KCMpsMFK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["No matter how many luxuries you get, something will be missing. No matter how carefully you choose, you'll never be totally happy."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A tiger can smile. A snake will say it loves you. Lies make us evil." - Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The murderer, the victim, the witness, each of us thinks our role is the lead." -Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There's no escaping fate, it just keeps going. Day and night, the future just keeps coming at you." - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I am the child of a lunatic. Not a child of God." - Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Everyone's in their own personal coma." - Diary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read Chuck's old short story from 1990, "Negative Reinforcement". Great Stuff. #ChuckPalahniuk ... http://t.co/gDdHM879]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The first time you meet that someone special, you can count on them one day being dead and in the ground." - Survivor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We have pain and hate and love and joy and war in the world because we want them." - Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BretEastonEllis: Most disturbing thing I've read in a long time is Michael Jackson's autopsy report in Vanity Fair. He had "no nose. ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["By the time you're thirty, your worst enemy is yourself." - Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The easiest way to avoid living is to just watch. Look for the details. Report. Don't participate." - Lullaby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tell-All Poster. #ChuckPalahniuk http://t.co/n8wo0yrT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["On a night without moon or stars you can't see a thing, but you can imagine anything." - Survivor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Our culture has made us all the same. We all want the same. Individually we are nothing." - Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The way you get to the huge, impossible yes is, you collect a lot of easy, small yeses." - Rant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Your being born makes your parents God. You owe them your life, and they can control you. Then puberty makes you Satan." Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rant artwork. #ChuckPalahniuk http://t.co/BL1FygKA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Just for the record, the weather today is bitter with occasional fits of jealous rage." - Diary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BretEastonEllis: Patrick Bateman is a Libra.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What we can't understand we call nonsense. What we can't read we call gibberish." - Survivor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["TV and the Internet are good because they keep stupid people from spending too much time in public." - Douglas Coupland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool recent interview with Chuck Palahniuk in Italian Vogue...  http://t.co/YavDQbBq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I want to find something else, unknowable, some place to be that's not on the map. A real adventure." - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The man himself. #ChuckPalahniuk http://t.co/Y752J5so]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's easy to cry when you realize everyone you love will reject you or die." - Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In light this bright, after so long in the dark, everything we can see is black and white. Only glaring shape-outlines we can blink against.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Someday, I'd like to live a life based on doing good stuff instead of just not doing bad stuff." - Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BretEastonEllis: An offended snowflake tweets to me: "How about you go fuck your own face?" Believe me, if I could I wouldn't be on  ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ChuckPalahniuk Quote http://t.co/C0Kbbuz2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You have to keep recycling yourself." - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["People used what they called a telephone because they hated being close together and they were too scared of being alone." - Survivor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If it comes down to a choice between being unloved and being vulnerable and sensitive and emotional, then you can just keep your love."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I'm in love. So kill me." - Lullaby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You are not special. You are not a beautiful or unique snowflake. You are the same decaying organic matter as everything else." -Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Look how black the sky is... I made it that way." - Bret Easton Ellis, Lunar Park]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marla Singer. Slide... #FightClub http://t.co/oNbJnQ0V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Give me lust baby. Give me malice. Give me detached existentialist ennui. Give me rampant intellectualism as a coping mechanism." - I.M.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We live and we die and anything else is just a delusion." - Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BretEastonEllis: It took me 48 years to finally understand women. I do now. It's horrifying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Right now, me getting killed would be redundant... Right now, getting killed would be a breath of spring." - Survivor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Any smart woman knows a beautiful man is her best fashion accessory." - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You're a different human being to everybody you meet." - Rant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BretEastonEllis: Namaah@The_HappyNoodle tweets: I miss when you were the genius who wrote Less Than Zero and Lunar Park. My reply: " ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BretEastonEllis: I've met many men who are transparent but I've probably never known a woman who is totally transparent. Not good or ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Art from #Snuff. #ChuckPalahniuk http://t.co/BDRMXKNq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you keep waiting for someone perfect then you'll never find love. Because it's how much you love them that makes them perfect." -Romance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What you run from only stays with you longer. When you fight something, you only make it stronger." - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Torture is torture and humiliation is humiliation only when you choose to suffer." - Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BretEastonEllis: Men are liars but in a fairly boring and predictable way. Women, on the other hand, have strange complicated ways o ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BretEastonEllis: When GENERATION WUSS starts complaining that I "used to write important books" I concur, then silently weep while l ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Invisible Monsters inspired art. #ChuckPalahniuk http://t.co/TMF6UGBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There's worse ways to be dead than dying." - Rant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Your past is just a story. And once you realize this, it has no power over you." - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you keep waiting for someone perfect then you'll never find love.  Because it's how much you love them that makes them perfect." Romance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You're that tree falling in the forrest that nobody gives a rat's ass about." - Survivor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Accidents happen. People you love will die. Nothing you treasure will last forever. And I need to accept and embrace that fact." - Rant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It only takes one mistake and nothing else you ever do will matter. You'll always be known for that one poor choice." - Snuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bret Easton Ellis, Less Than Zero... #DisappearHere http://t.co/2UbVmLnS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You wonder, if there had been a low turnout at the crucifixion, would they have rescheduled?" - Survivor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Help me give up my addiction to hope." - Damned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Sometimes the past seems too big for the present to hold."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BretEastonEllis: Skipped a Christmas party, laid on the couch and watched a depressing documentary about The Central Park Jogger cas ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shannon MacFarland. #InvisibleMonsters... Have a very Palahniuk X-Mas! ... http://t.co/bbX5U4QB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @harold_smith: @methadrone13 one of my favorite Palahniuk quotes on Christmas from Choke #averypalahniukchristmas http://t.co/AEzfNa5P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["That's what the ghosts want us to do -- all the exciting things they no longer can."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Everybody is somebody's nobody." - @CraigClevenger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Stop the excessive shopping and masturbation. Prove you're alive. If you don't claim your humanity, you will become a statistic." - F.C.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I loved you a lot more when you were dead."  - Diary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If we won't burn together, I'll burn alone." - Bret Easton Ellis, Rules of Attraction... #Brilliant #Disturbing...    https://t.co/2jXPQJWe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#InvisibleMonsters #ChuckPalahniuk http://t.co/h5lHVsU4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HollyGowisely: @methadrone13 I made myself a Christmas mug! http://t.co/532OSvcD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I'm giving you my life to prove to myself I can, I really can love somebody." - Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The weather today is partly angry, leading to resignation and ultimatums." - Diary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marla Singer. #FightClub #ChuckPalahniuk... http://t.co/NrPsfLCW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Maybe it's our sins that give God consolation when he finally has to give us cancer."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read &amp; RT... The short story that became the Invisible Monsters book. Great stuff... #ChuckPalahniuk ...  http://t.co/z5O2P8Mz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Here in your mind you have complete privacy. Here there's no difference between what is and what could be." - Choke]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>