<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Data Scientist: Category: Analytics and Emerging Digital Technologies City: Washington, District of Columbia, United States Position ID: J0817-0062 Employment Type: Full Time Meet our professionals CGI: An employer of choice Position Description:… https://t.co/32vVzVv2Lk https://t.co/T0aPBEv1NL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Member of Technical Staff – File Systems: Tintri builds storage. Those three words may not light your hair on fire … but it’s lighting up our customers’ lives. They are all excited about the agility of public cloud—AWS, Azure, etc.—and Tintri puts all… https://t.co/GcmuWic1E8 https://t.co/JgHVkeccW9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MTS- Full Stack Developer ( Cloud ): The MTS Web UI Developer position is an exciting position that includes Web UI requirements gathering, design and development of our critical developer and cloud interfaces. Ideal candidates will have a strong base in… https://t.co/WiUTvEwKok https://t.co/xzKcWZA7MU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automation Engineer / Developer: Automation Engineer / Developer Location: Woodbridge, VA J.G. Wentworth Home Lending is seeking a motivated, energetic Automation Engineer / Developer for our Woodbridge, VA location. We are looking for a team player with… https://t.co/edNinkYrdP https://t.co/JRteEhwEWn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PC – Senior Backend Engineer: Located In Kimball Junction, Park City – 20 minutes from Salt Lake! Banjo, a leader in Artificial Intelligence, is looking for a senior platform engineer in our Park City office. Banjo is changing the way the world… https://t.co/PhpHtkVS71 https://t.co/yX5IF51oWe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Python Developer Houston, Texas – United States Job Start Date – 03/13/18, Posted Date – 03/13/18 Primary SkillsPythonTax TermsC2COverview Job Description Role: Python Developer Location: Houston, TX Who are we looking for? Python OO… https://t.co/0I2b96n0fe https://t.co/sxVeDjLwOX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump attacks Amazon, again, over U.S. postal rates: (Reuters) - U.S. President Donald Trump launched his second attack in a week on https://t.co/LMWNyczHXz Inc on Saturday, accusing the world's biggest online retailer of getting unfairly cheap rates… https://t.co/cuPeYPFTiy https://t.co/yXdgROLTC4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python – C++ Developer – Hillsboro OR: Python/ C++ Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using Python/C ++ Familiar with any one Scripting language Python/Perl Strong debugging… https://t.co/FMc9B2aiMb https://t.co/Ruoa05apHF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Product Designer/Full Stack Developer (•Python•JS•React) 200k: San Francisco, CA Full-time $130k – $200k Posted Today Calling All Unicorns! If you are a Full Stack Developer with Product Design experience, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us… https://t.co/ljPkiU2Fvd https://t.co/72L0COwi5f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Python Developer: Are you an experienced Python/Django/Full Stack Developer looking to do work that matters? Forum One is looking for a Senior Developer to join our team and work out of our office in Washington, DC or Alexandria, VA. What you’ll… https://t.co/dy3nWHChNs https://t.co/0ZHqBS9s2D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Back-End/Platform: At BitGo, our mission is to make digital currencies usable for business. Since pioneering multi-signature technology in 2013, BitGo has grown to become one of the most well known and reputable brands in the digital… https://t.co/kJegHQWrLJ https://t.co/uToAcZTAAM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer: Python Automation Engineer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Programming Skills – Python (mandatory), Shell Scripting ,OOPS Concepts (Mandatory). Development of Test Script and Execution Hands-on experience in… https://t.co/2lr9fitZZU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Web Developer (Remote OK. $90-125k): Full Time Role (40+hrs/week) Onsite in NYC, or Remote (US Only) Croscon plans, builds, and grows digital products and services that help companies become leaders in their industry. Our clients range from… https://t.co/0P3WMBDhEF https://t.co/ETi0cQc7gK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer: About Us Disrupting the one-size-fits-all utility model, Inspires groundbreaking smart home subscription seamlessly combines personalized clean energy plans with best-in-class smart devices. Using the Inspire app, members can… https://t.co/B8w5BmXhFd https://t.co/E34IAAqFef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Python Developer: About Excella Excella is a technology consulting firm serving commercial, non-profit, and federal clients in the Washington, DC area. Excella builds innovative custom software solutions with a strong focus on Agile engineering… https://t.co/oBLnHsL01k https://t.co/ninVNx0OFB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Support Engineer: Job Description Job ID: R45681 201 Third Street (61049), United States of America, San Francisco, California At Capital One, we’re building a leading information-based technology company. Still founder-led by Chairman and… https://t.co/ENYgit62Qu https://t.co/nOqLIbp7v6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer – Python/.NET/C#: Purpose: Design, build, test and maintain scalable and stable off the shelf application or custom built technology solutions to meet business needs. Act as a subject matter expert for Application Software… https://t.co/gXkcVHZ8FJ https://t.co/sfmFaodzqP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Developer-Risk and Mid-Office: Reporting directly to the Risk and Operations Systems Architect, the successful candidate will be comfortable working directly with quant developers, risk analysts, operations analysts and risk managers to… https://t.co/JZAMIMkPo8 https://t.co/TRQ6Ovg8F1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Systems Engineer- Wireless TS/SCI Polygraph Clearance Required: Description: The Defense and Intelligence Division of Leidos has a career opportunity for a Senior Systems Engineer with a TS/SCI with a polygraph clearance. PRIMARY RESPONSIBILITIES:… https://t.co/Yc9DSsM6l6 https://t.co/eSqdoN3G2L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jr. Python Developer: Jr. Python Developer Ref No.: 18-19686 Location: Sunnyvale, California – Candidate should have strong hands-on developmentexperience in python scripting – Should have hands on experience in modelling in Python – Should have… https://t.co/4ljAX7w9xv https://t.co/VM6HMxgNLP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Developer Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: Python programming experience is a must. Should have atleast 2+ Years of experience in Python Application Development Able to understand OOPS concepts… https://t.co/PSEo1FaNmc https://t.co/ZSEVytqpzT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Backend Developer w/API: Looking for a mid-level (2-5 years experience) Python developer that ha experience doing Back End development and API. Some relational database experience is a plus. Must be comfortable with database paradigms, data… https://t.co/adUy49mpM1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer – Python – TS/SCI with polygraph required: Description: About Leidos At Leidos, we take responsibility for improving the quality of life of our employees, their families and the communities in which we live and work. Our commitment… https://t.co/w3fvxSdWmG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Modeler Intelligence Analyst, Senior: Job Description Job Description Job Number: R******* Booz Allen Hamilton has been at the forefront of strategy and technology for more than 100 years. Today, the firm provides management and technology… https://t.co/KSEAtPZEHj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python Familiar… https://t.co/whgDffbjWn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer: Python Automation Engineer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Experience in developing using Python / C# / C++. Candidate should have good experience or knowledge in scripting languages such as Python, Linux… https://t.co/Gr652TozhY https://t.co/ZeOwJcfVQd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Architect: Description:Leidos is looking for an experienced Cloud Architect with expertise in the following; designing and optimizing cloud infrastructure and services, a strong application security background, demonstrated success leading and… https://t.co/TSQh5SGaA8 https://t.co/90zwwzMggM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Description:Leidos ranks in the top 40 on LinkedIn’s 2017 "Top Companies" list. We offer challenging and meaningful problems, a collaborative culture, and support for your career goals and growth.       We are seeking a talented… https://t.co/lRlfPnYXlK https://t.co/cLRpUjw5b5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Python Developer: Senior Python Developer – What We Do Featured Using React Native to Build Two Native Apps &amp; Increase Paid B2B Subscriptions for Itemize Customer Story – Consult – Operate – Design – Optimize – Engineer – How We Do It – Our Work –… https://t.co/tlCsvZeoMx https://t.co/aa0PolpkcL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Description:Leidos is looking for a Software Developer to join our Corporate Computer Information Systems Group.   This position can be supported as 100% telecommute. In this role, you will work on building out a big data system to… https://t.co/kK9NQFampE https://t.co/MQvPv3j7kn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer Network Operations Analyst Programmer: Company Description ThreatConnect arms organizations with a powerful defense against cyber threats and the confidence to make strategic business decisions. Founded in 2011, ThreatConnect (then called… https://t.co/kh17YsXDTL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer (Python): Do you enjoy writing code that automates processes and focuses more on our infrastructure than the front-end? Our tech team operates in a fast-paced, collaborative, and iterative programming environment using c#, python… https://t.co/lAKxxniYQ5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python/C Developer: Req ID 95507BR Business Title Python/C Developer Group MCIS Location USA VIRGINIA Herndon Clearance Level Needed Secret Category Cyber Job Duties and Responsibilities The Python/C Developer will be a key member of our mission… https://t.co/npCqE5VLdp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Crimes Unit Technology Experienced Associate: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn… https://t.co/LU4nRRffqu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Associate, Marketing Cloud Technical Architect: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn… https://t.co/2bD7ZMCWqF https://t.co/L9glT2pMvq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Security Engineer 5 – EDS Guardium Engineer: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we want to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them succeed financially. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the center of… https://t.co/qkOCvvVsCh https://t.co/TZ98L5whvm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Python: Python Developer – Springfield, VA -Looking for a full-stack Python Developer to help develop a project which will support Intelligence Agencies efforts to patrol the Dark Web. -Project will include prototype design all the… https://t.co/XMUc2jAhkg https://t.co/9vlxv9GwK7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java/Python Developer – IV: JOB TITLE: SENIOR JAVA/PYTHON DEVELOPER DUTIES: Platform Engineering team is looking for developers for a green-field development project on AWS. Candidates will build self-service developers portals, business… https://t.co/23HmLvLRbq https://t.co/jocgC3tizM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer, Mid: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Herndon, VA Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 4/6/2018 Job Description Job Number: R******* Booz Allen Hamilton has been at the forefront of strategy and technology for… https://t.co/Cym4SZog8K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Window Server Systems Administrator: Description:Global Information Grid (GIG) Service Management-Operations (GSM-O), a Defense and Intelligence Group of Leidos has an opening for a Sr. Window Server Systems Administrator at Scott AFB, IL. JOB… https://t.co/mXVYdLYX7R https://t.co/2upFDe2olO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Develops and manages software tools in support of Enterprise Management. Formulates and defines specifications for software applications or modifies and maintains existing applications using engineering releases and utilities provided… https://t.co/rapzB8v2vg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer: Python Automation Engineer San Jose, CA Fulltime Position Job Description: – Should have Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science or equivalent stream – Should have 7-9 years of Experience in PowerShell or Python – Should Have… https://t.co/gKv5rQVGRO https://t.co/qPkp6scOLz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big Data Architect: Description:Leidos is seeking a Big Data Architect to join our Corporate Computer Information Systems Group. This position can be supported as 100% telecommute. In this role, you will work closely with Director of Cyber Transformation… https://t.co/NK1am9Sec9 https://t.co/7TvgDd4hJT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Director, Big Data: This position is the Architecture leader for a business unit or an operational area within the company and is a visible leader both internal and external to Magellan. This role will be included in evaluating potential mergers and… https://t.co/dzKOXRcHBG https://t.co/yM1SRbX1RT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embedded SW Engineer (Embedded C/C++, Python): Embedded SW Engineer (Embedded C/C++, Python) Ref No.: 18-16627 Location: san diego, California Hi, This is Shipra from Enterprise Solution Inc. I have a urgent requirement for the position mentioned below.… https://t.co/lOXcSdLxya]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Security Researcher/Software Engineer: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Linthicum Heights, MD Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 4/6/2018 Job Description Job Number: R******* Booz Allen Hamilton has been at the forefront of… https://t.co/1q0RrXeBii]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – TS Software Engineering Directorate (Arlington): Job Description If you are a technology driven individual who loves to create cutting edge software, this is the career opportunity for you. The FAST Labs business area is the… https://t.co/1fQ1nyV01w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back End Developer – Python: San Francisco, CA Full-time $100k – $120k Posted Today Are you a Back-End Developer? Do you have experience with Python? Do you have awesome communication skills? If so, then please read on! Based in San Francisco, CA, we are… https://t.co/qXVWMRXK3S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Systems Architect – SolidFire: Network Systems Architect – SolidFire Close By continuing to use and navigate this website, you are agreeing to the use of cookies. Accept – Careers – Featured Jobs – Customer Support Jobs – Engineering Jobs –… https://t.co/CP1KepLR7o https://t.co/otLRUdU7mr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Backend Software Engineer [Spark &amp; Python]: ABOUT THE ROLE Online video is exploding. The rates of both production and consumption of video content are growing exponentially over time. Our client is at the forefront of the digital video… https://t.co/V02RdMQUvZ https://t.co/zHyVnDUvhX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Specialist II: Position Overview The Finance and Analytics group is an innovative internal service provider to Tacoma Water and Tacoma Public Utilities, and is responsible for budget and rate development, financial planning, demand forecasting,… https://t.co/4hSq6d2VrI https://t.co/nJYgLrXX7T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer – Automation Engineer: NO SPONSORSHIP Looking for a Python Developer with 2+ years development and DevOps to automate the network. Must have experience working in an enterprise environment. You will automate select network operation… https://t.co/3ELMiCppKB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – GBU Processing, C++, Python: Software Engineer – GBU Processing, C++, Python Description at Raytheon Skip Navigation Raytheon – Cyber – News – What We Do – Who We Are – Global – Investors – Careers – Visit:Cyber – Who We Are – Leaders… https://t.co/xGQmmUwi0Z https://t.co/52239GYLvP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business System Analyst – Multiple Locations: We seek for a Business System Analyst with Agile testing and automation background to join our organization.   This is a rewarding opportunity for the right candidate to make good use of his/her analysis,… https://t.co/UaBuVZReK3 https://t.co/qXNH7t9ZVh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: Infosys CISRUN Technology Lead – US .Net Production support Engineer Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to create and execute strategies for their digital… https://t.co/C12qAsbCWw https://t.co/EeCqas6nqf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front End Web Developer: Interested in working for a growing, fast-paced company with diverse projects and technologies? COLAB is looking for talented team members to help shape the companys future. At COLAB, we have a close-knit team with no office… https://t.co/fjHjt62Ai7 https://t.co/RKNhHlNSZV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Performance Tester – Java, Jmeter, Python, Unix, SQL – Contract, US: PERFORMANCE TESTER – JAVA, JMETER, PYTHON, SQL – CONTRACT, US Role: PERFORMANCE TESTER Location: Washington DC or Brussles Duration: Contract Skills: JAVA, JMETER, Python, UNIX, SQL,… https://t.co/XunjJQ4R2F https://t.co/Ki8pk6N81E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior C++ Developer – Award Winning Market Leader in the Greater Providence, RI Area: We are looking for passionate individuals who want to be part of a very dynamic and successful team. We offer an entrepreneurial and casual work environment where each… https://t.co/kBBSQIkq96 https://t.co/HTeEwjIuHT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior DevOps Engineer: Location San Jose – CA, US Level Bachelor Experience 5-10 Experienced Available since 2018-01-30 Functional area Background Information Technology, Software Engineering Reference US03785 Introduction ASML brings together the most… https://t.co/wpE2MbyUTn https://t.co/TeRiaIKiWI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Front-End Software Engineer: WHO WE ARE: LifeDojo is on a mission to reverse the global epidemic of chronic disease by fundamentally reinventing how digital health improvement programs are delivered through companies, healthcare systems, schools and… https://t.co/Hn8Ny5qQJQ https://t.co/O7lra1VetB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Engineer Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: Strong Python (&gt; 2.7 Version) Programming experience is a must. Should have Application Development experience using Python Strong… https://t.co/TYiGbjsQV0 https://t.co/xjeXNaphBw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Python Developer Lombard, Illinois – United States Job Start Date – 04/25/18, Posted Date – 04/25/18 Primary SkillsPythonTax TermsC2COverviewThis is a 6-12 months contract. Phone and Skype. OPT is okay but must have good communication… https://t.co/kAsKTfsde7 https://t.co/iHSFSuWUm0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer-Python: Phantom is the only purpose-built Security Automation &amp; Orchestration platform, and the first to provide an open community for sharing Playbooks and Apps. It makes security smarter, faster, and stronger. We are an early-stage… https://t.co/IVtBU6IE3O https://t.co/OnCyBXxzzH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intern – Software Design Lab Developer: Intern – Software Design Lab Developer at HP Inc. Skip Navigation Careers Search for jobsWorking at HPFaqs Sign in &amp; apply Blog Search jobs Keyword CategorySelectAdministrationBusiness PlanningCorporate… https://t.co/5PSdC8tDr7 https://t.co/nHrlWNBBCk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Web Software Developer: Prestigious Financials Firm is currently seeking a Web Software Engineer with Python development skills. Candidate will design, develop, deploy, and support batch systems. Candidate will help architect systems, optimize… https://t.co/B7RIiBkovj https://t.co/LZglS5gEgw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Applications Systems Analyst: Requisition ID 2018-41572 Category Info Technology Position Type Regular Full-Time Department COM Biomedical Informatics Research Post End Date 5/1/2018 Overview The Genomics Application Systems Analyst/Programmer Develops,… https://t.co/e5AeaDB1xT https://t.co/KGb3MtwdcS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[storage Engineer ( EMC Platforms , cisco MDS): Storage Engineer Santa Clara, CA Fulltime position Job Description: Provide hands-on server, storage administration, system maintenance and operations support. Build, configure, and troubleshoot vSphere.… https://t.co/JNoJVtXNwG https://t.co/vZDNFVYJad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer – Analytics: Pindrop’s Protect product is used by major institutions throughout the world to identify fraudulent callers to their call centers by using advanced machine learning algorithms and signal processing of voice and… https://t.co/vKuCQ0AykE https://t.co/u8DZP9DPck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Backend Software Engineer [Spark &amp; Python]: ABOUT THE ROLE Online video is exploding. The rates of both production and consumption of video content are growing exponentially over time. Our client is at the forefront of the digital video… https://t.co/Mjx5KrRNOn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior DevOps Engineer: We are looking for a Senior Dev Operations Engineer to drive platform and operational management across the group for products including video, mobile, OTT, and web. He or she will be responsible for establishing and maintaining… https://t.co/TUQKr59msD https://t.co/LCphHkaGWM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Full Stack Software Engineer, Senior: Job Description Job Description Job Number: R******* Booz Allen Hamilton has been at the forefront of strategy and technology for more than 100 years. Today, the firm provides management and technology… https://t.co/5qTEOBUf82]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Software Engineer – Algorithms/AI – Mountain View: DataVisor is a next generation security company that utilizes industry leading unsupervised machine learning to detect fraudulent activity for financial transactions, mobile user acquisition, social… https://t.co/odLskUQpPa https://t.co/zCR6y0Vtdm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Security Engineer 5 – Continuous Monitoring Compliance Analysis and Reporting Team: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented… https://t.co/0C7CwZhaXI https://t.co/uuUzGwLijj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Artificial Intelligence Engineer – Python, TensorFLow, Caffe: San Francisco, CA Full-time $175k – $250k Posted Today If you are a Artificial Intelligence Engineer with experience, please read on! We are based in beautiful San Francisco, CA. We are an… https://t.co/CD3BPc2myH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer III – Control Systems Group (Unfilled): Come work at a place where innovation and teamwork come together to support the most exciting missions in the world! The Control Systems Group is building the future of management interfaces that… https://t.co/k49TKcvVgK https://t.co/S9UQ5v9YuQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior ASIC Verification Engineer: MaxLinear is seeking Verification Engineers to join our ASIC team in either of our Carlsbad or Irvine, CA design centers. In this role, will work on the verification for digital SoC and signal processing chipsets with… https://t.co/kjyYXBNjL2 https://t.co/vBlFA5FzAR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Engineer: Credible Behavioral Health Software is a leading Behavioral Health Enterprise Software company based in Rockville, MD and providing an Electronic Health Record (EHR) to the growing US Behavioral Health market. Recognized by Deloitte as… https://t.co/zdUuKRvpTi https://t.co/eRpAXYLYlT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon surprises Wall Street with huge profits, optimistic outlook: (Reuters) - https://t.co/LMWNyczHXz Inc's march in retail and cloud computing showed no sign of slowing on Thursday, as the company reported a surge in first-quarter profit and a rosy… https://t.co/pGqVu1Vobs https://t.co/MsyC8YVV0a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Security Engineer 5 – Continuous Monitoring Compliance Analysis and Reporting Team: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented… https://t.co/LWt9ABkRNG https://t.co/qKxEBsLiPE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Behavior Modeling Engineer, Senior: Do you enjoy using computational models and analysis techniques to solve complex problems? Would you like to advance the state-of-the art in the use of models for architecting the enterprise? Are you interested… https://t.co/g2GtZXocHe https://t.co/LPhKaCuXzd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Public Sector Cyber Risk Manager: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about us at… https://t.co/CiUK3MjCcP https://t.co/dqlDhJklWM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Validation Engineer (C#/Python): Validation Engineer (C#/Python) Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Responsibilities : * Understand the product features and develop test cases * Execution of test cases and publish test reports * Support… https://t.co/fd4JfPJLe4 https://t.co/jCNisqli5u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python developer: Python developer Ref No.: 18-14001 Location: Costa mesa, California Hi, Hope you are doing great! Please have a look at the job description below and let me know if you are interested:. Role: Python Developer Location: Costa Mesa, CA… https://t.co/3JeiLn7yCo https://t.co/pJrgoffZxy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Web Developer: Senior Web Developer – What We Do Featured Using React Native to Build Two Native Apps &amp; Increase Paid B2B Subscriptions for Itemize Customer Story – Consult – Operate – Design – Optimize – Engineer – How We Do It – Our Work –… https://t.co/Niov5a6Hgh https://t.co/VX6KU05kNa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Tools DevOps Engineer: Who is SugarCRM SugarCRM enables businesses to create extraordinary customer relationships with the most empowering, adaptable and affordable customer relationship management (CRM) solution on the market. We are the… https://t.co/oC6CvuIR7d https://t.co/3OPVpfV64u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Financial Developer – Python: Financial Python Developer McLean, VA $100-130K +bonus Design, develop and support systems within the financial modelling and research area. Design and develop new code and review existing code changes to ensure… https://t.co/dRS0ma7a7d https://t.co/uSf586tpFu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Programming Skills – Python (mandatory), Shell Scripting ,OOPS Concepts (Mandatory). Development of Test Script and Execution Hands-on experience… https://t.co/lkgOwAviNR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Systems Engineer,Senior: Why choose between doing meaningful work and having a fulfilling life? At MITRE, you can have both. That’s because MITRE people are committed to tackling our nation’s toughest challenges—and we’re committed to the… https://t.co/lClNmLIx8c https://t.co/fMXHQCqWH8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Security Engineer (TS/SCI Polygraph Clearance): As a member of MITRE’s Cyber Operations Department, help enable our customer to improve cyber security practices and designs for the DoD community. Key Functions: Develop technologies, tools,… https://t.co/fCaL9DqaAZ https://t.co/RcbS8QY1nc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mobile Software Engineer (Android): Granular is the leading software and analytics company for agriculture. We are revolutionizing one of the world’s largest and most important industries by making farmers lives easier and making them more profitable.… https://t.co/WuL9kYFtxk https://t.co/BWuf85jHq3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Team Lead: Web Team Lead with DRB Systems DRB Systems is a growing and vibrant software company in need a Web Team Lead. We are looking for motivated and enthusiastic individuals to help our organization succeed. The Web Team Lead will work on a… https://t.co/cTfduHV8Ib https://t.co/rjYnqzgNHY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blockchain Platform Developer: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Rockville, MD Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 4/18/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management… https://t.co/LiPGC6sUq9 https://t.co/JK8SORUPOS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Application Developer 3/4 (Mid – Sr. Level) Top Secret Clearance Required:   Job Description – Python Application Developer 3/4 (Mid – Sr. Level) Top Secret Clearance Required (18004882) Python Application Developer 3/4 (Mid – Sr. Level) Top… https://t.co/8KgLWsF7hN https://t.co/zEhQP4uICR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python Familiar with any one… https://t.co/s0qyGc19sO https://t.co/qIOjUiJ0vI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Programmer: Python Developer Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: You should possess at least a Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science, Computer Engineering or related field. A Master’s degree is preferred. Candidate should… https://t.co/IzGY1ytKiz https://t.co/6oVPaqNqhz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[python Automation developer: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python Familiar with any one… https://t.co/HVLRWcJlmI https://t.co/jDzfHV93Oi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Python Developer Ref No.:18-07182 Location: San Jose, California Experience Level: 5 Years Start Date: 04/18/2018 W2 contract coly and visa sponsorship is not available- Role: Python Developer Location: San Jose, CA Duration: 6+ Months… https://t.co/fKbmpcUv2s https://t.co/tNTLOJ75Zn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (C++/ Python): Software Engineer Hillsboro OR Job Responsibilities: Closely work with client POC to understand the requirements and priorities Contribute to the development of test automation framework Work with customers to determine… https://t.co/oztvVkivvk https://t.co/cCdqrHVou8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Fintech Data Analytics Manager: To support the Investment Management Fintech Strategies (IMFS) mission of exploring technologies that could dramatically improve investment performance or make capital markets work better, and to embed a culture of… https://t.co/lBiHjEomvS https://t.co/Y0GxKByNrm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Security Engineer 5 – Continuous Monitoring Compliance Analysis and Reporting Team: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented… https://t.co/tFiQOy2Q3X]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>