<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[We (San Francisco) have football weather during baseball season, and baseball weather during football season. - Herb Caen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome tennis t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the tennis lovers in your life!   http://t.co/GZORdtnwt4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learning is what most adults will do for a living in the 21st century. - Perelman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must either modify your dreams or magnify your skills. - Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Ankle Watches – Is This the New Place to Wear a Watch?  http://t.co/3zOimJ8gO9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just want one day off when I can go swimming and eat ice cream and look at rainbows.  Mariah Carey (pre-rehab)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Chi-Lites  http://t.co/4Wvd8fcOQV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The scenery was very beautiful. But I did not see the Great Wall. - Yang Liwei, China's first astronaut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cowboys, Mavs, Rangers and more read about the Sports teams of the Dallas Fort-Worth Metroplex - http://t.co/iF8dr9olNy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketing is too important to be left to the marketing department. - David Packard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Electric Light Orchestra  http://t.co/iTojEMytfi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The way you can understand all of the social media is as the creation of a new kind of public space - Dana Boyd, Social Media Research MSFT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spock. This child is about to wipe out every living thing on Earth. Now, what do you suggest we do? spank it? - Dr. McCoy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new source of power is not money in the hands of a few, but information in the hands of many. - John Naisbitt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys, that Chinese dude is going to get pretty crispy out here. How long are you going to keep him tied down like that? Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Egotism is the Knack of seeing desirable qualities in yourself that others can't see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is not the strongest of the species that survive, nor the most intelligent, but the one most responsive to change. - Charles Darwin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You could get rich manufacturing crutches for lame excuses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Ensure You Have Safe Drinking Water in a Disaster  http://t.co/BLvMjCmUmi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In any contest between power and patience -- bet on patience]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can tell whether a man is clever by his answers. You can tell whether a man is wise by his questions —&gt; Naguib Mahfouz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 12 - And so it begins...  http://t.co/kBNYgU0dRp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman is the only hunter who uses herself for bait]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Videos Games and Fitness with Wii and XBOX  http://t.co/Ta2aBo1hj0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Empty pockets never held anyone back. Only empty heads and empty hearts can do that.  Norman Vincent Peale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fish Hotel Aquarium - Jazz Up Your Office! http://t.co/v0S0yd6vou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have enemies? Good. That means you've stood up for something, sometime in your life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some days, you just can't get rid of a bomb! - Adam West, Batman &amp; Robin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Maxine Brown  http://t.co/cql2TPM319]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All our dreams can come true -- if we have the courage to pursue them. - Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious Pacifier with a Mustache  - Kids and Adults will love it! http://t.co/tceUUxSPEY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Leapy Lee the Classic Rock Artist?  http://t.co/tG30E0DjIK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it weren't for baseball, many kids wouldn't know what a millionaire looked like. - Phyllis Diller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Cascades  http://t.co/6fohi4iiWp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get up to Speed on Baseball with this Summary of Baseball Positions  http://t.co/ftucmbfJKn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have not failed. I've just found 10,000 ways that won't work - Thomas Alva Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman who doesn't wear perfume has no future. Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The purity of a person's heart can be quickly measured by how they regard animals - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is amazing how may drivers, even at the Formula One Level, think that the brakes are for slowing the car down. - Mario Andretti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball must be a great game to survive the fools who run it. - Bill Terry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ultimately, the only power to which man should aspire is that which he exercises over himself. - Elie Wiesel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I went through baseball as a player to be named later." - Joe Garagiola]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He ran out of talent about halfway through the corner. - Buddy Baker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History Of Samuel Adams Beer  http://t.co/EsS0Xv7Ai6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Capital as such is not evil; it is its wrong use that is evil. Capital in some form or other will always be needed.  Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hit the ball over the fence and you can take your time going around the bases. - John W. Raper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome cooking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the cooking lovers in your life!   http://t.co/Dr2YGuS422]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A patient man is one who likes slow catsup.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would give a million bucks to have seen my mother say "cute shoes" to a naked Ashley Judd. --&gt; Brian Fies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One day your life will flash before your eyes. Make sure it is worth watching - Mooie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Either write something worth reading or do something worth writing about.  Benjamin Franklin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Leif Garrett  http://t.co/vkqj8FxtzC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Their marriage is a partnership, he's the silent partner.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make Your House More Attractive With Fall Flowers  http://t.co/gkWyd0jznI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do elephants have trunks? - they don't have glove compartments]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dogs have owners, cats have staff. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the The Recent History of Beer  http://t.co/i4fm7We8ZH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Carpenters  http://t.co/7LSy6ZuZoK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the top burger chains in the US!  http://t.co/Yw45aBEY5p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Useful Products to Help Housebreak Your Pet  http://t.co/am1fs6DG3J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have no use for bodyguards, but I have very specific use for two highly trained certified public accountants. - Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The one thing my mom will let me get is a nice shoe sometimes. - Chloe Moretz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The good Lord gave you a body that can stand most anything. It's your mind you have to convince. - Vincent Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never threw an illegal pitch. The trouble is, once in a while I toss one that ain't never been seen by this generation. - Satchel Paige]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not wait to strike until the iron is hot; but make it hot by striking - William B. Sprague]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yum Yum Canned Unicorn Meat - great gag gift :&gt;)  http://t.co/HLXSX4RQmK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of KC and the Sunshine Band  http://t.co/tSTD5uE7Qs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If opportunity doesn't knock, build a door. - Milton Berle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How To Invest In Penny Stocks  http://t.co/fdXvyRZi7i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He who opens a school door, closes a prison. - Victor Hugo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these lovely Dos XX Most Interesting Main the World Commercials!  http://t.co/gfuArYO7Hj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is the only major sport that appears backward in a mirror. - George Carlin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science fiction writers foresee the inevitable, and although problems and catastrophes may be inevitable, solutions are not. - Isaac Asimov]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Hire a Strategy Consulting Firm?  http://t.co/JV24VSjdDb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the math geek in your life - the math clock... http://t.co/pIvSE0E8cN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spock. This child is about to wipe out every living thing on Earth. Now, what do you suggest we do? spank it? - Dr. McCoy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is not a rock opera. This is not Tommy. I can write songs that emote, and that's it. - John Mellencamp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame: Capture the Flag  http://t.co/sgelx6cNHS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Clear Lighted Skateboard with green LED Lights  http://t.co/HJVEt3GMco]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Adoption Part II - the Bulgaria Phase  http://t.co/WrpVOqy0Mp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It wasnt a mission to be a rock star. It wasnt a mission of mine to even be a movie star. I just intended to be a good actor. - Don Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It will work. I am a marketing genius. - Paris Hilton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a meat-eating world, wearing leather for shoes and even clothes, the discussion of fur is childish. --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My little dog -- a heartbeat at my feet. - Edith Wharton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Skol Beer  http://t.co/QiEKgjWKpX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Tom Petty and the Heartbreakers  http://t.co/ARMsGDFjhE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best use of life is to spend it for something that outlasts it - William James]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An office clock is rarely stolen --  everyone watches it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My own mother told me I didn't have a shot in hell of winning tonight.  A shocked Katherine Heigl upon winning an Emmy for Grey's Anatomy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome disco t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the disco lovers in your life!   http://t.co/BRMCR6Pgfw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its not so much about the shoes, but the person wearing them --&gt; Adriana Trigiani, Viola in Real Life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You may have to fight a battle more than once to win it. - Margaret Thatcher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Understanding Attention Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder (ADHD)  http://t.co/is1ot6n1hb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Increase Space in Your Garage with Suitable Garage Floors  http://t.co/HgUh1VhKlM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I find your lack of faith disturbing. - Darth Vader, Star Wars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Few people SUFFER from egotism. With most of them it's a PLEASURE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feed sparingly and defy the physician. - James Howell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Libby: How'd you get shot, anyway? Sawyer: With a gun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sawyer: You versus Sun - hot oil death match - my money's on you, Sheena. Kate: Thanks for your vote of confidence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My life is an open book. With illustrations.  Hugh Hefner]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>