<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's the result of 6 weeks of work - i just finished varnishing 15 new paintings..i want a beer http://t.co/hkVp0LXoie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a sweet new painting of a parking meter in turquoise/orange. #art #vancouver http://t.co/b1XVNZ3lXm http://t.co/pJEtAi7VbC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just wrapped up this painting of a parking meter. I really like the colour palette. The branded touches... http://t.co/cGZkUTVuba]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@colestudio hey mate thanks for following me..i got this upcoming show if you are able: https://t.co/cgcteVkM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a new painting. If you are familiar with old Hastings, you'll certainly recognize this :) http://t.co/SY7gB6Nh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh snap we are hanging our City:Life art show in one week! https://t.co/cgcteVkM #art #vancouver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parking Meter! http://t.co/y0zfXpGN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our sweet art show is up in a week and a half! Opening isnt until March 8 but you can see the show starting Feb 25! https://t.co/cgcteVkM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a great video summary of the Golden Brush event - you can see Jennifer and I working on our piece at the... http://t.co/hhyZjyDI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fifth and Maple
12" x 12" 
Ink and acrylic on wood panel

Note link.. http://t.co/n3AAmBR3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Abbott and Dunsmuir
12" x 12"
Ink and acrylic on wood panel

Note the goombas. http://t.co/2TZqolok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The City:Life show gets hung in just under two weeks. Pretty stoked, got 12 new works (and counting) ready for it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here is my upcoming art show! Would you like to join us for the opening!? http://t.co/u34Vl9L5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a brand new painting. I hope you like it! http://t.co/O7I8gljP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justinsears your work is pretty rad man, im not doing portrature right now but i also work on wood panels: http://t.co/XWF77qzi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool studio shot. Photo cred: Ricky Pizzacalla http://t.co/UARBrQ5L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's my submission to the charity auction tomorrow: It's a painting of the Peak2Peak gondola with TOMS shoes: http://t.co/lhYvzcZpPf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you wanna come hang tomorrow (Thursday) night I'll be at the Roundhouse Center in Yaletown with a few pieces,... http://t.co/DbPo7F58Qn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just slapped a whack of new paintings and art projects on my page: http://t.co/LhzLRuc2PE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some more progress on my TOMS-sponsored piece for Telus Fest this weekend. I've filled in some more areas of the... http://t.co/5HrmRpPPXc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kstennant oooohhh sorry haha misunderstood that! Ok perfect, that's even better!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@melissajanke yesssssssa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kstennant @makeitshow yup!! I'm there, I'd love to chat with ya! It's Friday-Sunday (19-21) :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@melissajanke mayor of givin-hugs-ville =me. I can give you one at SOTA this Friday if you're there.. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kstennant thanks friend! I'll be workin at the quay in the nice weather all summer long if you are ever there (near the round fountain)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kstennant I know exactly who bought it. We met at my apartment for the exchange! Also cool - I've now moved to north can - 3rd/lonsdale :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kstennant whose the sitter? Which piece was it? This sounds very
Intriguing..!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What! Which one..explain! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm currently working on a piece for the charity auction at State of the Art this Friday in Whistler - SOTA is the... http://t.co/IljCTJ5YJx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Photo: Getting new prints ready for #makeitvancouver in less than two weeks. I'll be glad to share these with you! http://t.co/gcdiYUuCZW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Progress shot - Frog part two :) http://t.co/B0Lxaw3rgD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just finished this commission piece for my friend Kirsten. I like it alot and its a good scale too - 3x3 ft... http://t.co/k9Xk08HbPn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I accompanied my friend Beth to the airport tonight. On the way back I started a new piece - I think I may start a... http://t.co/o8stH3n5iG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just sold my last green vulture shirt! Still got a couple grey ones left:... http://t.co/wwjF4ndy6V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@curranjosh pretty stoked about it man]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starting up a new cool project, making a piece of art on a baseball bat for the Blue Jays. Details and pics to come]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[haleyjo19 asked: WOW! I’m just speechless, cannot stop looking at your art. you’re so talented and... http://t.co/KiH7Fa71nq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hot off the press - prints of 8 of my favorite urban paintings. Do you like?? http://t.co/3lkmCAD5C2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HUSHVancouver Hello Hush magazine, how are you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rinamiriam nice background image!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three new prints of my recent city paintings now available on Art From Concentrate, a sweet online art store in TO: http://t.co/ABFkILjI0K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sketchbook Pages - #4

This one was just too fun. Needs green. http://t.co/SZuuQrrbqS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sketchbook Pages - #3

(I used some silver and brown sharpie on this one) http://t.co/lpqgX5JvpH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sketchbook Pages - #2 http://t.co/lOMlldL2Jm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sketchbook Pages - #1 http://t.co/oDGga8HVYJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/MTduWsJ66Q

If you are feeling the urge to write a note to a friend, I've got a few packs of cards left! http://t.co/BuV0uVYEvy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch me talk about my art! This is a really cool video interview, shot in my studio:... http://t.co/YI2XnnMYb1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blog post - an in-depth analysis about my phone booth painting titled "Dyadic"... http://t.co/sPY4UJomn5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dreamfevers  thanks friend - its a pretty good feeling being back in the studio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With our show up and the reception over, I'm back to a couple commission pieces: http://t.co/fBVmlMrykr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great success last night - thanks to all who came out!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[see you TONIGHT at the gallery :)

https://t.co/2BbtHzQS4c http://t.co/RsFUVLT1PP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[see you TONIGHT at the gallery :)

https://t.co/2BbtHzQS4c http://t.co/VbEDt2AguG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[see you TONIGHT at the gallery :)

https://t.co/2BbtHzQS4c http://t.co/wLUyuCiyog]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exploring the creation of one of my first abstract paintings: http://t.co/7AfUnIYlTb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/7AfUnIYlTb http://t.co/XeKzPiPS43]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some sweet Etsy Vancouver goodness: Vancouver Special by Tracy Matthews http://t.co/ZS5yLHLMf1 via @Etsy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's an alleyway sketch from Cambie and Hastings in Vancouver: https://t.co/ONI5gKXf89]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a wee sketch of @SackvilleTownNB  from my recent adventure back to the Maritimes: https://t.co/EJRLTs7L0U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I started a blue painting tonight..I really like how this paint collected on the palette...nice and relaxing :) http://t.co/O8sXMDLJLm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spent the last few days looking at art in Montreal. Mind = blown. Can't wait to get back to Van and work on new stuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At
Ylvp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I did this one last commission before my vacation. This is for a good friend, who really loves this fellow who is... http://t.co/IiQZFE2kok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Melky likes Land Rovers :) http://t.co/JAVs8KoCIq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a big fan of the wrap of film around the handle http://t.co/xU3QoV35m2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's another.. http://t.co/IrzK6HMuIB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the close up document shots of the bat painting :) http://t.co/yLnKp3Ua2R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this painting I made on a baseball bat for the Toronto Blue Jays' awesome foundation @JaysCare ! http://t.co/OnlpmE5pNK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a video of my baseball bat that i created for the @JaysCare Curve Ball auction happening shortly! http://t.co/XNbMcuUJlh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the event where my upcoming bat painting will be auctioned off, stoked! http://t.co/A3vGrJuKeB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a sneak peek of my bat for the 2013 Curve Ball charity gala for the @JaysCare  Foundation on May 13. http://t.co/cbT8a7UXiL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My painting is on ARTBOMB today! Check this out:

http://t.co/6IlX6SqmkB http://t.co/xkfwl4hZrV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Currently wrapping up a special project for a certain Toronto-based Baseball club :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's my piece I made for the @OpusArtSupplies painting contest today! I really like the alleys in Vancouver :) http://t.co/20cwFd7tn0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a sneak peek of my new card series. They're printed, and now I can prepare, package and batch them. http://t.co/MK2DGK9L3W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you like these Vancouver greeting cards? Developing them as a 3-pack item to sell. http://t.co/oKKrRibLgE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All my animal cards are for sale on my shop. I've started filling sales already! Have you seen??... http://t.co/T9ifQxhnRP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YapesPaints one day i might have to as well...and it terrifies me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out my Interview with a local news site here: http://t.co/2MgBAzRAZk via @goodnews_weekly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I shipped one of these cards to Tasmania. What a cool destination for my second sale! http://t.co/yXKznhpwdm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's some interesting observations from @makeitshow this weekend - http://t.co/TuuhyH4ZVH #makeitvancouver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back to the studio with two less original paintings. Glad these found good homes: http://t.co/IW3LuoU81j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@josiejose thanks for the follow friend!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Packin er in! Very successful weekend at Make-It. Think I'll need to do it again at Christmas :) http://t.co/8XD3vh0vyE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two successful days at the make-it show so far. Last chance to visit the show is today, 11-5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Black_Drop @portpaperco this is my first make-it show and I love all the creative, entrepreneurial inspiration and support-so grand!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/5ELZA8UlZF This is a brand new leopard card I've produced, you can snatch em up at my shop :) #makeitvancouver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Owl Art Card available here! It turned out sweeeeet! http://t.co/YJBnkDIiwc via @Etsy @makeitshow #makeitvancouver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Greeting Card! Elephant Painting! http://t.co/Aiz5WwTbZN via @Etsy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm working on a new painting of the street post that I love at main and broadway. I think I'll make it blue http://t.co/wbgOgzfkEz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm firing up the etsy shop with greeting cards - I think you will like these: http://t.co/6VHsgoOxsW via @Etsy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This painting of mine will be auctioned off on ARTBOMB shortly! Message me if you are interested... https://t.co/jbxOYqfF3B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm selling city cards @makeitshow this weekend, like this tasty fella-$4 a pop with a sweet brown recycled envelope! http://t.co/M3mumwkETV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/168mG9uYCp http://t.co/HPlaVMlrdi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GraemeBerglund thanks mate, watched your vid on HAWC, did one myself. Liked yours. Good job to you too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GraemeBerglund  ink and acrylic :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GraemeBerglund http://t.co/UGycO39qg1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GraemeBerglund http://t.co/qh5VJTtBvF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I primed up this wood panel for a cool commission piece I'm working on. Had to have the panel custom-built... http://t.co/cChrgazEuY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cheers and thanks to everybody who supported me at Car Free Day on Main Street yesterday! The day was fantastic!... http://t.co/kB58jYTTjd]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>