<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: Inside a train, circa 1800s. https://t.co/V34avy4vQR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mike Klimo makes a convincing argument for why the "Star Wars" prequels weren't so awful: https://t.co/qIbP2us2ZX. Seen it, @ItsAdamCanuck?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sarahsim Finally! A philosophy I can really support wholeheartedly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @doctorow: Local rock in great mood today!
https://t.co/MZaziETjdD https://t.co/cjERU1Cq8Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Courier12: There is no magic bullet. There is only this. https://t.co/Wa8fBDRGv7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @playwrightnow: Asking someone to read and critique your play is a huge favor. You get to do it once per person per script. #2amt #amwri…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mistershrewd "By the way, fellow babies -- Booogerrrr!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evanjstern Where've ya been? "Twilight" is what made Anna Kendrick famous. While we're talking about her -- ever seen "Drinking Buddies"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tarakjpratt Adulting is great! Sometimes I phone up my mother and say, "It's 15 minutes until dinner, and I'm eating cookies!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people accuse me of being a snob. But I'm not! Ask anybody. Well, anybody who matters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson Oh, "Chix Page -- I get it! It's a bit of a joke. Unfortunately, it's not a lot of a joke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another entertainer dead this year: Merle Haggard! I always thought this song was best taken as a lampoon: https://t.co/kBpJ34ahXW.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: A woman wearing a crinoline being dressed with the aid of long poles to lift her dress over the hoops, circa 1860. https…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Greengrass sez young people starting in film are being "screwed to the ground" if they don’t have rich parents. https://t.co/qLfzPLjK8V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people accuse me of being pretentious, but I can only say, "Au contraire!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@benjaminluk Oh, I see -- from "Harverd University". Hmm ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Criterion: The world premiere of IT'S A MAD, MAD, MAD, MAD WORLD (1963) doubled as opening night of the iconic Cinerama Dome. https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson The stuff about restoring fine lines is also interesting. Shame that for most of its history, comics printing was so poor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson Perhaps you've seen the posts by Sean Michael Robinson about restoring the B&amp;W art for "Cerebus": https://t.co/jVgdfN2rFG.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson Ha! Never even heard of it. Thanks; I love weird ephemera like that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson Would you include or exclude those "Spider-Man Teaches Arc-Welding" industrial Marvel comics?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evanjstern That's one of the worst haikus I've read all week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WernerTwertzog: And then they came for the nihilists, and I said nothing, because, you know, nothing really matters. Everyone dies at s…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @playwrightnow: Deadlines are good for at least two types of writers: those who need a push to get started, and those who have trouble l…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ubermichael The service at McDonald's is just getting worse and worse these days. @brawluk @ethorkel @lesterbergquist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Daredevil" season 2 shows what happens when you shoot, edit, and release a show without having a script first.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great news for fans of both government transparency and comic books: https://t.co/UoX9J0gg2g.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They've introduced Elektra into "Daredevil" season 2. She's acting out of character too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Daredevil" season 2 episode 4 features more of The Punisher acting out of character. Why is the character so hard for movies to handle?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RealEOC: Watch: Rare 1973 Interview With Malcolm McDowell On Stanley #Kubrick's 'A Clockwork Orange' https://t.co/yFXuCjoh9e https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Daredevil" season 2 episode 3: Did you like the one-take hallway fight scene in season 1? Here it is again!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson A good editor doesn't let tears stain the pages!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JMDeMatteis: "A good story is about pain and hope and the transition from one to the other... The essential quality is hope.”—David Ger…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MysteryOscar I suspect that nobody would be able to tell the difference.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nroshak @ReneeStephen There was a follow-up in the letters column too, a couple of issues later.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the hell is this Muzak? "If I'd never been born / If my corpse was still warm / Darling, would you still love me the same?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two episodes into Season 2 of "Daringdevil -- The Man Without Ears". So far The Punisher is acting out of character.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HeerJeet: The remarkable thing about late period Cerebus is Dave Sim created a new religion synthesizing the worst of Judaism, Christia…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Is Independent Film 'Healthy' If 99% of Us Fail?" The answer is no. https://t.co/PGWnzfWgiQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @playwrightnow: The huge, undersold value of a subplot is that you have something to cut away to. It gives you the ability to manipulate…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["At the level most producers work at, you have to make 10 movies just to make a living." https://t.co/PGWnzfWgiQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BadFatherHan: Your name is BEN. We named the dog "Kylo."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tarakjpratt "... dogs and cats living together ..!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evanjstern It wasn't one of those rude songs you sing when you're alone, was it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @maireadcase: long ago it was foretold https://t.co/3kyDwsboku]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson That's gotta be Bill Ward. (I perversely (pervertedly?) enjoyed his Nanny Dickering in "Cracked".) Where is this from, pls?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Sonic_Screwup: The psychology of BVS bears all the salience of a 15yo boy's pre-gun rampage tumblr manifesto.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't have a lot of hope for the project's success, but it's worth a try: https://t.co/rGBaOGK3g8.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson Or from the early 1940s Invaders, depending on how you look at it. (Roy Thomas's secret identity was Nostalgia Boy.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BiffMcLaughlin Take advantage of the ladies in hairnets handing out free samples of food! I call it "Costco Dim Sum".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson Is this from a Dell comic? It looks like Jack Manning art.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: Famous illusionist and stunt performer, Harry Houdini in 1914. Colorized by @_HistoryInColor. https://t.co/jI96Ikuemo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales of potato chips expected to hit $76 billion in four years! https://t.co/icmM5jzeNR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: Sony 8-301W Television, 1961. https://t.co/LgylFhxwm6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the best thing I've read all day! https://t.co/XrhemHCkJe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: Autochrome of women in Bohemian-esque dress, Paris, circa 1905. https://t.co/eB7gACkbOF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AKellumCreer And trees can be cut down and converted into money -- just as we would gladly sacrifice our lungs for a coupl'a bucks, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mccrabb_will: "When John picked-up the hand-held camera he became your scene partner."
--Ben Gazzara on Cassavetes https://t.co/HR9RbhS…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Kurt_Vonnegut: Humor is an almost physiological response to fear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: Olivia Newton-John and John Travolta in ‘Grease’, 1978. https://t.co/GlyO9lrOTO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cox_tom: "Take pity on me, for it is cold, all of 30 seconds since you let me out, and the catflap is a full 6 yards away." https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LC_Perez81 @garfunkeloates Wasn't she the youngest of her numerous sisters? In which case I guess she'd be "The Littlest Mermaid".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mchawk: Knew I'd seen that face before. Turns out @sinKEVitch can predict the future. Got milk? https://t.co/nBjULmqNwa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just heard an unbelievable piece of trivia. It said that many people think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SaySandra: @canadianglen https://t.co/r70FL19jyK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OUTtv: Happy St. Patricks Day! Here's @JoshRimer with the Top 10 holiday inspired list! Be safe, green and #fabulous! https://t.co/7jjT…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson That's the best term I've ever heard coined!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsAdamCanuck Claire's been nothing but honest since she was introduced! Although I think Emily is acting a bit out of character with this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @shanebee: So... about those "other" #starwars films that a lot of us don't like to talk about. https://t.co/YnNWQ8pZCV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsAdamCanuck Can you believe Raj fell for Emily's ruse, even after Claire warned him?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@freyburg It's not that they want micro-apartments; it's that that's all they can afford.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsAdamCanuck Unfortunately, that means you must admit to watching Chuck Lorre shows. What is it? "Big Bang Theory"? Oooo --!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevecavers I seem to remember that the remedy for that is to swallow a spider -- to catch the fly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TATJANASL: Federico Fellini on the set of 'Amarcord' (1973) https://t.co/d5XsnD72EV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MYSADCAT: My cat is sad because witnessing the break up of these two other cats' relationship has brought him close to tears https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good lord! Look at these people! https://t.co/S9dSmHXTrn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @STACEYNIGHTMARE: I don’t mind if fans call me “Mom” if they don’t mind me regurgitating food into their mouths!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsAdamCanuck Well, it was after the institution of the rule.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsAdamCanuck My family had to have a "No singing at the table" rule for suppertime.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @playwrightnow: One way to design a character is to work backwards. What character would be least suited for all the things she's about…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson That is probably an appropriate response.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: Carrie Fisher sitting on Chewbacca's lap, 1983. https://t.co/atyu5O9C4n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Writers beware! "Novelists warn about drug-resistant strain of writer’s block": https://t.co/4Xskf8iAKj.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HumphreyBogart: The one and only @MarilynMonroe would have celebrated her 90th birthday today. https://t.co/lhWUvbkWX0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then, I assume, he threw the toast away as wasted. The 'mites -- yecch. https://t.co/fpHqgVv721]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsAdamCanuck "Written and Directed by Adam Canuck Smithee".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@montypython @BlackSheepBeer @EricIdle What about "Stout Through the Head"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsAdamCanuck Damn! Well, where do people go? Laundromat! Thrift shop! Garage sale! Hiking (picturesque)! Day care! Alcoholics Anonymous!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsAdamCanuck Each other's place! Work! Grocery store! Beauty parlour / bridal shop / female thing! Bus stop! Club! Coffee shop! Old home!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsAdamCanuck Yeah, we've all known about those since before they were cool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JarelGeis Then you can finally start getting some stuff done around here!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They're both gettin' too old for this shit. https://t.co/gFlLmedMfI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @openculture: Terry Gilliam Explains The Difference Between Kubrick (Great Filmmaker)&amp; Spielberg (Less So) https://t.co/3zec5wbzmr https…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattdagley Yes! Join me in my campaign for the 30-hour day. I function much better awake for 20 hours and asleep for 10 than 16 / 8.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @evanjstern: memes are just inside jokes that everybody's in on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @_Reinette and anyone else who knows a blind dog -- have you seen this? https://t.co/kLJBg3GwPA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Kurt_Vonnegut: The two prime movers in the Universe are Time and Luck.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Filmkritter I haven't been that impressed with the DC Cinematic Universe -- really misfiring compared to the MCU -- but I like "The Flash".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Filmkritter Well, I'm the Damian from Earth-2, so make of that what you will.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“You don’t realize this because you go see so many plays, but normal people do not go to plays.” https://t.co/fvdtgb8AAs]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>