<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Life Is Not Easy, But So What? https://t.co/XR0ysppWK0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To reach something good it is very useful to have gone astray, and thus acquire experience. -St. Teresa of Avila]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes you have to be silent in order to be heard. It's easier to criticize than to do better. -Swiss Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I had to live my life over again, I'd try to make more mistakes next time. -Nadine Stair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boredom is the feeling that everything is a waste of time; serenity, that nothing is. -Thomas Szasz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let us not be too particular; it is better to have old secondhand diamonds than none at all. -Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Act as if what you do makes a difference. It does. -William James #quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While we may not be able to control all that happens to us, we can control what happens inside us. -Benjamin Franklin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellence Quotes https://t.co/CmMih6m730]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's good to do uncomfortable things. It's weight training for life. ~ Anne Lamott]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to achieve a high goal, you're going to have to take some chances. -Alberto Salazar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Successful people are successful because they form the habits of doing those things that failures don't like to do. -Albert Gray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter how often you are defeated, you are born to victory. -Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To succeed means that you may have to step out of line and march to the sound of your own drummer. -Keith Degreen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We do not remember days, we remember moments. The richness of life lies in memories we have forgotten. -Cesare Pavese]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 Aspiration Quotations https://t.co/cqAjosCgZ7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We judge ourselves by what we feel capable of doing, while others judge us by what we have already done. -Longfellow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never give up, for that is just the place and time that the tide will turn. -Harriet Beecher Stowe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will not meddle with that which I cannot mend. -Thomas Fuller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They only live who dare. -Lewis Morris]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So celebrate what you've accomplished, but raise the bar a little higher each time you succeed. -Mia Hamm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Better to master one mountain than a thousand foothills. -William A. Ward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The IF Poem https://t.co/I7lOxPrEkC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The person born with a talent they are meant to use will find their greatest happiness in using… https://t.co/PRtmJFiJ7I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People who take risks are the people you’ll lose against. -John Sculley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friendship Quotes https://t.co/7DyACPc6On]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make service your first priority, not success, and success will follow. -unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The more chance there is of stubbing your toe, the more chance you have of stepping into success. -Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being in Good Favor https://t.co/2bYfKeXoM9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your goals are the road maps that guide you and show you what is possible for your life. -Les Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Belief Quotes https://t.co/ZUAN4DPGCz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Variety is the very spice of life, that gives it all its flavor. -William Cowper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The lure of the distant and the difficult is deceptive. The great opportunity is where you are. -John Burroughs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Patience Quotes https://t.co/m5DdXl7EuB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep going, for success lies just around the corner for those who refuse to quit. -Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wealth Poem https://t.co/5515ZZyiLZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Desire! That's the one secret of every person's career. Not education, not being born with hidden talents. Desire. -Bobby Unser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to be successful, it's simple. Know what you are doing. Love what you are doing. And believe in what you are doing. -W. Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another Motivational Video of the Day https://t.co/eTLxKCKW7j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To burn always with this hard gem-like flame, to maintain this ecstasy, is success in life. -Walter Pater]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Success is not the place one arrives, but rather the spirit with which one undertakes and continues the journey. -Alex Noble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Possibility Quotes https://t.co/RGf24ZmTAg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Out of clutter, find simplicity. From discord, find harmony. In the middle of difficulty lies opportunity. -Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Successful people are not gifted; they just work hard, then succeed on purpose. -G.K. Nielson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Creativity Quotes https://t.co/i4BUTeTMKD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Success in almost any field depends more on energy and drive than it does on intelligence.  -Sloan Wilson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is often hard to distinguish between the hard knocks in life and those of opportunity. -Frederick Phillips]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Success comes from having dreams that are bigger than your fears. -Terry Litwiller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smile Quotes https://t.co/ADdxhbLSxj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It does not matter how slowly you do so long as you do not stop. -Confucius #quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Self discipline is when your conscience tells you to do something and you don't talk back. -W.K. Hope]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fulfillment Quotes https://t.co/jRiUQVTiXa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All you need is the plan, the road map, and the courage to press on to your destination. -Earl… https://t.co/dlXIwF1BSm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All you have to do is know where you're going. The answers will come to you of their own accord. -Earl Nightingale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We should not criticise those who trip by taking a more difficult than usual step. -Dick Hubbard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Set your target and keep trying until you reach it.  -Napoleon Hill #quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Work Quotes https://t.co/rFeSI8EG19]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wealth Quotes https://t.co/hTGQjbqVX6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I am idle and shiftless, my affairs become confused; when I work, I get results; not great results, but enough to encourage me. -E Howe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[20 Awesome Motivational Quotes https://t.co/tGOWBVZnbU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't be afraid to fail. Experience is just mistakes you don't make anymore. -Joe Garagiola]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[15 Democracy Quotes https://t.co/W3V4jB44Er]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the realm of ideas, everything depends on enthusiasm; in the real world, all rests on perseverance. -Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Motivation Quotes Can Inspire You To Take Action https://t.co/a12H5Q4O8l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[May we never be tempted to forget that there can be no real success apart from service, that success is but service visualized. -B.C. Forbes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To know even one life has breathed easier because you have lived -- this is to have succeeded. -Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trouble Quotes https://t.co/DjjeNZoAOj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you run into a wall, don't turn around and give up. Figure out how to climb it, go through it, or work around it. -Michael Jordan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It Isn't the Church - It's You https://t.co/AUXMZ56Y00]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Success isn't magic or hocus-pocus--its simply learning how to focus. -Jack Canfield]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have heard it said that the first ingredient of success-the earliest spark in the dreaming youth-is this: dream a great dream. -J Appleman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Do You Tackle Your Work? https://t.co/r9kADzaOCY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's amazing what ordinary people can do if they set out without preconceived notions. -Charles F. Kettering]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trust only movement. Life happens at the level of events, not of words. Trust movement. -Alfred Adler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never confuse a single defeat with a final defeat. -F. Scott Fitzgerald

-

-

-

#quotes… https://t.co/pF3KjZTe9V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 Random Motivational Quotes https://t.co/OOQjchV7Ba]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You may delay, but time will not, and lost time is never found again. -Benjamin Franklin #quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whatever we plant in our subconscious mind and nourish with repetition and emotion will one day become a reality. -Earl Nightingale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don’t spend time beating on a wall, hoping to transform it into a door. -Dr. Laura Schlessinger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inspirational Judgement Quotes https://t.co/ML3MTHyt7I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes adversity is what you need to face in order to become successful. -Zig… https://t.co/nVGImGQkhh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The more we do, the more we can do; the more busy we are, the more leisure we have. -William Hazlitt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 Great Success Quotes https://t.co/FPBAEY1dZu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes you have to forget what’s gone, appreciate what remains, and look forward to what’s coming next. -unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Past and Present Quotes https://t.co/qpZb5KYEvD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most important thing about having goals is having one. -Geoffrey F. Albert

.

.
.
.
#quotes… https://t.co/PdFmH6YF0J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never Too Late: Poem by Longfellow https://t.co/nIUptyHz0l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don’t go through life, grow through life. -Eric Butterworth

#quotes #sayings #proverbs… https://t.co/d9vFbCEwZQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don’t sit back and let things happen to you. Go out and happen to things. -unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Health Quotes https://t.co/b6iGwZW5Gr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just posted a photo https://t.co/pg5uXEwY5O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intuition Quotes https://t.co/7kAkQXCZA0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want things to be different, perhaps the answer is to become different yourself. -Norman… https://t.co/HIXtHbAKZp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Faith Quotes https://t.co/nFX32FgamG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be content with your lot; one cannot be first in everything. -Aesop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One minute of patience can result in ten years of peace. -Italian Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are richer today https://t.co/Za7Z9ILqrC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perseverance is not a long race; it is many races one after another. -Walter Elliot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool Motivational Quotes https://t.co/nqcX2uUyra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Failure is the opportunity to begin again more intelligently. -Moshe Arens

#quotes #sayings… https://t.co/XmHwHEc4AM]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>