<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of Skylanders: Spyro’s Adventure  http://t.co/IOeSOTp4DQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A college is a place where pebbles are polished and diamonds dimmed. - Robert Ingersoll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Little by little does the trick. - Aesop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the dressing room, I always put on my right shoe first. Same thing for my right wristband. -  Mary Lou Retton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of KC and the Sunshine Band  http://t.co/R28tp9H7st]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious Cat Scratch Rapper Music Mixer - Awesome!  http://t.co/7gxZmyd5gY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about the Bay Area city of Fremont, California  http://t.co/n06WASPYkX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When money talks these days, it's probably asking what happened]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about Oakland, California  http://t.co/uBN3GdoISD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exciting History of Baseball  http://t.co/CgdLJ0Ufr3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Brady Bunch is an American sitcom classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/uFImb4F2Zf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Isaac Asimov  http://t.co/Os35f2P9ia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every great batter works on the theory that the pitcher is more afraid of him than he is of the pitcher. - Ty Cobb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Animals are such agreeable friends - they ask no questions, they pass no criticisms. - George Elliot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 2 - Road Trip!!!  http://t.co/Gu2BarfKaf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was never interested in being a rock star. I always wanted to be Boris Karloff. - Gene Simmons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Auto racing, bull fighting, and mountain climbing are the only real sports --  all the others are games. - Ernest Hemingway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was always attracted to science fiction movies. - Tina Turner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Bert Kaempfert  http://t.co/UfwaZk49JX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never make fun of the geeks, one day they will be your boss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You teach best what you most need to learn. - Richard David Bach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are peaks and valleys in this game. We're in a valley - Death Valley. - Kirby Puckett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it time to go home yet? I keep clicking these damn shoes, but nothing happens. - Robin Hecht]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When a subject becomes totally obsolete we make it a required course. - Peter Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Arthur Alexander - The Unknown Legend  http://t.co/QIqXMNUWSE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can tell that you're in trouble when you feel the air on the back of your neck instead of in your face. - Buddy Baker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Top Secrets for Using Facebook Pages for Your Business  http://t.co/Qs3OFz2MYh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I'm not back in five minutes, just wait longer. - Ace Ventura, Ace ventura, Pet Detective]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He was born with a silver spoon --  but  never made a stir with it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Great Tours of Europe  http://t.co/rlHecY25R3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I speak my mind. I never mind what I speak!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I dig science fiction, though it was never really my thing. - Yancy Butler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Julie London  http://t.co/sjd0xaS6kT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatness of a nation and its moral progress can be judged by the way its animals are treated.- Mahatma Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of B.B. King  http://t.co/BwECRCnJB0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Cascades  http://t.co/dUXELRwZsB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Arthur Alexander - The Unknown Legend  http://t.co/QIqXMNUWSE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Personally, I'm always ready to learn, although I do not always like being taught. - Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What really decides consumers to buy or not to buy is the content of your advertising, not its form. - David Ogilvy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In my opinion Microsoft is a lot better at making money than it is at making good operating systems. Linus Torvalds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For women, shoes are the most important. Good shoes take you good places. --&gt; Seo Min Hyun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It costs a lot of money to look this cheap --&gt; Dolly Parton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is nothing permanent except change. - Heraclitus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Fun Science Ideas for Kids  http://t.co/c1MOvFbl36]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Electric Light Orchestra  http://t.co/NZjYyYHSL3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Johnny Ace: A Life of Unfulfilled Dreams  http://t.co/5HE0wIqeGH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All men are born free and equal, but most of them get married.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be nice to geek's, you'll probably end up working for one - Bill Gates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where there is an open mind, there will always be a frontier. - Charles F. Kettering]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of Armies of Magic – Facebook Game  http://t.co/wkalhPpV4a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Marmalade Insurance: Selecting The Right Insurance  http://t.co/bpARDe0Zfc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Book... The Shapeshifter  http://t.co/EG3bE7wfZ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flattery, like perfume, should be smelled, not swallowed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Remote Control Inflatable Flying Shark! AWESOME! http://t.co/miHIdD6pI6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Joe Tex  http://t.co/fN3t4xnGtx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live daringly, boldly, fearlessly. Taste the relish to be found in competition - in having put forth the best within you. - Henry J. Kaiser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this chicken what I have, or is this fish? I know it's tuna but it says 'Chicken of the Sea'.  Jessica Simpson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dress shabbily and they remember the dress; dress impeccably and they remember the woman. --&gt; Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ray, if someone asks you if you're a god, you say YES! - Winston, Ghostbusters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The dog represents all that is best in man. - Etienne Charlet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana’s Lyme Journey – Part 16 – Seven Months Later  http://t.co/zYvqwUS03o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crack is cheap I make too much $ to ever smoke crack. Lets get that straight. OK? We dont do crack We dont do that Crack is whack - Whtney H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The entrepreneur always searches for change, responds to it, and exploits it as an opportunity. - Peter F. Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dog is the only thing on earth that will love you more than you love yourself. - Josh Billings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No change in musical style will survive unless it is accompanied by a change in clothing style. Rock is to dress up to.  - Frank Zappa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome basketball t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the basketball lovers in your life!   http://t.co/yX5p2OMGbi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[80% of the final exam will be based on the one lecture you missed and the one book you didn't read.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But I'm a rock 'n' roll singer; that's my livelihood, my occupation.  - Little Richard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to know what a man is really like, take notice of how he acts when he loses money.  Simone Weil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Assisted Living - Some Things to Consider  http://t.co/z6S2TUhnNF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love making money, but you can't live your life waiting to get rich in a job that no longer feeds you artistically. Julianna Margulies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn Marketing Secrets for eCommerce Business  http://t.co/OcttUWr6n6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Chi-Lites  http://t.co/7QGQc5kKFr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strangers passing in the street, by chance two separate glances meet and I am you and what I see is me - Echoes - Pink Floyd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can lead a boy to college but you can't make him think. - Elbert Hubbard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One day your life will flash before your eyes. Make sure it is worth watching - Mooie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome disco t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the disco lovers in your life!   http://t.co/Z5RW9peeof]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Google Webmaster Tools  http://t.co/wy1cwXLEhv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You maniacs! You blew it up! Oh, damn you! Damn you all to hell! - Taylor, Planet of the Apes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hating the (New York) Yankees is as American as pizza pie, unwed mothers, and cheating on your income tax. - Mike Royko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool All Wood Watch! http://t.co/SrFsb9Axnp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Doobie Brothers  http://t.co/CAXOb9LfTW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't fix stupid - Larry Morgan, NHRA Pro Stock driver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating Introduction to Marmalade Insurance: How to Select an Insurance Agency  http://t.co/Rcve6ZOlS3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It costs a lot of money to look this cheap --&gt; Dolly Parton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of the Facebook Game: Miscrits of Sunfall Kingdom  http://t.co/ZD3DoztEAE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you don't do what's best for your body, you're the one who comes up on the short end. - Julius Erving]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Celiac Disease And Gluten Free Foods  http://t.co/bXqWUQwIu0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Mars Rover Curiosity  http://t.co/JQWVBkY8tR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life started getting good when I started making money. Balthazar Getty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just think it's great to show a gown that's $8,000 and a shoe that's, like, $25 - but still look fabulous together. - Christian Siriano]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the History Of Pac-Man  http://t.co/q9YRi5gK2x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lot of people love Oreos. So their manufacturer is making money. That means more dividends for shareholders. Maria Bartiromo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Yanjing Beer  http://t.co/eRspNCkZkw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I believe you are your work. Don't trade the stuff of your life, time, for nothing more than dollars. That's a rotten bargain - Rita  Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Donna Summer  http://t.co/YBEG3CY2eM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you cease to dream you cease to live - Malcolm Forbes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Beverly Hillbillies – An American Classic TV Series  http://t.co/QFmxLfNoYy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[History of Mojang - The makers of Minecraft - http://t.co/YC99NnMrSr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't get too caught up in making money or having a job, get excited about the fact that you can design your life. Darren L. Johnson]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>