<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@Froot_Loop18 haha loves it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@Froot_Loop18: Do you know ... The muffin man ??&gt;_&lt;” haha my favorite line in the movie!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@Joqzan: -Throws cookies and twizzlers at everyone -” yay twizzlers! Thank you!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrincessJoules haha I must look like I rolled in Doritos. Went boarding yesterday and burnt my face and neck, ouch!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @StephenAtHome: Our teens are getting drunk on Purell. But to be fair, it tastes better than Jagermeister.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow what a tear jerker! Chris Man and Xristina #TheVoice I have tears in my eyes and I rarely watch this show!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotta have a little crazy in u to do this #whistler http://t.co/4J2BwP1d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#7thheaven right here right now! Happy #NakedSunday everyone! #BeEpic #whistler http://t.co/4Hsa0V4b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#whistler, sun, tons of snow, unlimited visibility @Schwarzenegger.  Remember this? http://t.co/wmEkLUQA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Joqzan enjoying breakfast of champion on top of Blackcomb ready for first run of the day!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#whistler #beautifulbc snowboarding this #NakedSunday w the black bears grazing as i board on by #epic #priceless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Many Impressions Does it Really Take? - MarketingSavant http://t.co/VWfhlRA3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@IAmKarySit: Goodnite (-: zzzzzz” sweet dreams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On any team there r specialty teams within. Specific roles &amp; responsibilities. Teams that come together &amp; feed off their strengths, succeed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ConfessionNight I'm feeling the pressure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ayymiPAPITO: #ConfessionNight i've masturbated at Starbucks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Joqzan ya baby! Break of champions :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@Joqzan: Blunt + Cup Of Coffee = :D” insert: Cup of Tea = :D x 2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ayocaptn: I'm just in my own little world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pitch. Sign up. Raise. Develop. Passion and Persistence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mouth burning, nose running hot hot hot and damn good homemade Tom yum soup :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LA_Reid: “Difficulties mastered are opportunities won.” — Winston Churchill #BeEpic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning Twitterverse. Hope you all have an outstanding day and a fabulous week ahead! Onwards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Froot_Loop18 trying to shove one thru the phone now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Froot_Loop18 Protein packed, cinnamon, chocolate chip w raisins &amp; Manuka honey. Soo good!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cash flow is king]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Froot_Loop18 here you go! :P http://t.co/9BhHyV35]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mmmm #cookiemonster therapy http://t.co/OPkW7mZR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SunTzuSaid: If the enemy leaves a door open, you must rush in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@erichrich “#Taurus are crazy sexy and mad cool. A perfect combo!” yes we are!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@Henri_Do: @2ChrisSimpson that was some amazing sushi! #toshisushi #eatit” Soo good!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such a half assed workout. I really need to turn off data at the gym so I can focus and not get so distracted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SunTzuSaid: If it is to your advantage, make a forward move; if not, stay where you are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EAT ME RAW http://t.co/irlXW25N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last meeting of the week back @ Rodney's oyster house but this time with Richard and Elena. Intel+ http://t.co/4ZcRg6q6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Comfortably numb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Signed 2 new associations, 3 new distributors, met w potential investors, &amp; negotiating deals for 1000s of new subscribers #priceless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So you douse yourself with cologne only to go to the gym and force me to gag on your aqua velva?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making my escape for the gym. Today was huge and it is not over. Onwards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#IfItWasntForTwitter #vancouver for sale 2011 #Cadillac CTS-V Coupe on autoTRADER.ca. http://t.co/qvUlCGbd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nature's porn http://t.co/TQUlmUr8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoying low tide @ Rodney's Oyster House in #Yaletown http://t.co/LiecuiCl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For Sale 2011 CADILLAC CTS-V Coupe on autoTRADER.ca. http://t.co/qvUlCGbd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LA_Reid: Use your time efficiently and strategize exactly how you will accomplish your plan.  #TheEpicLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mmmm dim sum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stumbling home]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marioalv_ lol ok well safe travels nonetheless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shaneREACTI0N haha note to self]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marioalv_ safe travels Mario! Don't get wet, oh wait, yes do get wet!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shaneREACTI0N that was fast. They do come quick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@Schwarzenegger: Wow, you even found some of the shots from when we went to the pose for inmates. http://t.co/zrfVOiUr” incredible!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shaneREACTI0N isn't that what you ordered? A Chinese.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the gym. Biceps triceps forearms and core today. Not enough time for more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donydavid focus focus focus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MikePorter69 because they import it from BC!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LA_Reid: Motivation exists within your heart and mind...#TheEpicLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoying the sun setting at English Bay #vancouver http://t.co/aGhGCppA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy #420 everyone! Peace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marathon work day today! Many positive steps forward. Off to gym now then more work before bed. Onwards!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @erichrich: The more I see you, the more I want you. The more I get to know you, the more I want you close to me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SamJiraDesign ahhh ok carry on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SamJiraDesign What the?? Lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Silly rabbit. Trix are for kids]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Onwards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TGIF. I just had an epiphany. Think cirque. Think Montreal in September. The rest is history]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do I just squirt a little? Or u can squirt a lot. Mmm Really changes ur water. It changes everything! U can say that again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, what do you have there. Berry pomegranate Mio. Berry pomegranate Mio? Berry pomegranate Mio.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could this really be summer?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DalaiLama: When, from the depths of your heart, you spontaneously wish all beings to find true, lasting happiness, this is great love.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @click4time: “Yesterday is a canceled check; tomorrow is a promissory note; today is the only cash you have - so spend it wisely”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tuhin: Create, curate and consume. The 3Cs of social design.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @levie: Life is too short to not be working on a once in lifetime opportunity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@SamJiraDesign: @2ChrisSimpson be a predator lol! :p” haha yes you are!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haha too short too sweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously? http://t.co/lJjtGnol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't tell if it's the boat that moving or the booze is kicking in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoying the sun on @Vanbartenders cruise #vancouver with @ZyBeaudoin http://t.co/uTcvdRFY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@KarlLagerfeld: The KARL men's line will be unveiled with @LuisaViaRoma on June 18th !” Nice!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrincessJoules add the guy in Montreal who tied up bf naked, video'd, killed &amp; decapitated, him &amp; the cracks are showing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving the new wheels. Such a different vibe than my last. Less intense, more chill and relaxed to drive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How well do you know the one you are sleeping with? Don't be a victim. Play safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Integrity and Dignity. Maintain these and win.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ALePeilbetFANS: OMG FUNNIEST THING ALLLLL DAYYYYYYY..... Bahahahhaahhahahhahahahahahahha!I can't breath! http://t.co/IptsxFtE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Makes me smile endlessly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@IAmKarySit: I need a glass of wine!" I'll join you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @click4time: “You can't turn back the clock. But you can wind it up again.” - Bonnie Prudden]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[House of cards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheLewisBlack: Shit, piss, fuck, cunt, cocksucker, motherfucker, tits....Thanks, George. http://t.co/EAX6rV5H #7dirtywords #GeorgeCarlin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ayymiPAPITO it's tempting but I'm taken]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ayymiPAPITO haha yes when you open it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ayymiPAPITO perhaps if it wasn't so blurry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That moment when you realize one of your best friends is about to stab you in the back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LA_Reid: “The elevator to success is out of order. You’ll have to use the stairs…. One step at a time.” -Rande Wilson #BeEpic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DalaiLama: Genuine friendship depends on genuine affection and taking a sense of responsibility for each other.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning. I can smell bacon outside my window mmmm I want bacon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[07:00-01:48 mission accomplished. Nite Twitterverse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ayymiPAPITO: my birthday is over...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The stars are aligning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DepressedDarth: Join the Dark Side and never regret a bad decision again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LA_Reid: YOU have the power to make your dreams come true! #BeEpic]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>