<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[A princess hears of an orchid that grows amethysts, and decides to burn it down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sea serpent in Africa is made of the Sun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A volcano suddenly falls from the sky in London.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An undertaker invents a new type of clock based on the movement of peacocks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A drunk tsarina passes a law that everyone must be buttery.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A drunk king secretly wishes to have sexual intercourse with nudity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A vice president discovers that compassion does not exist, and is relieved.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A snake is reading Henry James's Portrait of a Lady.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A constipated YouTube star owns a crystal ball which lets him see every face since the birth of Christ.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By climbing to the top of a yurt, you can reach another world. It is like Ottawa, except everything is made of rubies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Egyptian psychologist is writing an impossibly complex theory of kaleidoscopes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Anatolian schoolmistress writes a book that is made out of the Vatican.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sorority of university professors invent a parallel universe where everything is electric guitars.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solve this mystery: A grandfather is found dead in a library. Beside him is a beret and a dishwasher.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bank manager discovers that sixty-four philosophers are controlling our lives.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A teenage dentist discovers a sandalwood tree made of wisdom.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A drag queen owns a piece of rose quartz that allows her to read every essay in Borneo at the same time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sorceress is eating a liquorice allsort on top of a porcelain lake.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A homeless congresswoman builds a mansion that is filled with post-natal depression.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A king proposes marriage to Broadway musicals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ninety-nine Scientologists come together to worship writers block.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Dutch manuscript describes an act of treachery that wishes to be a baroness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A 15th century manuscript describes a game in which competitors must fight music.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a solar eclipse a poem is etched into a moonstone belonging to a Maltese necromancer. It reads: "You'll never amount to anything."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sultan searches for a clockwork device which allows him to turn into a palace.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a lunar eclipse you suddenly become as wise as Leibniz.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A travel agent in Atlantic City writes a book on how to paint a picture of the American Dream.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A French tsar murders a homeless person with an unusual weapon: Christianity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a witch in Ohio that is 60 times more depressed than you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A serene billionaire hears of a lighthouse located inside a gold mine, and dedicates her life to finding it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A pirate plays a game of rock, paper, scissors with a giant sequoia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An astrologer discovers that the economy is under the control of childhood dreams.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A doctoral student in New Jersey wishes to substitute the tsar with a toilet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A hacker is falling in love with pornography.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Trojan psychiatrist sets up a clinic for scarecrows.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Galapagos tortoise made of photographs is born in Michigan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A creature is born in Sicily with the head of a rabbit and the body of a witch. It has the mind of a Palestinian spice merchant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An anaesthetist is playing Xbox. Suddenly, the Xbox turns into Gummi bears.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seven office managers are going on a quest. Their aim is to find a lost machine with the power to create emeralds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A veterinarian flies first class to Hawaii. In that time, he lives another life as a 14th century quantum physicist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A medieval nobleman appears in a McDonald's in Delhi. He knows exactly what to do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A travel agent reads a poem about a clock that can destroy the queen, and sets out to find it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman is reading a treatise by Spinoza on the subject of cellos.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook is researching how to turn people into burritoes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A girl remembers every marital argument that has taken place in Budapest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A cauliflower creates feelings of anger and resentment in everyone around it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A hippopotamus is weeping inside a ballgown.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An architect is writing a list of people he plans to kill: A bureaucrat, a woman and a math teacher.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By looking at a sock, a famous congresswoman is able to turn into an eagle. Then she flies to Toronto.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solve this riddle: Why did the clean fox walk into the candy store?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bottle of Bordeaux causes everyone who drinks it to disappear and reappear in the East Village.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An apple tree levitates over Burma. It is controlled by a zebra.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A queen decides to steal every clock in Montréal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Mexican rowboat sails across a sea of the rule of law.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A legendary novel describes a woman made of maps.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women whose name begins with the letter R have been drinking mojitos all afternoon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A secretive game show host has a penis instead of a stomach.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A kitten made of meaninglessness appears in Thailand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your mother tells you that you are a sweet potato.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sailor becomes a millionaire by buying and selling Hillary Clinton.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Bavarian social media manager has an unusual ability: She can smell Aretha Franklin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Afghan sheik tells the story of a rhinoceros with a bayonet instead of a horn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a tsunami in Addis Ababa. It is full of pineapples.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a gay sauna in Manchester. Everyone who goes there is an eye of a mosquito.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Sicilian fashion stylist sees a puddle of ice cream in the shape of a rose.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Chicago there is a poppy which has petals in the shape of sleep.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A neurosurgeon buys a spell from a witch. It causes him to gradually turn into a nose.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Beijing there is a desert island that is made of busboys.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Punjabi man writes a poem about JavaScript.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Caribbean queen decrees that everyone must try to destroy corruption.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A princess hears of a swamp made of treatises, and sends an army to burn it down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A duchess sentences a supernova to death.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is an army officer in heaven who has 342 shoulders.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A caliph owns a Japanese woodblock print which depicts every embarrassing moment by a warlock.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Venezuelan witch has a passionate love affair with a gigantic book.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dictator makes love to a pearl inside a clockwork temple.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lonely tsar plays a tennis match with a planet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Las Vegas there is a castle which works as an undertaker.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Mesopotamian scholar spends all his time writing a poem about unicorns.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Venice there is a mango which is getting married to a ghoul.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Frankfurt School is playing a game of Monopoly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A showgirl switches bodies with an elf.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An archivist writes a PhD thesis about every eel's death that has taken place in Sri Lanka.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Danish woman discovers that her son is her grandmother.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You discover that you are an ocean.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A jelly bean is playing the slot machines at Vegas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A congresswoman decides to destroy your heart's desire.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A prince passes a law against tombstones.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A tsarina decrees that there will be a new sign of the zodiac: The lobster.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Instagram celebrity steals the patriarchy and hides it inside a merry-go-round.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Tibet is a textbook whose every page is a swimming pool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Spanish nun spends all her time writing an opera about angel's wings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A satrap in Marrakech is famous for torturing mediocrity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a volcano in Madagascar. It spews out skulls.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Swiss clinical psychologist establishes a practice that assists silent demons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An ostrich creates feelings of shame in everyone nearby.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On New Year's Eve miniature bats roam the streets of Mumbai.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A spider made of moustaches is born in Detroit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By touching a playing card, you can reach another world. It is located inside a puppy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A grandmother is climbing up the side of a lobster. It has been her childhood dream.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>