<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The road to success is dotted with many tempting parking places. - Unknown Author]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The primary one being, like I said, I don't like rock 'n' roll piano.  - Warren Zevon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fellow who rocks the boat is never the fellow at the oars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Gladys Knight and the Pips  http://t.co/rlG3ARrZ0E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ability is the art of getting credit for all the home runs somebody else hits. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this gallery of the top 10 Asian beers!  http://t.co/qRYlWEOI2w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Yanjing Beer  http://t.co/jUemf0wYTy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An extravagance is anything you buy that is of no earthly use to your wife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seniors Gain from Social Networking Technology  http://t.co/ygIdP1qQeX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Lovin' Spoonful  http://t.co/56xp42OSMa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never wear the same shoe twice. - Dion Sanders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I am become Death, the destroyer of worlds - J. Robert Oppenheimer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dream house is one that cost twice as much as you ever dreamed it would…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Some Young People Need Mentoring  http://t.co/sAbK3h4bjy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of Skylanders: Spyro’s Adventure  http://t.co/IAEPQ1qkUt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about the Bay Area city of Fremont, California  http://t.co/SywfqxPOrI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If high heels were so wonderful, men would be wearing them. - Sue Grafton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Alice Cooper  http://t.co/YTtrHBsmsU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one can make you feel inferior without your permission. - Eleanor Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So now I'm left with cigarettes, and I'm trying to scrape that off my shoe and then I'll be done. - Diane Lane]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the Major Work Shoe Brands  http://t.co/9bw46lgKvy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't go into details, I've already told you  more than I overheard myself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana’s Lyme Journey – Part 16 – Seven Months Later  http://t.co/UXCZHqM284]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who can believe that there is no soul behind those luminous doggie eyes! - Theophile Gautier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Book Review - Endangered: Drakensang  http://t.co/QpmKfeFFuY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just think it's great to show a gown that's $8,000 and a shoe that's, like, $25 - but still look fabulous together. - Christian Siriano]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool All Wood Watch! http://t.co/3YsxjZtMCu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool Geek Tech - Mini USB Fan - Keep cool at your desk! --&gt; http://t.co/2vhH6dYisF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the animals: God has given them the rudiments of thought and joy untroubled - Fyodor Dostoyevsky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only point in making money is, you can tell some big shot where to go. Humphrey Bogart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Rose Royce  http://t.co/IlwKDkpLxO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Andy Kim  http://t.co/5BEayVXncF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Cool History of Science Fiction  http://t.co/euVmUE1WP0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Giant Swiss Army Knife - with Over 87 Tools!  http://t.co/z5IgFPQ3We]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How To Invest In Penny Stocks  http://t.co/LWBODpovTH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Fitness Apps – Is There One That Is the Best?  http://t.co/5g4H1r7wJQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Musical Legend – Johnny Adams  http://t.co/U4Dkj9rBAE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They just couldn't live without each other --  so they got married and discovered they could]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Condolence:  something that aches when everything else feels so good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips for Effective Use of LinkedIn for Your Company  http://t.co/HJIpOL8QfK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He had a forward spring... And an early fall...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some days, you just can't get rid of a bomb! - Adam West, Batman &amp; Robin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to ZZ Top  http://t.co/KAW0tLNS7C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't do any vulgar movements.  -  Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very cool Star Wars windshield sun reflector - may the force be with you!   http://t.co/4ndJIeek0v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Flea and Tick Control For Your Pet  http://t.co/Vge4uMfCts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips To Draw More Traffic With Quality Link Building  http://t.co/s6BN7YE37X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stiletto, I look at it more as an attitude as opposed to a high-heeled shoe. - Lita Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The groundwork of all happiness is health. - Leigh Hunt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is Horology?  http://t.co/nRo7v87IeK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science fiction is no more written for scientists than ghost stories are written for ghosts. - Brian W. Aldiss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How To Find The Right Gluten Free Foods  http://t.co/cZYaDoQ0yx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Cowboy Boots  http://t.co/tv9h01Oez9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lot of people love Oreos. So their manufacturer is making money. That means more dividends for shareholders. Maria Bartiromo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learning Styles - Learn About Teaching so They Can Learn  http://t.co/Go8KVkkUvM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Music from this Bose Blue Tooth system - iPad, iPhone and more - easy great sound -&gt; http://t.co/ysxCUn2ViK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Parliament  http://t.co/WKX1M1MDlH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Colonize Mars: Can This Dream Become a Reality?  http://t.co/S3ExpKK4F7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What people forget is that every movie that gets made keeps making money for somebody FOREVER. Dave Thomas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to The Knack  http://t.co/ryKu12wOu3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no room in baseball for discrimination. It is our national pastime and a game for all. - Lou Gehrig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smartphones are reinventing the connection between companies and their customers.  Rich Miner - Partner Google Ventures]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is 10% what happens to us and 90% how we react to it. - Ennis P. Kimbro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They just couldn't live without each other --  so they got married and discovered they could]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the top science fiction movies of all time!  http://t.co/EQrK5FMdKw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Foxy  http://t.co/i4fhQs1OKP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Interesting Burger Facts and History  http://t.co/C9uwKKXuA0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Blondie  http://t.co/xh2UAlRRbH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Blue Oyster Cult   http://t.co/xoaGvYJ6o9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Don Henley  http://t.co/hgTg4gjH02]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WOW - Very Cool A Sticky Note Wrist Watch! http://t.co/ny1id246fT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We can judge the heart of a man by his treatment of animals. - Immanual Kant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What is Fiverr Exactly and Why All the Buzz?  http://t.co/8q9o7CkiEA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sex and the City changed New York - New York's become a big shoe store now, unfortunately. -  Chris Noth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are 10 types of people in the world: those who understand binary, and those who don't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Lulu  http://t.co/pNv9QwclD9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space is the stature of God. - Joseph Joubert]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Led Zeppelin  http://t.co/l3jYN6Htos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating history of Wrigley Field!  http://t.co/KCyfvuFt4p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Design is a constant challenge to balance comfort with luxe, the practical with the desirable. - Donna Karan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The internet has turned what used to be a controlled, one-way message into a real-time dialogue with millions - Danniel Sacks, Fast Company]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History Of Samuel Adams Beer  http://t.co/BVfLv5Ruaj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is Ununpentium?  http://t.co/yCVwyhMoip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So exactly what is an atomic clock?  http://t.co/GfJkZnVGTf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instead of giving myself reasons why I can't, I give myself reasons why I can. - Unknown Author]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The scenery was very beautiful. But I did not see the Great Wall. - Yang Liwei, China's first astronaut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Skiing in Canada - learn more!  http://t.co/fUyhDuemfu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you are thin, don't eat fast. If you are fat, don't eat fast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The right shoe can make everything different. - Jimmy Choo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must accept finite disappointment, but we must never lose infinite hope. - Martin Luther King, Jr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The reason Las Vegas is getting so big is nobody can afford to buy a ticket to leave.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop praising a woman, she'll think you don't love her.  Keep it up and she'll think she is too good for you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Paul Evans the Classic Rock Artist?  http://t.co/8SXcEbgj45]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Creating Beautiful Gardens with Butterflies - Easy Steps  http://t.co/Qf3YLVNant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The task of the modern educator is not to cut down jungles, but to irrigate deserts. - C. S. Lewis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is not a technology.  It's a conversation. And it's happening with our with out you.  Charlene Li - Co-Author Groundswell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you wish to grow thinner, diminish your dinner. - Henry Sambrooke Leigh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn The Importance of a Good Pitching Repertoire for Young Pitchers  http://t.co/UGVJmwdsEW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Genesis  http://t.co/Ibv2OlCjtO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the great department store of life, baseball is the toy department. - Author Unknown]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>