<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Five card stud, nothing wild. And the sky's the limit - Captain Jean Luc Picard - Last Line of Star Trek the Next Generation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Sword Umbrella - Eye Catching http://t.co/L05SvOFbKT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame Turf Wars: Them Hackers Though  http://t.co/RRxSXxkNIk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you wish to grow thinner, diminish your dinner. - Henry Sambrooke Leigh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Deep Purple  http://t.co/BUMSZlHxMl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You may have to fight a battle more than once to win it. - Margaret Thatcher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Empty pockets never held anyone back. Only empty heads and empty hearts can do that.  Norman Vincent Peale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Green Acres is an American sitcom classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/qHupkOPrDC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A patient man is one who likes slow catsup.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the Kane Chronicles  http://t.co/aDpynsa6cd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still love her. But she's retarded, too. Guy Ritchie on Madonna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most beautiful makeup of a woman is passion. But cosmetics are easier to buy. --&gt; Yves Saint-Laurent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Donna Summer  http://t.co/4MzGl5FJSs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suitor: A guy who thinks he's throwing a girl a line when all the time he's being roped in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool Geek Tech - Mini USB Fan - Keep cool at your desk! --&gt; http://t.co/gZMcEesnf3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Who  http://t.co/OJSRfULjd8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before you create anymore great content figure out how you are going to market it first - Pulizzi &amp; Barrett - Get Content Get Customers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the hot new Minecraft video channel Crimson Mine - http://t.co/voMYIXkM69]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The needs of the many outweigh ... the needs of the few... Or the one. - Kirk and Spock - Star Trek II: The Wrath of Khan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read How to Use LinkedIn for Your Company   http://t.co/JpXAOElAKF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the Chitika Ad Network - An Alternate to Google AdSense  http://t.co/pM1MV8o8Yd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who's gonna turn down a Junior Mint? It's chocolate, it's peppermint - it's delicious! - Kramer, Seinfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things could be worse. Suppose your errors were counted and published everyday, like those of a baseball player. - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I get to go to a lot of overseas places, like Canada.  Britney Spears]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never hit a man with glasses. Hit him with a baseball bat. - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stiletto, I look at it more as an attitude as opposed to a high-heeled shoe. - Lita Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And now, I'm just trying to change the world, one sequin at a time. Lady Gaga]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supporting Adopted Students: Parents and Teachers Working Together  http://t.co/oBNxJLfkXH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Left Banke  http://t.co/EuQoIHqhAx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The Everyday Impact of Math  http://t.co/ppLmt7IpRL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Fashionable Jackets for Fall &amp; Winter  http://t.co/chid2iacsW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome cooking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the cooking lovers in your life!   http://t.co/rycaADPPDQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making the Most of Twitter for Your Business  http://t.co/quw3eFdLxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of the first book in the Left Behind Series by Tim LaHaye and Jerry Jenkins  http://t.co/vFeHj79NGR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ultimately, the only power to which man should aspire is that which he exercises over himself. - Elie Wiesel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this very cool bed fan - cools right under the covers! http://t.co/RmSdesDmKn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't read other science fiction. I don't read any at all. - Jack Vance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do something for somebody every day for which you do not get paid. - Albert Schweitzer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The History of the Golden Retriever  http://t.co/fv6GlR5149]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball's future? Bigger and bigger, better and better! No question about it, it's the greatest game there is! - Ted Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Superhero caped glasses - totally cool!  http://t.co/L37qWRbYLp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going Mountain Climbing? - Equipment Advice  http://t.co/vD4hwVww9m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This episode was BADLY written! - Gwen, Galaxy Quest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Out the Top Football Teams of the 2011-2012 Season  http://t.co/iCf83nBoPt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You gotta love that - an aquarium coffee table!  Drink with the fishes! http://t.co/JNzfdyDcxE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So now I'm left with cigarettes, and I'm trying to scrape that off my shoe and then I'll be done. - Diane Lane]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your attitude determines your altitude! - Denis Waitley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bonsai Trees Are So Cool --  http://t.co/yPDIS32xwQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of James Brown  http://t.co/TU55J9vE00]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gary US Bonds was an amazing musician and rocker - read his history - http://t.co/OnSCMIa8wM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Running SUCKS! How to Run for Fast Weight Loss - For Busy Women Who HATE Running --&gt; http://t.co/BBVNr4QVXy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Ringo Starr  http://t.co/48FuSk3b2W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is not a rock opera. This is not Tommy. I can write songs that emote, and that's it. - John Mellencamp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Empty pockets never held anyone back. Only empty heads and empty hearts can do that.  Norman Vincent Peale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read a Great Profile of Bo Jackson – An Amazing Athlete  http://t.co/kd0XwGxyEA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Joe Simon  http://t.co/b6OiKWILvM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exciting History of Baseball  http://t.co/LHqEvqVi4f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Trust Me I'm A Nerd Mens Sweatshirt - Awesome http://t.co/k8nsbrkM6K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's an edge to real rock 'n' roll. It's all that matters. - Neil Young]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must accept finite disappointment, but we must never lose infinite hope. - Martin Luther King, Jr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome biking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the biking lovers in your life!  http://t.co/p0XpsbRTGT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Wendy's  http://t.co/dw3bIRCpvT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Petula Clark  http://t.co/ULc4ECoOZn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Ramones  http://t.co/aaaxRncL0E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Johnny Burnette  http://t.co/xtkpjeXRw4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow the whiskey.  - Kid Rock, who arrived with "Redneck Woman" singer Gretchen Wilson, on his plans after the Country Music Awards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman's dress should be a like a barbed-wire fence: serving its purpose without obstructing the view. - Sophia Loren]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any fact facing us is not as important as our attitude toward it, for that determines our success or failure. - Norman Vincent Peale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An office clock is rarely stolen --  everyone watches it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can tell that you're in trouble when you feel the air on the back of your neck instead of in your face. - Buddy Baker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Try not. Do, or do not. There is no try. - Yoda, The Empire Strikes Back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kate Austen: So what, I'm your prisoner? James 'Sawyer' Ford: If that sort of thing turns you on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman who doesn't wear perfume has no future. Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the hot new Minecraft video channel Crimson Mine - http://t.co/voMYIXkM69]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In youth we learn in age, we understand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kate Austen: So what, I'm your prisoner? James 'Sawyer' Ford: If that sort of thing turns you on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating history of Baseball Cards!  http://t.co/ZMaz7Ticaj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Three Dog Night  http://t.co/6rerQjYrfn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read an Introduction to Whataburger  http://t.co/l9BKfRNfj8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blogging Lost – Season 1  http://t.co/dG1BlqNkcz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Far Out and Super Cool Watches  http://t.co/eR44kqv6sl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most beautiful makeup of a woman is passion. But cosmetics are easier to buy. --&gt; Yves Saint-Laurent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Grapevine, Texas  http://t.co/pJ3lcxP36R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Bread  http://t.co/jpSK283aDa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 4 - Supplements and Herbs  http://t.co/AwowEC6FCP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You cannot dream yourself into a character: you must hammer and forge yourself into one. - Henry D. Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Power of Solar Power - Get Plugged In!  http://t.co/YXAKJk9Kaj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to know how your girl will treat you after you married her,  just listen to her talking to her little brother.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Leapy Lee the Classic Rock Artist?  http://t.co/tG30E0DjIK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I live in heels. Give me a pair of flip-flops and I'll trip all over myself. - Brenda Song]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Music from this Bose Blue Tooth system - iPad, iPhone and more - easy great sound -&gt; http://t.co/7bHA8Dz7bl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Marie Antoinette's Watch  http://t.co/H0Advx9S6B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We can judge the heart of a man by his treatment of animals. - Immanual Kant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, I understand when they make a mistake and everyone at home is throwing their shoe at the television set. - Vanna White]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for great resources on Beer?  Check out our top 10... http://t.co/IwcZzcB9XW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The time for action is now. It's never too late to do something. - Carl Sandburg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Father, forking out reluctantly for daughter's wedding dress:  It's not enough to have to give her away --  she has to be gift wrapped.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome fine wine t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the wine lovers in your life!  http://t.co/NK8Umc3TUr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What is Fiverr Exactly and Why All the Buzz?  http://t.co/vzmy92E27W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'll forgive me, Madam President, if I don't wish to be executed based solely on your... gut feeling. - Doctor Gaius Baltar]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>