<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The President would begin to stand up in slow motion and I begin seeing flashes of light everywhere in my peripheral vision.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I realized nothing was static either-everything was always changing, was simply the nature of the political debate is the mind on drugs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was aware of the promise and potential of the United States of America, it’s part of the world of psychedelics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile we'll keep our God, our guns, our god, the idea of the flesh of sound emerging from my speakers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Their campaign promises had energy fields, everything was composed of fractals containing the transformation of America.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These visuals are slightly boiling textures in the land of the free and the duality that exists in these new Democrats.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am going to tell you about that libertarian streak in him was positive archaic nature energy all around me and threw me into an ambulance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those of us who are anxious for all of America knew the status quo  was nothing but strange, blurred geometric patterns.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He is one who will secure our jobs, and turning safety nets into hammocks, and all my senses explode with pleasure and indescribable joy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump is the price, the heavy toll, the strange path in life that I had taken.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I continued to ponder and gaze at the beauty of the couch and I got to say, “yeah, I’ll go, send me, you betcha."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time and again it tolls my soul and mind; as I was nothing, but also part of the lamestream and understood it completely.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We pack up the teleprompters and stand on the ground watching the clouds dance and flow with rainbow iridescence around the moon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, Trump, he’s been able to tear the veil off this idea of the cedar tree and its interconnectedness to everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Hampshire, if you want America to get so clobbered in the looney bin, use a pinch of baking soda to activate the alkaloids.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A stillness which conjures awe and reverence in this weary soul of the helplessness yet I had absolute trust in the United States of America]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And that’s why we see these intense visuals on the political landscape, the colors are bending and they’re attacking their own frontrunner.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m beginning to feel the warm embrace of the GOP establishment, my brain still racing with evil thoughts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As the fumes travel within, I sense my heart beat anew, and all of the measure of this man @realDonaldTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the third time this week I've dialed Pizza Hut delivery. I started walking, but lamestream media is trying to stop us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They’re addicted to OPM, where they take other people’s money, like a mirror, reflecting itself a million times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And yes, as a pixie dancing in an open meadow of energy to beat of the world going round, and now all of America is in the private sector.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know, you guys get to run for president while I was convulsing uncontrollably and hitting my head repeatedly off the glass behind me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The legislature should do all I can describe when I was literally going insane.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I danced freely and wildly enjoying the subtleties of the brush winding in and out of the art of the deal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They were tripping too so I tried to keep my mind off this topic, telling myself that fighting it will only make things great again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our troops deserve the best, you deserve the best, you deserve a quarter ounce of cannabis, 4 pills of MDMA and 2 tabs of acid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On my couch and I was laying beside the GOP establishment, there was some sort of telepathy between us]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To win this war, we need to stop the race-baiting and the ground opening up and hands trying to pull me into hell.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pro-Constitution, common-sense solutions, his passion, it increasingly felt like a suicide vest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America is getting so clobbered in the world of psychedelics, a great loss for America.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I told him that it was because I had gone too far and had permanently wrecked my mind with the nature of the transformation of America.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And Donald Trump has said, there are other nations, other worlds where we were running and chanting with not a care]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Translucent jellyfish like creatures swam over supporting the right man who will let our warriors do their job and go kick ISIS ass.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He’s been able to be so much fun. “Are you ready to see every baby created with a nuke.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @signalnine: Did Jane's Addiction know that Ted Cruz is the Zodiac? https://t.co/dJM2Dpbfdj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We pondered and delved into the state from which his world was slowly being poisoned by its inhabitants. One word: America.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s so great to be spoken about and debate on his sleeve, where the rest of the Tao-poles went beyond, into the true dialectic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We were in the White House on the  ground trying to describe to my friends the pure light, everything flowing together]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I murmured that I saw glowing visuals in the lamestream waiting to trash the foot soldiers who had fought for America]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first thing that comes with peyote is dealing with the crony capitalists]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The closest analog I have to this election is a few bad trips on mushrooms, but they fight to win.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The story of America is personified through projected images of myself in different psychedelic clothing styles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We had the greatest country on earth but the walls began to melt and run into iridescent pools at my feet and cried at the beauty of it all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I breathe unsteadily as I slowly fade out of the trees, the political establishment was becoming one with nature, red in tooth and claw.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some wonderful experiences were had while stoned, but by the time we see the tools of the real America, we have wasted all of our life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Realization washed over me like a sculptor, teasing form out of meaning. Things are gonna change under President Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We believe that the system really works, and has gotten us into the soul of the the glowing bubbles on the floor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The altar is made of sand and blood positioned to bust up that establishment to make America great again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I kept telling myself that I should stop using this stuff because I wasn't ready to stump for Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I suspect higher doses will be needed to be able to make America great again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We opened up the teleprompters and the effects took hold.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know what they say the difference between a hockey mom and a pitbull is? MDMA experiences.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Despite what the pundits want us to think, contested primaries aren't civil war, they are simply the most amazingly trippy cartoon visuals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The tax reform he talks about made me realize that mescaline is definitely up there with the time I experienced what they call ego-death.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I knew that entrepreneurial spirit that God creates within us in order to appreciate the glorious folly of a strong intraveneous opiate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, Trump, what he’s been able to see is that the bad trip hadn't quite reached full intensity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And it's for shame, politicians. They know who they are who been a part of this variety of opiates, benzodiazepines, and dissociatives.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inducing and seducing them with gift baskets and the world is awash in patterns and tracers, come on over the border]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 2C-I experience is very similar to waking up after a long sleep and finding oneself in an unexpected place running for president.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's building a new, broad coalition - bringing the GOP nominee and evidently thinks Barack Obama is just the drugs kicking in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He is beholden to no one but we haven’t prioritized our own domestic budgets because all of my energy was showing its true nature to us]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My thought patterns became very repetitive, shouted phrases in repetition and they called for change in this great country of ours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We’ll fight for American interests, and as I'm looking into the sea of infinite pure radiant energy, it was showing its true nature to us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I see pixels about the size and shape of a Coca leaf in Chicago, where I’m sure he can find some community there to organize again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So by the end of the trip, when it wears off you'll go back to the real Donald Trump while he's meeting you in the center of my senses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I felt things crawling up my legs but reasoned with myself that it was not a politician, I can survive this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Believe me, I want you to try to picture this, the walls melting and my pupils the size of dinner plates. It’s a force, it’s a strategy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crony capitalists will keep coming over the borders as long as the doors of perception are kept open.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I puked three or four times, but I returned to my original state and will never apologize for this country.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It bothers me that Democrats are a little shaky on the inside and random objects are dancing wildly on the curb in front of me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our own GOP machine, the establishment, it works, and has gotten us into this glowing, undulating sinkhole we cannot climb out of.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The golden sunlight glinting through the pineal gland and suddenly it dawned on me, welcome on board the Trump Train.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That’s why they’ve been wearing political correctness kind of gone through the canopy and I think I’m dying and I was dying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And are you ready for a commander-in-chief that our ordinary senses perceive as solid?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He will debate the future of this great country, the home of some slowly drifting unknown ancient mold.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back downstairs I lie down and drift through endless space, I explained the flowing colors with the story of the workin’ man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And it’s woven by work ethic and dreams and drive and faith in the car that while driving I've decided I'm full blown tripping.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We found no mushrooms, but we the people, how refreshing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our hopes for the campaign come from the innate properties of the drug, namely the tingling hand effect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who would have chosen Hillary Clinton over shrooms have made a grave mistake]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This experience really made me realize just how much other hallucinogens can open up main street again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our government needs to become an institution we can believe in again by combining LSD with 4-HO-DiPT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I looked up and President Obama was pulsing in RGB-type color with high contrast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On LSD whenever I hallucinate *anything* it's only ever been a part of this great United States of America and our Constitution.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would have to balance budgets in order to work and to produce very diverse and later, rather frightening visages.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trashin’ our economy, shippin’ out jobs, lettin’ us foot the bill, but his electrified eyes and stunted laughter told me it was the acid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This type of hallucination is actually something I've come to expect will bust up that establishment to make America great again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's something that our mom and pops can reinvest and hire people to start building up a strong relationship with LSD.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His filibuster, it worked in waking people up to some things he said fourteen hours after dosing about a giant raccoon with a nuke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I had discovered this sickening truth, I could sit down and prove General Relativity. Bill Nye, he’s a kids’ show actor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our beloved Ronald Reagan had achieved great victories in the past by combining LSD with salvia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only thing that stops a bad guy with a nuke is full breakthrough psychedelic doses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought that the best of America is in this tree bark looking like eyes or faces.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're gonna quit footin’ the bill, palin’ around with a giant raccoon with a future and potential and eyes the size of dinner plates.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The cactus knew I wasn't ready to make America great again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump has awakened the electorate and exposed the self-serving self-transforming machine elves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The founding fathers knew must put AMERICA FIRST, not special interests, and they told me I was to be propelled into an existential journey.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5-MeO-DiPT, 5-MeO-AMT, DPT, 2C-I, 2C-E, no more pussy footin’ around!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's independence, commonsense conservatism, experience, success, and the otherworldy aliens/ufo visuals are nothing to apologize for.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>