<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber aims to go all-electric in London in 2025: Uber plans for every car on its taxi app in London to be fully electric in 2025 and will add a clean air fee to each trip from early next year, its boss told reporters in the British capital city on Tuesday. https://t.co/vCEZ9VrDuh https://t.co/P9jUxjoGIU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Xerox falls short on revenue, raises buybacks: Xerox Corp, engaged in a tense standoff with Fujifilm Holdings Corp over an aborted merger, missed analysts' estimates for quarterly revenue on Tuesday, as corporates cut back spending on printers and… https://t.co/291gguTa1H https://t.co/l9kVirpOv1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Xerox reports 5.8 percent drop in revenue: Xerox Corp, engaged in a tense standoff with Fujifilm Holdings Corp over an aborted merger, reported a 5.8 percent drop in quarterly revenue on Tuesday, as corporates cut back spending on printers and… https://t.co/rtd32FpWY5 https://t.co/iuoigB2xai]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SoftBank's Vision Fund says portfolio reached 65 companies so far: SoftBank's Vision Fund has built up a portfolio of about 65 companies so far, managing partner Saleh Romeih said on Tuesday. https://t.co/7Cd5GTs9yX https://t.co/PuIQ4fMrvT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SoftBank CEO cancels speaking role at Saudi conference: source: SoftBank Group Corp Chief Executive Masayoshi Son has cancelled a speaking engagement at the Future Investment Initiative conference in Saudi Arabia, said a source close to the matter. https://t.co/nCgInqxS1V https://t.co/ABQaMo4aAZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nissan Leaf approved for vehicle-to-grid use in Germany: Nissan's Leaf became the first electric vehicle (EV) to secure regulatory approval as an energy backstop for Germany's electricity grid, the Japanese carmaker and Daimler-backed The Mobility House… https://t.co/0pB8h7Qm5b https://t.co/pWJoxRi9aH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Analyst: Why We Work at Dun &amp; Bradstreet Life here at Dun &amp; Bradstreet is changing for the better. With almost two centuries of experience and a new modern vibe, work at D&amp;B has never been more exhilarating. Our purpose is to grow the most… https://t.co/x7pIXInSDo https://t.co/63LVUJYBHX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Linux Developer: Senior Linux Developer – Careers in United States – Careers This site uses cookies. By continuing to browse the site you are agreeing to our use of cookies. Learn More Continue Some cookies on this site are essential. The site… https://t.co/i72wO28H2e https://t.co/HHbcFKYNaq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need Senior Java Software Engineer: SR. SOFTWARE ENGINEER – JAVA SPECIFIC. DESCRIPTION: * Motivated, Hard Working, detail oriented, deadline and quality driven individual to develop a cloud based Enterprise Application in an Agile development… https://t.co/fBTdY4JWqv https://t.co/4cAIJ5oHdy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/XCGE1TBbK6, Qualcomm to put Alexa assistant in more headphones: Microchip firm Qualcomm Inc is joining https://t.co/XCGE1TBbK6 Inc to spread the use of Amazon's Alexa voice assistant in wireless headphones, the companies said on Monday. https://t.co/VUqiKw8iag https://t.co/dvrLzBIDAM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Specialist, Strategic Planning (Data Analyst): The Specialist, Strategic Planning (Data Analyst) is responsible for working in conjunction with business units, support groups and technology teams to define and build out the data repository and data… https://t.co/eGXtXbfiC2 https://t.co/2TLvqh9W07]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber's dealmaking chief Poetzscher resigns: Cameron Poetzscher, who oversaw a string of high-profile deals at Uber Technologies Inc [UBER.UL], has resigned, weeks after a report on allegations of sexual misconduct against him at the ride-hailing firm. https://t.co/xDcSyiE1L8 https://t.co/NnylE0U9Yp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Category Strategist (Professional Services): The Finance division is home to Employer’s experts in Corporate Financial Services, Fund Financial Services, Internal Audit and the Finance Transformation Program. Our crew are high caliber professionals who… https://t.co/f0bF0PLGYL https://t.co/cWxabp2igj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. regulator orders halt to self-driving school bus test in Florida: The National Highway Traffic Safety Administration on Monday said it had ordered Transdev North America to immediately stop transporting school children in Florida in a driverless… https://t.co/McarvUL5HX https://t.co/6EY9w6tReV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber's head of corporate development Poetzscher resigns: WSJ: Uber Technologies Inc's head of corporate development Cameron Poetzscher has resigned, the Wall Street Journal reported on Monday, weeks after the newspaper reported allegations of sexual… https://t.co/BosIFbq74o https://t.co/LlvwzihIJI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Launch of new iPhones helps chipmaker AMS's profit surge: Austrian chipmaker AMS AG reported a 49 percent increase in its third-quarter core profit and gave an upbeat forecast for the next period, largely because Apple started mass production of new… https://t.co/QhHikRJLC2 https://t.co/Jnt1K0YePa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Developer: Job ID : 77874BR Location : US – Pennsylvania – Pittsburgh : Job Description DUTIES: Develop, support and manage business initiatives and technical projects relating to the AMPS application. Lead java code development efforts… https://t.co/2tvCf69Kq0 https://t.co/Af2sSBJPnK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oculus co-founder to leave Facebook: VR headset maker Oculus co-founder Brendan Trexler Iribe is leaving Facebook Inc, according to his post on the social media network on Monday. https://t.co/tzpHyP8WjK https://t.co/2uu57BtkYH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aptoide wins court battle against Google in landmark case: Portuguese app store Aptoide said on Monday that a local court had ruled against Alphabet Inc's Google in a landmark case, ordering the U.S. giant to stop removing its app from users' mobile… https://t.co/MUAme1B0cq https://t.co/jc6yxd9Aqe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Netflix adds to growing debt pile with $2 billion bond issue: Netflix Inc announced on Monday it will tap debt markets for a second time this year, aiming to raise another $2 billion as the streaming video pioneer invests heavily in production of… https://t.co/NBSL7RgAKZ https://t.co/5cQ8nUtiug]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Global rules on cryptocurrencies needed: Circle CEO: Major economies should launch coordinated regulation of cryptocurrencies, the head of Goldman Sachs-backed startup Circle said on Monday, underscoring growing industry support for international rules… https://t.co/sr1gLP1Coq https://t.co/SeCG85zWM4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Portugal's Aptoide says wins first court ruling against Google: Portuguese app store Aptoide said on Monday a local court has ruled against Alphabet Inc's Google, ordering it to stop removing Aptoide's app from users' mobile phones without their… https://t.co/X5dquzDF3U https://t.co/9t3BcqnJwH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Netflix $2 billion debt issue adds to spending nerves: Netflix Inc announced its third tap of debt markets in a year on Monday, aiming to raise another $2 billion as the streaming video pioneer invests heavily in original shows and acquiring content to… https://t.co/lqJrqPvxWg https://t.co/Qrrg5nvzJp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analytics Analyst – Level I – IT Business Intelligence – Full Time: Regular/Temporary Regular Guthrie Entity The Guthrie Clinic Shift Days 40 hours a week Pay Grade TGC A13 FLSA Status Exempt Main Function The Analytics Analyst will work as part of the… https://t.co/CHPj91ipAo https://t.co/x1tMzMgiZz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Discovery, PGA Tour to launch video streaming platform: The PGA Tour and pay TV operator Discovery Inc unveiled a live and on-demand video-streaming service on Monday that will allow golf fans access to nearly 150 tournaments annually. https://t.co/YrwpGJZOYH https://t.co/EyO4FEM5rp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Automation Engineer: Healthcare IT Career Opportunities : M*Modal Careers | ********** We’re Here to Help! xStart Chat M*Modal – Browse Open Jobs – Search Open Jobs – Edit Your Profile – View Submitted Applications Job Details Requisition… https://t.co/60Eui5kBUF https://t.co/iZOk7ApwPk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber, Ola drivers strike in India, demanding higher fares: Hundreds of drivers for ride-hailing giant Uber and its local rival Ola went on strike in the two biggest Indian cities, Delhi and Mumbai, on Monday, demanding higher fares to meet rising fuel… https://t.co/kZV6lXpzID https://t.co/F1nJcvnkgQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Netflix unveils $2 billion debt issue to fund new content: Netflix Inc announced its third tap of debt markets in a year on Monday, aiming to raise about $2 billion as the streaming video pioneer invests heavily in original shows and acquiring content to… https://t.co/sRkJRL7q7U https://t.co/RJfC36CToU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Netflix plans to raise $2 billion to fund new content: Netflix Inc said on Monday it plans to raise about $2 billion in debt to fund original shows, acquire content and for possible acquisitions. https://t.co/ZXfpMA1VLI https://t.co/lgAdhEMPJf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PayPal backs emerging markets lender Tala: PayPal Inc Holdings Inc has made a strategic investment in Tala, a financial technology startup that lends to underserved consumers in emerging markets, the companies said on Monday. https://t.co/qOncIl03fU https://t.co/v99Ck6iY51]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Super Micro to review hardware for malicious chips: Super Micro Computer Inc said on Monday it will review its hardware for any proof of malicious chips as alleged in a recent media report. https://t.co/8SEDCCfvdv https://t.co/ugJbnYrVpq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Specialist Developer — Java, Oracle, Kofax: Specialist Developer ‘ Java, Oracle, Kofax Provides application software design, development and support services for applications supporting Document Custody Service related applications and associated… https://t.co/kUvdZ5Kod3 https://t.co/QspXZ0t2mi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Telefonica Deutschland calls for regulators to block Vodafone-Liberty deal: The head of Telefonica Deutschland called on Monday for EU regulators to block Vodafone's planned acquisition of Liberty Global, saying it would lead to a "quasi-monopolisation"… https://t.co/ZqMleXSScT https://t.co/8x7r3yNjow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Specialist Systems Engineer/Programmer – Senior AV Engineer: Job Description TECHNOLOGY SERVICES GROUP (TSG) is the central infrastructure services group with a proven track record of innovating to help BNY Mellon and its customers have most reliable,… https://t.co/OPQ16BVzpt https://t.co/XnTJ9UZPwW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Account Manager: Requisition ID 2018-61843 Category Information Technology Employment Type Regular – Full Time (4) Travel Requirements 50-60% Position Code 8142 Position Description The IT Account Manager will provide account and application support… https://t.co/RSZT5M7786 https://t.co/KPAEYeg4q2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Japan tells Facebook to improve data protection: Japan's government on Monday told U.S. technology firm Facebook Inc to better protect its users' personal data following lapses this year affecting tens of millions of people globally. https://t.co/aqYPwy3I8Z https://t.co/gQAS3xCc15]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Developer, https://t.co/laoeHXDbxn, Visual Studio, SSIS, SQL Server: Lead Developer, *******, Visual Studio, SSIS, SQL Server ‘ Provides application software development services or technical support in situations of moderate complexity. May also be… https://t.co/KxiSjEYJ1Q https://t.co/Rg5XUA4TqF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PNC partners with OnDeck for online small business lending: PNC Financial Services Group's PNC Bank will use technology from digital lender OnDeck Capital to extend loans to small businesses online, the companies said on Monday. https://t.co/qhne4AdOZp https://t.co/4PwroeZ4aW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber to appeal Singapore's competition watchdog decision on Grab deal: Uber Technologies Inc has decided to appeal a decision by the Singapore competition regulator that its merger with regional rival Grab violated the city-state's competition laws, the… https://t.co/XBKLmejOyx https://t.co/RvOk9g5fkv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Japan to tell Facebook to improve data protection: Kyodo: The Japanese government is set to tell Facebook Inc to better protect its users' personal data after a leak involving British firm Cambridge Analytica that affected 87 million users globally,… https://t.co/VkG7kyErrx https://t.co/BiRaNOdQiz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C#/WPF Developer Need: THE CANDIDATE WILL BE REQUIRED TO DEMONSTRATE PROFICIENCY IN: * C# * WPF * Object Oriented Design and implementation * MVVM Implementation Knowledge * Unit test and Code Documentation skills * Effective debugging skills * Effective… https://t.co/rtCRu1R6SE https://t.co/h65y9McBjC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Specialist Systems Engineer/Programmer (Windows Systems Administrator) (Shift 30pm Tuesday-Saturday OR Sun: TECHNOLOGY SERVICES GROUP (TSG) is the central infrastructure services group with a proven track record of innovating to help BNY Mellon… https://t.co/CGYUqBV0KS https://t.co/aoGT6bzWYW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goldman-backed fintech startup Marqeta launches in Europe: Marqeta, a U.S. financial technology startup that helps young companies including digital-only banks issue payment cards, has expanded into Europe, the company said on Sunday. https://t.co/v9QN5bjPAG https://t.co/jVeDAA4aMq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remote Facilities IT Support Manager: Remote Facilities IT Support Manager Ref No.:18-00481 Category: ************* Location: Gettysburg, Pennsylvania Position Type:Full-time Experience Level: 10 Years Start Date: 10/01/2018 Job Req -Additional Info… https://t.co/rePaobMfbX https://t.co/VjnUs0Yq3B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director Global Animal Health Manufacturing IT Large Molecules lead: Job Title: Director Global Animal Health Manufacturing IT Large Molecules lead – ACC****** Description Merck &amp; Co., Inc. Kenilworth, N.J., U.S.A. known as Merck in the United States and… https://t.co/qqhNox6jJm https://t.co/ieHIXnGtiT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Audi's electric SUV faces four-week delay because of software bug: Audi's first electric sport utility vehicle (SUV) will hit showrooms four weeks later than planned because of a software development issue, a spokesman for the German luxury car brand… https://t.co/BibHXumESZ https://t.co/goOjjjCe8m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Statistical Programmer II (Project Lead): This is an exciting opportunity to work within the Biostatistics &amp; Programming department at ICON, a leading global provider of outsourced development services to the pharmaceutical, biotechnology and medical… https://t.co/nzNrac6zYF https://t.co/zU4EguigKH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Architect: Technical Architect Ref No.: 18-40727 Location: Philadelphia, Pennsylvania Start Date: 07/23/2018 JD for Technical Architect on Scaled Agile Participate in planning, definition, and high-level design of the solution and explore… https://t.co/IFONekOexj https://t.co/2g5nz4YUyw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spec st Appl Support Analyst: As a Senior Application Support Analyst for Corporate Treasury and Finance, you will have a production services support role for a suite of applications and services.’ A support analyst will be primarily involved with… https://t.co/JmfF4kc8sB https://t.co/pckyoqV88F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Devops Engineer: Devops Engineer Ref No.:18-00557 Location: Philadelphia, Pennsylvania Start Date: 10/12/2018 Job Description: – Develop a proof of concept of a DevOps pipeline which enables continuous deployment of known good images of integrated… https://t.co/rvK4nsgkDU https://t.co/TOi7eObPu0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UX Consultant: UX Consultant Ref No.: 18-40735 Location: Philadelphia, Pennsylvania Start Date: 07/23/2018 JD UX Designer JD Minimum of 6-7 years of relevant experience. Strong conceptualization and strong visual communication ability. Exceptional design… https://t.co/sRitEPuyG8 https://t.co/YeUWaVRphJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Application Architect: Job Description Cloud Application Architect Location: US-PA-Virtual Location – Pennsylvani Job ID: ****** Company: : Amazon Web Services, Inc. Job Description Are you an experienced cloud architect/developer who can assist… https://t.co/tiaWnUewxO https://t.co/NBW7Rks8rO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Specialist Infrastructure Operations Analyst – Mainframe zVM and zLinux Infrastructure Automation: TECHNOLOGY SERVICES GROUP (TSG)’ is the central infrastructure services group with a proven track record of innovating to help BNY Mellon and its… https://t.co/TSIbtmp5pl https://t.co/234LonDZ8E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Desktop Support Technician: A Technician I will be responsible for resolving escalated issues from first level analysts. This position must have customer service skills with the ability to communicate face to face as well as via telephone to troubleshoot… https://t.co/yRhZl4SmYG https://t.co/LTlCOJCt5U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Full Stack Lead: Java Full Stack Lead Ref No.: 18-50905 Location: Malvern, Pennsylvania Position Type: Contract Start Date: 09/11/2018 JD 8-10 years’ experience in technical specialty. For development technical leads, includes 3-5 years’ hands on… https://t.co/DuOoGgCEto https://t.co/ROmwFif8Ci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Support Analyst: Job Description BNYM Technology has a mission to provide our business partners withtechnology based solutions that enhance their ability to be successful throughworld-class software solutions maintained on a stable and… https://t.co/7WVRqLwdic https://t.co/FIZe6C9uKP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Network Analyst: Fox Roach/Trident in Berwyn, PA is seeking an IT Network Analyst. At a minimum, a Bachelors degree in Information Systems and 48 months of experience as a Network Engineer or related position are required. IT Network Analyst must have… https://t.co/wBfCsR6b9n https://t.co/I3twpInUcn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Information Analyst: Senior Information Analyst Job ID: 72637 Job Category: Information Services/Technology/Service Desk/Telecom Specialty Area: Information Services/Technology/Service Desk/Telec Primary Shift: Day Work Schedule: Full-Time Penn… https://t.co/FiyHdg7xYE https://t.co/EMyYeE86Ki]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EDA Software Engineer: At Cadence, we hire and develop leaders and innovators who want to make an impact on the world of technology. – At Cadence, we hire and develop leaders and innovators who want to make an impact on the world of technology. The… https://t.co/xeQ5bdr9kb https://t.co/pPmufYA0nf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Technician: Researches, troubleshoots, monitors and maintains systems that affect critical system components for the business and/or stakeholders. May perform duties in one or more of the following disciplines: Print/Document, Telecommunications,… https://t.co/OV2sydqL6v https://t.co/MkqmCgNlWb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brazil election battle rages over Facebook's WhatsApp: Facebook Inc's WhatsApp messaging service became the frontline in Brazil's bitter presidential campaign on Friday, as front-runner Jair Bolsonaro angrily denied accusations he had encouraged… https://t.co/rjkMWo6ZQ7 https://t.co/qLGRlseicd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: At Cadence, we hire and develop leaders and innovators who want to make an impact on the world of technology. – At Cadence, we hire and develop leaders and innovators who want to make an impact on the world of technology. The Cadence… https://t.co/cIOXAHFAMf https://t.co/GHNXoZvYO5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple CEO urges Bloomberg to retract spy chip story: Apple Inc Chief Executive Tim Cook on Friday told an online news website that Bloomberg should retract a story that claimed Apple's internal computer systems had been infiltrated by malicious computer… https://t.co/a3jJFGRXmq https://t.co/QKsrkR8hHB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook's WhatsApp taking legal action against Brazil election spammers: Facebook Inc's WhatsApp messaging application business said on Friday it was "taking immediate legal action" against companies that are sending spam messages ahead of the Brazilian… https://t.co/n8nOOcezZW https://t.co/MmirQOcxiw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exclusive: CrowdStrike hires Goldman Sachs to lead IPO - sources: Cybersecurity software maker CrowdStrike Inc has hired investment bank Goldman Sachs Group to prepare for an initial public offering that could come in the first half of next year, people… https://t.co/Ogd48yCfBV https://t.co/EEYaixMtmQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google to charge Android partners up to $40 per device for apps: source: Alphabet Inc's Google will charge hardware firms up to $40 per device to use its apps under a new licensing system to replace one that the European Union this year deemed… https://t.co/J7P1IeMhl4 https://t.co/kOPAtjHCPR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Job Information: Software Developer – ******* Job Email Opening Title Software Developer – ******* EOE StatementCarnegie Mellon University is an Equal Opportunity Employer/Disability/Veteran. Description What We Do: At the SEI… https://t.co/xFXFW0qZRg https://t.co/NM4Zhhqlkw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money-laundering watchdog to set first cryptocurrency rules by June: The global watchdog for money laundering will set up its first rules on oversight of cryptocurrencies by June, a major step towards creating international standards for an asset… https://t.co/lPNal2Trgn https://t.co/7RIjHnr4Xa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dell to take $21.7 billion tracking stock offer to December vote: sources: Dell Technologies Inc will ask holders of "tracking stock" tied to its software company VMware Inc to vote on its $21.7 billion cash-and-stock offer to buy it back from them on… https://t.co/P6MAUzxvat https://t.co/rR5AAJ62rY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EU Commission approves Microsoft's acquisition of Github: The European Commission approved on Friday the acquisition of software development tool maker GitHub by software giant Microsoft without conditions saying the purchase would not damage competition… https://t.co/7RKk0Zp7YX https://t.co/134KaHn145]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook hires Nick Clegg as head of global affairs: Facebook Inc has hired former U.K. Deputy Prime Minister Nick Clegg to lead its global affairs and communications team, making him the most senior European politician ever in a leadership role in… https://t.co/UCClY6xYGg https://t.co/b8iZ9RdVTw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watchdog calls for regulation of cryptocurrency firms over money laundering: A global money-laundering watchdog said on Friday that cryptocurrency exchanges and other firms should be regulated or licensed to prevent digital money being used for money… https://t.co/3SjrMTEMWC https://t.co/CWkGIHMbB5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook hires Nick Clegg as head of global affairs: FT: Facebook Inc has hired former U.K. deputy prime minister Nick Clegg as head of the social network's global affairs and communications team, the Financial Times reported on Friday. https://t.co/eiYLxcfPRR https://t.co/3CoVlHqBhU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Machine Learning Consultant / Data Scientist – Newtown Square Job: Requisition ID: ****** Work Area: Consulting and Professional Services Expected Travel: 0 – 100% Career Status: Professional Employment Type: Regular Full Time COMPANY DESCRIPTION SAP… https://t.co/UKO9NR83MU https://t.co/fCO5PBMMaD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Volkswagen a winner as EU set to favour wifi over 5G: draft: The European Commission is set to approve and set rules for the use of wifi in cars, giving Volkswagen and Renault who have pursued this technology the edge over Daimler and others who invested… https://t.co/lum77yuhaV https://t.co/Lt9oY3G9l9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cisco Certified Network Associate: Cisco Certified Network Associate – TEK Connexion – Pittsburgh, PA | ********** Loading…Server error, please try again laterSorry! It looks like you are in private browsing mode, which is not supported. Please switch… https://t.co/6zWKel7WwK https://t.co/Apd0opC4Vx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AV Coordinator, Electrical Computer Engineering: Job Description AV Coordinator, Electrical &amp; Computer Engineering (*******) The Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering (ECE) at Carnegie Mellon University (CMU) has an immediate opening for an… https://t.co/uF9mKYEQgu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Business Systems Analyst for Payment Applications: Description The Senior Business Systems Analyst for Payment Applications leads and coordinates BSA colleagues in the development of functional specifications for major systems and applications… https://t.co/6YYvqK3UYE https://t.co/VurqLOYTXi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guest Service Desk Team Member: Guest Service Desk Team Member Description: As a Guest Service team member, you are the front end and the face of what we stand for. You’ll be motivated by and always look for opportunities to go above and beyond guest… https://t.co/7Vy2vv3hnV https://t.co/wPGX4XQM3i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla launches new $45,000 Model 3: Tesla Inc on Thursday introduced a new $45,000 version of its Model 3 sedan on its website, launching the car as U.S. tax breaks for Tesla cars are about to decrease. https://t.co/k8osfidDih https://t.co/lApRIcQeXp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Developer: Principal Developer-&gt;&gt; Consults with internal business groups to provide high-level application software development services or technical support. Provides comprehensive senior-level technical consulting to IT management and senior… https://t.co/rA81ywLSa3 https://t.co/zjhXNn7YYY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla launches new Model 3 with mid-range battery: Electrek: Tesla Inc is launching a new version of its Model 3 sedan with a "mid-range" battery priced at $45,000, automotive news website Electrek reported on Thursday. https://t.co/pdnZe2z0Xw https://t.co/DPO7bAfhKn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PayPal quarterly profit beats estimates, shares rise: PayPal Holdings Inc on Thursday reported a third-quarter profit that beat analysts' estimates as the company signed up more new customers and volume of payments processed grew. https://t.co/dXSo3aDqzy https://t.co/m6V590tVNC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon to open Manchester office as it adds 1,000 British jobs: https://t.co/XCGE1TBbK6 is opening its first office in Manchester, northern England, and expanding two other centers to house 1,000 new R&amp;D roles in what it said was a major new investment… https://t.co/tm96qOyuwo https://t.co/YZxIAPdyRm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Micron to buy Intel's stake in joint venture IM Flash Technologies: Micron Technology Inc said on Thursday it would buy Intel Corp's non-controlling interest in their IM Flash Technologies joint venture for about $1.5 billion in cash. https://t.co/ZjG6Hicemk https://t.co/I2bRHiMOLR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Internet provider groups sue Vermont over net neutrality law: Four industry groups representing major internet providers and cable companies filed suit on Thursday seeking to block Vermont's state law barring companies that do not abide by net neutrality… https://t.co/T92t7eDXIa https://t.co/qLLWQyubvR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Comcast says its fastest internet reaches more U.S. homes than any other provider: Comcast Corp said on Thursday that its fastest-speed gigabit internet service now reaches more homes than any other provider in the United States after it completed… https://t.co/noavMzeM2u https://t.co/03x2PJ44zx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Eagle Developer: FFS2020 program is a multi-year program that will transform global operating model, processes, technology and data infrastructure to enable FFS to scale efficiently with uncompromised quality and controls and provide flexibility… https://t.co/J7pFxArnHH https://t.co/uMNd8P4RCS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. making serious efforts to comply with EU data rules: EU officials: The United States is making serious efforts to comply with a landmark data transfer pact agreed two years ago, EU officials said on Thursday amidst criticism by some civil liberties… https://t.co/AzGoSXrtps https://t.co/UpGZ9S5gzw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Systems Analyst / IT Manager: EQT Corp. – Lead Systems Analyst / IT Manager Job in Pittsburgh, PA Toggle navigation – Who We Are – What We Do – Life at EQT – Campus Recruiting – Careers Home – &gt; Lead Systems Analyst / IT Manager Job in Pittsburgh,… https://t.co/vfA2kHXohJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Netflix needs lower prices to woo India: Netflix Inc's Indian operation drew attention in a surge of international subscribers in the third quarter, but it faces fierce competition and a difficult cultural conundrum to make inroads with the country's… https://t.co/Mg6TLya4Qg https://t.co/F0RLWd1r70]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sirius XM, Amazon join forces in push linked to Echo devices: Satellite radio company Sirius XM Holdings Inc is teaming up with https://t.co/XCGE1TBbK6 in its push into listeners' homes to move beyond its stronghold inside vehicles. https://t.co/mmWdEB8imE https://t.co/N15NqDoaM2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TSMC sees modest fourth quarter revenue growth, shrugs off trade war impact: Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co (TSMC) offered a modest fourth-quarter revenue growth outlook, predicting weaker sales of high-performance computers for cryptocurrency… https://t.co/rcOlWi7ajA https://t.co/oRQCl0ot9G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Website Developer (part-time), Psychology: Job Description Website Developer (part-time), Psychology (*******) Dr. Brad Mahon’s lab in the Department of Psychology seeks an experienced website developer with expertise in 3D rendering. The project’s aim… https://t.co/U1JykQewcc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Enough excuses!' France's Le Maire grows impatient over GAFA tax: Europe has talked long enough about whether to make internet giants like Google , Apple and Facebook pay more taxes and it is time for a decision, French Finance Minister Bruno Le Maire… https://t.co/uUuYH1i4QA https://t.co/1XgEZjat6Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China's https://t.co/bwYJSm2bUN unwraps FedEx-style parcel business to bolster sales: Chinese e-commerce firm https://t.co/bwYJSm2bUN Inc said on Thursday it would add a FedEx-style parcel delivery service to its e-commerce offerings, a move which could… https://t.co/jf1TzHzulH https://t.co/GHIi7x2yat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Security Consultant: SAP Security Consultant Job Close By continuing to use and navigate this website, you are agreeing to the use of cookies. Accept – SAP Careers home – SAP employees – Join our talent community Search by Keyword Search by Location… https://t.co/zXIfHRP0SQ https://t.co/TG40YNovjS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thousands of Seoul taxi-drivers rally against plans for carpool service: Tens of thousands of South Korean taxi-drivers held a rally on Thursday in Seoul, the capital, saying a carpooling service planned by the operator of the country's top chat app… https://t.co/F4cEh24l8J https://t.co/hJWLcajfCb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China robot market growth to slump this year as trade war weighs: Sales of industrial robots in China, the world's biggest market, will grow this year at only about a third of last year as an escalating Sino-U.S. trade war hits spending on equipment, a… https://t.co/W621VAm8XH https://t.co/khowjl3Zt4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ericsson tops third-quarter forecasts as savings and 5G sales kick in: Mobile telecom equipment maker Ericsson beat third-quarter operating profit forecasts on Thursday, boosted by sales of next-generation 5G gear in North America, and said it was making… https://t.co/PsMRZU55m7 https://t.co/F6DwF5o8b9]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>