<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[(Ab Initio) ETL Developer: (Ab Initio) ETL Developer ========================= Req #: ******Location: Arlington, VA USJob Category: Information TechnologySecurity Clearance: SecretClearance Status: Must be Obtainable Job Description POSITION SUMMARY:… https://t.co/WEyowwB0n5 https://t.co/2nBOw4bYJV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer – Grantmaking: About Blackbaud: Leading uniquely at the intersection point of technology and social good, Blackbaud provides software, services, expertise, and data intelligence that empowers and connects people to advance the… https://t.co/mPJLzXUCJ2 https://t.co/kITnOdxYDT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer: Sr. Software Engineer RMS is the world leader in catastrophe risk modeling. From earthquakes and hurricanes to terrorism and infectious disease, our models provide critical risk management solutions to hundreds of financial… https://t.co/Ku0H3RYcws https://t.co/XJ7xMSDFS3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Administrator (SA) – Level 0 TS/SCI w/Poly Required: Clearance Level Must Currently Possess: Top Secret w/SCI eligibility Clearance Level Must Be Able to Obtain: Top Secret SCI Suitability: Polygraph Job Family: Customer Support Job Description:… https://t.co/NFbJPzNUfP https://t.co/hOWBj4Z7uA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Construction Project Engineer:       Position Summary   As a member of the Corporate Construction team reporting to either the U.S. Construction Manager or other senior project manager, the Project Engineer will work on capital projects including new… https://t.co/6OOQIzww8e https://t.co/eJU9vNuTNu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Field Engineer Asc: Req ID : 389357BR_2 Job Code/Title : E1691:Field Engineer Asc Job Description : At Lockheed Martin Rotary and Mission Systems (RMS), we are driven by innovation and integrity. We believe that by applying the highest standards of… https://t.co/c2A1NquUzW https://t.co/rAGI1BgsIv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Storage Engineer Job: Date: Mar 24, 2018 Location:Fort Belvoir, VA, US Company: SAIC Cloud Storage Engineer (Job Number:435308) Description: SAIC is looking for a Cloud Storage Engineer in Fort Belvoir, VA. Responsibilities: – Manages the… https://t.co/VVL3OK5FZs https://t.co/fBTIq2mTbU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst: This position is project based and will be supporting various projects. You will be working with the lead analyst who will lead you through the internal BSC process. Duties * Understanding source information &amp; target mapping * Mapping of… https://t.co/gsEgEWlfBF https://t.co/w2io8v3xxT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager 2: Job Description Project Manager 2 Manages all aspects of medium sized or moderately complex projects. Competency Requirements Project Management Can leverage experience in assessing business benefits, costs and risks on medium-to-high… https://t.co/nDjgIW05ro https://t.co/iqmknamOz2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Public Sector Agile IT UX/UI Designer Experienced Associate: PwC/LOS Overview PwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities.… https://t.co/VKWNNUmKbP https://t.co/RMJUrRWLao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Technologies Service Management Senior Associate: PwC/LOS Overview PwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities.… https://t.co/AzO0wD5HrK https://t.co/dMnF3lqiLu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Public Sector Cybersecurity Engineer Experienced Associate: PwC/LOS Overview PwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities.… https://t.co/JDzc04Gdk5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Security Engineering Manager: PwC/LOS Overview PwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about us at… https://t.co/mFLMx6zkKv https://t.co/ZoGmFi7uSN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Roadway Engineer: WHO WE ARE Michael Baker International is a global leader in Engineering, Architecture and Consulting professionals dedicated to developing and implementing innovative solutions to the world’s infrastructure and environmental… https://t.co/ygx8nmlpnm https://t.co/7clr9cdfcG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Representative: Overview Provides technical support to customers, field technicians, and employees who are diagnosing, troubleshooting and repairing Garage door access systems. Provides detailed support on shipped or installed products,… https://t.co/fU6bvUWfq0 https://t.co/tbz5ibOmK2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Administrator: System Administrator Location: Quantico, VA Job Code: 2982 # of openings: 1 Description Bay State Computers, Inc. is a professional services firm and a leading provider of Information Technology (IT) services and products to the… https://t.co/XTdMSTNICe https://t.co/9Pi6A6lMTJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automation Engineer: Hi, Greetings from Macropace Technologies !! We have a job opening with suits for you, please find below job description and let me know your if you are interested for this position. We are looking for below skills mainly. Please let… https://t.co/ZyojpSdtMp https://t.co/SfHBYowlof]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Mobile Full Stack Developer: Senior Mobile Full Stack Developer $90-135K +Bonus Irving, TX .*Looking for all level Mobile Developers, please apply if you work with iOS or Android Development, though we prefer both skill sets* Company is currently… https://t.co/p3aI062Ub8 https://t.co/juk7oF2AD0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cisco Certified Training Instructor – Consultant / Work From Home: Who We Are: INE is the premiere provider of Technical Training for the IT Industry. We are revolutionizing the digital learning industry through the implementation of adaptive… https://t.co/fj6dN1GiH2 https://t.co/hxKrBN9huJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OBIEE Developer: OBIEE Developer =============== Req #: ******Location: Chantilly, VA USJob Category: Information TechnologySecurity Clearance: SecretClearance Status: Must be Obtainable Job Description Job Description Interested in steering your career… https://t.co/DsHj1lYB4y https://t.co/mYtvxK5t8g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager I: CO-OP Financial Servicesprovides technically superior products and services to financial institutions across the nation. We are seeking a talentedProject Manager Ito be responsible for applying fundamental project management knowledge… https://t.co/npn7DVJQLt https://t.co/olEMPMy8og]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer: Data Center Technician TECHNOLOGY Help build the next generation of systems behind Facebook’s products. Facebook, Inc. currently has multiple openings in Fort Worth, TX (various levels/types): Data Center Technician (133532N) Assist… https://t.co/Uu3257Z7MR https://t.co/280p3tGbuL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Software Engineer: ENGINEERING: Principal Software Engineer Embedded Systems (Belmont, CA), responsible for shaping and strengthening the electronics development for Audi and the VW Group; targeted towards Audi electronics; development,… https://t.co/9JKxXpnznc https://t.co/R18g9MqqD2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Developer #R10001338: IT: Senior Developer job open at Twentieth Century Fox Film Corporation in Los Angeles, CA. Job # R10001338 Job Description: Senior Developer sought by Twentieth Century Fox Film Corporation in Los Angeles, CA to utilize… https://t.co/JsGnGHjIVf https://t.co/7dhHGY741a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Asset Protection: Position Description * Communicates with (or to) individuals or groups verbally and/or in writing (for example, customers, suppliers, associates) and conducts directed shrink related audits and report findings to appropriate leader or… https://t.co/7vM15erzwJ https://t.co/DYpLvjCGSX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Sales ConsultantSalesVA – Vienna: IT Sales Consultant VA – Vienna Job Description All Covered, IT Services Division of Konica Minolta Business Solutions (KMBS), is the leading national IT services company serving SMB to enterprise markets. Offering a… https://t.co/1pHguCIoDz https://t.co/FbLZtHpsAf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electrical Engineer Job: Electrical Engineer (Job Number:420016) Description: JOB DESCRIPTION: Identify and manage electrical/electronic hardware requirements (validity, traceability, verification across multiple segments into an end to end architecture… https://t.co/M8szlFmhOx https://t.co/UZSsaOUiAw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Management Analyst 2:   Job Description – Business Management Analyst 2 (18004510) Business Management Analyst 2 Requisition ID : 18004510 Location : United States-California-San Diego US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation… https://t.co/CekcxaD9El https://t.co/eBE7nKUSYL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Penetration Tester: Senior Penetration Tester Location: Washington, DC Job Code: 3317 # of openings: 1 Description Bay State Computers, Inc. is a professional services firm and a leading provider of Information Technology (IT) services and… https://t.co/QsHuAHCI0g https://t.co/hgLncDpGlB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Program Manager #A2Z157: Technical Program Manager A2Z Development Center, Inc. – Irvine, CA.  Position Responsibilities: Coordinate and manage technical program development of large-scale, distributed software applications, systems, platforms,… https://t.co/1L3UXBUe5T https://t.co/GIdjivpjNU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist – Senior Associate: PwC/LOS Overview PwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about us at… https://t.co/p0qU9lDQWA https://t.co/RFtv8Pu8vy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer (Integration Lead): Overview Are you a seasoned JAVA developer who thrives in enabling technology partnerships ? We’re looking for a results-oriented, dynamic engineer to join our team as a Senior Software Developer –… https://t.co/DRWs8kKgAj https://t.co/4ZbFqxcCOQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Services- Digital, Robotics (RPA), Exp Associate: PwC/LOS Overview PwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities.… https://t.co/qcXVOFaW8o https://t.co/jHKvVljt6E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Lyft, Inc. has the following openings in Seattle, WA. Software Engineer (SWE) (multiple). recblid 39ypo69ybe7dhq7o3w6ctpa635ui1b https://t.co/XDV3xsw8Ra https://t.co/cEUQsiNYqL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT-Assistant Vice President: IT-Assistant Vice President (Research Triangle Park, NC): Design, develop, &amp; support trading &amp; risk management applications covering securitized products. Design &amp; develop application components using SDLC, C#, .NET,… https://t.co/eb2oO061A4 https://t.co/I70HteJJ86]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[P&amp;O – Workday HCM Experienced Associate: PwC/LOS Overview PwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about us at… https://t.co/TUrrBWVlsi https://t.co/jUKRVV3AQh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Environmental Project Manager: ENVIRONMENTAL PROJECT MANAGER PSI, an Intertek Company is currently seeking an Environmental Project Manager who has an interest in developing long-term client relationships with increasing project and professional… https://t.co/KC2zIVQW8v https://t.co/G3i8jRHBzk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Housing and Processing Supervisor: Req ID : 417106BR Job Code/Title : L3233:Mult Func Manufacturing Supv Job Description : Sikorsky a Lockheed Martin Company is a world leader in the design and manufacture of advanced helicopters for commercial and… https://t.co/60gFk2Vbr6 https://t.co/eaVMAbWR7w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director, Physical Security Operations, Stamford:   Job Description – Director, Physical Security Operations, Stamford (00018237) Job Description  Director, Physical Security Operations, Stamford – (00018237) Description   EXCEPTIONAL OPPORTUNITIES FOR… https://t.co/9Fzxrq2AVt https://t.co/fkS4l0IPmH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advanced Analytics Program Analyst: Req ID 96757BR Business Title Advanced Analytics Program Analyst Group MSS Location USA VIRGINIA Alexandria Clearance Level Needed Secret Category Programs &amp; Operations Job Duties and Responsibilities ManTech is… https://t.co/oxMAHwrWCK https://t.co/MSCpxp4Jv9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Start apply with LinkedIn Start apply with Facebook Start apply with Xing Apply Now Please wait… Location: Morristown, NJ, New Jersey, US Requisition ID: 15661 Location: Morristown, NJ, New Jersey, United States  Requisition ID: 15661 … https://t.co/5JdrYzikKk https://t.co/Ov3fPyJZ9c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer I: Come work at a place where innovation and teamwork come together to support the most exciting missions in the world! Position Summary Excellent opportunity for a fast learner to gain lots of technical depth in a variety of areas in a… https://t.co/vxNvxenXlL https://t.co/vnOepPET3U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Software License Management Analyst (Specialist Business Process Analyst): TECHNOLOGY SERVICES GROUP (TSG) is the central infrastructure services group with a proven track record of innovating to help BNY Mellon and its customers have most reliable,… https://t.co/6gsa30liHG https://t.co/rMoVjFVIHI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Linux Cluster Systems Administrator – Utah: Linux Cluster Systems Administrator – Utah ========================================== Req #: ******Location: Bluffdale, UT USJob Category: Information TechnologySecurity Clearance: TS/SCI with… https://t.co/Ynr7bwskjb https://t.co/IQpz9jtrEW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead System Architect: IT/SOFTWARE Lead System Architect. Configuration of complex enterprise software systems, including Pegasystems PRPC, design and architectural oversight of software solutions. Bachelor’s or higher in comp. sci. 5 yrs exp. Exp with:… https://t.co/zt3mUex8QM https://t.co/xKEEQA4RLG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Careers: Your new Tech Job is just one search away! 👉 https://t.co/Ucfv7Wm2zk 👈 #IT #hire #career #recruiter #recruiting #hiring #tech #ITJobPro https://t.co/dDNXVGMekS https://t.co/Z8eQuJScLN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Specialist #4137: Information Specialist – (Rural Health Information Hub) The Center for Rural Health (CRH) at the University of North Dakota is seeking experienced and talented applicants to serve as an Information Specialist for the Rural… https://t.co/vuLHZqei75 https://t.co/R4fYJaaGpc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Architect: Arrow Electronics, Inc (Englewood, Colorado) is looking for Enterprise Architect. Work across Information Technology domains as well as business applications to identify opportunities for improving efficiency, enhancing quality of… https://t.co/KiyEfSGyhv https://t.co/l7XDF54UVu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Sr. Engineer: Data Domain LLC (a Dell Technologies company) is seeking a Software Sr. Engineer at our Santa Clara, CA facility to develop software solutions for external clients based on detailed specifications from technology/ systems… https://t.co/2Qk1cRIjAI https://t.co/4P75JeYtTj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Telecom Analyst #80159P: Telecom Analyst The Telecommunications Analyst position is a technical role to support the telemanagement system responsible for inside and outside cable plant records. This position will create and maintain accurate… https://t.co/9pDeTgaq40 https://t.co/8ytqc9A0WE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RAVPower Power Bank Exclusive Deal: A WIRED deal on an outstanding battery pack, Air Force-grade smartwatch, and other gadgets galore. https://t.co/DCnFcgrgCU https://t.co/xtZ3OZZdtJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Software Developer The Office of the Revisor of Statutes, a nonpartisan office in the Minnesota Legislature, is seeking applicants for a Systems Analyst/Programmer I position. The office has implemented an XML-based, bill drafting,… https://t.co/foHkPN3rIK https://t.co/Lt8zsfQ4IF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Engineer: Software Development Engineer Responsibilities: * Analysis huge data in Microsoft big data platform Cosmos. * Develop Scope scripts in Visual Studio to proceed business big data into small data sets as data source of Power… https://t.co/qKvsHQG2hc https://t.co/Hq09cvnBer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer Applications: Apple Inc. has multiple positions available in Cupertino, CA: Software Engineer Applications (Req#ALN2DS) Rspnsble fr dvlping &amp; deplying SW apps. Software Development Engineer (Req#AMV8AM) Responsible for dsgn, devpmnt, &amp;… https://t.co/Bom9e5iKUe https://t.co/vIccXm71jK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chief Engineering Officer: Beverage Co-packer in N. LV seeks Chief Engineering Officer. Must have Masters in Electronic Engineering &amp; available to travel. Must have 15+ years of experience w/: (a) nonalcoholic beverage manufacturing plant managing 100+… https://t.co/KEsOwyOyik https://t.co/EhWaAqorcH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle EBS Business Analyst (Windham): *** No one with less than 2 years industry experience will be considered. *** *** No third party candidates will be considered. *** Candidates MUST have a minimum of specific domain experience and no resumes will be… https://t.co/548kkdLz2O https://t.co/fUeY82pnNb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: Infosys DX Technology Lead – US React JS Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to create and execute strategies for their digital transformation. From… https://t.co/WdxrKx2xkR https://t.co/yaTBXZIhY8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Security Specialist Quality Assurance: Req ID 94389BR Business Title Security Specialist Quality Assurance Group MCIS Location USA VIRGINIA Springfield Clearance Level Needed TS/SCI Category Security Job Duties and Responsibilities Become an integral… https://t.co/TnjvDxoTlw https://t.co/VYlElIGPjD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Product Manager, Data Science: Job Summary: We are seeking an experienced Product Manager/Product Owner to join our team supporting the integration of data science methodologies such as natural language processing and machine learning into services… https://t.co/Y4h8lIMtCp https://t.co/sOOT6MPb4R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unified Communications Manager Job: Date: Mar 19, 2018 Location: Baltimore, MD, US Company: SAIC Unified Communications Manager (Job Number:434935) Description: SAIC is looking for a Unified Communications Manager to lead operations on-site technical… https://t.co/ynS0E9feu9 https://t.co/5VCAOZEZIQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: The Advanced Concepts division of Solute is an organization of world class technologists that builds cutting edge technology in cutting edge Software, Cyber Security, Data Analytics, Cloud Computing, Mobility, and Advanced… https://t.co/m7a5f4MmyP https://t.co/uwuGu8xB0k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solution Architect: Job Title: Solution Architect (JDA Fulfillment) Location: Chicago, IL Experience: 10-12 Years JDA experience Job Responsibilities: * Design and Architect supply chain solutions that best meets the clients requirements based on latest… https://t.co/OuIAvqJ7Oz https://t.co/T83a10q4zk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist, Financial Planning Analysis: Data Scientist, Financial Planning &amp; Analysis (IT Systems) Full Time NBC Universal Orlando, United States, Florida, United StatesIt takes a special kind of person to work at all of our destinations. An… https://t.co/59wfJKcerP https://t.co/RQ73SNj3Fe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst: You will collect, maintain, manage and interpret data from internal and external sources; work with business users and subject matter experts to clarify business needs, develop report specifications, and test results to ensure business… https://t.co/coy9XQwWBc https://t.co/lek3tCpArx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer Analyst #PA327SA: KIP Information Technologies, Inc. has an opening for a Programmer Analyst (Code PA327SA) to work in Arlington Heights, IL and various unanticipated locations throughout the US. Duties include: create, modify &amp; test the code,… https://t.co/B4wWJGkPx0 https://t.co/Y0lmLRgaoA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Engineer: Software Development Engineer Responsibilities: * Analysis huge data in Microsoft big data platform Cosmos. * Develop Scope scripts in Visual Studio to proceed business big data into small data sets as data source of Power… https://t.co/DYLxSriGK9 https://t.co/YPqnA9evXk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer: Senior Software Developer, Austin, TX, General Motors. Develop, deploy, &amp; test GM Cimplicity based solutions within manufacturing environment, such as Production Routing &amp;Tracking, Production Pull System, &amp; Electronic Pull… https://t.co/X82YpoxxUp https://t.co/vCQwua0i5T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Project Manager #80165P: IT Project Manager (Vacancy #80165P) IT Services (ITS) at Iowa State is seeking qualified applicants for an experienced IT Project Manager. This position will be responsible for managing small to large technology related… https://t.co/YpcZ45ui4Z https://t.co/kTFRQ1NzaB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analytics Data Integration Developer: Senior Healthcare Analytics Data Integration Developer (Memorial Health Services, 17360 Brookhurst Street, Fountain Valley, CA 92708) POSITION DUTIES: Develop data integration solutions to end user and application… https://t.co/fzFKAHsb45 https://t.co/LzfBtyscFN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Desktop Support Technician: Grand Lake Mental Health Center, Inc. Claremore, OK Desktop Support Tech We are currently seeking a Desktop Support Technician with at least three (3) years of experience in computer repair and maintenance. Some basic… https://t.co/iJaQJR6371 https://t.co/rrIWwV0HxM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Administrator, Database Administrator: Network Administrator &amp; Database Administrator $5,857 – $7,122 per month   EOE This company is an equal opportunity employer to all, regardless of age, ancestry, color, disability (mental and physical),… https://t.co/BeDlNZw9SB https://t.co/3B72Ffo5RR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Program Director – Health Information Technology: Program Director – Health Information Technology Exciting opportunities exist at a diverse and highly regarded community college located in the heart of the Piedmont Triad! GTCC is the third largest… https://t.co/LH9M5h95D6 https://t.co/aMTepeQzdh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forecast Analyst Staff: Cypress Semiconductor Corporation, leading provider of high-performance, mixed-signal, programmable solutions, has openings in San Jose, CA for Forecast Analyst Staff (FA01): Without direct reports, perform all forecasting and… https://t.co/6rCi50FxeU https://t.co/fZdyA9sJm8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Developer: SAP Labs, LLC seeks a Senior Developer at our South San Francisco, CA location to support the total design and implementation effort and participates in multiple projects, consistently solve complex problems. Bach dgr in Comp Sci, Engg,… https://t.co/uE9qmakLum https://t.co/Uu2zEJa3O7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Administrator: Network Administrator Roaring Fork Transportation Authority Hiring a full-time Network Administrator to upgrade and support connectivity of RFTA’s network. Must provide technical oversight of WAN, monitor network performance,… https://t.co/uBWU3QVAQa https://t.co/lqARgZjB3v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 Best Smartphones of 2018: Guide to Android, Samsung Galaxy, iPhone: If you're on the prowl for a new Android, Galaxy, or iPhone, read our full guide to the best smartphones of 2018. https://t.co/klEDOoPOPg https://t.co/n0iEvZB8nV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Engineer: Peer Bearing Co. seeks Application Engineer, Waukegan, IL Supports company’s growth and expansion. Supports Engineering customer day preparation and presentation. Assist Sales on fixing technical issues related to customer design,… https://t.co/5NafTZ3u3K https://t.co/rGLISRHKL8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JAVA APPLICATION DEVELOPER: KRONSYS is hiring for 2 positions (travel req): Java Application Developer – MS CS, EE or closely rel. XML, Oracle, Java; Business Data Analyst – MS Comp App, Info Sys, MBA or closely rel. + 2 yrs exp. or BS + 5 yrs exp. or… https://t.co/0P04ckfZPc https://t.co/ZEiQdIT6pD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle EBS Business Analyst (Woburn): *** No one with less than 2 years industry experience will be considered. *** *** No third party candidates will be considered. *** Candidates MUST have a minimum of specific domain experience and no resumes will be… https://t.co/cp5NBy8Y6n https://t.co/CGm8UGnNft]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cisco Headend Engineer III: Client Reference Code: 214300 Job Scope The Cisco Headend Engineer III is responsible for effective operations and other related infrastructure to support video applications. The individual will support multiple internal and… https://t.co/NcZGTnKm8i https://t.co/GbgEobqdJL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer – Backend Services: Sr. Software Engineer – Backend Services at Twilio (View all jobs) San Francisco, CA or Mountain View, CA The Twilio platform enables companies to integrate communications directly into their applications via… https://t.co/s1KNA6Rd3x https://t.co/Kxzwzfj6Qt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Trimble is recruiting for a software engineer to fill a position in Chicago, IL or the South Bend / Mishawaka / Wakarusa, IN areas.  Job Summary Develop applications and contribute to the complete life cycle; from concept and design to… https://t.co/KOJlyy393D https://t.co/dbqddLagyI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Operations Analyst 4:   Job Description – Operations Analyst 4 (18003506) Operations Analyst 4 Requisition ID : 18003506 Location : United States-Virginia-Arlington US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation Assistance: No relocation… https://t.co/lvY8q4mzqc https://t.co/lCRAiTWzWK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manager Quality 2:   Job Description – Manager Quality 2 (18006162) Manager Quality 2 Requisition ID : 18006162 Location : United States-California-Sunnyvale US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation Assistance: No relocation assistance… https://t.co/6mlc54SFmk https://t.co/4EIQHeiTox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Software Engineer: Principal Software Engineer Embedded Systems (Belmont, CA), responsible for shaping and strengthening the electronics development for Audi and the VW Group; targeted towards Audi electronics; development, optimization, and… https://t.co/TmHA4kBeR6 https://t.co/h2qh7v0wdi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Healthcare Data Analyst – Irvine, CA: You are a thought leader who thrives on developing new solutions to solve tough challenges. As a critical member of our business analysis team, you will help rewrite the future of UnitedHealth Group. Here,… https://t.co/QNjXQiuepx https://t.co/brOn5pQIkE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Public Sector – Data Analytics Consultant – Senior Associate: PwC/LOS Overview PwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities.… https://t.co/U3hXVAidFC https://t.co/bmWy1sCAkz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Check If Cambridge Analytica Could Access Your Facebook Data: Facebook has released a tool that lets you see if you were caught up in the Cambridge Analytica fiasco—and what other apps know about you know. https://t.co/kcoFKfvnXR https://t.co/ZhzzuC81ij]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Director, Healthcare Economics – Minnetonka, MN: We invite you to bring your performance, ideas and innovations to an elite team within a culture built for collaboration. At UnitedHealth Group, we seek individuals who have the ability to drive… https://t.co/NxsXqweT4i https://t.co/YZUKGWUHfS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Backend Engineer: Livongo Health, Inc. in Mountain View, CA seeks a Senior Software Backend Engineer to assist a team of software engineers to create software features for the company’s new data cloud. Must have Bachelor’s degree or… https://t.co/5FKHYCl4Lj https://t.co/F5vOb8fnbF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JRSS Network Operation Controller: Description: The Defense and Intelligence Group of Leidos, has an opening for Network Operation Controller for JRSS NOC at Scott AFB, IL. PROGRAM SUMMARY: Defense Information Systems Agency (DISA), located at Scott AFB,… https://t.co/rv0DwCsiwR https://t.co/sEISsAzZZk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Staff Engineer: Senior Staff Engineer (job location is Seattle, WA) Design &amp; write code for video services designed to enhance HBO’s video streaming capability &amp; content associated w/ company’s interactive endeavors. Perform site architecture &amp;… https://t.co/1ghgl0CkFt https://t.co/6UnRy1d8EQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solution Engineer: Quantum Secure Inc (San Jose, CA) F/T positions: Solution Engineer III: Resp for analyze &amp; cust security suite; req Master’s or equiv + 2 yr exp + skills (telcom. ok). Big Data Engineer: Resp for large data sets; req Master’s or equiv… https://t.co/UYvNRsCMBH https://t.co/2LNZUKOzHD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Design Engineer: Design Engineer Application Software sought by RGB Systems DBA Extron Electronics in Anaheim, CA. Work on team of highly skilled software engineers to build cutting-edge software applications focused on the AV industry. recblid… https://t.co/nGv722uiNQ https://t.co/NTGqx4kq2I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Database Analyst position: hibu Inc. is seeking a Senior Database Analyst position for its King of Prussia, PA office. The Senior Database Analyst is responsible for performing database systems development, contributes to the data management… https://t.co/YjsYGCjuaC https://t.co/aDxV0TWfld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SR. SOFTWARE ENGINEERS: Sr. Software Engineers, Fort Worth, Texas: Develop s/w reqs specs, functional specs, &amp; s/w design docs. Develop, design, test, implement &amp; support modular s/w components, memory mgmt techniques, standard calling conventions, low… https://t.co/lRbHQ3dFQt https://t.co/NLtxoguPI1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Project Manager #80165P: IT Project Manager (Vacancy #80165P) IT Services (ITS) at Iowa State is seeking qualified applicants for an experienced IT Project Manager. This position will be responsible for managing small to large technology related… https://t.co/8U55gqKjYu https://t.co/58q1Hvpz7w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Lead # TY18: Sofbang, LLC a Chicago, IL IT Consulting Firm, is looking for a Technical Lead with : Master’s Degree in Computer Applications, Information Technology, Computer Science, Engineering, or Math; and 2 year’s experience with Oracle… https://t.co/niCae7AqXC https://t.co/44WByb2tGq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist: CooperVision, Inc. seeks a Data Scientist-Global Strategic Pricing in Pleasanton, CA to support global pricing strategy and compliance through analysis of pricing data, tracking of competitive pricing/promotional programs, and monitoring… https://t.co/l6cAGbXiMy https://t.co/X3zmT7kY82]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Gently Breathing Somnox Robot Cuddles You to Sleep: The Somnox is a fuzzy, bean-shaped robot that mimics human breathing to help the human holding it fall asleep. https://t.co/DAM1uRz1Oi https://t.co/0sZ6RuFOLY]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>