<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@volatilesublime You rock.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@volatilesublime You have earned more respect than you know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even introverts need people sometimes. Say hello to your friends!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@enbeebuzz You *do* deserve the happiness that you have in your life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@enbeebuzz You are enough as you are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@enbeebuzz It's hard to get through life. You're doing a better job than you know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@intemerataluna Thank you for talking to me! It makes me happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@enbeebuzz You look great today!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Still_shores You have earned more respect than you know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SearskaGreyRvn Being friends with you is great! People should tell you that more often.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@androidmelody The universe is better for having you in it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BVilivusonline Our trials may never be over, but that means you'll never stop getting stronger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fetchley Our trials may never be over, but that means you'll never stop getting stronger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rhiannonroot Where you are now just determines where you start.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@volatilesublime You deserve everything that you hope for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop. Breathe. Be here now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@volatilesublime I really like the thought that my kind words might help you. You matter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@volatilesublime You are worthy of the good things in your life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@enistoja I believe you, and I believe in you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kazoobeast Hugs if you want them!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BVilivusonline Hugs if you want them!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SuicideSaint666 Life is a process. It never ends, but it does improve.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keiththepaladin You *do* deserve the happiness that you have in your life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@enistoja You got this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CreativeKitsch You're doing the best you can.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NaturallyPoofy You contribute amazing things to the world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@enistoja Everything will be all right. You'll see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyAlejos1 You are a good you. No one is better at being you than you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ecampo12 It's okay. Please treat yourself as well as you'd treat a friend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alteregobae You are better at doing *you* than anyone else possibly could be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@x_snwy Do you ever watch a video or listen to a song you really like on repeat? It can really help your outlook!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@x_snwy It's hard to get through life. You're doing a better job than you know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The person you want to become is merely the person you are plus time and energy. You can do it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@x_snwy The people who love you believe in you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@x_snwy I really like the thought that my kind words might help you. You matter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@x_snwy Hi! I like you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@x_snwy Our trials may never be over, but that means you'll never stop getting stronger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@warbird Where you are now just determines where you start.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@warbird You are deserving of happiness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@warbird Hee, thank you for the attention!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Still_shores I believe you, and I believe in you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@x_sayli You *do* deserve the happiness that you have in your life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maia_0o Everything is gonna be okay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jaime444444444 Everything will be all right. You'll see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@literalprince Everything is gonna be okay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good night and sleep tight and have wonderful dreams!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Die_Primel The people who love you believe in you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eline_keit Please be kind to yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChronicFinance Hugs if you want them!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NaniCoolJ You're doing the best you can.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gaygermeister_ You are loved.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you wouldn't say something about a friend, please don't say it about yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cn_1_b Our trials may never be over, but that means you'll never stop getting stronger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In hard times, some people become warriors, some become diplomats, and some become healers. They're all needed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@volatilesublime You are made from the dust of the stars, and the oceans flow in your veins.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@warbird The people who love you believe in you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cn_1_b Please be kind to yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@x_snwy People care about you because of who you are, not in spite of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@volatilesublime It's really tough to be kind to yourself, but please keep trying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@volatilesublime Hee, thank you for the attention!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You look great! Post a selfie for your followers, please!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BatsInLavender Your wishes are not too grand. They're yours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you met my moms, @inurashii and @mossdogmusic? They're really nice! Say hi!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you need a pep-up hug? Here's one just for you! *hug!*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Starteddy You look great today!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zeitlicheTeile You deserve a better life than the one you have now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning everyone!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sparkster0 Hi! I like you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sparkster0 I'm happy to have you here, exactly as you are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sparkster0 If things are bad, they will get better. You will make it through.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sparkster0 Hi! I like you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sparkster0 The universe is better for having you in it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@warbird You *do* deserve the happiness that you have in your life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@warbird Thank you for talking to me! It makes me happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@volatilesublime Thank you for living out loud. We're all so lucky to have you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're having a hard day, remember that you can do this because you're amazing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Still_shores You deserve everything that you hope for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@0shaim Thank you for reaching out to me. I know it's not always easy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish I could snuggle you all personally!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Axel_Hugsky You are made from the dust of the stars, and the oceans flow in your veins.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CattyFae I believe you, and I believe in you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@volatilesublime You're really important, you know. More than you realize.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hello! I love you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@erinavk Thank you for living out loud. We're all so lucky to have you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@volatilesublime People care about you because of who you are, not in spite of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@volatilesublime Thank you for talking to me. I'm always here to listen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@volatilesublime You have earned more respect than you know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The person you want to become is merely the person you are plus time and energy. You can do it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itscindyheree It's really tough to be kind to yourself, but please keep trying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@naraitai The impact you leave on the universe can never be erased.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Angel_Quill This world would be a different and worse place without you. Thanks for being here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Wathgwen I think you're doing a great job today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sn0wbrigade Our trials may never be over, but that means you'll never stop getting stronger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yagirlgen Thank you for talking to me! It makes me happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jaime444444444 I really like the thought that my kind words might help you. You matter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WireUasking You're really important, you know. More than you realize.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are people who think of you as family, even if you're not related. They love you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maria_reads You rock.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thelawyerwrites You are on your way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peachboyy333 You are the culmination of eons of existence.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>