<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager Multifamily/Wood Frame: Houston, TX Full-time $80k – $120k Posted Today If you are a Project Manager with experience, please read on! What You Will Be Doing – Answering to a Senior Project Manager – 5-10 years’ experience (APM or new PM)… https://t.co/I8GMZaIsSn https://t.co/p6OVLmGzvt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Walker Elliott:Job Title: Software Engineer, Information Technology, Houston – Texas Close HOME EMPLOYERS CANDIDATES ABOUT US BLOG JOB SEARCH HOME EMPLOYERS CANDIDATES ABOUT US BLOG JOB SEARCH Job Detail: Software Engineer CANDIDATES… https://t.co/2PnImJ6OdM https://t.co/0Nuwj8PNRN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer with Clouds experience: DevOps Engineer with Clouds experience Toggle navigation – About Us – Inside Luxoft – Benefits – Automotive – Excelian – Training &amp; Communities – Relocation Program – Social Responsibility – Discover Us – Events –… https://t.co/ggiIRBuIas https://t.co/QHGIba26rQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instructor Web Design – Adjunct Pool: Employer Houston Community College Location Houston, TX Posted Jun 01, 2018 Institution Type Community College You need to sign in or create an account to save SUMMARY Provide the expertise and knowledge that support… https://t.co/tHrMKQMbD3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Superintendent-K-12/Education construction-Ground Up/Renovations: Houston, TX Full-time $65k – $140k Posted Today If you are a Superintendent-K -12/Education construction-Ground Up/TI with experience, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us 90% of… https://t.co/oOj3KDvCkG https://t.co/nVvyFmV52p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Manager, Instructional Design &amp; Technology: at Endurance International Group (View all jobs) Houston, TX or Tempe, AZ Looking for an opportunity to make a significant impact in a high growth technology company? Do you have a passion for creating… https://t.co/ETyaFyO8QF https://t.co/epUWvkzASO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fault Management Engineer: Req ID : 434611BR Job Code/Title : E1074:Software Engineer Stf Job Description : This position supports the Orion SEIT-Fault Management team in the design, test and verification of the off nominal operation of the Orion… https://t.co/YEyS6EKHmb https://t.co/yuzB5A4A8q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: DevOps Engineer Ref No.: 18-26089 Location: Houston, Texas Position: DevOps Engineer Location: Houston, TX Mandatory Technical Skills, Experience Linux Admin: Mount, Security Group, Backup, Disk space, user, group, server &amp; process… https://t.co/jpo4Oswr9m https://t.co/YxwLLPhM74]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Project Manager (Remote/Virtual) Job: Technical Project Manager (Remote/Virtual) (Job Number:437597) Description: JOB DESCRIPTION: – SAIC is hiring a Technical Project Manager – Virtual /Remote Location. – This position, and others on the SAIC… https://t.co/WH0sTrSivu https://t.co/9CjTcgDQBc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETC Web Application Development and Data Analytics Analyst: ETC – Web Application Development and Data Analytics Analyst ============================================================ Date: May 23, 2018 Location: Houston, TX Texas, US now now * Start apply… https://t.co/ztnh4itNcq https://t.co/zo2Nds4VVJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer Ref No.:18-14697 Location: Houston, Texas Job Title: .NET developer Job Location: Houston, TX Job Duration: 12+ Months Responsibilities: – The applications are manufacturing and business supporting. – The candidate must… https://t.co/boq8VSqapF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Project Logistics (Wind Energy Vertical): What’s the opportunity? Project Manager – Project Logistics (Wind Energy Vertical; located off of highway 249) is responsible for the overall management and coordination of project operations in… https://t.co/FKduC3Ue8j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unix Administrator: LONG-TERM CONTRACT * Perform Unix Systems Administration for Enterprise Sun Solaris10/Oracle linux OVM Systems to include: * Sun 25K/SunFire series, M3000/M4000/M5000/T5120/T5220/T5240/ T5440/V240/V280/V490 / CISCO Blade servers *… https://t.co/b3attA1NVm https://t.co/bMDr7e7gHo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facilities Project Manager: Requisition ID 2018-26159 Work Location US-TX-Houston Department / Discipline Facilities / Maintenance / Office Services Position Type Staff / Permanent Overview / Responsibilities We are currently sourcing a Facilities… https://t.co/Er3f82Jhsx https://t.co/F8bEa0BXo8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analyst – Application Developer I/II: Kinder Morgan – Job Details Sign In to access application status, saved documents and Job Search Agents Job Details New Search View Job Cart (0) Send This Job to a Friend View My Account Analyst – Application… https://t.co/FSsRaEuDix https://t.co/H9ARPJ7Y2B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Knowledge Management Specialist: at Endurance International Group (View all jobs) Houston, TX or Tempe, AZ To be a part of the Endurance Learning &amp; Employee Success team, you have to be passionate about learning and helping others to grow and succeed.… https://t.co/m9Hkg0XN09 https://t.co/NaSv9bs5RK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer Angular 2: Project Description One of the world’s largest providers of products and services to the energy industry has a need to develop, support and integrate software systems in Oil &amp; Gas domain. Systems capabilities include data… https://t.co/kpT3GdHmWx https://t.co/r5OGftFQVo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Scheduled Maintenance The SAP SuccessFactors HCM Suite is currently undergoing scheduled maintenance. We apologise for any inconvenience this may cause. Please visit the Support Portal or contact Customer Support if you need further… https://t.co/ANXZJ94UiI https://t.co/xIdMbwIR3a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MIT Account Executive, Enterprise: MIT Account Executive, Enterprise Why Work at Dell? Endless challenges and rewards. Opportunities on six continents. A team of colleagues fueled by collaboration. All this, and a company deeply committed to integrity… https://t.co/0mCKZeJ9EC https://t.co/4yAjuZqVYD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Trading Business Analyst: IT Trading Business Analyst =========================== Date: May 23, 2018 Location: Houston, TX Texas, US now now * Start apply with LinkedIn Start apply with LinkedIn Help * * Start apply with Seek Start apply with Seek… https://t.co/qgf8xKu98o https://t.co/u2UdwbBjMG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital Oil Field Technical Lead: Salary/Rate N/A Permanent Location Houston, TX Texas, US, United States Posted By Chevron Date Posted 33 minutes ago Expires 22 Jun 2018 Qualifications None Digital Oil Field Technical Lead in Houston, TX Texas, US,… https://t.co/F3n6tngjkY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solutions Account Executive – HPI – Dallas/Houston, TX: Solutions Account Executive – HPI – Dallas/Houston, TX Location US-TX-Dallas Req Number 2018-21133 Weekly Work Hours 40 Shift 8-5 Travel Required 70% Relocation Assistance Available Yes Working Time… https://t.co/96YzrPWfLq https://t.co/Y3NR6VGurA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When a text can trigger a lynching: WhatsApp struggles with incendiary messages in India: MUMBAI (Reuters) - A WhatsApp text circulating in some districts of India's central Madhya Pradesh state helped to inflame a mob of 50-60 villagers into savagely… https://t.co/8XfuYDg3pz https://t.co/a2Iv1iVmGj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SW Engineer QA Cloud Software: Blog Search jobs Keyword CategorySelectAdministrationBusiness PlanningCorporate AdministrationEngineeringEngineering ServicesFinanceGeneral ManagementHuman ResourcesInformation TechnologyLearning &amp;… https://t.co/NYU5aYnsYu https://t.co/KdIXPFdg6o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meituan-Dianping files Hong Kong IPO, said to raise over $4 billion: HONG KONG/SHANGHAI (Reuters) - China's Meituan-Dianping, an online food delivery-to-ticketing services platform, filed for a Hong Kong IPO on Monday, an offering that aims to raise more… https://t.co/XQcwWowDZZ https://t.co/FCIkYBodeN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Support Engineer – STAR-CCM+ – Houston, TX: **Application Support Engineer – STAR-CCM+ – Houston, TX** Locations:Houston, Texas Job Family: Engineering New Search Apply English (US) **Job Description** **Division:** Digital Factory **Business… https://t.co/k3s9P6z8qg https://t.co/SqG7cZUlIN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior C#/C++ developer: Project Description One of the world’s largest providers of products and services to the energy industry has a need to develop and support enterprise information system in Oil &amp; Gas domain. Project is related to collection,… https://t.co/lBKuYLo68w https://t.co/id1y13PBDX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intern: Software Engineering SQL, JavaScript: Intern: Software Engineering – SQL, JavaScript Tracking Code ******* Job Description Please note that our internships run in perpetuity throughout a students degree program, therefore you must live within… https://t.co/3cvA5Bqfx4 https://t.co/NTF5XFczBH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Engineer: Project Description One of the world’s largest providers of products and services to the energy industry has a need to develop and support enterprise information system in Oil &amp; Gas domain. Project is related to collection, visualization and… https://t.co/7d2Zdd74GC https://t.co/yWLga4LTdV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Juniper Network Engineer: This is a 40 hour per week position, on-site, at the customer location and may require additional work hours and on-call support for critical issues which will be compensated for with Comp time. * To hold network information… https://t.co/oKI1eaovEG https://t.co/IKQwK5zSYW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer Intern: Requisition ID 2018-25960 Work Location US-TX-Houston Department / Discipline Information Technology Position Type Trainee / Internship Overview / Responsibilities Wood has an opportunity available for a Software Developer… https://t.co/uqs8XBkZMa https://t.co/JjfrjAbL7u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Operations Analyst: Save job Job ID ******* Primary Location Houston, Texas, United States of America Date posted 06/12/2018 Applies intermediate level of subject matter knowledge to solve a variety of common business issues. Works on problems… https://t.co/zRVV9QYspp https://t.co/BVJQHcJa1t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer NetIQ Directory and Resource Administrator Houston, TX: Software Engineer – NetIQ Directory and Resource Administrator – Houston, TX Tracking Code ******* Job Description Discover the new Micro Focus – now the world’s 7th largest… https://t.co/xWThNl5J0c https://t.co/NxYiqj2QMV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer – North Houston: Job Description Growing IT Infrastructure Firm looking for Network Engineers BEMA Information Technologies is a highly recognized provider of IT services to churches, schools and medium-sized businesses. We are 17 years… https://t.co/pwrsGiuMTG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Multifamily Superintendent- Top Tier Owner/Builder: Houston, TX Compensation Unspecified Posted 05/15/2018 As a company we hold a strong belief in building successful long term relationships with our clients. We as a company, work with our clients as a… https://t.co/6BUVZpbCV1 https://t.co/Fh5EBG995M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack LAMP Developer: Walker Elliott:Job Title: Full Stack LAMP Developer, Information Technology, Houston – Texas Close HOME EMPLOYERS CANDIDATES ABOUT US CONTACT JOB SEARCH HOME EMPLOYERS CANDIDATES ABOUT US BLOG JOB SEARCH Job Detail: Full Stack… https://t.co/Ao1ytvPjNv https://t.co/p5W1Sr4iZK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineers: Kastech – Home – About us – Services – Products – Blog – case studies – Careers – Contact careers Are you looking for a great career opportunity? Current Openings Cheers !! Be the first person to step into the innovation team. Looking… https://t.co/EQZ2ZHqGwl https://t.co/ZMMOvaOxbT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla recycling machine catches fire at Fremont, California campus: (Reuters) - A machine used for paper recycling caught fire Thursday night at Tesla Inc's Fremont, California, campus, outside the company's car production factory, but manufacturing was… https://t.co/XjocYxxnXs https://t.co/QZZbbxf2Aw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Walker Elliott:Job Title: Software Engineer, Information Technology, Houston – Texas Close HOME EMPLOYERS CANDIDATES ABOUT US BLOG JOB SEARCH HOME EMPLOYERS CANDIDATES ABOUT US BLOG JOB SEARCH Job Detail: Software Engineer CANDIDATES… https://t.co/Clp2AJdi74 https://t.co/yUDYksE6zI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Application Developer: – IT Application Developer Location Address US-TX-Houston Job ID 2018-2735 # of Openings 1 Location Name NSMG Home Office, TX Department IT Type Full-Time Overview At NorthStar Memorial Group, we choose collaboration over… https://t.co/ozd5QMYJ41 https://t.co/jjcUX0qyOT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[User Experience Designer: User Experience Designer ======================== Location: Houston, TX, US Company: ExxonMobil [IMAGE] Job Role Summary The User Experience (UX) Designer designs software for a community of engineers and geoscientists. The… https://t.co/Av5R2Olq5O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solution Architect – Southeast Region: Job Description Solution Architect – Southeast Region ABB Inc., in Houston, TX is looking for a Solution Architect – Southeast Region to join our Measurement and Analytics Business Unit, a part of our Industrial… https://t.co/tzB1qzFeBA https://t.co/HTwbe08ALo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer – North Houston: Job Description Growing IT Infrastructure Firm looking for Network Engineers BEMA Information Technologies is a highly recognized provider of IT services to churches, schools and medium-sized businesses. We are 17 years… https://t.co/JhPU09P1zn https://t.co/QzS4IXoDGr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analyst – Application Developer I/II: Kinder Morgan – Job Details Sign In to access application status, saved documents and Job Search Agents Job Details New Search View Job Cart (0) Send This Job to a Friend View My Account Analyst – Application… https://t.co/X7YGQafk0Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Engineer: Project Description One of the world’s largest providers of products and services to the energy industry has a need to develop and support enterprise information system in Oil &amp; Gas domain. Project is related to collection, visualization and… https://t.co/ofF5LjiqHy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer: Title: Developer 13152 Duration: 6 Months Contract to hire Location: 10353 Richmond Ave Houston TX 77042 Job Duties : NOV Rig Technologies IS group is looking for an application developer to help our teams design and deliver web application… https://t.co/GVGfQfLmNI https://t.co/4Ro3eVjlDg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer Ref No.:18-10623 Location: Houston, Ohio Position Type:Contract Start Date: 06/14/2018 Role: .Net Developer Location: Houston, OH Job Type: Contract Roles and responsibilities: – Resource should be strong on C# Design and… https://t.co/98rkcBaGrd https://t.co/S2eqeaAltS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supreme Court lets states force online retailers to collect sales tax: WASHINGTON (Reuters) - States may force online retailers to collect potentially billions of dollars in sales taxes, the U.S. Supreme Court said in a major ruling on Thursday that… https://t.co/znAHGFPl5J https://t.co/RTK1G1L0kV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Project Logistics (Wind Energy Vertical): What’s the opportunity? Project Manager – Project Logistics (Wind Energy Vertical; located off of highway 249) is responsible for the overall management and coordination of project operations in… https://t.co/jN8RsbkY1c https://t.co/hiceit3HWV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Delivery Factory Software Engineer: Chevron is one of the world’s leading energy companies, with approximately 60,000 employees working in countries around the world. We explore, produce and transport crude oil and natural gas; refine, market… https://t.co/AnnSbBr3UZ https://t.co/0jh8vXDR5e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.net Developer: .Net Developer Houtson, Texas – United States Job Start Date – 06/04/18, Posted Date – 06/04/18 Primary ********** developerTax TermsC2COverview A .NET Developer at Avanade focuses on designing, developing and testing mission critical… https://t.co/0xT1AbF8rV https://t.co/LWubg7WJQ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Developer (C#/WPF, Houston): Senior Developer (C#/WPF, Houston) Toggle navigation – About Us – Inside Luxoft – Benefits – Automotive – Excelian – Training &amp; Communities – Relocation Program – Social Responsibility – Discover Us – Events – Referral… https://t.co/Tqeugk8dP7 https://t.co/iioTP7Iy8D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Geological Geophysical Application Developer: Geological &amp; Geophysical Application Developer ============================================== Date: May 23, 2018 Location: Houston, TX Texas, US Apply now Apply now * Start apply with LinkedIn Start apply… https://t.co/dlakLSOxyi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Manager, Instructional Design &amp; Technology: Senior Manager, Instructional Design &amp; Technology at Endurance International Group (View all jobs) Houston, TX or Tempe, AZ Looking for an opportunity to make a significant impact in a high growth… https://t.co/ft57LkHwGO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instructor Web Design (Part Time) – Adjunct Pool: Employer Houston Community College Location Houston, TX Posted Jun 01, 2018 Institution Type Community College You need to sign in or create an account to save SUMMARY Provide the expertise and knowledge… https://t.co/mAFz63luRp https://t.co/X6ONKy7k8G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Business Analyst: Recruiter PROS Location Houston Houston United States Salary Competitive Posted 28 May 2018 Closes 24 Jun 2018 Job role Accountant Sector Telecommunications Contract type Permanent Hours Full time You need to sign in or create an… https://t.co/er7vD0odRR https://t.co/n7yQndxbgB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump to meet lawmakers about 'problematic' ZTE amendment: spokeswoman: WASHINGTON (Reuters) - U.S. President Donald Trump and a group of lawmakers from the Senate and House of Representatives will meet at the White House on Wednesday to discuss their… https://t.co/4105x0ADja https://t.co/gn9RS0RrTo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla's Musk says Germany a front runner for Europe Gigafactory: STOCKHOLM (Reuters) - U.S. electric carmaker Tesla favors Germany as the location for its first European Gigafactory, its chief executive said, in what would be the latest move by an… https://t.co/DfKcQV2L7m https://t.co/nKcELtpImt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Security Engineer: Application Security Engineer at HP Inc. Skip Navigation Careers Search for jobsWorking at HPFaqs Sign in &amp; apply Blog Search jobs Keyword CategorySelectAdministrationBusiness PlanningCorporate… https://t.co/6a7bSuukMd https://t.co/YsHXtxanbc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China's Xiaomi targets as much as $6.1 billion in Hong Kong IPO: sources: HONG KONG (Reuters/IFR) - Chinese smartphone maker Xiaomi Corp is planning to raise up to $6.1 billion from a Hong Kong IPO launching this week, people with knowledge of the matter… https://t.co/xddreRtvrR https://t.co/aVxAC87Hjq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ERP Application and Reporting Administrator – AX: * ERP Application and Reporting Administrator – AX Location US-TX-Houston ID 16580 Business Unit SESI Corporate, LLC About Superior Energy Services Superior Energy Services is a leading provider of… https://t.co/Z4ZyI8l2Yh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South Korea's Bithumb loses $32 million in digital money heist, bitcoin falls: SEOUL (Reuters) - South Korean cryptocurrency exchange Bithumb said 35 billion won ($31.5 million) worth of virtual coins were stolen by hackers, the second local exchange… https://t.co/5sfrbRu09u https://t.co/HE14FE1pnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Field Engineer II: 117020BR Job Description: Raytheon Intelligence, Information &amp; Services Division (IIS) has opportunities for TSA IT Specialist. As a TSA IT Specialist you will perform a wide variety of task with respect to TSA computer hardware,… https://t.co/EEtNeXyayl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instructor Web Design – Adjunct Pool: Employer Houston Community College Location Houston, TX Posted Jun 01, 2018 Institution Type Community College You need to sign in or create an account to save SUMMARY Provide the expertise and knowledge that support… https://t.co/bXqudaekdm https://t.co/gEML3xF8kc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Job Posting Title Sr Technical Support Consultant Chemical Engineering: – Sr Technical Support Consultant – Chemical Engineering Job Locations US-TX-Houston Req # 9787 # of Openings 1 Job Posting Category Technical Support &amp; Training Overview Aspen… https://t.co/ql5kDawQRp https://t.co/4KP8iC6q90]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ZTE, U.S. suppliers shares tank after Senate puts Trump reprieve in doubt: HONG KONG (Reuters) - Shares of ZTE Corp and its American business partners took a hit on Tuesday after the U.S. Senate's passage of a defense bill set up a potential battle with… https://t.co/ql2rMPNnfA https://t.co/ZZxM8Cx8XR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Walker Elliott:Job Title: Software Engineer, Information Technology, Houston – Texas Close HOME EMPLOYERS CANDIDATES ABOUT US BLOG JOB SEARCH HOME EMPLOYERS CANDIDATES ABOUT US BLOG JOB SEARCH Job Detail: Software Engineer CANDIDATES… https://t.co/HA0m5atNWr https://t.co/6HApnOgreN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Software Engineer: Microsemi, Inc. has an early career Quality Systems Engineer opening based in Houston, Texas to be a key contributor in the testing effort of our storage firmware and driver applications. In this role, you will be responsible… https://t.co/yDmnsK9xLw https://t.co/z9zrRNJKGO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Trading Business Analyst: Salary/Rate N/A Permanent Location Houston, TX Texas, US, United States Posted By Chevron Date Posted 33 minutes ago Expires 22 Jun 2018 Qualifications None IT Trading Business Analyst in Houston, TX Texas, US, United States… https://t.co/01auvnc0Av https://t.co/HGPZykOJhL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Developer: Lead Developer (C#/WPF) Toggle navigation – About Us – Inside Luxoft – Benefits – Automotive – Excelian – Training &amp; Communities – Relocation Program – Social Responsibility – Discover Us – Events – Referral Program – Recruitment Process… https://t.co/GS21nESC6q https://t.co/GGlXs9Oukx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer Intern: Requisition ID 2018-25960 Work Location US-TX-Houston Department / Discipline Information Technology Position Type Trainee / Internship Overview / Responsibilities Wood has an opportunity available for a Software Developer… https://t.co/ocZvLOj05q https://t.co/O3IOlLJD7y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Administrator: System Administrator ==================== Req #: ******Location: Fort Sam Houston, TX USJob Category: Information TechnologySecurity Clearance: SecretClearance Status: Must Be Current Job Description CACI has an immediate opening… https://t.co/RdAcUYgN2s https://t.co/vXRi5fXsQr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETC Web Application Development and Data Analytics Analyst: ETC – Web Application Development and Data Analytics Analyst ============================================================ Date: May 23, 2018 Location: Houston, TX Texas, US now now * Start apply… https://t.co/I4NYzHhgIT https://t.co/prw7qEEjIC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Developer (C#/WPF): Lead Developer (C#/WPF) Toggle navigation – About Us – Inside Luxoft – Benefits – Automotive – Excelian – Training &amp; Communities – Relocation Program – Social Responsibility – Discover Us – Events – Referral Program – Recruitment… https://t.co/Xh9DYM53JU https://t.co/EbcWrpu6cN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital Oil Field Technical Lead: Digital Oil Field Technical Lead ================================ Date: May 23, 2018 Location: Houston, TX Texas, US now now * Start apply with LinkedIn Start apply with LinkedIn Help * * Start apply with Seek Start… https://t.co/m5zww5uCbY https://t.co/0Pnx4FVLiu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP ABAP: SAP ABAP (APO Technical) Ref No.: 18-23698 Location: Houston, Texas At NTT DATA, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The quality, integrity, and commitment of our employees are key factors in our company’s growth,… https://t.co/RW5bktpsNk https://t.co/CrTmpkLaWg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Geological Geophysical Application Developer: Salary/Rate N/A Permanent Location Houston, TX Texas, US, United States Posted By Chevron Date Posted 33 minutes ago Expires 22 Jun 2018 Qualifications None Geological &amp; Geophysical Application Developer in… https://t.co/P3H3F0kp0S https://t.co/mxx19ir5Z0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Walker Elliott:Job Title: Software Engineer, Information Technology, Houston – Texas Close HOME EMPLOYERS CANDIDATES ABOUT US BLOG JOB SEARCH HOME EMPLOYERS CANDIDATES ABOUT US BLOG JOB SEARCH Job Detail: Software Engineer CANDIDATES… https://t.co/5xeR4BLgvp https://t.co/sdb28WtJNg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google to invest $550 million in Chinese e-commerce giant https://t.co/Szvr35YYvR: (Reuters) - Google will invest $550 million in Chinese e-commerce powerhouse https://t.co/Szvr35YYvR, part of the U.S. internet giant's efforts to expand its presence in… https://t.co/WxDbIKg1Mz https://t.co/FxEAmPJ3Li]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Data Scientist/Computational Scientist: Senior Data Scientist/Computational Scientist ============================================= Date: Jun 14, 2018 Location: Houston, TX Texas, US Apply now Apply now * Start apply with LinkedIn Start apply with… https://t.co/x1oaZmsLeV https://t.co/Dtt6pEr8QI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Superintendent-K-12/Education construction-Ground Up/Renovations: Houston, TX Full-time $65k – $140k Posted Today If you are a Superintendent-K -12/Education construction-Ground Up/TI with experience, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us 90% of… https://t.co/zMyxIqQZT3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales Manager – Southwest:   Job Description – Sales Manager – Southwest (39930) Job Description  Sales Manager – Southwest-39930 Description   Company: Hitachi High-Technologies Division: Sales Territory: Southwest (Including but not limited to: TX, LA,… https://t.co/JgQVMTtyP2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETL Developer: ETL Developer Houston, Texas – United States Job Start Date – 05/31/18, Posted Date – 05/31/18 Primary SkillsETLTax TermsC2COverview Phone and skype. Duration- 6months. Rates- 50. No H1B. Location Houston, TX General Description… https://t.co/7SQSLZXPBg https://t.co/k5gRL9cRJj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer: Title: Developer 13152 Duration: 6 Months Contract to hire Location: 10353 Richmond Ave Houston TX 77042 Job Duties : NOV Rig Technologies IS group is looking for an application developer to help our teams design and deliver web application… https://t.co/JlKvkMG2IK https://t.co/CmvBWLRsuH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Programmer: At Expero, we ship software products for our clients. Complex domains and large datasets are the hallmark of our engagements. But our world-class UX people and front-end programmers can only make interactive applications if they have… https://t.co/U06fzvdxIu https://t.co/xdQfxUnKKu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: HigherEducation: DevOps Engineer We Work Remotely See more DevOps &amp; Sysadmin jobs Back to all jobs DevOps Engineer Posted May 28 HigherEducation Headquarters: Houston, TX ******************************* View all HigherEducation jobs… https://t.co/CAujY1xIfT https://t.co/Dh9vFaiyCG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South Africa's Liberty Holdings suffers cyber attack: JOHANNESBURG (Reuters) - South African insurer Liberty Holdings said on Sunday it had become the victim of a cyber attack, with an external party claiming to have seized data from the firm and… https://t.co/NI3kEc5ZVc https://t.co/12kGkHngiH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETC – Web Application Development and Data Analytics Analyst: ETC – Web Application Development and Data Analytics Analyst ============================================================ Date: May 23, 2018 Location: Houston, TX Texas, US Apply now Apply now… https://t.co/1pTDmLL0xY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Technical Analyst Finance Systems: Business Technical Analyst – Finance Systems ============================================ Location: Houston, TX, US Company: ExxonMobil [IMAGE] Job Role Summary ExxonMobil is looking for outstanding candidates… https://t.co/5mKvAH719Z https://t.co/7w1bvZSBZI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer Microservices: Project Description One of the world’s largest providers of products and services to the energy industry has a need to develop, support and integrate software systems in Oil &amp; Gas domain. Systems capabilities include… https://t.co/84cp0dWhaQ https://t.co/nmJLdaZ8Ll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital Oil Field Technical Lead: Salary/Rate N/A Permanent Location Houston, TX Texas, US, United States Posted By Chevron Date Posted 33 minutes ago Expires 22 Jun 2018 Qualifications None Digital Oil Field Technical Lead in Houston, TX Texas, US,… https://t.co/GOISOYkCvv https://t.co/ERso25jjsV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network security Engineer: Network security Engineer Ref No.: 18-24735 Location: houston, Texas Hi, Hope you are doing great! Please have a look at the job description below and let me know if you are interested: Role: Network Security Engineer Location:… https://t.co/cGFtfuFILM https://t.co/UB2xqFfMv4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Administrator: System Administrator ==================== Req #: ******Location: Fort Sam Houston, TX USJob Category: Information TechnologySecurity Clearance: SecretClearance Status: Must Be Current Job Description CACI has an immediate opening… https://t.co/oC7Jt41x5M https://t.co/FE4KFS6pvW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manager, Organization Effectiveness:   Job Description – Manager, Organization Effectiveness (38904) Job Description  Manager, Organization Effectiveness-38904 Description   Manager, Organization Effectiveness (OE)  Hitachi Consulting is seeking Manager… https://t.co/pLRX5Z1TOg https://t.co/mEJoDEL7wk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GCFIT Executive IT Support Analyst: GCFIT – Executive IT Support Analyst ==================================== Date: May 21, 2018 Location: Houston, TX Texas, US now now * Start apply with LinkedIn Start apply with LinkedIn Help * * Start apply with Seek… https://t.co/hqCeRgpImQ https://t.co/Y24XBoyUNu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Project Manager: Salary/Rate N/A Permanent Location Houston, TX, US, United States Posted By ExxonMobil Date Posted 28 minutes ago Expires 10 Jul 2018 Qualifications None 2018USH – IT Project Manager in &amp; #60;span class &amp; #61; &amp; #39;jobLocation &amp; #39;… https://t.co/HEH1AeNHAr https://t.co/PBd6nDRwUl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior System Software Engineer: Texas Instruments – Job detailsTI Careers – – – Applicant Login – About TI – Company – Careers – Investor relations – Citizenship – University – Public policy – Careers – Our company – Why TI – Career paths – Search jobs… https://t.co/VJ12lja4GY https://t.co/1QSwVOtuCB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Storage and Backup Lead Engineer (Remote/Virtual) Job: Storage and Backup Lead Engineer (Remote/Virtual) (Job Number:437328) Description: Job Description – Looking for a Lead Enterprise Storage and Data Protection Senior Engineer with design and O&amp;M… https://t.co/2HQsaR4yE7 https://t.co/oypijVQmsQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anywhere Expert Device Replacement Onboarding Acting Coach (Houston):   Job Description – Anywhere Expert Device Replacement Onboarding Acting Coach (Houston) (PSS29817) Job Description*  Anywhere Expert Device Replacement Onboarding Acting Coach… https://t.co/iVyMNM86yR https://t.co/HA21MOHChE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump sets $50 billion in China tariffs; Beijing vows to strike back: WASHINGTON/BEIJING (Reuters) - U.S. President Donald Trump said he was pushing ahead with hefty tariffs on $50 billion of Chinese imports on Friday, and the smoldering trade war… https://t.co/TfzCtTuhMm https://t.co/oXzfdAaiIy]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>