<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Ray Conniff  http://t.co/3o3hQwRDfU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Importance of Competitive Analysis of Strategy Consulting Firms  http://t.co/RAj4EU7cIM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Profiles of Major Watch Designers  http://t.co/TWmCqBOKM7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Petula Clark  http://t.co/1dgKsTEJDH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Psychiatry is a pseudoscience. You don't know the history of psychiatry. I do. Matt. - Tom Cruise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be successful, you have to have your heart in your business, and your business in your heart. - Thomas Watson, Sr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Clear Lighted Skateboard with green LED Lights  http://t.co/naYFlQqmZm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So what is Bitcoin and the Bitcoin block chain exactly? http://t.co/NoA5lZFnvO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marvel's The Avengers - ALL FOUR Movies in one Collection - including The Avengers - VERY COOL!!!! http://t.co/YJc6P5ETWG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The reason Las Vegas is getting so big is nobody can afford to buy a ticket to leave.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'll forgive me, Madam President, if I don't wish to be executed based solely on your... gut feeling. - Doctor Gaius Baltar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stay Ahead in eCommerce With Marketing Tips  http://t.co/mGQm20VUuQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things could be worse. Suppose your errors were counted and published everyday, like those of a baseball player. - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Marmalade Insurance: Selecting The Right Insurance  http://t.co/wkW3mpOiPQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I went through baseball as a player to be named later." - Joe Garagiola]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Mike Clifford - A One-Hit Wonder  http://t.co/AHaJ4KuNWS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't pay good wages because I have a lot of money; I have a lot of money because I pay good wages. - Robert Bosch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NASA Unveils a Very Cool New Space Suit  http://t.co/RA1yp1YQgW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buzz: Be sure not to lock it on my way out. On surface, Neil: Isn't that something? Magnificent sight out here. Buzz: Magnificent desolation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Great Tips from Web Marketing Experts  http://t.co/PM0l9Y43XX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To win without risk is to triumph without glory. - Pierre Corneille]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You want to fall in love with a shoe go ahead. A shoe can't love you back, a shoe can't hurt you too deeply either. - Allan Sherman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1,000 Incredible Costume and Cosplay Ideas http://t.co/IPGc5SBMoP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was a pretty good coach and working with marketing was like coaching. - Bernard Ebbers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is the best deodorant. - Elizabeth Taylor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about the Bay Area city of Fremont, California  http://t.co/N9Q6HK2hzM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool Garages and Flooring Types  http://t.co/xdQGQhLKZ7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A respectable appearance is sufficient to make people more interested in your soul --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of the Inheritance Series Third Volume – Brisingr  http://t.co/0hB6bbWsBt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business has only two functions - marketing and innovation. - Milan Kundera]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Babysitter: a teenager who acts like a Grownup while grownups are acting like teenagers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ultimately, the only power to which man should aspire is that which he exercises over himself. - Elie Wiesel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome kayaking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the paddling lovers in your life!   http://t.co/6YHsJV2ATA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How to Create an Effective Company Blog  http://t.co/CLJI4cHAun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay, that thing in the woods, maybe it's a monster, maybe it's a pissed off giraffe, I don't know. Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for great resources on Beer?  Check out our top 10... http://t.co/QuwvvwP9Rb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True friends are like diamonds - bright, beautiful, valuable, and always in style. --&gt; Nicole Richie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Overview of Bluetooth Enabled Watches  http://t.co/laTLHBN9bC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Sword Umbrella - Eye Catching http://t.co/X55rBEZKZo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is that which discloses to the wise and disguises from the foolish their lack of understanding. - Ambrose Bierce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never go in against a Sicilian when death is on the line! - Vizzini, The Princess Bride]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Book Review - Endangered: Drakensang  http://t.co/ivTrfwNnjW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I die, I'm leaving my body to science fiction. - Steven Wright]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future belongs to those who believe in the beauty of their dreams. - Eleanor Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Small Dogs Can Make Great Pets - Picking the Right Breed  http://t.co/IeDraH6bBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've looked into the eye of this island, and what I saw was beautiful. - John Locke, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love making money, but you can't live your life waiting to get rich in a job that no longer feeds you artistically. Julianna Margulies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The rest of the world lives to eat, while I eat to live. - Socrates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Are the Different Types of Web Hosting?  http://t.co/AdWB1zjUNm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep NFL Football Is Here To Stay!  http://t.co/BwuFqxMwQ4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do women want? Shoes. --&gt; Mimi Pond]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dis Be Da Place]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the fascinating history of that classic baseball park - Wrigley Field - http://t.co/geIwCS0aZr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gold Glitter Lips - Cool Look!  http://t.co/SGhW7peXH8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A mosquito is just like a child, when it stops making noise, you know it's getting into something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Do Parents Pick Favorite Things for their Kids?  http://t.co/W1xNAZYD5M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Different Types of Ashes Scattering Services  http://t.co/v73nlBGClj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Grapevine, Texas  http://t.co/icWivbU9Xy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel like punching the boss' jaw again  "Did you say again?" "Yes, I felt like doing it once before today!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Credit card sized took kit with 2-Inch Serrated Knife, can/bottle opener &amp; Flat screwdriver, tweezers &amp; toothpick! http://t.co/DJ8mMc1Sfg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hokey religions and ancient weapons are no substitute for a good blaster at your side, kid. - Han Solo, Star Wars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Three Styles of BMX Bikes and their Uses  http://t.co/XsbFvossuV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Three Dog Night  http://t.co/2LYBEzAXy0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Best Tips Given for Facebook Pages Geared for Business  http://t.co/vMDEro07xv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The studios have been taken over by marketing people and accountants. - Joe Eszterhas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can You Imagine Melting Clock - Very Cool - Jazz Up Your Office Space! http://t.co/WncSmyjqM0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The safest way to double your money is to fold it over and put it in your pocket. - Kin Hubbard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dr. Who Blue Tardis Min-Fridge - so “COOL”! - http://t.co/Pw5kvZiYcW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Building Experts - Get Some Free Tips  http://t.co/L6in9z3Fzh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I play with my cat, who knows whether she is not amusing herself with me more than I with her. - Montaigne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Bob Dylan -- His Biography    http://t.co/UBy5NQb34P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Whispers  http://t.co/tvmwa7CU1Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to 3D Printing  http://t.co/540hnIqP3C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was never interested in being a rock star. I always wanted to be Boris Karloff. - Gene Simmons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very cool 23 mile range walkie talkies!  Stay connected!  http://t.co/30RSPwS7Vq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Leif Garrett  http://t.co/KlBpNa1gY8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest thing in this world is not so much where we stand, as in what direction we are moving. - Oliver Wendall Holmes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Rolling Stones  http://t.co/3zKm3yHMNu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A patient man is one who likes slow catsup.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is only a tool. It will take you wherever you wish, but it will not replace you as the driver.  Ayn Rand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think about it... Mistakes are just small steps to perfection...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Best Tips Given for Facebook Pages Geared for Business  http://t.co/vMDEro07xv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Using Instagram for Web Marketing  http://t.co/nAdUGqCATb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supporting Adopted Students: Parents and Teachers Working Together  http://t.co/v8MBr5gq3D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The right shoe can make everything different. - Jimmy Choo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the American Hamburger  http://t.co/CY3AREYLb0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CONSCIENCE: The thing that hurts when everything  else feels good…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatness of a nation and its moral progress can be judged by the way its animals are treated.- Mahatma Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome marriage t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the lovers in your life!   http://t.co/7d7egwaity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tom Cruise is rumored to wear them - shoe lifts - read their fascinating history... http://t.co/uHUrtIlsbk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You only have to do a very few things right in your life so long as you don't do too many things wrong. - Warren Buffett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I started racing my father told me, "˜Cristiano, nobody has three balls but some people have two very good ones. - Cristiano Da Matta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does it mean when a person is such a pacifist that they get shot? I can never understand that. - John Lennon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Who Invented the Modern Watch?  http://t.co/W2OefOrkFf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's better to have fewer things of quality than too much expendable junk. - Rachel Zoe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting fired is nature's way of telling you that you had the wrong job in the first place. - Hal Lancaster]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I am become Death, the destroyer of worlds - J. Robert Oppenheimer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Evolution of the Wooden Clog  http://t.co/f04fb5GhFB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plastic surgeons can do almost anything with a nose these days, except keep it out of other people's business]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A tax collector has what it takes to take what you got]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>