<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Worrying will never change the outcome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't live a perfect day without doing something for someone who will never be able to repay you. -John Wooden]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lnspire_me: We could never learn to be brave &amp; patient, if there were only joys in the world. -Helen Keller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bitterness is like drinking poison &amp; waiting for the other person to die. -Steve Ostten]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laugh on. https://t.co/Fm8tPJeRy7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FaithReeI: https://t.co/hbGl79Tgo5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you have never made a mistake then it means you have never tried something new.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you do not enjoy what you are doing, you will never be good at it. -Luke Parker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't change what's going on around you until you start changing what's going on within you. https://t.co/3Vr4JPQRY0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have never really lived until you have done something for someone who can never repay you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lnspireMeNow: Truth above all else. https://t.co/uBxr1MtOk2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where you invest your love you invest your life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life consists not in holding good cards, but in playing those cards you hold well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our live are full of moments. Enjoy them. https://t.co/fgF3nu4g4n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it is important to you, you will find a way. If it's not, you'll find an excuse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When your mind says give up, hope whispers one more try.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mother_know: It's always mom! https://t.co/RFnpekWels]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No color, no religion, no nationality should come between us, we are all children of God. - Mother Teresa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not enough to be compassionate, you must act.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only put off until tomorrow what you are willing to die having left undone. - Pablo Picasso]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good things come to those who wait. But better things come to those who work for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is to short to spend it with the wrong people. https://t.co/v0nKxCl3qv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 rules of a relationship:
1. Stay faithful.
2. Make them feel wanted.
3. Respect your partner.
4. Don't flirt with others.
5. Make time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's important to give it all you have while you have the chance. -Shania Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never be afraid to try something new. Remember, amateurs built the ark. Professionals built the Titanic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't think outside the box. Think like there is no box]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheDaiIyPuppy: Gotta love 'em! ^^

Get your westie tee here --&gt; https://t.co/ZiBKRckaZ5 https://t.co/XfwvKwJrRu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DCoffeeDG: We all could use a little happy. https://t.co/9puOU836VR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you accept the expectations of others, especially negative ones, then you never will change the outcome. -Michael Jordan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TabithaKhaye: Good or bad, sooner or later, the things we say &amp; do eventually come back to bless or haunt us. It's self sabotaging to d…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Climb the mountain so you can see the world, not so the world can see you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do what you can, with what you have, where you are. -Theodore Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conquer your bad habits or they will conquer you. - Rob Gilbert]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love, there is nothing stronger. https://t.co/XjTOHEhZ9A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no pillow so soft as a clear conscience. -French proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fall seven times, stand up eight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By becoming the answer to someone's prayer, we often find the answers to our own.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The answer lies within ourselves. If we can't find peace and happiness there, it's not going to come from the outside. - Tenzin Palmo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The more I think of it, the more I realize there are no answers. Life is to be lived. - Marilyn Monroe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LittleHeadBigH: Fear can keep us up all night long, but faith makes one fine pillow. -Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes you gotta create what you want to be part of. -Geri Weitzman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Work hard in silence; let success make the noise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["So do not worry about tomorrow, for tomorrow will take care of itself." -Matthew 6:34]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I choose to be happy today. https://t.co/767XqpZdRC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is about laughing &amp; living in good &amp; bad times. Getting through whatever comes our way &amp; looking back with a smile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FaithReeI: https://t.co/0rnE43xEZM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True.. https://t.co/Ai7FFS1ba5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Comparison is the thief of joy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Participate in life instead of just watching it pass you by.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They always say time changes things, but you actually have to change them yourself. - Andy Warhol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best pieces of advice. https://t.co/8dji31J2uT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can be comfortable or courageous, but you cannot be both.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are where you're supposed to be at this very moment. Every experience is part of God's divine plan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DCoffeeDG: Stay positive. https://t.co/Dh7bBlqMmp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank God for your life tonight. For your health, your family, or your home. Many people don't have these things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great advice!! https://t.co/Orpoc4DGJg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always be kinder than you feel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AthIetesForGod: We wish it was ;(

Get this tee here --&gt; https://t.co/6fGbNaed46 https://t.co/4FjPxxjW6f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What we see depends mainly on what we look for. #perspective]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You cannot find peace by avoiding life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hate is not the first enemy of love. Fear is. It destroys your ability to trust.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Inspire_Us: Pray more, worry less.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't let other people tell you who you are. You have to decide that for yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you choose to forgive those who have hurt you, you take away their power.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be you :) https://t.co/QWKGVys6QQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great relationships aren't built in a day - great relationships are built daily.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Respect yourself enough to walk away from anything that no longer grows you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lnspire_me: Don't put the key to your happiness in someone else's pocket.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do the best you can until you know better. Then when you know better, do better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the secrets of life is that all that is really worth the doing is what we do for others. -Levi Strauss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Better late then never. https://t.co/D09ppYAgJq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You cannot always wait for the perfect time. Sometimes you must dare to jump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great point https://t.co/WAQXXIgrZd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the right light, at the right time, everything is extraordinary. - Aaron Rose]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Sports_Greats: Excuses are not an option!

Get your motivational t-shirt here --&gt; https://t.co/ybK9NnAzPk https://t.co/xngnoSH6A4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is the wealthy man's curtain which hides all his defects from the world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We make a living by what we get, we make a life by what we give. - Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sports_moxy: Show me someone who has done something worthwhile, and I'll show you someone who has overcome adversity. -Lou Holtz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very very true. https://t.co/ori5SCHeTs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live in the moment. Forget the past and don't concern yourself with the future.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every scar has a story. Don't be afraid to tell it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's better to give then receive. https://t.co/HGgWOOXz8k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Inspire_Us: Spread good vibes only! :)

Get this awesome tee here --&gt; https://t.co/QlMDvywfKm https://t.co/WCgFzvDFcv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Truth is not diminished by the number of people who believe it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your value doesn't decrease based on someone's inability to see your worth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If your happiness depends on what somebody else does, I guess you do have a problem. - Richard Bach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @The_Gospels: Begin and End today with prayer. Visit -&gt; https://t.co/1qRf0GTTd3 &amp; sign up for our daily emails. https://t.co/bgHJsXqnx5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twinkle Twinkle. https://t.co/qmPjvSWdVb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perfection is not of the world. Do your best and forget the rest. https://t.co/nVCCxKqM84]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All a girl really wants is for one guy to prove to her that they are not all the same. -Marilyn Monroe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lnspireMeNow: Life is not about waiting for the storm to pass, It is about learning to dance in the rain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Giving is a lifestyle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest mistake you can make in life is to continually be afraid you will make one. - Elbert Hubbard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anything I've done that was ultimately worthwhile initially scared me to death. -Betty Bender]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today is another chance to get it right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes you gotta fall before you fly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The ones who are crazy enough to think they can change the world are the ones that do. https://t.co/x3PcljZiv4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Quote_Soup: It's hard to beat a person who never gives up. -Babe Ruth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's hard to beat a person who never gives up. -Babe Ruth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God only gives three answers to prayer:
1. Yes!
2. Not yet.
3. I have something better in mind.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>