<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Cane Corso Italiano – Beloved Dog of Italy  http://t.co/pMTqedFE6H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In youth we learn in age, we understand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never expected to be anybody important.  - Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who can believe that there is no soul behind those luminous doggie eyes! - Theophile Gautier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leave it to Beaver is an American sitcom classic - read all about its history -  http://t.co/uCcIJV5z2F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes are the quickest way for women to achieve instant metamorphosis - Manolo Blahnik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to make the donuts (love that commercial!!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kneel before Zod. - Zod, Superman II]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Highland Village, Texas  http://t.co/DVDYZ8LZ9m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A New Star Wars Movie Is Coming in 2015!  http://t.co/hDj4cMhMJK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you tried to give rock and roll another name, you might call it 'Chuck Berry'. - John Lennon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It just seems to happen that by the time most of us get a little money to burn,  "the fire goes out."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Options for Using Slimmers and Trimmers for Weight Loss  http://t.co/gNe7o2e29K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 10 - Support Group Meeting  http://t.co/iHWTvhh95t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Lesley Gore  http://t.co/10ElIIZZpL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Coors Beer  http://t.co/ivQcprZ6nD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its better to own the racecourse then the race horse - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We never repent of having eaten too little. - Thomas Jefferson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You call the driver of a car a motorist, until he comes just little too close.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where there is an open mind, there will always be a frontier. - Charles F. Kettering]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bank is a place that will lend you money if you can prove that you don't need it. - Bob Hope]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A women with good shoes is never ugly. They are the last touch of elegance. - Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great History of the Rolling Stones  http://t.co/TCrkIZRXJO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Matrimony bonds are no good unless the interest keeps up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill, strange things are afoot at the Circle K. - Ted, Bill &amp; Ted's Excellent Adventure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Are the Different Types of Web Hosting?  http://t.co/xcyAAuy4jT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love making money, but you can't live your life waiting to get rich in a job that no longer feeds you artistically. Julianna Margulies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Barbara Acklin a Great Singer http://t.co/ZPS7y820cv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Emmylou Harris  http://t.co/vB8bvsxd02]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Deep Purple  http://t.co/aJJznDxNMV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I have any beliefs about immortality it is that certain dogs I know will go to heaven, and very very few people. - James Thurber]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Carlos Santana  http://t.co/ydnyzvNAvz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In 1905 Albert discovered Relativity, in 1906 he invented Rock and Roll.  - Yahoo Serious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cooking - A Simple Way To Bond With Kids  http://t.co/uOfSTuwf41]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is a Creative Writing Degree for You?  http://t.co/bYg7o2YoUl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who will wear a shoe that hurts him, because the shoe-maker tells him 'tis well made? - Algernon Sydney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If science fiction is the mythology of modern technology, then its myth is tragic. - Ursula K. Le Guin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live the Thug Life with These Temporary Tattoos! http://t.co/S7K1GrHCEp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Options for Using Slimmers and Trimmers for Weight Loss  http://t.co/ITL8cIpSVU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Who Is SpaceX?  http://t.co/qR3nQE3nEQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are seven winners of the Monaco Grand Prix on the starting line today, and four of them are Michael Schumacher. - Murray Walker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Reviews By Children Affect a Product’s Sale  http://t.co/aqRFix3i1v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Big-Dog Pet Fountain - Keeps Fresh and Tasty Water for Your Big Dog! http://t.co/kmTEfQiMNX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You may have to fight a battle more than once to win it. - Margaret Thatcher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any manager who can't get along with a .400 hitter is crazy. - Joe McCarthy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conversation:  when three women are talking together.  Gossip:  When one of them leaves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of 'em, any of 'em that have been in front of me over all these years.  Sarah Palin on the newspapers she reads]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Clear Lighted Skateboard with green LED Lights  http://t.co/9SFRvjWIWj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome - The World's Smallest Solar Powered Car! http://t.co/slB1AHgtD8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have heard of Bitcoin?  Read these 10 important things you should know... http://t.co/drt4CUrPS2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most serious mistakes are not being made as a result of wrong answers. The truly dangerous thing is asking the wrong question P Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sam Cooke was the king of soul - read his history - http://t.co/sCE04ENfoR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It cost more to amuse a child that it cost to educate the father.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not a marketing person. I don't ask myself questions. I go by instinct. - Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sports do not build character. They reveal it. - Heywood Broun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Overview of the X-Files  http://t.co/k8tbkzR0hc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I take a dim view of watching my own destruction. - Jack, "Invasion of the Body Snatchers"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriousness is stupidity sent to college. P. J. O'Rourke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool All Wood Watch! http://t.co/M0rjBPT8Z8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Advanced Weight Scales and Body Monitoring – Keeping Track of your Body Weight  http://t.co/YY9CtuMnHu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LinkedIn for Your Company Proves to be Effective  http://t.co/c23A6pfokh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The earth is the cradle of humankind, but one cannot live in the cradle forever. - Konstantin Tsiolkovsky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the parents of a Little Leaguer, a baseball game is simply a nervous breakdown into innings. - Earl Wilson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you drag your shoe a bit those plastic spikes or rubber spikes can be almost as bad as metal spikes. - Bernhard Langer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My little dog -- a heartbeat at my feet. - Edith Wharton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really love this Han Solo iPhone case - may the force be with you! http://t.co/5bCoreU85D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Are the Major Kinds of Insurance?  http://t.co/cMnp0v9580]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I'm hungry, I eat. When I'm thirsty, I drink. When I feel like saying something, I say it. Madonna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's hard to shake hands  with a clenched fist!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hops Holster 12 Can Ammo Pack - Beer Anywhere!  http://t.co/rgNi71zS55]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Scientific Explorer's Mind Blowing Science Kit! http://t.co/G5kGyJRkOD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding the Right Fitness Gadgets  http://t.co/sHUuFGAjMW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome biking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the biking lovers in your life!  http://t.co/KMuJVDl20S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's behind you doesn't matter. - Enzo Ferrari]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In my opinion Microsoft is a lot better at making money than it is at making good operating systems. Linus Torvalds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What --  is the air-speed velocity of an unladen swallow? - Bridgekeeper, Monty Python and the Holy Grail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Aretha Franklin  http://t.co/QWQTu0ybxG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a rock 'n' roll thing to have one-night stands. - Rick Springfield]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Successful Alternatives For Link Building  http://t.co/1mQjNi6hVl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd make a wonderful Lady Macbeth. I'll wear a pair of platform shoes or something - Bette Midler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[College isn't the place to go for ideas. - Helen Keller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The primary one being, like I said, I don't like rock 'n' roll piano.  - Warren Zevon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two sides: One is light, one is dark." -- John Locke, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I led the league in Go get 'em next time." - Bob Uecker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Bread  http://t.co/F8mPh1YZRr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Jackson Browne  http://t.co/O1fyKHcbzu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Blue Oyster Cult   http://t.co/7AYj3abdzc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Lobo the Classic Rock Group?  http://t.co/toQ8UkT2Hi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Left Banke  http://t.co/4Zi62ikJZR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Patsy Cline  http://t.co/yV7B3thwET]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The years are adding up when it takes us longer to get rested than it does to get tired. . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Courtship is the period during which a girl decides whether or not she can do better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marriage lets you annoy and aggravate one special person for the rest of your life.  What a joy LOL!!  :&gt;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I believe you are your work. Don't trade the stuff of your life, time, for nothing more than dollars. That's a rotten bargain - Rita  Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Famous Canadian Places to Visit  http://t.co/HTQQQyx1eN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The History of the Golden Retriever  http://t.co/ZLbrhcItTS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's hard to shake hands  with a clenched fist!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 meals a day a roof over my head, two cars, a boat, a power mower and a contented  wife -- why shouldn't I be in debt?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some of the greatest Hollywood actors are not the award winners, but those congratulating them on their triumph]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How Small Business Can Grow with Social Media Sites  http://t.co/Ol94SWw9PD]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>