<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA["Don't fight a battle if you don't gain anything by winning."
- Erwin Rommel #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surviving is important. Thriving is elegant. - Maya Angelou #quote  #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/SRNMrZTqqN https://t.co/KQnsoZwz5t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another amazing sundown in Ellensburg. What a day!

#eclipse #sunset #walkabout #summer @… https://t.co/o1hLME7uq2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you in the USA? Do you shop online? Take a look at this, I was blown away by it! All in my latest blog! https://t.co/uZlhskW8YY #shop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is not how much we have, but how much we enjoy, that makes happiness. - Charles Spurgeon #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is she doing?

#eclipse #funinthesun #sun @ Historic Ellensburg https://t.co/4VRVjIDv0E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fitting Kannaway CBD Products into Your Busy Schedule. Read this blog:https://t.co/uxAmJsbmxu #CBD #Hemp #hempoil #medicalmarijuana https://t.co/OoUr5NDLyJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How's watching the eclipse right now? You can stream it live right here=&gt;https://t.co/HHOd6N4Xzz Watch a little of history in the making!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Do not let what you cannot do interfere with what you can
do."
- John Wooden #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything ultimately comes down to trust.- Marcus Sheridan #quote #socialmedia #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know of only one duty, and that is to love. - Albert Camus #quote #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are never too old to set another goal or to dream a new dream. - C.S. Lewis #quote  #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who shops online? Who gets paid to shop online? If I could show you how that is done: Would you be interested? USA only. DM if you want info https://t.co/tSD1QcueLi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sundown in Ellensburg! Made me think of all my friends in Europe and the sun is coming up! The… https://t.co/kjRzqPZEF4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you can dream it you can build it. If you can build it, you can live it. - Pam Moore #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Determine never to be idle... It is wonderful how much may
be done if we are always doing.”
- Thomas Jefferson #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exhausting is okay. It means you're in the game. You're on the way up and you're not on the way down. - Lee Rosen #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beware that the detours in your life don't turn into destinations. - Tim Fargo #quote #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What you choose today will determine who you are tomorrow. - Tim Fargo #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've got a quick question! Do you order stuff online? How about getting paid to shop online? Free to join&gt;https://t.co/uSrzQBT4E0 #shopping]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Small town Americana!

#america #smalltown #farmersmarket @ Kittitas County Farmers Market https://t.co/qNgBO8WQNt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes life takes an unexpected wrong turn in the right direction. - Unknown #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we have no identity apart from our jobs, we are truly vulnerable. - Dan Miller #quote #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can normally tell how intelligent a man is by how stupid he thinks I am. - Cormac McCarthy #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analyze your mistakes. You've already paid the tuition, you might as well get the lesson. - Tim Fargo #quote #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People may not always tell you how they feel about you, but they will always show you. Pay attention. - Kim Garst #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you find yourself in a hole, quit digging. - Will Rogers #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Every great leap forward in your life comes after you have
made a clear decision of some kind"
- Brian Tracy #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life doesn't get easier or more forgiving; we get stronger and more resilient. - Steve Maraboli #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If winning isn't everything, why do they keep score?"
- Vince Lombardi #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are no shortcuts to any place worth going. - Beverly Sills #quote  #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fishing the Klickitat River with Matt!

#chinook #salmon #fishon #fish #fishing @ Lyle, Washington https://t.co/gMTJwlZ5U4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How you treat yourself sets the standard for how others will treat you. - Steve Maraboli #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Failure is not fatal, but failure to change might be."
- John Wooden #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't look for ideas to confirm your thinking, rather look for trends that will disrupt your thinking. - Rich Simmonds #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live life as if it were your last day on this planet! #johnbdeleo https://t.co/SNKWCGJFUN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nodding the head does not row the boat. - Irish Proverb #quote  #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fight against something and we focus on the thing we hate. Fight for something and we focus on the thing we love. - Simon Sinek #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When people say they'd like to be in your shoes, it's usually after the difficult journey is finished. - Tim Fargo #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9
“The power of imagination makes us infinite.”
- John Muir #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can normally tell how intelligent a man is by how stupid he thinks I am. - Cormac McCarthy #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to my top interactors! @IlluminexLED via #SocialJukebox https://t.co/g9O0oSxImJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The big question: what are we going to do for humanity? Serving others is the essence of leading at a higher level. - Ken Blanchard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/JuruEflxaT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Determine never to be idle... It is wonderful how much may
be done if we are always doing.”
- Thomas Jefferson #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you don't pass your values on to your kids, someone else will. - Frank Sonnenberg #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Success consists of going from failure to failure without loss
of enthusiasm."
- Winston Churchill #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes life takes an unexpected wrong turn in the right direction. - Unknown #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your value doesn't decrease based on someone's inability to see your worth. - Ted Rubin #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You have to learn the rules of the game. And then you have
to play better than anyone else.”
- Albert Einstein #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything ultimately comes down to trust.- Marcus Sheridan #quote #socialmedia #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[G.K. Chesterton is one of my favorite authors, really love his book called Orthodoxy.  #johnbdeleo https://t.co/KKTgq0SVy6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't judge me by my past. I don't live there anymore. - Petteri Tarkkonen #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bite of the 'Burg!

#college #wildcats #food #freefood @ Historic Ellensburg https://t.co/FeCkdKjaPY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You never know what worse luck your bad luck has saved you from. - Cormac McCarthy #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I quit now, I will be back to where I started, &amp; when I started I was desperately wishing to be where I am now. - Unknown #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything from your past does not belong in your present. - Lolly Daskal #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If we cannot see the possibility of greatness, how can we
dream it?"
- Lee Strasberg #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love doesn't make the world go round; love is what makes the ride worthwhile. - Elizabeth Barrett Browning #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't give up what you want most, for what you want now. - Zig Ziglar #quote  #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We must concentrate not merely on the negative expulsion
of war but the positive affirmation of peace."
-
Martin Luther King #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your worth consists in what you are and not in what you have. - Thomas Edison #quote  #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I myself am made entirely of flaws, stitched together with good intentions. - Augusten Burroughs #quote #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't look for it outside. Joy is always in you, all you've got to do is awaken to it. - Roxana Jones #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me and Paul taking a little break by the mighty Columbia River!

#motorcycle #motoguzzi #moto… https://t.co/hoImwp3Utx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Out for a ride down near the Columbia River today! 

#motoguzzi #italy #friends #ride #goodday @… https://t.co/eH6vgPD8if]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don’t try to be original, just try to be good. — Paul Rand #quote #startup #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Success is not a destination, it's a journey"
-Zig Ziglar #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The biggest mistake you can make is listening to people who've given up on their dreams telling you to give up on yours. - Umair Hague]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Wisdom is not a product of schooling but of the lifelong
attempt to acquire it"
- Albert Einstein #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Freedom begins with owning your flaws and disowning your fears. - Umair Hague #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What you choose today will determine who you are tomorrow. - Tim Fargo #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In order to succeed you must fail, so that you know what not
to do the next time."
- Anthony J. D'Angelo #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gratitude is the first sign of a thinking, rational creature. - Solanus Casey #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Think before you act and then act decisively. Fortune favors
the brave"
- Brian Tracy #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People may not always tell you how they feel about you, but they will always show you. Pay attention. - Kim Garst #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A couple very red sun photos on my walk last night. Fires are still burning!

#fire #firefighter… https://t.co/RC0XI2yXQm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Success comes from knowing that you did your best to
become the best that you are capable of being."
- John Wooden #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Self-Esteem begins and ends with you. The more you know about yourself, the less moved you'll be by the opinions of others. - B. Dilley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["First we form habits, then they form us. Conquer your bad
habits or they will conquer you."
- Rob Gilbert #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our greatest glory is, not in never falling, but in rising every time we fall.
 Ancient Proverb #failure  #succeed  #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to my top interactors! @dealsmeet @QuoTweety via #SocialJukebox https://t.co/g9O0oSxImJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exhausting is okay. It means you're in the game. You're on the way up and you're not on the way down. - Lee Rosen #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we have no identity apart from our jobs, we are truly vulnerable. - Dan Miller #quote #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The bad news: nothing is permanent. The good news: nothing is permanent. - Lolly Daskal #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You can disagree without being disagreeable"
-Zig Ziglar #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't exercise your freedom of speech until you have exercised your freedom of thought. - Tim Fargo #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Successful people make the most of the best and the best of the worst. - Steve Keating #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The person that said winning isn't everything, never won
anything."
- Mia Hamm #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love all, trust a few, do wrong to none. - Shakespeare #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To respond is positive, to react is negative"
-Zig Ziglar #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'll do more GOOD if you aim to SERVE more than you aim to PLEASE. - Chris Edmonds #quote #leadership #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embarrassment lasts a moment, regrets last a lifetime. - Petteri Tarkkonen #quote   #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Learn to help people with more than just their jobs; help
them with their lives”
- Jim Rohn #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't wait. The time will never be just right. -Napoleon Hill #quote  #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Dream big dreams! Imagine that you have no limitations,
and then decide what's right before you decide what's
possible"
- Brian Tracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret to success is doing the stuff other people won't do &amp; doing it for a really long time. - John Jantsch #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future belongs to those who believe in the beauty of their dreams. -Eleanor Roosevelt #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now we are really pirates!

#fun #pirates #love @ Puget Island, Washington https://t.co/qc5VsgwYQ3]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>