<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer: Software Developers Required in Bristol, Various Backgrounds Considered as training offered 40/55K Plus bonus and package.  We are looking for a Senior Software Engineer to join one of our teams as we continue to work on the… https://t.co/RZNE6F4nYC https://t.co/kz7wfxk8EX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Regional Project Manager, EMEA: Regional Project Manager, EMEA Reading Brook Street is currently working on behalf of our Global IT Client to recruit a Regional Project Manager. This is a contract role based in Reading for 9 months initially. As a Brook… https://t.co/R9Ied39KOu https://t.co/xu5MOUR2HX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PHP Developer: Full-stack PHP Developer urgently needed by an Ecommerce company based in Central London, working in an Agile team across a variety of projects across their Ecommerce platform predominately using PHP7 and JavaScript. The ideal PHP… https://t.co/ozrFzllkQl https://t.co/HGb2FM6PJ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trainee Cyber Security: Trainee Cyber Security * Are you looking for an industry recognised online IT training solution that can lead to a permanent IT Cyber Security position with excellent earning potential? * Are you technically minded? * Do your… https://t.co/fSDrmHBa3u https://t.co/jGkWdURkAW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twilio shops, Uber and Lyft IPO scuttlebutt, and Instacart raises $600M: Hello and welcome back to Equity, TechCrunch’s venture capital-focused podcast, where we unpack the numbers behind the headlines. This week we had the Three Excellent Friends… https://t.co/dCd3Clnm2m https://t.co/diZYJPB6yJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hiver lets you manage shared email addresses from Gmail: Meet Hiver, a service that lets you collaborate on generic email addresses, such as jobs@yourcompany.com, support@, sales@, etc. Hiver isn’t the only company working on shared inboxes. But compared… https://t.co/66NwEzKrVn https://t.co/MRup0JENhC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior C# Software Developer – Bournemouth – £55K: A Senior Software Developer is required by a highly successful, well-established and growing business based in Bournemouth. Experience in software development technologies such as C# and .NET is… https://t.co/jCTr6vQiUl https://t.co/YwPe3pHXt0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Office Coordinator: We have a great opportunity for a confident, curious Office Coordinator who will, quite literally, be the face and voice of our London hub, greeting external visitors and also responsible for incoming office enquiries by telephone.… https://t.co/yG0TSgrYtW https://t.co/Rin4Jwqayh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Net MVC / C# Software Developer £50k Medway + Bonuses: Net MVC / C# Software Developer £50k Medway + Bonuses and Benefits – Car / Travel Allowance .Net MVC / C# Software Developer £30k-£50k Medway + Bonuses and Benefits – Car / Travel Allowance, Private… https://t.co/da0uLWjsee https://t.co/VCUhvZF4gm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Online sellers 'pay for positive reviews' https://t.co/GHKL4dpAYn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worries among tenants over deposit return https://t.co/bZh5DBazju]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front-End Developer / £40,000 / Leeds / Vue.js / JavaScript: Front-End Developer / £40,000 / Leeds / Vue.js / JavaScript Are you a Front-End Developer with a passion for new technology and a desire to create exciting, cross-platform, user focused… https://t.co/tpJDndmYWl https://t.co/EBmuEOLCod]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lessons from building Brex into a billion-dollar startup: Henrique Dubugras Contributor Share on Twitter Henrique Dubugras is the founder Brex, the billion-dollar corporate credit provider for startups. When I think about my experience as an immigrant… https://t.co/au8H1HqLKe https://t.co/vWaC23KSUs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computing Teacher: Our client is a forward-looking College of Further &amp; Higher Education that serves a large area of South East England with a wide range of vocational and academic courses, both full and part time. The College is situated in Ewell, close… https://t.co/NVvGwbNbom https://t.co/Cg89Pp3yGV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital Business Analyst (Supply Chain): Digital Business Analyst (Supply chain) Role: Digital Business Analyst Location: Central London Salary: Up to £55,000 (depending on experience) My client, a superb, dynamic market leader based in a convenient… https://t.co/Pe7Zf3gC0R https://t.co/CaADlTdOeW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Product Owner – Bournemouth – £50K: A Product Owner is required by a highly successful, well-established and growing business based in Bournemouth. Experience in IT business change and product management is essential. As a Product Owner, you will join a… https://t.co/hm1hjlR4VD https://t.co/A9ikpSk0lz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TrackR is rebranding to Adero as it looks beyond small devices to track lost items: When TrackR raised $50 million from investors that included Amazon a year ago, the Santa Barbara startup made a big splash in the growing market for small connected… https://t.co/TirFIpmC9r https://t.co/Moxedfjsu1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google-style tech company – junior – mid level DevOps Engineers: How would you like to be part of a company that puts so much importance on open source projects (for their own sake!) that they allow their whole tech team to take every Friday afternoon… https://t.co/g2d2ruKQQa https://t.co/az9W41fTBR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Graduate Business Analyst: Graduate Business Analyst, Southampton – £21k (OTE of up to £29k!) An industry award-winning company are looking to grow their team in Leeds with the addition of talented graduates displaying great commercial acumen, ambition… https://t.co/qN97164SOh https://t.co/zp1vwwXlZb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plastic recycling firms accused of abusing market https://t.co/xCqdEQdklJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon says it will add 1,000 more employees in the UK, bringing the total to 28,500, bucking the Brexit chill: A lot of uncertainty hangs over the U.K. as it continues its slow march out of the European Union, but today one of the world’s biggest… https://t.co/lYXbUhOOYV https://t.co/bsIMJXPMPx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital Marketing Coordinator: Digital Marketing Coordinator Thames Valley Park, Reading Contract is until June 2019 initially Brook Street is currently working on behalf of our Global IT Client to recruit a Digital marketing Coordinator. This is a… https://t.co/NHScgSqjOv https://t.co/NRsub94pwM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PHP Developer – Quality Software, progressive tech: Work at one of the best known and most respected software houses in the area. – Diverse tech stack; PHP(7.2), MySQL, PHP MVC,  JavaScript (Vue/React), AWS. – Excellent career progression, challenging… https://t.co/JfLDDKGxaQ https://t.co/OjM8MioCbf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[eBay revs up to take on Auto Trader in car ads https://t.co/Op4CET1qYh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google improves Android App Bundles and makes building Instant Apps easier: Google is launching a number of new features for Android app developers today that will make it easier for them to build smaller apps that download faster and to release instant… https://t.co/FfDPjYTzru https://t.co/UOGvprre6R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/F0psJql2dR, VB6, Oracle, Oracle PL/SQL, https://t.co/sI32uNl3fA: Developer- C#, .Net, https://t.co/uMXTwwSh3n, VB6, Oracle, Oracle PL/SQL, https://t.co/sI32uNl3fA My client are a global software provider to the finance and insurance sectors.… https://t.co/vSi6rELOM2 https://t.co/hV6VPcBRp1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Persimmon boss refuses to answer questions about £75m bonus https://t.co/5TB4hr9rez]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Half of banks have closed to 13 million people https://t.co/E1sE2REnKT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft Dynamics CRM Developer – Guildford – £45k: Microsoft Dynamics CRM Developer – Guildford – £45k Role Overview An experienced Microsoft Dynamics Developer is required by a leading employer based in Guildford, Surrey. You can expect a salary of up… https://t.co/GIsZsJcEXL https://t.co/UVoIO0d64E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trainee Cyber Security: Trainee Cyber Security * Are you looking for an industry recognised online IT training solution that can lead to a permanent IT Cyber Security position with excellent earning potential? * Are you technically minded? * Do your… https://t.co/x6UGtMpOff https://t.co/8VF4HlprUD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China's third quarter growth misses expectations at 6.5% https://t.co/gz72iYbkcH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MoviePass is under investigation for securities fraud in New York state: More bad news for MoviePass. At the direction of New York Attorney General Barbara Underwood, MoviePass parent company Helios and Matheson is now the subject of a fraud probe in New… https://t.co/JgtrEYh4yM https://t.co/LqayBYp7K6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US economy under Trump: Is it the best in history? https://t.co/acAupE69s0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's the point of concept cars? https://t.co/8ZbBk0zSGo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Diesel and petrol ban should come much faster, say MPs https://t.co/9pz100AJPW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alexa’s new Whisper Mode goes live: At Amazon’s Alexa event last month in Seattle, the company teased a new feature soon coming to its voice assistant: the ability to whisper. The company demonstrated how whispering a request – like “play a lullaby” – to… https://t.co/ZBq9n1cZ4P https://t.co/klIabyhUqU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C++ Developer: C++ Developer Competitive Salary Cambridge This is an exclusive job opportunity for a Graduate or Junior C++ Software Developer to join a forward thinking, innovative, rapidly growing company in Cambridge. With offices in both Cambridge,… https://t.co/tyEzHHLW41 https://t.co/Mme4zWMtqq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Mansize' tissue to 'housewife' pillowcase https://t.co/JXT2S449Zu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Contract Front End Developer required, Glasgow: Supporting an innovative and expanding client with offices in south Glasgow, we are looking for a Front End Developer for an important re-development programme. The project will last for a minimum of 6… https://t.co/hgIcmebljT https://t.co/eYpXHlFqtd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager (IT &amp; Change) – Staffordshire: IT &amp; Change Project Manager – Stoke-on-Trent £40K + Benefits (initial 6 months Fixed Term) Talented Project Manager now required!! Initially for maternity leave cover, we now require a Project Manager for… https://t.co/kehM7bHX2Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why so many tech companies are creating shows: Editor’s note: Jay Acunzo is the author of the new book Break the Wheel, which explores how the world’s best creators break from conventional thinking to think for themselves. He’s a former digital media… https://t.co/2zjNmJ3y3C https://t.co/GmMTcwdsst]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Web Developer: Senior Web Developer (Thetford) Competitive salary Are you a PHP Developer looking to work for a market leader? If so we may have the role for you. My client is the UK’s largest service provider within their field, as well as also… https://t.co/Tv77OChUb1 https://t.co/XOaI7ISZNs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Call for social media adtech to be probed by UK competition watchdog: A British Conservative politician, who has called repeatedly for Mark Zuckerberg to come to parliament to answer questions about how Facebook fences fake news — only to be repeatedly… https://t.co/0tLucTH8Ej https://t.co/JXjm0sVtoW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Senior Software Developer (java) – Wellingborough – Salary to £50k plus bonus and package Java, linux, JBoss, spring My client is leading software house who are disrupting the ecommerce and retail sector. They are now looking to expand… https://t.co/jjYSNHgGzm https://t.co/6u5AElmuFT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ESA underpayment: Who is entitled to backdated benefits? https://t.co/ZobJIOv8mG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AWS Developer: AWS Developer – London – 12 months – Market Rates Currenty working alongside a leading energy company based in central London who are searching for an AWS Developer for an initial 12 months contract. You will be required to be onsite with… https://t.co/K4P5b9FIFJ https://t.co/g6C4WlrQAs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brexit: EU ready to extend transition period https://t.co/bCcD09eL1R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gillette partners with Formlabs to 3D print razor handles: 3D printing for manufacturing is one of those things that gets talked about a lot, but we’ve yet to see a lot of truly mainstream applications for the technology. A new partnership between… https://t.co/VvDBjLQ5qV https://t.co/4i1ubuhU7x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital Project Manager – London – 3 month contract – £350p/d: Digital Project Manager – London – 3 month contract – £350p/d Lynx is working with a dynamic and fast-growing digital business who deliver online solutions for a wide variety of clients… https://t.co/pEcV034XIh https://t.co/5tANVEdUSk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Developer: We are seeking a Database Developer to join a Software Solutions Specialist based near Harrow. You will be joining an experienced team of developers and will have the opportunity to work alongside experienced programmers and… https://t.co/D6BYzce4UB https://t.co/QLczxRHOxa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Name checks to begin on bank payments https://t.co/fOrDhKSmed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Development Manager – IT/Technical: Due to continuous expansion our client, a prestigious market leader within their industry is seeking a passionate, committed and tenacious high level Business Development/Sales Manager to join their team.… https://t.co/RwEGXUyKSL https://t.co/9SoFNtQCPy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Service Design and Transition Manager: We are looking for an Associate Service Design and Transition Manager in Newcastle who will be responsible for managing the smooth and effective IT Service Design, Transition and Implementation of business… https://t.co/h1ghFtBi8w https://t.co/xHniHRpyQF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kleenex bins 'Mansize' tissue brand https://t.co/V1QPCCN3OP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PHP Developer: PHP Developer (permanent) – Manchester – £25,000-£35,000 per annum For my prestigious client, I am looking for an experienced PHP Developer who is willing to constantly learn new technologies and join a compact team in fast-paced… https://t.co/0FNaV7l1NM https://t.co/9uudlmA3uK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Cloud (Azure) Architect: Our client is a FTSE 250 eCommerce Business whose award-winning digital channels generate revenues in excess of £750,000 during peak hours. Human Capital Ventures is acting as a preferred partner in the recruitment of a Lead… https://t.co/HMs1zoeVIq https://t.co/mIb9OO3g0L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Essential lays off nearly one-third of its staff: Layoffs are never an easy pill to swallow, but for Essential, it seems the writing was on the wall for a while with this one. After months of reports highlighting its struggles, the Andy Rubin-led… https://t.co/zm9JfhsMCy https://t.co/hsAjLyPd0E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should universal credit be paid weekly? https://t.co/Vr4JHk9dE7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst – FinTech – SQL, Tableau, Python: Data Analyst – FinTech – £45k + bonus &amp; benefits An exciting new opportunity for an enthusiastic and ambitious Data Analyst to work within the Data Science division of a fast-growing Financial Technology… https://t.co/ix9rxFKCTA https://t.co/NlmyFnP8bf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AV Engineer: iRecruit Specialist are working with a growing company who are seeing an additional person to join the field engineer team. This role will focus on AV installation and integration. This role will include installation, configuration, and… https://t.co/DSUmCPuYav https://t.co/W4A9B1UJ7w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Skully AR motorcycle helmet returns from the dead under new ownership: It’s been a long, bumpy road for the Skully augmented reality motorcycle helmet brand. But under the leadership of Ivan Contreras, who acquired the assets of Skully in 2017, the… https://t.co/bczlRiWWXJ https://t.co/MnVe0xqNU5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maintenance Supervisor (Electrical Bias) M/F: General information Entity Bouygues Energies &amp; Services operates in over 30 countries globally. Using the expertise of our 2,640 UK employees, we provide engineering and service capabilities committed to… https://t.co/bbt9OZEsxN https://t.co/NxLu7Ixxii]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cypriot budget airline Cobalt has suspended operations https://t.co/n8zAZUybsB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SpatialOS Software Engineer, Enterprise: SpatialOS Software Engineer, Enterprise London Engineering – Engineering Full-time Permanent Our Purpose Improbable is dedicated to building powerful technology designed to help solve previously impossible… https://t.co/9M9RqjfFAY https://t.co/2t6sIeGLMD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Postmates launches food delivery in 134 additional US cities: Homebodies across the U.S. have reason to celebrate. Postmates — the on-demand food delivery service so popular in major cities that it’s a verb now — just launched in 134 new markets. Those… https://t.co/G0pvFiKCap https://t.co/oDxgmkRI7W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer:   Job Description – Software Developer (27315) Job Description  Software Developer – 27315  Profession : Solution Development  Work Location : Europe-United Kingdom-London  Schedule :Full-time  Description   PURPOSE Engaged in the… https://t.co/FU5d0gncHI https://t.co/6M3zIhfsay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Presales Consultant – Identity Solutions – £80k OTE £100k: Presales Consultant – Identity Solutions – £80k OTE £100k * New management team with ambition * Real opportunity for growth * Respected solution within the ID and IT security industry Benefits of… https://t.co/SCTOM5kHSv https://t.co/zvLoavjkgb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EBay files lawsuit against Amazon over 'seller recruitment' https://t.co/2v9eju6sTD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump launches process to quit 144-year-old postal treaty https://t.co/TDeFxxna8b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Noor Inayat Khan or Harry Maguire: Who will be on the new £50 note? https://t.co/eDYspp9etm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Senior Java Software Engineer – (Java, J2ee, spring, spring boot) – Permanent – Reading – upto £70K + benefits Senior Java Software Engineer – (Java, J2ee, spring, spring boot) – Permanent – Reading – upto £70K + benefits My… https://t.co/34wcNEfvDB https://t.co/0XIqEvTwkR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla inks deal for Gigafactory 3 in China: Tesla has secured the rights to about 210 acres of land in Lingang, Shanghai, the site of the electric automaker's planned factory and its first outside of the U.S. https://t.co/k3Htrmch18 https://t.co/UGlFAFyZE9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WordPress Web Developer: Are you an experienced WordPress Web Developer based near Leicester? * An amazing and rare opportunity to join a well-established web development and digital marketing company An exciting opportunity exists for a talented… https://t.co/3Hye6Fy7F8 https://t.co/0ITEe86ecb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MIT researchers say memory splitting breakthrough could prevent another Meltdown or Spectre: Virtually every modern computer processor was thrown under the bus earlier this year when researchers found a fundamental design weakness in Intel, AMD and ARM… https://t.co/miNBirICoQ https://t.co/nnUwytVK7r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[eLearning Consultant: eLearning Consultant – Brighton – Permanent – up to £35k I'm working with a growing organisation based in Brighton. They are a part of a global team of open source technologists with offices in New Zealand, Australia and Europe.… https://t.co/Jn28qUZSNW https://t.co/we9RzEPYr2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lyft hires former United Airlines exec to lead market expansion: Lyft has brought on former United Airlines Chief Commercial Officer Julia Haywood to serve as its VP of Strategy. The plan is for her to own Lyft’s market expansion efforts and accelerate… https://t.co/Mq0M8lI4rk https://t.co/ymZy6cJDwp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[British farmers shouldn't get cheap EU labour - government adviser https://t.co/HWM2qSguN1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roku to resume sales in Mexico, following court ruling: Last year, Roku lost a legal battle in Mexico over piracy which resulted in a ban on sales of its devices in the country. Now, that ban has been lifted, the company says, following a favorable… https://t.co/pHb5Bc6lwq https://t.co/3zi4w1t8K4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Support Engineer – Virtualisation/Infrastructure: System Support Engineer – Virtualisation/Infrastructure A globally renowned company require a System Support Engineer to further develop their IT Infrastructure but also aid with providing support… https://t.co/9ZaGXShXag https://t.co/LL463kk00U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Infrastructure Engineer – Wintel, O365, Azure, Citrix: Are you an experienced 2nd/3rd Line Infrastructure Support Analyst? Do you have recent experience of supporting Microsoft technologies, virtualised servers, Azure and Office 365? If so Code… https://t.co/6fuvJ5YxqL https://t.co/l0tVotTrRn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WhiteSource nabs $35M to track open source code for security vulnerabilities: Open source software — a $14 billion market — has become a cornerstone for building apps and other IT services, with some 97 percent of developers today using using open source… https://t.co/UX6QVY2DLq https://t.co/HWjjC71Vk7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chinese firm fined $1.3bn for illegal production of rabies vaccine https://t.co/fePOVT3lNG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1ST/2ND Line Support Technician: 1st / 2nd Line Support Technician A market leading Software firm is looking for an IT Support Technician with great customer service experience to join the IT team providing 1st / 2nd Line support to customers. Good… https://t.co/lHLl5aI9Oz https://t.co/VYTnoMJvr9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where are house prices rising the fastest? https://t.co/AHG2rup6bI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infrastructure Analyst: Infrastructure Analyst – Caerphilly – DOE I am currently working with a very interesting company based in Caerphilly who due to continued growth have an exciting opportunity for an Infrastructure Analyst to join their thriving… https://t.co/PlaLwpNnNw https://t.co/xcPc9wKAfT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cheaper food drives UK inflation lower in September https://t.co/FBkmIfWyud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cognata raises $18.5M as race to deploy autonomous vehicles quickens: Cognata has raised $18.5 million in a funding round led by Scale Venture Partners, fresh capital that the Israeli autonomous simulation startup will use to meet demand for technology… https://t.co/Lo2SRLwspC https://t.co/1udKT1Lrbs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Net Developer – Manchester – £45,000: Net Developer – Manchester – £45,000 An amazing opportunity has arisen for a Full Stack .Net Developer to work on exciting new projects utilising the latest technology for a successful Manchester based business. This… https://t.co/z3m3CvXAnu https://t.co/Zce4iLwj9X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snr Software Developer – Java/.NET/Oracle PL/SQL – Edinburgh – Up to: Senior Software Developer – Java/.NET/Oracle PL/SQL – Edinburgh – Up to £50k Do you want the opportunity to be let loose to design and develop software solutions that will enhance the… https://t.co/peEgziGbKp https://t.co/JzFXehUbbu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infrastructure Engineer: INFRASTRUCTURE ENGINEER – MANCHESTER £23K-£35K + BENEFITS Talented Infrastructure Engineer now required!! Our client is an IT Managed solutions provider working with a range of clients in the North West. Due to recent promotions… https://t.co/DrNTmakD21 https://t.co/2aTZHNFVHy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Asos still in fashion as profits and sales keep soaring https://t.co/qbi5W85LYa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Samsung acquires network analytics startup Zhilabs to help its transition to 5G: Samsung Electronics is betting that acquiring Zhilabs, a real-time networks analytics startup based in Barcelona, will ease its transition from 4G to 5G technologies.… https://t.co/y9u5euYec5 https://t.co/hX7lhN7LzA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada becomes second country to legalise recreational marijuana https://t.co/SXTb6DqN08]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Digital / E-Commerce (Contract): Senior Project Manager – Digital Transformation (Daily Rate Contract) Duration : 6 – 12 Months Initially Daily Rates : €400 – €500 P/D DOE. My client, a global organisation located in Dublin are… https://t.co/mtP4lF5pCD https://t.co/CyGRnWLI9o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[APEX Developer 6 month contract: APEX Developer 6 month contract – full time (Potential to extend) Bromley, UK – 4 days onsite, 1 day remote £350-£400 per day Experience: Minimum 4 years Starting: ASAP VR/02405R The project need is to develop APEX… https://t.co/KrH6zlRQtA https://t.co/ewcJyikezh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 lessons from Marketo’s growth to a multi-billion-dollar exit: It’s hard for entrepreneurs to know the trade-offs required when making the tough decisions -- especially early on. Here are some suggestions. https://t.co/Ti6kIzuaII https://t.co/njcUWrHJMy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Research Analyst I, Powertrain Costing: Sr Research Analyst I, Powertrain Costing As a key member of the Cost to Compliance organization which is part of IHS Markit Powertrain and CO2 compliance team, the Fellow Cost Engineer will be responsible for… https://t.co/f8KJZwva6s https://t.co/mYfcGpIIKF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US plans trade deals with UK, Japan and EU https://t.co/Gh9YUuyeqY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Passport, a customer service company focused on shipping, has raised $3 million in seed funding from some notable names: Founders building a brand today are largely relying on new infrastructure to do it, though they’re still heavily reliant on legacy… https://t.co/YZ0cEoFo8S https://t.co/GADM3a9TFH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How California is changing the US https://t.co/b7oWp7HxkB]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>