<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to leave, you can. I'll remember you, though. I remember everyone who leaves. –Lilo (Lilo &amp; Stitch)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s a mistake not to give people a chance to learn to depend on themselves while they are young. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be there someday. I can go the distance. I will find my way if I can be strong. –Hercules]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have faith in your dreams and someday your rainbow will come smiling through. –Cinderella]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes the things that you’re looking for,  you can’t see with your eyes. You have to see them with your heart. –Peter Pan(Disney Dreams)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even miracles take a little time. –Fairy Godmother (Cinderella)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you walk the footsteps of a stranger, you'll learn things you never knew. –Pocahontas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will not lose faith. –Mushu (Mulan)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The dream is gone, but then there's hope. –Tarzan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One thing it takes to accomplish something is courage. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m sure I’ll get along somehow. Everything’s going to be alright. –Snow White]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you're curious, you find lots of interesting things to do. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dream’s made of magic, and music, and you. –Peter Pan (Disney Dreams)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can say goodbye and you can say hello, but you'll always find your way back home. –Hannah Montana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When something becomes difficult, I must stick with it and not look for an easy way out. –Aurora (Enchanted Tales)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who knows the right thing to say when I'm feeling so blue? –Piglet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Retweet if you wish your parents bought this for you&gt;&gt; http://t.co/cUduXQAebc sp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nani: “I shouldn't have yelled at you.” | Lilo: “We're sisters. It's our job.” –Lilo and Stitch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where do words go when they are not spoken? Are they hiding, shy or frightened, crying or smiling? –Book of Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The outside world is a dangerous place, filled with horrible, selfish people. –Mother Gothel (Tangled)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't undo what's been done. It's done. –Innoko (Brother Bear 2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being normal is vastly overrated. –Aggie (Halloweentown)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Retweet if you think these Celebs were the worst dressed at the Oscars!&gt;&gt; http://t.co/DmzLU1TYWN sp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it wrong to be loved, to face the future with another who means more than any other? –The Rescuers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any man who falls behind is left behind. –Jack Sparrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People do take love for granted. Sad but true. –Quasimodo (Hunchback of Notre Dame II)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's Mickey without Minnie, what's Piglet without Pooh, what's Donald without Daisy, that's me without you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The flower that blooms in adversity is the most rare and beautiful of all. –The Emperor (Mulan)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only thing predictable about life is its unpredictability. –Remy (Ratatouille)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only way to get what you want in this world is through hard work. –Tiana (Princess and the Frog)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things will look better in the morning. –Bagheera (The Jungle Book)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hercules: “How can I?” | Zeus: “Look inside your heart.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don’t want to grow up. –Wendy (Peter Pan)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anne: “When I grow up?” | Peter Pan: “That’s when you’ll need to remember your dreams the most.” –Disney Dreams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So this is the miracle that I've been dreaming of. So this is love. –Cinderella]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You got someone you think you know well. It  turns out a stranger. The minute you turn your back, you're in it all by  yourself. –Toy Story]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never look back, darling. It distracts from the now. –Edna Mode (The Incredibles)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you're true to who you are, you will always find your star. –Disney Fairies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I won't stop. For every minute of the rest of my life, I will fight. –Rapunzel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That’s a pie crust promise. Easily made, easily broken. –Mary Poppins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only rules that really matter are these: what a man can do and what a man can't do. –Jack Sparrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s okay to be afraid. –Mulan (Mulan II)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @hazelll3: before i die, i want to tell everyone the honest stories behind the real me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @hazelll3: damn i feel like shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @hazelll3: damn.. when nemo swims back to hug his dad, i get tears]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll know he's the one when he makes me laugh. –Minnie Mouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Close your eyes and pretend it’s all a bad dream. That’s how I get by. –Jack Sparrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Retweet if you remember these Disney Stars&gt;&gt; http://t.co/KbtpRT3abF #sp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes you try your hardest, but things don't work out the way you want them to. –Nani (Lilo &amp; Stitch)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After all, what are birthdays? Here today and gone tomorrow. Help yourself. –Eeyore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WOW if you haven't watched the The Purge movie trailer you should get on that!! #SurviveTheNight http://t.co/JiYrDRVEPC #sp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is the great lesson of 'Beauty and the Beast,' that a thing must be loved before it is lovable. –G.K. Chesterton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It'd be nice if someone would smile. It'd be a nice surprise to get flowers. But otherwise, it's not too bad being me. –Eeyore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I realized that I miss you and I need you. –Kermit (The Muppets)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perhaps, someday the dreams that I wish will come true. –Cinderella]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know it’s hard to keep the faith sometimes. –Lilo (Lilo &amp; Stitch 2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's okay to fight. Everybody fights now and then, especially best friends. But you got to make up fast. –Uncle Topolino (Cars 2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're dead if you aim only for kids. Adults are only kids grown up, anyway. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When life gets you down, you know what you gotta do? Just keep swimming, just keep swimming. –Dory (Finding Nemo)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who says you have to grow up? –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Retweet if you wish you were on a Disney Cruise RIGHT now http://t.co/RWPu80WMy0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Put your faith in what you most believe in. –Tarzan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is just a part of growing up. A little adventure, a little rebellion, that's good. Healthy, even. –Flynn Rider (Tangled)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My heart has wings and I can fly. I'll touch every star in the sky. So this is the miracle that I've been dreaming of. –Cinderella]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I do remember, and then when I try to remember, I forget. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you ever stop to think, and forget to start again? –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just don't see how a world that makes such wonderful things could be bad. –Ariel (Little Mermaid)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That’s the real trouble with the world, too many people grow up. They forget. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friends can be new, friends can be old. All of them are as precious as gold. –Roo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Piglet: “When you wake up in the morning, what's the first thing you say to yourself?" | Pooh: "What's for breakfast?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When there’s a smile in your heart, there’s no better time to start. –Peter Pan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is my reflection someone I don't know? Somehow I cannot hide who I am though I've tried. –Mulan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He'll never give up on you, ever. He'll be there for you, no matter what. –Andy (Toy Story 3)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If your nerves are raw and your brain is fried, just grab a friend and take a ride. –Goofy (A Goofy Movie)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing can go wrong if everything is right, and everything is right somehow. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So this is the miracle that I've been dreaming of. So this is love. –Cinderella]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must be imaginative, strong-hearted. You must try things that may not work. –Gusteau (Ratatouille)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you smile, it's pure perfection. It shines through everything you do. –Ariel (Little Mermaid Series)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When there's too much to do, don't let it bother you. Forget your troubles. –Snow White]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where one thing falls, another grows. Maybe not what was there before, but something new and wonderful all the same. –Bambi’s Mother]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s okay to be afraid. –Mulan (Mulan II)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I admire a person who's willing to do whatever's necessary. –Jack Sparrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dreams are like stars. You can't touch them, but if you follow them, they will lead you to your destiny. –Spudnick (Space Buddies)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't you know how you've changed me? Strange how I finally see. –Belle (Beauty and the Beast Broadway)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some things never change. –Mickey Mouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Retweet if you think these are the funniest Disney Quotes!&gt;&gt; http://t.co/t2UpbuJhtF #sp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alice: “This is impossible.” | The Mad Hatter: “Only if you believe it is.” –Alice in Wonderland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes the impossible can become possible if you're awesome. –Rhino (Bolt)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You got to put your past behind you. –Timon (The Lion King)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's special moments are tomorrow's memories. –Genie (The Return of Jafar)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have given so much happiness to others, that you deserve to have your wish come true. –The Blue Fairy (Pinocchio)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First of all, I would like to make one thing clear. I never explain anything. –Mary Poppins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the morning comes and the sun begins to rise, I will lose you because it's just a dream. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s a mistake not to give people a chance to learn to depend on themselves while they are young. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's important to have someone who loves you, no matter what. –Jasmine (Aladdin Series)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My love is higher than the sky, deeper than the ocean, warmer than the sun shining down on me, quiet as a prayer. –Ariel’s Beginning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most fantastic, magical things can happen, and it all starts with a wish. –Jiminy Cricket (Pinocchio)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don’t pay any attention to me. Nobody ever does. –Eeyore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything will be alright, because in a Prince’s arm, I’ve found a love I can’t deny. –Cinderella (Cinderella 3)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Without trust, there can be no relationship. –Mushu (Mulan II)]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>