<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[An exhausted Reince Preibus persuades President Trump that wealthy executives are ripe for a prank. A man in a yellow cloak gets lost at the zoo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a bender, Pete Sessions boldly informs Betsy DeVos that the McCains are victims of a misunderstanding. Eric Trump wears a cowboy hat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While watching Fox, Steven Mnuchin explains to President Trump that coal miners are in on the joke. Melania's bodyguard wrote this week's episode.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a prank, Rex Tillerson announces to Kellyanne Conway that Kremlin officials are tying up the phone lines. Trump's body double quotes Nietzsche.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As part of a bet, Rex Tillerson tries to persuade Melania that millennials are deserving of a tax cut. Scott Walker interviews the President.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the men's room, Sam Brownback confesses to Kellyanne Conway that Canadians are too turnt. President Bush hallucinates.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smiling serenely, Peter King reveals to Ben Carson that paleoconservatives are dangerous. Barry Goldwater's ghost records all conversations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On July 4th, Mark Sanford divulges to President Trump that Trump's sons are not reading Breitbart. Erick Erickson listens on the extension.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A panicked Mitch McConnell divulges to Ben Carson that Satanists are drains on public coffers. Hulk Hogan gets kicked out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a diner, Liz Cheney boldly informs President Trump that corporate executives are patriotic Americans. Tucker Carlson makes a prophecy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Without meaning to, Steven Mnuchin accidentally convinces President Trump that rappers are international bankers. A man in a yellow cloak picks a booger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Jerusalem, Rand Paul reveals to President Trump that the New England Patriots are big donors. Carl Higbie quotes Reagan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A weary Liz Cheney reluctantly admits to Kellyanne Conway that white women are true Americans. An ex-girlfriend hacks Trump's Twitter account.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Mar-a-Lago, Rick Snyder tries to convince President Trump that Trump's sons are excessively fastidious. Richard Spencer makes a racist joke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A delirious Louie Gohmert calmly tells Katrina Pierson that skeptics are lurking everywhere. Scottie Nell Hughes posts comments on Facebook.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In New York, Jared Kushner tries to convince Ben Carson that ATF agents are calling for impeachment. The maid confesses a longtime crush.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An exhausted Mitch McConnell explains to Jeff Sessions that black politicians are potential voters. Hulk Hogan quotes the Quran.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Monday, Jared Kushner tells Jeff Sessions that corporate executives are becoming too powerful. Stacey Dash joins the military.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In an elevator, Sean Spicer reveals to President Trump that Russian oil executives are up to no good. Cthulhu quotes Plato.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a press conference, Darrell Issa fails to convince President Trump that red state governors are hoarding Trump steaks. Victoria Jackson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Saturday, David Shulkin accidentally convinces Melania that liberal activists are still alive. Mike Tyson gets tackled by Secret Service.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a restaurant, Scott Pruitt carefully explains to Katrina Pierson that the backup dancers are patriotic Americans. Ann Coulter learns about memes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a photo op, Ivanka confesses to Katrina Pierson that rappers are indebted to Satan. George Will is caught stealing documents.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In front of the press, Mike Huckabee fails to convince Omarosa Manigault that Republicans are tormented by excessive regulations. A lovable old man]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During yoga, Liz Cheney convinces President Trump that prostitutes are digging holes in the yard. Scott Baio kisses a man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a meeting, Marco Rubio persuades Katrina Pierson that police officers are deserving of human rights. Milo Yiannopoulos has a meltdown.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bedraggled Reince Preibus calmly tells Betsy DeVos that Congressional pages are indebted to Satan. Charles Krauthammer finally takes a shower.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Via text message, Steve Bannon rudely informs Betsy DeVos that ATF agents are not really worth the time. Newt Gingrich goes to the circus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While soaking wet, Pete Sessions rudely informs President Trump that the IT guys are enlightened leaders. The butler finds a lost ring.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While lifting weights, Sean Spicer proclaims to Omarosa Manigault that skeptics are Schwarzenegger fans. Michelle Malkin ruins Christmas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Dallas, VP Pence accidentally convinces President Trump that corporate executives are just like the rest of us. Alex Jones walks into a spider web.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Monday, Justin Amash politely tells President Trump that ISIS soldiers are useful idiots. Glenn Beck hosts the clip show.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the hot tub, Mitch McConnell tells Jeff Sessions that the caterers are disciples of Cthulhu. Ivanka's bodyguard botches an important interview.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a diner, Darrell Issa calmly tells Jeff Sessions that wealthy executives are ready to negotiate. Michael Savage wears a fake mustache.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A polite Jared Kushner tells President Trump that Nordstroms employees are unusually angry this week. Dana Perino throws a dildo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During Christmas, Roger Stone insists to Ben Carson that NBC reporters are boycotting Ivanka's products. Kayleigh McEnany takes candy from a baby.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a press conference, Darrell Issa decides not to tell Betsy DeVos that Mormons are traitors. An obsequious reporter dresses in drag.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With clenched fists, Rick Snyder proclaims to Katrina Pierson that Russian agents are in covert ops. Trump's bodyguard leaks state secrets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During Festivus, Darrell Issa overhears someone tell Betsy DeVos that wealthy executives are not good with computers. James Caan quotes the Quran.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Los Angeles, Lindsey Graham explains to Jeff Sessions that civil rights activists are organizing resistance. An adorable orphan goes shopping.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the power goes out, Lindsey Graham decides not to tell Melania that AARP members are selling land in National Parks. The sommelier quotes Mussolini.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a joke, Rick Scott reluctantly explains to Betsy DeVos that Alaskans are not really worth the time. Rush Limbaugh learns to fly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the basement, Rick Scott tries to persuade President Trump that convicts are on point. Erick Erickson joins a cult.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An exhausted Justin Amash admits to President Trump that the kids are extremely wealthy. Willie Robertson can't follow directions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a lost episode, Elaine Chao persuades President Trump that Cubans are ignorant hayseeds. Milo Yiannopoulos harasses celebrities.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While sharing a cab, Lindsey Graham mistakenly tells Katrina Pierson that leftist college students are supporters of Brexit. Peter Thiel learns how to love.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An angry David Shulkin carefully explains to Jeff Sessions that Russian spies are pro-Trump. Trump's bodyguard makes fun of a handicapped child.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shivering uncontrollably, Ted Cruz mistakenly tells Melania that conspiracy theorists are not really important. A White House tourist tries BDSM.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Moscow, Rick Santorum insists to Melania that North Koreans are not good with computers. Kayleigh McEnany runs for office.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A grinning Jared Kushner divulges to Katrina Pierson that virgins are still waiting on hold. An adorable orphan pulls a muscle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A time-traveling Lindsey Graham announces to Jeff Sessions that civil rights activists are untrustworthy. President Bush dresses in drag.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a confusing mixup, Paul LePage politely tells Rick Perry that the in-laws are no threat at all. Newt Gingrich goes into mourning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While on vacation, Paul LePage insists to President Trump that phone companies are harmless. A lovable old man wears a fake mustache.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In front of tourists, Pete Sessions persuades President Trump that Pussy Riot are not really worth the time. Victoria Jackson launches a new product line.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before breakfast, Scott Pruitt tries to persuade Kellyanne Conway that Russian oil executives are pro-Trump. An ex-girlfriend watches Netflix.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After a sleepless night, Scott Pruitt convinces Kellyanne Conway that prisoners are too turnt. Melania's bodyguard gets tackled by Secret Service.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Trump Tower, Kevin McCarthy confesses to Katrina Pierson that neoconservatives are not watching Fox News. A local TV anchor quotes Naomi Wolf.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A panicked Mike Huckabee fails to convince Rick Perry that rural youth are filing frivolous lawsuits. Cthulhu collects a welfare check.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While drunk, Scott Pruitt decides not to tell Katrina Pierson that ACLU lawyers are carrying concealed weapons. Bill Kristol listens on the extension.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a bonus episode, Rick Snyder tries to convince Katrina Pierson that cult leaders are not returning phone calls. A corporate lobbyist develops an addiction.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A tense Paul Ryan explains to President Trump that Communists are dropping big hints. Sean Hannity hallucinates.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A time-traveling Matt Bevin admits to President Trump that rappers are not returning phone calls. A corporate lobbyist develops a twitch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While flirting, Kevin McCarthy fails to convince Katrina Pierson that leftist college students are heavily armed. Mike Tyson tries yoga.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Darrell Issa fails to persuade Melania that Biggie and Tupac are extremely wealthy. Trump Junior hires an assassin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While skinny-dipping, Jared Kushner informs President Trump that white women are astonishingly successful. Victoria Jackson works the room.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A time-traveling Nikki Haley calmly tells President Trump that Syrian refugees are big fans. Bobby Jindal goes into mourning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Sunday, Lindsey Graham accidentally convinces Rick Perry that the IT guys are potential voters. Corey Lewandowski wins the lottery.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An incensed Paul LePage carefully explains to Melania that ACLU members are jealous of Trump. Dana Perino joins a sex club.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Sept. 11th, Ivanka calmly tells President Trump that international bankers are tying up the phone lines. Ivanka's bodyguard tweets compulsively.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A terminally ill Jared Kushner mistakenly tells Rick Perry that union members are special guests. Dana Perino normalizes fascism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During Christmas, Lamar Smith tells President Trump that the hired help are withdrawing support. Corey Lewandowski knits a lovely hat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Camp David, General Mattis boldly informs Betsy DeVos that the Obamas are infiltrators. A local TV anchor has a vision.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A polite Jared Kushner fails to convince President Trump that Presbyterians are trying to make ends meet. Barry Goldwater's ghost stalks the neighbor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a press conference, Ivanka boldly informs Betsy DeVos that Trump's sons are terrorists. A local TV anchor has jury duty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a photo op, Mitch McConnell calmly tells President Trump that those girls are total losers. A local TV anchor bids farewell.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On live TV, Louie Gohmert overhears someone tell Omarosa Manigault that cult leaders are not very affluent. Don King ruins Christmas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During church, Jared Kushner accidentally convinces Omarosa Manigault that most voters are not very smart. Michael Savage violates a trade agreement.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breathlessly, Peter King admits to President Trump that KGB spies are standing in the kitchen. Eric Trump donates three dollars.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a roomful of children, Jared Kushner carefully explains to Katrina Pierson that Tumblr users are really good at dancing. Hulk Hogan gives a Roman salute.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During Christmas, Sean Spicer accidentally convinces President Trump that the New Black Panthers are double agents. An ambassador learns what love is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over coffee, Jason Chaffetz boldly informs Betsy DeVos that Muslims are not good with computers. A corporate lobbyist pretends to be blind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Easter, Liz Cheney announces to President Trump that atheists are big fans. A "fixer" pukes in Trump's lap.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over hors d'oeuvres, Pete Sessions politely tells Rick Perry that Apple and Microsoft are not real. David Brooks learns to cook.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a press conference, Carly Fiorina tries to convince President Trump that prison guards are releasing Trump's tax returns. Ann Coulter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During church, Steve Bannon divulges to Melania that KGB spies are actually gay. The valet quotes Scripture.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A grinning Matt Bevin tells Betsy DeVos that poets are headed to prison. Bill Kristol is caught stealing documents.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Late at night, Reince Preibus reluctantly explains to President Trump that their Twitter followers are probably contagious. Michael Savage eats the entire cake.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During yoga, Mark Sanford insists to President Trump that liberal activists are ignorant hayseeds. Trump's bodyguard compulsively shoplifts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With clenched fists, Jason Chaffetz carefully explains to Betsy DeVos that government employees are buying up Trump properties. Hulk Hogan learns to sew.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Los Angeles, Liz Cheney calmly tells Ben Carson that wealthy executives are capable bureaucrats. Sean Hannity talks awkwardly about sex.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a panic, Ryan Zinke fails to persuade President Trump that Amway executives are excellent chefs. A White House tourist greets visitors.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While drunk, Lindsey Graham tries to persuade President Trump that Somalian immigrants are organizing resistance. Larry the Cable Guy wears a hoodie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Tuesday, Elaine Chao rudely informs Ben Carson that Republicans are withering under excessive regulations. Newt Gingrich watches Netflix.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After a long meeting, Stephen Miller patiently explains to Kellyanne Conway that black politicians are coming for dinner. Adam Sandler unleashes a virus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bedridden Sean Spicer tells Katrina Pierson that liberal activists are drains on public coffers. Chris Christie interviews the President.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After a long meeting, Jared Kushner tells Rick Perry that angry parents are total winners. James Caan kneels before a new master.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A leering Nikki Haley insists to Jeff Sessions that bisexuals are alcoholics. Barry Goldwater's ghost bids farewell.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a joke, Roger Stone persuades President Trump that Cubans are always strapped. Michelle Malkin goes vegetarian.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In front of the press, Roger Stone persuades Betsy DeVos that conspiracy theorists are faithful conservatives. A lovable old man slides down the bannister.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After the two argue, Jared Kushner divulges to Betsy DeVos that the interns are capable of great things. A corporate lobbyist works the room.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>