<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LarrereMathilde: Il y a 147 ans

Débutait......

LA COMMUNE DE PARIS!!!!!!!!!! https://t.co/ertT8Z5y6b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@DianaEvansOP makes the case for Updike https://t.co/LBOITWy7Wt https://t.co/wO6YUFskep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meet the Brexit negotiators: David Davis and Michel Barnier  https://t.co/zibKf6Wpr0 https://t.co/7qRtsRJ12V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@ftproperty runs the rule over my manor https://t.co/BDLUjhyl6i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't normally do this. But hugely proud of son &amp; his friends (Year 10) for sticking up for beleaguered year 7 &amp; going to his birthday party]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@DulwichHamletFC fans and friends send a message to Meadow https://t.co/61PnbTqwxv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KCMANC @DulwichHamletFC Probably. You going?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big turnout for the Save @DulwichHamletFC rally in East Dulwich https://t.co/qshp6zZMvH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's the best of the @FinancialTimes' comment and opinion this week on Russia, Putin and the Skripal affair https://t.co/A4SNhm2BHr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@helenbarrett @emmavj Lovely. We bought that one in Crystal Palace, by the way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@helenbarrett @emmavj We have one more #kitchelfie https://t.co/k1z1y79kd3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@emmavj I think we've created a new Twitter genre! That's great, by the way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This example of the genre adorns our kitchen wall https://t.co/WFQIyPLCBU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Nous sommes tous indésirables" : the visual art of May '68 https://t.co/pQDwtBV8MA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lucbronner: Edgar Morin, Paul Ricœur, Raymond Aron, Alain Touraine... ce qu’ils ont écrit à chaud sur Mai 68 https://t.co/O7aHt8R6nN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lovely piece by our much-missed colleague @grimes_ce on vinyl-hunting (and sushi) in Tokyo https://t.co/hRo4nzoYS2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ChrisGiles_: You might think  - what with Brexit - taking control was in vogue

But Philip Hammond this week put these three lads in ch…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This by @anjahuja on how Hawking pushed physics to the limits and the research programme he left behind is excellent https://t.co/nD8IJ6pxWt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnCassidy @gideonrachman @Robert___Harris Not sure the cases are analogous. Russell hadn't done any original work in philosophy for 50-odd years by the time he died.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My colleagues on the @FinancialTimes Big Read created a Spotify playlist to accompany their piece on the streaming service https://t.co/XIKqF2P5WC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@johngapper imagines the Goldman succession as resembling the contest between Jacob and Esau  https://t.co/vdWtIRMfpW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PressAwardsuk: The FT's win of Newspaper of the Year at #PressAwards was down to boldness and 'not just Brexit' says @lionelbarber Edit…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SpiegelPeter: Award number 3 for @FT at #PressAwards: Sue Mattias accepts news team award for #Europopulists series https://t.co/sdJDSk…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one can be a pioneer twice - @KuperSimon on Arsène Wenger https://t.co/1UZRLF36Pc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good from @bronwenmaddox on Windrush, the Home Office and nonsensical immigration targets https://t.co/W5SHGAXIfM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Abdulrazak Gurnah on the Windrush saga and "Britain’s centuries-long prevarication between sanctuary and xenophobia" https://t.co/JBIZyrqShV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nytimesbooks: 4/19/1941: "I cannot go on any longer in these terrible times," Virginia Woolf wrote her husband in a farewell note https…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delighted to see FT Big Picture rocketing up the iTunes podcast chart https://t.co/uJhGpvhBNU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brexit is a disaster, but a second referendum would tear the country apart, says @martinwolf_ https://t.co/OLB8CubiYo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Rebeccamead_NYC: Peekah is still missing. Thanks for all the kind words, advice, and the RTs. https://t.co/ldG4kRCR9x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, @katie_martin_fx, what have you done? https://t.co/M37jFSdgaW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This by @KuperSimon is excellent on the misconception that Macron wants to make France more "Anglo-Saxon" https://t.co/4fE0yVXwhd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SebastianEPayne: Spot something different in your @FinancialTimes today? Our Comment page has been renamed Opinion and we’ve dropped “S…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TrineeshB: Great start to FT’s new ‘Big Picture’ podcast. Martin Wolf looks at western democracies’ struggles with globalisation &amp; tech…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to write an op-ed for the @FinancialTimes? Here's what we're looking for https://t.co/YwQVtFj4dF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@philipstephens on Emmanuel Macron and the spirit of 1968  https://t.co/WtOAKagt4O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @brookeamasters: Itching to write for the FT? Read our new guide. https://t.co/QrIcltSFHg via @financialtimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give land to the landless: @davidpilling makes the case for thoroughgoing land reform in South Africa https://t.co/YZBBJQt7BN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feeling's Linton Kwesi Johnson's "Sonny's Lettah" very keenly on my commute this morning https://t.co/VVvzit80Z3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JamesDMorris: Lucky to have worked a tiny bit with @RuthSmeeth who embodies exactly what any sensible person would want in an MP. Abuse…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JackPittBrooke Les Herbiers have done pretty well, too https://t.co/y3pj9BnPD3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pulitzer Prize winners, 2007 and 2018 https://t.co/HwS8kVZDQY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@valeria_wants Yes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't sleep after reading John Seabook's piece about black ice https://t.co/dKDtNtNfPD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TrineeshB @sarahoconnor_ @martinwolf_ Thank you! I hope you're not disappointed!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kendrick Lamar, Pulitzer Prize winner https://t.co/TJ2ttRk1aB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you enjoyed @martinwolf_ on the crisis of democratic capitalism, then look out for episode 2 of FT Big Picture, out on Monday April 23: @sarahoconnor_ on the changing world of work https://t.co/RjQsfqdQuX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating column by @johnthornhillft on how attitudes in Asia towards robots differ dramatically from those in the west https://t.co/LLXvmjrrse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The scandal of the Windrush cases doesn't augur well for attempts to settle the status of EU citizens in the UK, argues @sundersays https://t.co/5S7Y6knsSg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@ChassNews on last night's Bourdin and Plenel show  https://t.co/9R1EDZesBk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ftcomment: Podcast: Join Martin Wolf as he explores the crisis of democratic capitalism https://t.co/xKsgzEfAv5 https://t.co/AmuYEgG5dg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnmcternan Indeed!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnmcternan Does Callaghan count? He had *been* home secretary, though was at the Foreign Office when he succeeded Wilson as PM.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SebastianEPayne: 🎉 New @FinancialTimes podcast! 🎉

The Big Picture: @Jderbyshire examines the policy challenges of 21st century with ou…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first episode of FT Big Picture - a new podcast from the @FinancialTimes - is out today: Martin Wolf on the crisis of democratic capitalism https://t.co/85WrG2KFax]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bourdin is a disgrace. There are hard questions to be asked of Macron. But he's too high on his own supply to ask them #macronbfmediapart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AgnesCPoirier He's better in this set-up than Bourdin, whose self-righteous sonority is unbearable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SebastianEPayne Says US, UK and France have succeeded in dividing Turkey and Russia on Syria and chemical weapons. Now doing tax evasion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@edwyplenel is a much more effective interrogator.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Macron is going to keep this up for two hours - despite the self-admiring interruptions of Jean-Jacques Bourdin https://t.co/Z7Ot84hIgn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seconds out! Macron v Bourdin and Plenel https://t.co/5gpKgSh6BZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lobs: #MacronBFMTV Au Théâtre national de Chaillot ce soir, le président de la République affronte deux journalistes qui ont juré sa pe…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pep Guardiola and English anti-intellectualism - very good piece by @JackPittBrooke https://t.co/1i0IuH2qpW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to Fabian Delph for giving his shirt to my son at the end of tonight's game https://t.co/kfQnKmAI2q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @philosophybites: The elusive self: @Jderbyshire on Galen Strawson’s new book of essays @FT  https://t.co/3zsyOjTTRr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@soratcli It's a wonderful collection.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@djmgaffneyw4 No!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_paullay Exactly!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't believe I've only just made acquaintance with this record https://t.co/CNKRsfPkwC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sundersays: Its been good to see the breadth of support on this issue. It is clear many on left/centre/right &amp; remain/leave have exactl…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lacking deep familiarity with the US legal system, I don't know what a "special master" is, but it sounds fishy https://t.co/OEKGsRDaQa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I reviewed Galen Strawson's very entertaining collection of essays about selfhood, free will and the philosophy of mind https://t.co/gfviqL5xQl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Resistance to Macron's eurozone reform agenda is crystallising in Berlin, says @TonyBarber8 https://t.co/3xlBhtl8G7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@harikunzru Or indeed Victoria Park, April 30, 1978 https://t.co/2qSIrOGtRo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@johnmcternan wrote a good piece about the legacy of Powell (and Benn) for @ftcomment a few months ago https://t.co/TfF5N0ITpG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KateMaltby @FinancialTimes Thanks, Kate. Hope you enjoy it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big Picture, a new podcast from the @FinancialTimes, launches on Monday
 https://t.co/ntXqKWkt3U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adam_tooze My pleasure. It looks splendid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonderful book post to return to @adam_tooze https://t.co/ocENpmpULw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Macron's encounter with Edwy Plenel and others on Sunday will be worth watching. Two hours on his first year. https://t.co/ZqeDdnRU9H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_paullay Well, quite.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Didn't have Varoufakis down as a prog fan. Thought he'd be Second Viennese School, Stockhausen and Boulez. https://t.co/9U6HtTh6xf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be read alongside Philip Roth's Zuckerman novels, obviously. Hadn't realised scale &amp; relative lateness of black migration from the South.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reading New Jersey gov's report into 1967 Newark riot - remarkable analysis of death &amp; life of great American cities https://t.co/wzqcgw523f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ChassNews: I could have beaten Emmanuel Macron, says Hollande who published a book criticizing policies that are deepening inequalities…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poem for today https://t.co/SHQ3nVG1rX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The past is another country: @IPR_NickP on fantasies of the Anglosphere https://t.co/OnuZY16CZi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sferg100 @nick_sidi Listened to it last night. Fab.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peter Navarro fires a salvo in the US-China trade war for @ftcomment https://t.co/x05vu4lhFu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever wondered why Britain sold off the railways? @greenmiranda tries to find out in this excellent film https://t.co/AoPhlexyE9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Politics intrudes into James Wood's novel more as a draught than a gunshot. Dazzling essay by Thomas Meaney https://t.co/jYp0Pz6QuL…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Splendid @JasonCowleyNS interview with the great Bryan Magee https://t.co/odZmpTW5YI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This looks very good https://t.co/5SA334iFKh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RenaudDely: Le compte à suivre absolument pour tout comprendre du nouveau mai 68 étudiant qui se prépare....😉 https://t.co/gSD5kET9zf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An exhibition of the photographs of Derek Parfit opening in London on May 11 https://t.co/SDV9bkEtmN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of my favourite Cecil Taylor dates - with Coltrane and Kenny Dorham, October 1958 https://t.co/Szgvrp3k5m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JBenguigui: Le 6 Avril 1944 les enfants juifs d’Izieu raflés puis déportes  a Auchwitz par Klaus Barbie ne les oublions JAMAIS ! https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonderful piece on the greatness of Pep Guardiola by @RorySmith  https://t.co/EM5wujna3a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Billions is preposterous but irresistible. Especially when Taylor instructs traders at Axe Capital to fulfill their "teleological purpose".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tianran: Anthony Scaramucci on Bannon and back-stabbing in DC https://t.co/Eey14iemlN blimey @EdwardGLuce is rarely without words but t…]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>