<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Software Engineer II (JSE)| Detroit MI| 1 Year| Position- 1: Enterprise Software Engineer II 1. Major Duties and Responsibilities a. Define, design, build, test, deploy, and support software products b. Consistently follow the specified… https://t.co/Ufj2iKHDBt https://t.co/T0TFYKK2Ch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Zuckerberg Will Testify Before Congress on Cambridge Scandal: Facebook CEO will answer questions about the company's privacy practices and the use of its data. https://t.co/duyi6QgG79 https://t.co/eBii5p8IgN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Script and HTML5 Front End Developer|Detroit MI| Positions – 1: Participate in and lead requirements analysis, specifications and design of custom-developed applications. Assist in the development of implementation/rollout plans. Ensure that… https://t.co/RRA7c1pz18 https://t.co/Sj4nTj9u8k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: ACTRON SYSTEMS – Markets – Access Control – CCTV Systems – Government Sales – Electronic Monitoring – Intrusion Alarms – Virtual Presence – Clients – About – Management Team – Careers – Contact – 1-************ – ************ –… https://t.co/fb3f6tTSgf https://t.co/GzUG4y4A5t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT/Cable Technician (100% Nationwide – Great Pay): JOB TITLE: Level 2: Lead Cable / Hardware Installation Technician Level 3: Certified Lead Cable / Hardware Installation, Telco and Troubleshooting Technician SUMMARY BY LEVEL: Level 2: Leads and manages… https://t.co/mBc62YlPZh https://t.co/6BFvnc15X0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kiddie YouTube: Companies Are Cashing in on Reality TV for Tots: While the strategy carries risks, if it pans out, you could soon see more kids in their own Netflix series or on smartphone apps—or wherever kids are. https://t.co/UGdcQoT8jI https://t.co/uGvWK1kiGr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UI Designer .: Were looking for an experienced visual designer/user interface designer for our office in Detroit. ABOUT THE POSITION Your heart beats fast whether you are perfectly positioning a tiny pixel or helping create the next generation of digital… https://t.co/6kRvvo7KbV https://t.co/8P5AmXJDqF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Installation Technician (Detroit Lakes, MN): Detroit Lakes, MN, USAHourlyFull Time Inside Out provides competitive compensation, health insurance, PTO, and retirement benefits! Inside Out is an installation contracting company headquartered in Detroit… https://t.co/FFzLLKkJaT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Cloud Infrastructure Automation Lead: 3046693 Senior Cloud Infrastructure Automation Lead Oil &amp; Gas Headquarters GE Oil &amp; Gas United States Provide IT leadership on multiple automation build projects. Help prioritize and drive results for the… https://t.co/ZSoFHqWyeO https://t.co/crPdRzKyr7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OnSite iOS Developer: Detroit Labs OnSite is looking an iOS Developer to join one of our projects in downtown Detroit. This role is with our OnSite business unit; successful applicants will be working at the client location in Detroit. This team member… https://t.co/MemyVVmCCr https://t.co/s3uWdhvJd7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rant: No, a $38 Water Bottle Can't Turn You Into a #Brave #Boss: There’s no mundanity safe from the impulses of millennial-hungry startups catering to their favorite demographic. https://t.co/rqOeYK5Jq6 https://t.co/XbmHpy5QTh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Quality Analyst III| Detroit MI| 10 Months| Positions-1: Test Case Authoring: Develop detailed Test Cases based on the Functional Requirements and Design Documents. Execute the Test Cases and Analyze the Test Results. Usage of test tools as ALM… https://t.co/awKJCRAqdr https://t.co/2lylm0uJOB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill Hader aims higher with HBO's 'Barry': "Barry" invites comparisons to "Get Shorty," focusing as it does on a hit man who's suddenly and somewhat inexplicably bitten by the acting bug. But this HBO series from Bill Hader and "Silicon Valley's" Alec… https://t.co/FLi8WxjgvP https://t.co/dtNww6V6DC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infotainment Application Software Engineer – Android|Detroit MI|10 Months | Positions-3: QUALIFICATIONS REQUIRED: BS in Computer Science or other field of study along with applicable work experience Experience with Android UI design (including custom… https://t.co/6gO4uSQl8b https://t.co/G6cqi3up02]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front End Developer (Mobile Device) |Detroit MI|1 Year| Positions- 3: JOB SUMMARY Responsible for front-end design and development at the product application layers. Requires a good understanding of programming web based applications in order to meet… https://t.co/PhEhipXWvq https://t.co/Sq0dai3ce7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle Financial consultant: Title: Oracle Financial consultant Type of Employment: Direct Hire/Permanent Job Description: An experienced consulting professional who has a broad understanding of solutions, industry best practices, multiple business… https://t.co/2WjGfnwiNn https://t.co/Zu7kn5THfZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Global Value Chain Engineer: # of Openings 1 Job Locations US-MI-DetroitPosted Date 12 hours ago Category Sales Overview The GVCE achieves material- and part-approvals. He/she drives key projects in close teamwork with the local tesa-KAMs and the global… https://t.co/dPoISrJFF0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager: Job Details (*Employee Referral Program applies to this job) Job No. PM00001 Job Title Senior Project Manager Description Summary: Position Description: AD – Deployment manager will coordinate with hardware installers, network… https://t.co/nYl9fzvBxP https://t.co/6FY1Bkn7Yp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Software Engineer II (JSE)| Detroit MI| 1 Year| Position- 1: Enterprise Software Engineer II 1. Major Duties and Responsibilities a. Define, design, build, test, deploy, and support software products b. Consistently follow the specified… https://t.co/2BWu8H6zeC https://t.co/Cr22zoeBLP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .Net Developer: Senior .Net Developer Senior .Net Developer Company Autobooks Location US-MI-Detroit Opportunity Details What You’ll Do/Need Within this role at Autobooks you will be a senior participant in the design and development of… https://t.co/egeB66aQaz https://t.co/tDm12uCmhB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Solution Architect: Cloud Solution Architect Microsoft envisions a world where passionate innovators come to collaborate, envisioning what can be and taking their careers places they simply couldn’t anywhere else. This is a world of more… https://t.co/PpJz4c9aKD https://t.co/UHv1a4B2Ko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OnSite iOS Developer: Detroit Labs OnSite is looking an iOS Developer to join one of our projects in downtown Detroit. This role is with our OnSite business unit; successful applicants will be working at the client location in Detroit. This team member… https://t.co/l8jc49RQY6 https://t.co/u8TqOYhvBt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[General Labor – Construction: Detroit Lakes, MN, USAFull Time Arvig seeks General Laborers who want to make a difference, grow their future, and have fun in the process AND who want competitive pay ($16.50/hr to start), overtime potential, multiple pay… https://t.co/PC2bZKUmqM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infotainment Application Software Engineer – Android|Detroit MI|10 Months | Positions-3: QUALIFICATIONS REQUIRED: BS in Computer Science or other field of study along with applicable work experience Experience with Android UI design (including custom… https://t.co/8mOitSjFgD https://t.co/W0yHEQ9F8J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT/Cable Technician (100% Travel – Nationwide): JOB TITLE: Level 2: Lead Cable / Hardware Installation Technician Level 3: Certified Lead Cable / Hardware Installation, Telco and Troubleshooting Technician SUMMARY BY LEVEL: Level 2: Leads and manages a… https://t.co/8hfpADJ8TB https://t.co/TEdNzkr5WS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Primary Skills JAVA,JAVASCRIPT,IBM ISIM,IBM TFIM Development Overview PROLIM Global Corporation (**************) is currently seeking Java Developer for location Detroit , MI for one of our Top client. Job Description: IT… https://t.co/5s6WV2rM26 https://t.co/ElFhEXTGpb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT/Cable Technician (100% Nationwide – Great Pay): JOB TITLE: Level 2: Lead Cable / Hardware Installation Technician Level 3: Certified Lead Cable / Hardware Installation, Telco and Troubleshooting Technician SUMMARY BY LEVEL: Level 2: Leads and manages… https://t.co/4HkAGntZ0m https://t.co/HE5Me0GaYI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 classic journeys from 'The Golden Age of Travel' https://t.co/0FFPicxlWW https://t.co/D9y5c5v7N8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager (IT Security)- PMP: Project Manager (Security)- PMP Location: Detroit, MI Interview Mode: In-person preferred after telephonic round Project Duration: 12+ months * 10+ Years in project management or involvement on projects * Client needs… https://t.co/dr7SfmxNLr https://t.co/FhxwBRe8mm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Quality Analyst III| Detroit MI| 10 Months| Positions-1: Test Case Authoring: Develop detailed Test Cases based on the Functional Requirements and Design Documents. Execute the Test Cases and Analyze the Test Results. Usage of test tools as ALM… https://t.co/AUoXuxPfzU https://t.co/HPmceKBzC0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Installation Technician (Detroit Lakes, MN): Detroit Lakes, MN, USAHourlyFull Time Inside Out provides competitive compensation, health insurance, PTO, and retirement benefits! Inside Out is an installation contracting company headquartered in Detroit… https://t.co/DSrN8ZCMtk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Project Manager Ref No.: 18-10731 Location: Detroit, Michigan Role : Project Manager Duration : 12 Months Location : Detroit, MI Job Description : Experience in legacy to SAP rolloutsData Migration End user testing,integration test… https://t.co/pUtS5HM5sF https://t.co/VYd1jcSxQD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Software Engineer – Automotive: Ready to turn the wheel in the _AUTOMOTIVE _industry with a _HYPERGROWTH STARTUP_? MULTINATIONAL AUTOMOTIVE MANUFACTURER has already established connected car technologies abroad and are on the verge of the biggest… https://t.co/WGCc4MUQqX https://t.co/dhHsqOPAqn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The FTC Is Officially Investigating Facebook's Data Practices: The Federal Trade Commission's probe comes on the heels of the Cambridge Analytica scandal, in which 50 million Americans' Facebook data was reportedly improperly retained by the data firm. https://t.co/pmCHRuXKpO https://t.co/ARFHMavcjF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Devops Engineer: Job Overview: Provide end-to-end DevOps solution by employing the most appropriate tools for CI/CD set up, continuous feedback, continuous monitoring, continuous planning, and continuous testing. Responsibilities: * Consult to provide… https://t.co/ImK4RJEu3p https://t.co/qnExbDrlbO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering Project Manager: Job Description We are AAM. We have the POWER to move the world. At AAM, we’re looking for associates who push boundaries and drive solutions for the future. Innovators. Thinkers. Dreamers. Doers. No matter the role or… https://t.co/2SiL0yo0Oq https://t.co/KZFHL9CiLA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps/ Platform Engineer: DevOps/ Platform Engineer is focused on: * Retail, Operating Systems, systems hardening, Virtualization and Automation. * 4 or more years of Linux or Windows systems administration experience. * Experience with modern… https://t.co/LIBIUU8qzD https://t.co/cdOjQu7rj4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Brooklyn Architect Wants to Rewire Puerto Rico with Solar: Architect Jonathan Marvel is building solar arrays to serve community centers, and soon, he hopes, communities. https://t.co/KdLveqPBim https://t.co/tPZEAC9C3N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Software Engineer II| 118640| Detroit MI| 1 year| position -1: ENTERPRISE SOFTWARE ENGINEER II 1. Major Duties and Responsibilities a. Define, design, build, test, deploy, and support software products b. Consistently follow the specified… https://t.co/4wsGGYDAma https://t.co/IB6fChiISQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Key Account Manager OEM / OES: # of Openings 1 Job Locations US-MI-DetroitPosted Date 1 hour ago Category Sales Overview The Key Account Manager (KAM) is the owner of and the expert for the assigned Automotive Tier 1 Suppliers and their value chain… https://t.co/eRhcRhnHnU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front End Developer (Mobile Device) |Detroit MI|1 Year| Positions- 3: JOB SUMMARY Responsible for front-end design and development at the product application layers. Requires a good understanding of programming web based applications in order to meet… https://t.co/wY7SKthomn https://t.co/khNFTG8vR0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid to Senior Software Engineer – React: At Sift we take a consumer approach to B2B software: emphasizing understanding of the user experience and building beautiful and easy to use software that delights our clients. Were looking for a talented engineer… https://t.co/sfIEnqWh1D https://t.co/tTFPJLvHC4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Some Schools Pay More Than Others When Buying From Apple: Administrators face tough restrictions from Apple and often don't share data, leaving them in the dark when they go to buy computers and software. https://t.co/cN6hWrGkXU https://t.co/yKz57HXTqR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Android Infotainment Software Engineer |Detroit MI| Positions- 1: KEY RESPONSIBILITIES: The Software Engineer will be responsible for application development and support including story elaboration, estimation, analysis, design, programming,… https://t.co/hyXffVptFi https://t.co/BTCFmhsCcq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fox News poll: Dems' midterms edge shrinks: A Fox News poll finds President Donald Trump's approval rating holding steady at 45% and the GOP closing the gap on the Democrats' lead in terms of which party voters favor in their congressional districts. https://t.co/5p6cjRNUFY https://t.co/Gpq443Cyfy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle DBA: Oracle DBA detroit, Michigan – United States Job Start Date – 02/27/18, Posted Date – 02/27/18 Primary SkillsOracle DBATax TermsC2COverview SR. Oracle DBA Interviewing ASAP 5 years of hard-core DBA with both stand-alone and RAC databases.… https://t.co/no7DtSxqW3 https://t.co/VBSeLDjWug]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager: Job Details (*Employee Referral Program applies to this job) Job No. PM00001 Job Title Senior Project Manager Description Summary: Position Description: AD – Deployment manager will coordinate with hardware installers, network… https://t.co/VnjjhKiIKE https://t.co/cNNvyTf1m0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer (Java Spring) – Detroit: ABOUT US TribalScale is an innovation firm that brings organizations – from the startup to the enterprise – into the future. We build digital products, transform teams, and grow startups. Were… https://t.co/lc3zuoOIB3 https://t.co/OKLYl8idpl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Key Account Manager OEM / OES: # of Openings 1 Job Locations US-MI-DetroitPosted Date 1 hour ago Category Sales Overview The Key Account Manager (KAM) is the owner of and the expert for the assigned Automotive Tier 1 Suppliers and their value chain… https://t.co/tlGS2WDgvf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: ACTRON SYSTEMS – Markets – Access Control – CCTV Systems – Government Sales – Electronic Monitoring – Intrusion Alarms – Virtual Presence – Clients – About – Management Team – Careers – Contact – 1-************ – ************ –… https://t.co/WZwiZUv5Wp https://t.co/OJQe0zpkne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Systems Security Specialist: **This is a Full Time position (not a contract). Must be authorized to work in the U.S. without sponsorship. Must be a US citizen or a green card holder. F1 OPT and Corp to corp candidates will not be… https://t.co/J5CdZscITl https://t.co/ivdj0DhJcD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Support &amp; UNIX Administrator| Detroit MI | 1 Year| Position- 1: MANAGER REQUIRED MINIMUM Software SkillsBEA WeblogicYes 1-3 https://t.co/sFVU8g9u3A SkillsJ2EEYes4-6 yrs. Software SkillsJavaYes4-6 yrs. Software SkillsPerlYes1-3 yrs. Software… https://t.co/k0EXPqv4E2 https://t.co/zdHnAI2IGe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[General Labor – Construction: Detroit Lakes, MN, USAFull Time Arvig seeks General Laborers who want to make a difference, grow their future, and have fun in the process AND who want competitive pay ($16.50/hr to start), overtime potential, multiple pay… https://t.co/tNUsKvRka4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This fiercely outspoken teen stunned America with her silence: She strode on stage at the March for Our Lives rally in Washington over the weekend, and listed the names of the 17 students and staff gunned down at her high school in Parkland, Florida. And… https://t.co/Cyz3KyMnsQ https://t.co/O0bgFiZu3s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Global Value Chain Engineer: # of Openings 1 Job Locations US-MI-DetroitPosted Date 12 hours ago Category Sales Overview The GVCE achieves material- and part-approvals. He/she drives key projects in close teamwork with the local tesa-KAMs and the global… https://t.co/uacDifKTuP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Installation Technician (Detroit Lakes, MN): Detroit Lakes, MN, USAHourlyFull Time Inside Out provides competitive compensation, health insurance, PTO, and retirement benefits! Inside Out is an installation contracting company headquartered in Detroit… https://t.co/7zffECWI5e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Construction Inspector: Construction Inspector Beam, Longest &amp; Neff, LLC (BLN), is a leading provider of engineering, construction and technical services for public agencies and private sector companies around the United States. The Company offers a… https://t.co/X4yFhag8tl https://t.co/zNpFXNqMME]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lawyer: This is proof of Trump's affair with porn star: The lawyer representing the porn star suing President Donald Trump called a tweet he posted of an apparent data disc a "warning shot" to the President. https://t.co/vMjCbks8Dj https://t.co/qA780uC1Bd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle DBA: Oracle DBA detroit, Michigan – United States Job Start Date – 02/27/18, Posted Date – 02/27/18 Primary SkillsOracle DBATax TermsC2COverview SR. Oracle DBA Interviewing ASAP 5 years of hard-core DBA with both stand-alone and RAC databases.… https://t.co/DTufFCAZKA https://t.co/uIdMRaw01D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Solution Architect: Cloud Solution Architect Microsoft envisions a world where passionate innovators come to collaborate, envisioning what can be and taking their careers places they simply couldn’t anywhere else. This is a world of more… https://t.co/T4QK75chWe https://t.co/tsH1U7JwsV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager (IT Security)- PMP: Project Manager (Security)- PMP Location: Detroit, MI Interview Mode: In-person preferred after telephonic round Project Duration: 12+ months * 10+ Years in project management or involvement on projects * Client needs… https://t.co/gmTi2eGGAw https://t.co/h7sUFMEpgV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Global Value Chain Engineer: # of Openings 1 Job Locations US-MI-DetroitPosted Date 12 hours ago Category Sales Overview The GVCE achieves material- and part-approvals. He/she drives key projects in close teamwork with the local tesa-KAMs and the global… https://t.co/8YxIG3iVRF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT/Cable Technician (100% Nationwide – Great Pay): JOB TITLE: Level 2: Lead Cable / Hardware Installation Technician Level 3: Certified Lead Cable / Hardware Installation, Telco and Troubleshooting Technician SUMMARY BY LEVEL: Level 2: Leads and manages… https://t.co/Vi5iMw1pwH https://t.co/SAymSeDth9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps/ Platform Engineer: DevOps/ Platform Engineer is focused on: * Retail, Operating Systems, systems hardening, Virtualization and Automation. * 4 or more years of Linux or Windows systems administration experience. * Experience with modern… https://t.co/fbczB4TKi0 https://t.co/RWByUxqEPj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Software Engineer II| 118640| Detroit MI| 1 year| position -1: ENTERPRISE SOFTWARE ENGINEER II 1. Major Duties and Responsibilities a. Define, design, build, test, deploy, and support software products b. Consistently follow the specified… https://t.co/efXftaSyyF https://t.co/3asld0bagH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .Net Developer: Senior .Net Developer Senior .Net Developer Company Autobooks Location US-MI-Detroit Opportunity Details What You’ll Do/Need Within this role at Autobooks you will be a senior participant in the design and development of… https://t.co/ucE9c9QWGS https://t.co/6Ug2Ad2kAs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Project Manager Ref No.: 18-10731 Location: Detroit, Michigan Role : Project Manager Duration : 12 Months Location : Detroit, MI Job Description : Experience in legacy to SAP rolloutsData Migration End user testing,integration test… https://t.co/hmst3hn2Rh https://t.co/Lky3xSL7LH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[General Labor – Construction: Detroit Lakes, MN, USAFull Time Arvig seeks General Laborers who want to make a difference, grow their future, and have fun in the process AND who want competitive pay ($16.50/hr to start), overtime potential, multiple pay… https://t.co/usHYbZy7gx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer (807): Direct hire position available for a DevOps Engineer with in-depth knowledge of Linux operating systems and Amazon Web Services (AWS). Additionally, a thorough understanding of network communications and experience in various… https://t.co/bCfQD3bAEl https://t.co/5V9hDklFcf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: ACTRON SYSTEMS – Markets – Access Control – CCTV Systems – Government Sales – Electronic Monitoring – Intrusion Alarms – Virtual Presence – Clients – About – Management Team – Careers – Contact – 1-************ – ************ –… https://t.co/8HoEDRNwlb https://t.co/7uJSzF0mQp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Support &amp; UNIX Administrator| Detroit MI | 1 Year| Position- 1: MANAGER REQUIRED MINIMUM Software SkillsBEA WeblogicYes 1-3 https://t.co/sFVU8g9u3A SkillsJ2EEYes4-6 yrs. Software SkillsJavaYes4-6 yrs. Software SkillsPerlYes1-3 yrs. Software… https://t.co/gBiuW2HPyC https://t.co/XJuMkIslAe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infotainment Application Software Engineer – Android|Detroit MI|10 Months | Positions-3: QUALIFICATIONS REQUIRED: BS in Computer Science or other field of study along with applicable work experience Experience with Android UI design (including custom… https://t.co/FUjUIXCaDV https://t.co/AasLWP9McL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NCAA Tournament: And then there were 8 https://t.co/733Ggi1Rr5 https://t.co/YoRtWyhiyC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OnSite iOS Developer: Detroit Labs OnSite is looking an iOS Developer to join one of our projects in downtown Detroit. This role is with our OnSite business unit; successful applicants will be working at the client location in Detroit. This team member… https://t.co/Ra9jlxbXpT https://t.co/h8JFZBKYJ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid to Senior Software Engineer – React: At Sift we take a consumer approach to B2B software: emphasizing understanding of the user experience and building beautiful and easy to use software that delights our clients. Were looking for a talented engineer… https://t.co/JV8ovBvRza https://t.co/5Lf4SvFSfG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Installation Technician (Detroit Lakes, MN): Detroit Lakes, MN, USAHourlyFull Time Inside Out provides competitive compensation, health insurance, PTO, and retirement benefits! Inside Out is an installation contracting company headquartered in Detroit… https://t.co/BAQUaUAi4s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Android Infotainment Software Engineer |Detroit MI| Positions- 1: KEY RESPONSIBILITIES: The Software Engineer will be responsible for application development and support including story elaboration, estimation, analysis, design, programming,… https://t.co/Gm6dAY7hhQ https://t.co/hABVmsY7aV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UI Designer .: Were looking for an experienced visual designer/user interface designer for our office in Detroit. ABOUT THE POSITION Your heart beats fast whether you are perfectly positioning a tiny pixel or helping create the next generation of digital… https://t.co/VFSMdYZbID https://t.co/pZCDdnmmaC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Software Engineer II (JSE)| Detroit MI| 1 Year| Position- 1: Enterprise Software Engineer II 1. Major Duties and Responsibilities a. Define, design, build, test, deploy, and support software products b. Consistently follow the specified… https://t.co/nDLdWOTbbo https://t.co/UkszXf2dVm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Script and HTML5 Front End Developer|Detroit MI| Positions – 1: Participate in and lead requirements analysis, specifications and design of custom-developed applications. Assist in the development of implementation/rollout plans. Ensure that… https://t.co/JpDVxSn3Rv https://t.co/iJ4QV9ft4i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT/Cable Technician (100% Travel – Nationwide): JOB TITLE: Level 2: Lead Cable / Hardware Installation Technician Level 3: Certified Lead Cable / Hardware Installation, Telco and Troubleshooting Technician SUMMARY BY LEVEL: Level 2: Leads and manages a… https://t.co/hZOOFDmdtN https://t.co/JG812fOfzp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Systems Security Specialist: **This is a Full Time position (not a contract). Must be authorized to work in the U.S. without sponsorship. Must be a US citizen or a green card holder. F1 OPT and Corp to corp candidates will not be… https://t.co/PgmRa6sysh https://t.co/58qyrJZY8S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Outside Sales Representative: Detroit, MI: SalesDetroit, Michigan As an Outside Sales Representative, you’ll be part of an award-winning culture in a family-oriented environment where employees are valued and rewarded. RevLocal is the leader in… https://t.co/cJt8ukGEZi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front End Developer (Mobile Device) |Detroit MI|1 Year| Positions- 3: JOB SUMMARY Responsible for front-end design and development at the product application layers. Requires a good understanding of programming web based applications in order to meet… https://t.co/derzXPAr3Y https://t.co/qSV5aR1Tdx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering Project Manager: Job Description We are AAM. We have the POWER to move the world. At AAM, we’re looking for associates who push boundaries and drive solutions for the future. Innovators. Thinkers. Dreamers. Doers. No matter the role or… https://t.co/5F3rBmAv9U https://t.co/GnBeyG5M4H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle Financial consultant: Title: Oracle Financial consultant Type of Employment: Direct Hire/Permanent Job Description: An experienced consulting professional who has a broad understanding of solutions, industry best practices, multiple business… https://t.co/DeNbwZtV4Q https://t.co/7oSMeVgbvp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why former No. 1 MLB pick left baseball at age 26 https://t.co/cgkYfovrrS https://t.co/Aip07ZXQHt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Cloud Infrastructure Automation Lead: 3046693 Senior Cloud Infrastructure Automation Lead Oil &amp; Gas Headquarters GE Oil &amp; Gas United States Provide IT leadership on multiple automation build projects. Help prioritize and drive results for the… https://t.co/fdMa7YvcC1 https://t.co/Q7bBOi20RA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Quality Analyst III| Detroit MI| 10 Months| Positions-1: Test Case Authoring: Develop detailed Test Cases based on the Functional Requirements and Design Documents. Execute the Test Cases and Analyze the Test Results. Usage of test tools as ALM… https://t.co/xLtBIsXWz9 https://t.co/qdl7vlh8sQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Primary Skills JAVA,JAVASCRIPT,IBM ISIM,IBM TFIM Development Overview PROLIM Global Corporation (**************) is currently seeking Java Developer for location Detroit , MI for one of our Top client. Job Description: IT… https://t.co/SpNPRL5MAe https://t.co/qvEYsZlEWU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Global Value Chain Engineer: # of Openings 1 Job Locations US-MI-DetroitPosted Date 12 hours ago Category Sales Overview The GVCE achieves material- and part-approvals. He/she drives key projects in close teamwork with the local tesa-KAMs and the global… https://t.co/fOGJ9gYw1z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Devops Engineer: Job Overview: Provide end-to-end DevOps solution by employing the most appropriate tools for CI/CD set up, continuous feedback, continuous monitoring, continuous planning, and continuous testing. Responsibilities: * Consult to provide… https://t.co/AjCA52RoVM https://t.co/NclMZeb7sI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Software Engineer – Automotive: Ready to turn the wheel in the _AUTOMOTIVE _industry with a _HYPERGROWTH STARTUP_? MULTINATIONAL AUTOMOTIVE MANUFACTURER has already established connected car technologies abroad and are on the verge of the biggest… https://t.co/LLPsQZKFuT https://t.co/uuKUlgxnGo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Quality Analyst III| Detroit MI| 10 Months| Positions-1: Test Case Authoring: Develop detailed Test Cases based on the Functional Requirements and Design Documents. Execute the Test Cases and Analyze the Test Results. Usage of test tools as ALM… https://t.co/ZyD8j9KhxB https://t.co/HKE8QabYIz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Devops Engineer: Job Overview: Provide end-to-end DevOps solution by employing the most appropriate tools for CI/CD set up, continuous feedback, continuous monitoring, continuous planning, and continuous testing. Responsibilities: * Consult to provide… https://t.co/1to44Hluvl https://t.co/rQFUE1t2RN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Software Engineer II (JSE)| Detroit MI| 1 Year| Position- 1: Enterprise Software Engineer II 1. Major Duties and Responsibilities a. Define, design, build, test, deploy, and support software products b. Consistently follow the specified… https://t.co/lOl31UVK7B https://t.co/khNPW6C51v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Solution Architect: Cloud Solution Architect Microsoft envisions a world where passionate innovators come to collaborate, envisioning what can be and taking their careers places they simply couldn’t anywhere else. This is a world of more… https://t.co/GU76tWzLE8 https://t.co/Iem0NRSfM7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Outside Sales Representative: Detroit, MI: SalesDetroit, Michigan As an Outside Sales Representative, you’ll be part of an award-winning culture in a family-oriented environment where employees are valued and rewarded. RevLocal is the leader in… https://t.co/lpXzNrj3jl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Android Infotainment Software Engineer |Detroit MI| Positions- 1: KEY RESPONSIBILITIES: The Software Engineer will be responsible for application development and support including story elaboration, estimation, analysis, design, programming,… https://t.co/KhrxeABewY https://t.co/aHOeu506Lh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .Net Developer: Senior .Net Developer Senior .Net Developer Company Autobooks Location US-MI-Detroit Opportunity Details What You’ll Do/Need Within this role at Autobooks you will be a senior participant in the design and development of… https://t.co/xqb5W3UfV2 https://t.co/crmZwt8iUB]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>