<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Mike Clifford - A One-Hit Wonder  http://t.co/GEzqELffyk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only person who is educated is the one who has learned how to learn and change. - Carl Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it's too close to bother to buckle your seat belt it's close enough to walk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is A Hedge Fund?  http://t.co/OoHnZpKWaK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's recording techniques would have been regarded as science fiction forty years ago. - Tony Visconti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Arthur Lyman -- The Pioneer of "Exotica" Music http://t.co/4K65R9qytP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A pedestrian is someone who thought there were a couple of gallons left in the tank. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These aren't the droids you're looking fore. - Obi-Wan, Star Wars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stumbling is not falling. - Portuguese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With four pairs of shoes I can travel the world. - Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[History of Mojang - The makers of Minecraft - http://t.co/ziJj8eqdJj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These aren't the droids you're looking fore. - Obi-Wan, Star Wars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Running SUCKS! How to Run for Fast Weight Loss - For Busy Women Who HATE Running --&gt; http://t.co/GayrO0CtNO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making the Most of Twitter for Your Business  http://t.co/izfsBADTul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome darts t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the darts lovers in your life!   http://t.co/UGO5PzBESu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Guide - Four ways to keep your printing environmentally friendly  http://t.co/zJBqcG9atS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Health and Mana Video Game Inspired Earrings with Key Charms!  Cool! http://t.co/1jaKf2Z8YK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is the ability to listen to almost anything without losing your temper or your self-confidence. - Robert Frost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL - Cool - A Computer Mouse with a Spider in it!   http://t.co/4ckjUuMMgT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before the marriage, he talks &amp; she listens.  During honeymoon, she talks &amp; he listens.  Later, they both talk &amp; the neighbors listen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are three things you can do in a baseball game. You can win, or you can lose, or it can rain. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winners never quit and quitters never win. - Vince Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion changes, but style endures. --&gt; Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The universe, as far as we can observe it, is a wonderful and immense engine. - George Santayana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hold fast to dreams, for if dreams die, life is a broken winged bird that cannot fly. - Langston Hughes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's always itching for money, but he never scratches for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two sides: One is light, one is dark." -- John Locke, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out Why Technology Is Helpful To Seniors  http://t.co/wOvX8aFg6D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The main part of intellectual education is not the acquisition of facts but learning how to make facts live." - Oliver Wendell Holmes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crack is cheap I make too much $ to ever smoke crack. Lets get that straight. OK? We dont do crack We dont do that Crack is whack - Whtney H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Ivory Joe Hunter  http://t.co/3SsfJdstFs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So cool and elegant - what is the history behind Ballet shoes?  http://t.co/IL0vuD4jse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blow off some steam, or rather, shoot some smoke rings. The Zero Fog Blaster is a ray gun - totally cool!  http://t.co/oF3wPMGzH6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Manolo Blahnik  http://t.co/cjydxKU5O2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't do any vulgar movements.  -  Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The thing about science fiction is that it's totally wide open. But it's wide open in a conditional way. - Octavia Butler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Platform Shoes  http://t.co/qFdNPdpMwo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teenagers do everything we did…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is Ununpentium?  http://t.co/5eXh1X2S8H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Marketing Experts Reveal Tips to Success  http://t.co/yWQExzul38]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Arthur Lyman -- The Pioneer of "Exotica" Music http://t.co/4K65R9qytP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome - The World's Smallest Solar Powered Car! http://t.co/cUBqvm2JNi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You cannot dream yourself into a character: you must hammer and forge yourself into one. - Henry D. Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can accept failure, but I can't accept not trying. - Michael Jordan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any government big enough to give you everything you want is big enough to take it away from you, too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If a lot of people said what they think, they would be speechless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A computer lets you make more mistakes faster than any invention in human history - with the possible exceptions of handguns and tequila.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 14 - Doctor Decides to Discontinue IV Treatment  http://t.co/hXLq7CMkMD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like to literally put women on a pedestal. - Vivienne Westwood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The scenery was very beautiful. But I did not see the Great Wall. - Yang Liwei, China's first astronaut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Religion Both Protestant and Catholics  http://t.co/jdOMBaJwPL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips for Effective Use of LinkedIn for Your Company  http://t.co/WxJXiL3eQ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I could walk a mile in ur shoes but I already know they are just as uncomfortable as mine. Lets walk next to each other instead Lynda Meyers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did You Know this About Blackbeard in Pirates of the Caribbean 4  http://t.co/nPvgkdbEPx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I won't be a rock star. I will be a legend. - Freddie Mercury]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can never be overdressed or overeducated. --&gt; Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I could have played another year, but I would have been playing for the money, and baseball deserves better than that. - George Brett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peter Townshend shows us it's all right to grow up. There is dignity after rock'n'roll. - Sting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't really see science fiction as fiction. I can imagine colonies on Mars and everything. - Sigourney Weaver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before you judge a man, walk a mile in his shoes. After that who cares? He's a mile away and you've got his shoes - Billy Connolly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The reason Las Vegas is getting so big is nobody can afford to buy a ticket to leave.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learning is what most adults will do for a living in the 21st century. - Perelman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't care half so much about making money as I do about making my point, and coming out ahead. Cornelius Vanderbilt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have not failed. I've just found 10,000 ways that won't work - Thomas Alva Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Flying Alarm Clock - COOL!  http://t.co/qaHaheeVmV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Corinth Texas  http://t.co/NCm1R3hS1L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Underwater Scooter - How Cool! http://t.co/2ZJWXfkVeC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An animal's eyes have the power to speak a great language. - Martin Buber]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good teachers are those who know how little they know. Bad teachers are those who think they know more than they don't know. - R. Verdi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If there are kids who want to follow in my footsteps, I'd say that my shoes are 2 big for them to! Their shoe size is perfect. Q. Latifah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was sad because I had no shoes, until I met a man who had no feet. So I said, Got any shoes you're not using? --&gt; Steven Wright]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd like to compliment you on your work -- When will you start?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Experience is not what happens to a man. It is what a man does with what happens to him. - Aldous Huxley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent Blue LED light stemmed Umbrella - a unique take on the Umbrella! http://t.co/U2GvOjP3Cj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One may go wrong in many directions but one may go right in only one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The man who can drive himself further once the effort gets painful is the man who will win. - Roger Bannister]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Hallmarks of a Quality Insurance Company  http://t.co/AxZ2LdimI6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Foreigner  http://t.co/a32dAiSvp9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome kayaking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the paddling lovers in your life!   http://t.co/2SLFm7eQjf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elegance is refusal. --&gt; Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did You Know this About Blackbeard in Pirates of the Caribbean 4  http://t.co/nPvgkdbEPx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Ray Conniff  http://t.co/drgvqOr3t0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no crying in baseball. - Tom Hanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Don McLean  http://t.co/WfSpO5cFCU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I didn't grow up thinking, 'Oh, maybe someday I'm going to have a shoe named after me.' -  Sheryl Swoopes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool just found these 25 Original Unopened Packs of Vintage Baseball Cards (80s-90s) - can find some value in there!  http://t.co/j6pd63NfkS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes many a tumble to keep us humble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can You Imagine Melting Clock - Very Cool - Jazz Up Your Office Space! http://t.co/2ufLbOVzJ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know anything about music. In my line you don't have to.  - Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got hit in the head pretty hard. My clock ran backwards for two years. - Buddy Baker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One Person’s Musings on Elvis  http://t.co/sgka6iMs1r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About The Beginning Of Christian Religion  http://t.co/de9sQGbIPU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Arthur Lyman -- The Pioneer of "Exotica" Music http://t.co/4K65R9qytP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supporting Adopted Students: Parents and Teachers Working Together  http://t.co/oqdQqGqzcj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Tips on Using Other Websites for Link Building  http://t.co/poMWWKKSBJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Each man has his own vocation; his talent is his call. There is one direction in which all space is open to him. - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What becomes of the broken-hearted? They buy shoes. - Mimi Pond]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where to find Great Gluten Free Recipes  http://t.co/lqOGAtjffy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read an Introduction to Sonic Drive-In  http://t.co/6TIDp1oQCo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Top 10 Burger Chains in the US  http://t.co/kj6lQ2rUKC]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>