<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I will be selling brand new prints and greeting cards of my recent paintings tomorrow at Main and 26th for... http://t.co/hZnlq7wttD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This piece is now sold, I'm sad to see it go but I'm happy it found a good home :)

Cheers, Keith :) http://t.co/kYyucOC0Yx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[seannair94 asked: your art is amazing i love it man ! what inspires u man ?? http://t.co/8xeXpm75yK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[willow-bird asked: wow i love your art style! :D can i ask what you use to paint? http://t.co/nnXnEbFWUL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[inanelephantear asked: Your art is very fresh and inspiring http://t.co/CzFEhjcsb8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[youcancallmecoop asked: Holy shit your art is amazing I love the structured simplicity of it with the vivid... http://t.co/yftZ0d5001]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[nanodronerrf asked: Okay, I know I’m probably kind of stupid for asking this, but how do you get a drawing,... http://t.co/76jDMQYeAH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[lizziexxmarie asked: i love some of your work dude, pretty cool http://t.co/NP6VdoDgrg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[mojoswork asked: Love your work! Question about the coloring… Is it actual watercolor or digital? The color... http://t.co/wDEobt75kv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Third stage in this alleyway painting. Highlights next. More at http://t.co/A32WWASG3K http://t.co/ldbQfYxM2y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First layers of paint. I'm establishing a main colour palette of various greens and reds. This is the alley behind... http://t.co/tSQJNZmVM8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[a new painting ive been working on while commuting to and from work on the vancouver seabus: https://t.co/qdRbXbLHGg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[youre bio/description is enough to make me want to have coffee and talk art with you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Latest blog post, outlining the creation of my recent painting of a red-eyed tree frog:... http://t.co/fr721QXdrn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New blog post about how I painted this red-eyed tree frog: http://t.co/Onn3O6x4dN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dreamfevers  might get to u after a short while ya. u should look into kits]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dreamfevers ya no worries. plus i draw up there haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dreamfevers  all neighborhoods will cost plenty if u live solo, roommates can really cut the cost down. I live in north van cuz its quiet:)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This painting continues the direction of making art about specific intersections in Vancouver. Main and Broadway: http://t.co/FS7oSBLvOK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dreamfevers that sounds cool! Blending of styles :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've just finished this new painting of the street post at Main and Broadway in Vancouver. The orange and blue... http://t.co/5LFiPALbqc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MacLarenVan: Agency Spy @MacLarenVan MacLarenVanites participate in Shoreline Cleanup. Yup, we found a tire. #AgencySpy #BTS http://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friday after work i painted on the boardwalk at lonsdale quay. My city in the front, the "real"city in the back :) http://t.co/8wGZmCLsD3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BORNWILD_ART thats a fine tiger my friend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Painting by the water after work. My city being painted, the real city in the distance http://t.co/20hiQ7P1bO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This painting is of a street post at the corner of Main and Broadway in Vancouver, it's one of my faves. http://t.co/nVUzt64Dip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this is rad http://t.co/xERkdLhtWV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WinsorGallery: gheeeeeawwww! http://t.co/JfoxWrLwgq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sneak peek at a new piece in the works. It is also being documented in a video for the opus blog, due out in July. http://t.co/BM6WMECL94]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[red-lipstick: Santiago Ydañez - Untitled, 2012 Paintings: Oil on Wood http://t.co/aqYh2PfAd8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @simonekilworth: New facebook page... https://t.co/IGUMptBG41]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted this frog! #art #vancouver #frog #green #nature http://t.co/btKcipz05L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All done! This piece was a lot of fun. So many cool colours textures and shapes http://t.co/RQ5ZiQ9j9f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MalindaArt: @artismovement I'm productive 7 days a week! That's what happens when your job is the thing you love doing more than anythi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New painting - Main and Broadway, Vancouver. Not sure the contrasting colour yet, probably orange, what do you think? http://t.co/yTriHBW9Uc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In this interview with Moov Magazine (Toronto) I discuss the process and inspiration behind my city paintings: http://t.co/prIS5ROliC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dreamfevers  sounds good friend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arianek @OpusArtSupplies amazing thanks! those guys are a great bunch :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted a new street post. Here it is. I like it. It has a panda and a lucky cat! http://t.co/ZjvxkYAoSO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arianek thanks for following my artventures on twitter, friend!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/t1DjzaKxKR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All done!

This is a new painting of the street parker post at Main and Pender in Vancouver. Big on the... http://t.co/JtM5GWmSNY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a picture of me in the studio with an in-progress commission octopus painting. http://t.co/ajMgzjcWi5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a really neat commission I'm working on for a good fellow in TO. Drawing's all done, I'm gonna start... http://t.co/af9ftJhVNr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Vancouver there are a lot of alleyways that are haphazard layers of buildings, cables, wooden beams, etc. … http://t.co/VRanoZQ4tV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All done!

Very happy with how this piece turned out. It'll be on display starting late August for my show at... http://t.co/s12Iqdgij4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am really happy with how this painting of the Chinatown street marker post is shaping up: http://t.co/EJAXQC7jfW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My latest blog post examines the step-by-step creation of Vancouver's East Broadway @ Main street post: http://t.co/4mSHGuCkMO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I enjoy painting scenes of Vancouver urbanity. Lately I've started focusing on alleyways as a subject matter.… http://t.co/h5DVEtSAiM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a new alleyway painting I'm working on: https://t.co/eNDZWYKpWV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these prints my painting of the woodwards building sign in Vancouver: https://t.co/cseT5hy491?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Throwback post - here's my first ever painting of my current work..from 2011 http://t.co/bSw5zbvl9i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeoKooGallery Np - My friend told me about you guys. Lookin sharp!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing! my art will be featured on Collective Arts Brewing beer labels starting in September! Radddd http://t.co/YYV9qZkWZQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New print for sale. The original of this piece will be shown at my exhibit at The Cultch at summer's end :) https://t.co/hWxTzB2Uhf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New street sign painting, Pender street; Chinatown; Vancouver http://t.co/MVTePh8qp7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New piece in the works, subject matter = chinatown, Vancouver. Got some neat little painted additions planned for... http://t.co/VkWhteZ3r6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[jonclaytor: The view from my studio window on a peaceful winter morning. http://t.co/m0p6iPXdnM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just sold this painting of the Sun Tower in Vancouver. I'm happy its gone to a good home! https://t.co/ZAfh7wSFuG http://t.co/FlrfEZORET]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a new tree frog painting I've done, and made prints of for sale. If you are curious, see them here: https://t.co/gOTJ1PuQON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a new commission piece I'm working on. I'm very pleased with the drawing and excited to start painting it... http://t.co/UzKsQRVslC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks Opus for including two of my friends and I in this month's newsletter! Very honoured :) http://t.co/UnjNbxz0QB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this new video by Opus Art Supplies - It documents the creation of one of my latest paintings:... http://t.co/t1tDgwEyNB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OpusArtSupplies: NEW OPUS VIDEO &amp; ARTICLE featuring #Vancouver artists @JonShawPainting, @Mar_killing &amp; Sean Karemaker: http://t.co/h08…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the evenings I can often be found drawing in the Park near my house in North Van. Here's latest outdoor piece http://t.co/5lxsGE7td8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this painting I made of the Sun Tower, where @MacLarenVan can be found! http://t.co/tcjxCrgsBS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm happy to say that this parrot painting found a great new home today - cheers Kevin! http://t.co/bL5Nsbupc5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a new print I've just listed for sale. Urban Decay meets phone booth meets Vancouver!  http://t.co/Too9xDY7k8 via @Etsy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm into the painting stage on this octopus commission piece. Plenty of work to be had still, but it's starting to... http://t.co/1t4EfnOVBo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Horse Art Print 12 x 12 Reproduction Of by JonShawPaintings http://t.co/4O1DuSaf6e via @Etsy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm very excited to be part of the new Kimoto Gallery!

These four pieces will be part of the upcoming "A Grand... http://t.co/DGSsCm0UVt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meeting of the minds - Pic of East Coast buddies and I at my show at the @TheCultch - Show is up until Sept 28! http://t.co/qCzAZCPga4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KimotoGallery: Handmade sandwich board done! One more thing off the list for the opening #ArtwalkSG http://t.co/AyAbdrEEj8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The studio is quite empty right now after hanging my show at the Cultch! I even cleaned under the tables to... http://t.co/ZUw9AzoTds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnnysmooth thanks for the follow, my similarly-named artist friend!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I started painting this octopus commission piece. It's going to come together very well this month. Great subject. http://t.co/Wxknm5dRIP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook http://t.co/8gLcQWgTDg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook http://t.co/G4ov9rKv4d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted 19 photos on Facebook in the album "Opening Reception - Street Signs and Alleyways" http://t.co/ycXN7EKTPP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks so much everyone for coming out to the show last night! It was a great and fantastic success! Fun was had... http://t.co/HsnluARP48]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New show opening TONIGHT at the cultch, all new paintings!! https://t.co/08HGjIE9dt for details!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My show opens TONIGHT at the Cultch. Hope you can make it out! Here are the details: https://t.co/08HGjIE9dt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[new painting! http://t.co/V9RWySeNru]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to everyone who has helped my facebook art page reach 1,000 followers: https://t.co/VVpDv5H3A8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What’s that off in the distance? It kind of looks like a UFO! #spotted #vancouver 
#ufo http://t.co/99E8UOjEzY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the third alleyway painting I've made, and the final one for my show that opens this Wednesday! I'm all done! http://t.co/FezTcmUrxP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Photo: A new alleyway painting. My previous alleys were specific places that I photographed in Vancouver... http://t.co/O31YmMlrdi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Progress shot #1 from my third alleyway painting. The line work is about 75% done in this image. I'm a fan of the... http://t.co/bCe24Woi26]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekend art project by the water/campsite http://t.co/uaEGUOnwXK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@glenmitchell stoked man, i hope thats your head in the water I see. Last year we went and saw three trees catch on fire when lightning hit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm stoked to make a new drawing over the next four days at Birkenhead Lake! Outdoor art is the best.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have an upcoming show of new paintings at @TheCultch opening Wed, Aug 28 from 6 - 8pm. Come have a beer! Details: https://t.co/08HGjIE9dt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MacLarenVan: Fist Bump Wed. @MacLarenVan shoutout to our own, super-talented digital designer/painter @JonShawPainting Congrats! http:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MacLarenVan: #AgencySpy @MacLarenVan Young agency creatives wearing ties. Surely the apocalypse is not far off. #BTS #MMV http://t.co/9…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a new painting for my show in two weeks. This piece examines the colours, mood and look of Gastown in... http://t.co/JGaxJSh5C2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out my latest painting of a street post at Cordova and Carrall streets: http://t.co/Mpa8YYeWBM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My work is used in this magazine ad in the States: http://t.co/gB8OoAtfvt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing!

My work has been used Staedtler's recent full page ad in the August issue of American Artist Drawing... http://t.co/w8ocHB4YCh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Vancouver_Now Thanks for plugging my exhibition..its gonna be great! The new pieces are looking very good in the studio :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UPCOMING SHOW!

Hey there friends! I have an opening at the Cultch on Wednesday, August 28, 6-8pm.

You get to... http://t.co/KEU2JnwEaQ]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>