<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Capitalism has destroyed our belief in any effective power but that of self interest backed by force. ~George Shaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[History is a tool used by capitalist politicians to justify their intentions. ~Ted Koppel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democracy no longer works for the poor if capitalist politicians treat them as a separate race. ~Frank Field]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A capitalist politician's goal is always to manipulate public debate. ~Dean Koontz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advertising men and capitalist politicians are dangerous if they are separated. Together they are diabolical. ~ Adams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These capitalists generally act harmoniously and in concert, to fleece the people. ~Lincoln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The guiding principle is not to manufacture the goods everyone needs, rather to earn profits for a few capitalists. ~ Ulbricht]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is impossible for capitalists and laborers to have common interests. ~Samuel Gompers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Capitalists are no more capable of self-sacrifice than a man is capable of lifting himself up by his own bootstraps. ~Lenin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liberate the minds of men and ultimately you will liberate the bodies of men. ~Marcus Garvey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every time we liberate a woman, we liberate a man. ~Margaret Mead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is better to die on your feet than to live on your knees. - Emiliano Zapata]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The essence of government is force, and most often that force is used to accomplish evil ends. - Walter Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you don't control your mind, someone else will. - John Allston]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nobody can give you freedom. Nobody can give you equality or justice or anything. If you're a man, you take it. - Malcolm X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In order to become the master, the politician poses as the servant. - Charles de Gaulle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Propaganda is to a democracy what the bludgeon is to a totalitarian state. - Noam Chomsky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most common way people give up their power is by thinking they don't have any. - Alice Walker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Capitalist democracy consists of choosing your dictators, after they've told you what you think it is you want to hear. - Alan Coren]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we choose, we can live in a world of comforting illusion. - Noam Chomsky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one is free who is not master of himself. - Claudius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Serial killers do, on a small scale, what capitalist governments do on a large one.- Richard Ramirez]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Without deviation progress is not possible. - Frank Zappa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be conscious that you are ignorant is a great step to knowledge. - Benjamin Disraeli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PeopleYouNeed: Revolutionary organizers, they will inject in your life a sense of political and social direction.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any dictator would admire the uniformity and obedience of the U.S. media. - Noam Chomsky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's no measure of health to be well adjusted to a profoundly sick society. - Krishnamurti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reasons2BLazy: Being unproductive for the corporations is a great revolutionary act that delegitimizes corporate rule.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your mind is totally controlled, it has been stuffed into my mold.  And you will do as you are told, until the rights to you are sold. - FZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man is no less a slave because he is allowed to choose a new master once in a term of years. - Lysander Spooner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JohnMaynKeynes: The capitalist economy is not real, not one bit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The tragedy of modern war is that the young men die fighting each other - instead of their real enemies back home in the capitals. - Abbey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heresy is only another word for freedom of thought. - Graham Greene]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In capitalist society, we can do anything we like as long as it is UNIMPORTANT. - Theodore Kaczynski]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The great are great only because we are on our knees. Let us rise! --Max Stirner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RacismFacts: According to AAA, men with racist tendencies are far more likely to own a car that they cannot afford.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thus, the struggle for peace includes the struggle for freedom and justice for the masses of all countries. ~Arthur Henderson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The press should be not only a collective propagandist and a collective agitator, but also a collective organizer of the masses. ~Lenin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Religion is not merely the opium of the masses, it's the cyanide. ~Tom Robbins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Politics begin where the masses are, not where there are thousands, but where there are millions, that is where serious politics begin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WealthyFacts: According to the NYTimes, the wealthier you are the less social and socialistic you become!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Often the masses are plundered and do not know it. ~Frederic Bastiat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No amount of political freedom will satisfy the hungry masses. ~Vladimir Lenin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reasons2BLazy: Unproductivity is a great way for workers to seize control of the economy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn from the masses, and then teach them. ~Mao Tse-Tung]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MARTlNLUTHERK: Capitalism is designed to destroy human beings by turning their energy towards the acquisitive drive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In America, it is sport that is the opiate of the masses. ~Russell Baker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have never intimidated the masses... I only intimidate corrupt officials. ~Zhu Rongji]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OvertDictionary: The Fashion Industry: an industry which does not only control what women see, it more importantly controls how women s…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give me your tired, your poor, your huddled masses yearning to breathe free. ~Emma Lazarus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The motive power of democracy is love. ~Henri Bergson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GoreVidaI: The mass media of the ruling elites is essentially a platform for psychological warfare against the minds of the people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democracy is not so much a form of government as a set of principles. ~Woodrow Wilson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democracy is indispensable to socialism. ~Vladimir Lenin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democracy is the road to socialism. ~Karl Marx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WealthyFacts: Wealthy people are not intelligent! According to the BBC, the upper class reads less and even thinks less than the genera…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a democracy the poor will have more power than the rich, because there are more of them, and the will of the majority is supreme.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democracy is when the indigent, and not the men of property, are the rulers. ~Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Malcom___X: The struggle of African Americans is the struggle of all citizens of the globe crushed on a daily basis by the forces of ca…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As I would not be a slave, so I would not be a master. This expresses my idea of democracy.~Abraham Lincoln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like a cyclone, imperialism spins across the globe; militarism crushes peoples and sucks their blood like a vampire. ~Karl Liebknecht]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OvertDictionary: Imagine: a word that is often associated with winning the jackpot, when it should be associated with creating a more h…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imperialism is the monopoly stage of capitalism.~Lenin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For behind all imperialism is ultimately the imperialistic individual, just as behind all peace is ultimately the peaceful individual.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democracy is now going forth on a crusade against imperialism. ~Irving Babbitt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Labor can and will become its own employer through co-operative association. ~Leland Stanford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PabIoPicasso: The artist is the revolution, the vision of the artist is the highest form of revolutionary creation..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Average real wages in Mexican manufacturing are lower than they were 10 years ago, if you can believe that.~Stephen F. Lynch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free trade should not mean free labor. ~Stephen F. Lynch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HowAdsBrainwash: by making you feel that corporations are your friends.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A truly American sentiment recognizes the dignity of labor and the fact that honor lies in honest toil. ~Grover Cleveland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no real wealth but the labor of man. ~ Percy Bysshe Shelley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DearTVAddicts: The television is used to make workers fear (and love) their capitalist exploiters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every man is dishonest who lives upon the labor of others, no matter if he occupies a throne. ~Robert Green Ingersoll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Affluence creates poverty. ~Marshall McLuhan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ThomasJeffersin: Revolutions are built on the backs of millions of politically conscious citizens.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Without labor nothing prospers. ~Sophocles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He who tampers with the currency robs labor of its bread. ~Daniel Webster]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @InjusticeFacts: Out of 15 Security Council members, the U.S. is the only one to always veto resolutions condemning Israel's violence ag…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A mule will labor ten years willingly and patiently for you, for the privilege of kicking you once. William Faulkner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All wealth is the product of labor. John Locke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RadicalProverbs: The famous man is a narcissistic man, he drowns in himself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All labor that uplifts humanity has dignity and importance and should be undertaken with painstaking excellence. MLK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They talk about the failure of socialism but where is the success of capitalism in Africa, Asia and Latin America? -Castro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RadicalProverbs: Don't fall in love with your banker.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When we hang the Capitalists they will sell us the rope. - Joseph Stalin (Former USSR leader)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The revolution is not an apple that falls when it is ripe. You have to make it fall. - Che Guevara (Cuban Revolutionary)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @_Che___Guevara_: Poor nations are enslaved by local elites who are nothing more than agents working for imperialist interests.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who make peaceful revolution impossible will make violent revolution inevitable. - John F. Kennedy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RadicalOrSlave: Do you despise the cultural elite and their political attitudes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Politicians are the same all over. They promise to build bridges even when there are no rivers. - Nikita Khrushchev]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Freedom is always the freedom of dissenters. - Rosa Luxemburg (Political Writer/Activist)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @How2GetFired: Be a pest, be pesky, annoying, the thorn in the side of the corporate pigs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To tell the truth is revolutionary. - Antonio Gramsci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In order to conquer, what we need is Audacity, more audacity, always audacity. -Danton (French Revolutionary)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @YgamblingSucks: Gambling is designed to intensify your debts, and thus your obedience, to the capitalist system.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone should play their role in tearing down the wall of hatred. - Lalu Prasad Yadav]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can jail a Revolutionary, but you can't jail the Revolution. - Huey Newton (Black-Power Civil Rights Activist)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do something. If it doesn't work, do something else. No idea is too crazy. - Jim Hightower. (Activist)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OvertDictionary: Capitalism: a machine which washes all authentic human dreams and replaces them with material obsessions.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>