<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[This rare feat hasn't happened since 1979 https://t.co/AAtoBsmM8Q https://t.co/srK3ZCH3wk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boost Your Nintendo Switch Experience With These Accessories: A rich ecosystem of Switch add-ons makes Nintendo’s compact console even more fun. https://t.co/WLagfjcIiJ https://t.co/EcBvPmojqu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer-RTI000TM LexisNexis : NA-USA-PA-Horsham Description The Reed Tech Software Engineer, as a member of an Agile team, participates in the design, analysis, coding, testing, debugging, maintenance and documentation of… https://t.co/PjTrV9Y1il https://t.co/gz6DXoO4zG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Architect/Engineer: Location:San Rafael, CA Requisition ID: 17WD24867 Position Overview Are you looking for a high energy team where you can make a direct contribution to building a new data API platform? Autodesk is looking for a talented Sr. Principal… https://t.co/BwfgYn5SLC https://t.co/n4Lt1TypyU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software QA Engineer Internship – Provo, UT: Software QA Engineer Internship – Provo, UT Tracking Code ******* Job Description Please note that our internships run in perpetuity throughout a students degree program, therefore you must live within… https://t.co/lNEGBr5Ptb https://t.co/bEfUHz0uSv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PErformance tuning DBA: PErformance tuning DBA Ref No.: 18-20847 Location: sunnyvale, California Role: Performance Tuning DBA Location: Sunnyvale, CA Duration: 12months Contract ONLY W2 Thanks &amp; Regards. Vatan Kumar Enterprise Solutions, Inc Phone :… https://t.co/niwMcZz14w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ireland votes overwhelmingly to repeal abortion ban: Ireland has voted an emphatic "Yes" to amend the country's constitution to enable legislation that would allow women to have an abortion in a historic and emotionally charged referendum. https://t.co/Pw1npWYFOo https://t.co/1hXUHG4tJH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Quality Assurance Analyst: Senior Quality Assurance Analyst Princeton Posted May 15, 2018 – Requisition No. 67099 Are you interested in joining a team that maintains Bloomberg’s status as the world’s leader in execution management and trading… https://t.co/UFgmkYxcaw https://t.co/4OzZpwgyJo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Desktop Support: Desktop Support Ref No.: 18-22547 Location: Hoboken, New Jersey Contracting profiles required for Desktop Support / Hoboken, NJ Skills: Excellent communication skills, both verbal and written, and confident in their abilities IT Support… https://t.co/YO79P2R8Q9 https://t.co/1vvrgTn5Lb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director, Information Security: MAJOR PURPOSE The Director of Information Security will be responsible for assisting Major League Baseball and its Clubs with the implementation, management and incident response for the league-wide cybersecurity program.… https://t.co/uyillAgdGN https://t.co/P89UR4ljhs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Cyber Security Engineer: What We Do: The SEI helps advance software engineering principles and practices and serves as a national resource in software engineering, computer security, and process improvement. The SEI works closely with defense… https://t.co/MFfmfcd6Ym https://t.co/dQgifEEZUg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Firmware Engineer – Breakthrough Innovation (HTAS): SBD’s Hand Tools Storage and Accesories Breakthrough Innovation team is looking for an aggressive creative thinker to join its team. This individual should feel comfortable working in the front end of… https://t.co/j3PJwJi3CS https://t.co/eHCaJRjD4O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Process/Project Engineer: Company Description Tessenderlo Kerley, Inc., is a company of diverse businesses unified by shared values and vision. We serve the agriculture, mining, industrial and water reclamation markets with a broad range of products and… https://t.co/R2iLSBIOyM https://t.co/owJuUdIcAI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VR Headsets That Will Transport You, Wherever the Destination: Whether you’re beaming up to the *Enterprise* or crashing your friend’s destination wedding from your sofa, these headsets take you there. https://t.co/bjdPuOZ6Am https://t.co/lF6PesHQWQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator: Clearance Level Must Currently Possess: Top Secret w/SCI eligibility Clearance Level Must Be Able to Obtain: Top Secret SCI Suitability: Agency Specific Job Family: Information Technology Job Description: As part of the U.S. Coast… https://t.co/Fda1qkrDHw https://t.co/nuhwXDUdCb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GOP rep. loses endorsement for saying it's OK to not sell homes to gay people: Republican Rep. Dana Rohrabacher of California is facing criticism and has lost an endorsement from a Realtors group for saying that people should be able to refuse to sell… https://t.co/CyW2IHroF3 https://t.co/xbQGmuThox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Assurance Policy Lead &amp; Specialist: The Cyber COAST is recruiting versatile, hands-on Information Assurance Policy experts for a major Federal Civilian agency. This opportunity will have a start date between April and May of 2018. Looking for… https://t.co/1n6VVATBFP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Site Acquisition Project Manager: Job Description Site Acquisition Project Manager (19255) Position Summary This position drives the completion of site acquisition functions through lifecycle of project into construction. This position performs, leads,… https://t.co/AZMKttdYcr https://t.co/h5V6FPnQkH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gadget Lab Podcast: The Very Human Element of Self-Driving Cars: WIRED’s Alex Davies and Aarian Marshall join this week’s Gadget Lab podcast to talk all things transportation–and yes, that includes Elon Musk. https://t.co/TqMcYn3XDd https://t.co/vsZRsYHKfi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Operations Research Specialist: BNSF Railway seeks multiple Sr. Ops. Research Specialists in Fort Worth to design, develop, implement &amp; integrate innovative computer-based decision tools. Must have Master’s in Operations Research, Industrial… https://t.co/5opg93JUEv https://t.co/ME7OnWxS5P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer Analyst: Programmer-Analyst Full Time at Denken Solutions, Inc. in Irvine, CA. Although position is based out of Orange County, CA HQ, position may be assigned to various unanticipated client or project sites anywhere in U.S. Duties: Support… https://t.co/lJHkQ9n5wt https://t.co/2pByuJ07Zt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lava gushes from volcanic cracks in Hawaii https://t.co/QjWmB077bH https://t.co/T41QLSbcwE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior System Engineer: A strong Scientific and technological pioneering spirit drives bioMérieux development since its creation in 1963. We design innovative in vitro diagnostic solutions for our customers that initiate new forms of scientific… https://t.co/ipz4hf1KiO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elon Musk is humiliating himself https://t.co/lxCRubJ3vv https://t.co/T0mxJQ4m9Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate, Strategic Analytics, CCB Risk #180046020: Associate, Strategic Analytics, CCB Risk – Columbus, OH. Analyzing &amp; quantifying risk based customer acquisition strategies, through implementation of strategy, &amp; ongoing monitoring to optimize… https://t.co/XH4jHNhngO https://t.co/t2nUOwGCdQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Data Analyst – Requisition ID R46823: Requisition ID R46823 West Creek 5 (12075), United States of America, Richmond, Virginia At Capital One, we’re building a leading information-based technology company. Still founder-led by Chairman and… https://t.co/7DlKO3cpbT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hardware Engineer: Hardware Engineer : Waymo LLC., San Francisco, CA 94126  job # below: Hardware Engineer (Mountain View, CA) Design, develop, modify, &amp;/or test hardware needed for various Waymo projects. #1615.34186 Exp Incl: floorplan dsgns w/… https://t.co/pcl1G7FyrO https://t.co/lKPxSYExHf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The actor responds to a CNN report on alleged inappropriate behavior, says he would not intentionally make anyone feel 'uncomfortable or disrespected': A young production assistant thought she had landed the job of her dreams when, in the summer of 2015,… https://t.co/ith12WRfAh https://t.co/0CfD4i0kdI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Firmware Engineer: Tesla, Inc. has the following positions available at its Palo Alto corporate headquarters and the Tesla campuses in Fremont and San Mateo. PALO ALTO POSITIONS Engineering Firmware Engineer. GG-031191. Approx. 15% travel required (10%… https://t.co/CV8WLW6mlv https://t.co/OGSNaOuXLZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineers – Job #42618-1: At Proofpoint’s Broomfield, CO office, seek DevOps Engineers to plan, design, develop &amp; test backend systems for software enhancements &amp; new products including cloud-based tools.  recblid 2cykhlgtx1vhduyfxvkvbkcmpwqgz5 https://t.co/THlMhywWKA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pearl worth $632,000 goes up for auction: The world's largest known freshwater pearl is going on sale at a public auction in the Netherlands next week. Known as "The Sleeping Lion" due to its unique shape, the rare natural object weighs almost 120 grams… https://t.co/7L4hEYTTPH https://t.co/PwqCR7N4so]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Consultants: Kavi Associates LLC seeks Sr. Consultants, Research &amp; Development for Barrington, IL to make architectural installation &amp; implementation plans for analytics &amp; dw. Master’s in Computer Science/Comp Engineering +2 years experience or… https://t.co/1vVqGEwjCN https://t.co/1yN82cBZVo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Engineer: QA and Support Automation Engineer Role Overview As a QA Automation Engineer, you will be involved throughout the development lifecycle of the Development Team with responsibility in the quality assurance of software development and test… https://t.co/tM8p2uwQpZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What to Think About Before Buying a Used Smartphone: New isn’t always better, but there are three key things to consider before you take the pre-owned plunge. https://t.co/KcoGdF5Dk4 https://t.co/D4b2bFW0zM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frontend Software Engineer – UI/UX Development and Design: Are you a Frontend Software Engineer who loves to create beautiful software design in an engaging environment?. We are looking for exceptional web developers with strong software engineering… https://t.co/qYxLipCMp0 https://t.co/LPMnp6aErc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Graphic/Web Designer: Graphic/Web Designer Overview Are you an experienced Graphic/Web Designer who is passionate about translating your creativity into viable campaigns and websites?  If so, we may have the position for you. The digital division of our… https://t.co/GGxUQxXLEt https://t.co/3WPOcpykyG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She was too short to play Goofy. Then she invented Spanx. Now she's a billionaire https://t.co/Lft8GL0LRz https://t.co/AGXmy6scW3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Europe's New Data Protections Will Affect You Too. Here's How.: Yes, they mainly affect those who live inside the EU. But non-Europeans should pay attention too. https://t.co/wobwCKYouI https://t.co/HacyWcniYO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[N. Korea warns of nuclear showdown, calls Pence 'political dummy': A North Korean official has lashed out at US Vice President Mike Pence and said Pyongyang is ready for a nuclear showdown if dialogue with the United States fails. https://t.co/Xa8MDBWJNF https://t.co/iILCTstRlz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Analyst -CRM &amp; Digital: Leo Burnett is seeking a Senior Analyst to lead a team dedicated to creating custom data and analytical solutions for our Clients. We are looking for a candidate with in-depth knowledge of digital and social media analytics,… https://t.co/IfEw8xCH0i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SCRUM Master: MetroStar Systems Careers ========================= SCRUM Master Program Management Suitland, Maryland Apply MetroStar Systems is looking for a Certified Scrum Master with a technical background that is passionate about leading technical… https://t.co/yYk279aGLo https://t.co/sMLjORs2kz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer II: Job Summary Independently code complex, n-tiered applications. principles of software engineering to the design, development, maintenance, testing and evaluation of the enterprise software and systems, as well as, interact with… https://t.co/o1tonan9hn https://t.co/f0ipJrzOe2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP FI/CO Consultant: SAP FI/CO consultant required to assist client on multiple projects in Ohio. Candidate should have at least 5+ years SAP experience and excellent communication skills. Please apply via this Jobserve link in this advert. https://t.co/9YYJ973CUC https://t.co/hC2p3RjadA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Software Engineer II: Bring your talent and skills to the Raytheon Intelligence, Information and Services (IIS) State College Engineering team! Our team is focused on providing solutions to challenging problems to enable the success of our… https://t.co/kK2FxkY25l https://t.co/VK8j4LEOMk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tinder Wants to Match You With People Who Go to the Same Places: The dating app is testing a new feature aimed at connecting users who hang out at the same spots. https://t.co/14jXUurXHN https://t.co/w5y4VZtgPF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sinkhole appears on White House lawn: A sinkhole has appeared steps from the entrance to the White House briefing room. https://t.co/s6dXB5lccQ https://t.co/H8ftk1C5l0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republicans rush to defend Ryan as rebellion rumors swirl: The rumors of House Speaker Paul Ryan's looming demise are exaggerated -- at least according to the very members who would be responsible for throwing him out earlier than his planned January… https://t.co/1vbOU3ZMoD https://t.co/N8vtwNtuL0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advisory Cyber Security: KPMG LLP, Manager, Advisory Cyber Security (Mult. Pos.), Santa Clara, CA. Monitor, detect, analyze, &amp; investigate threat activity of cloud infrastructure. Req’ts incl.: Master’s degree or foreign equiv. in IT, Comp. Sci., Comp.… https://t.co/JYt15Kf30B https://t.co/tJMg3tyVHY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President's legal team trying to get the special counsel to limit questions related to obstruction of justice: Donald Trump's legal team is trying to narrow the scope of the President's potential interview with special counsel Robert Mueller to questions… https://t.co/otpTtrQsJm https://t.co/8cQRYQXY5J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Developer: SAP Labs, LLC seeks a Senior Developer at our Palo Alto, CA location to be responsible for development focusing on design, coding, testing, quality assurance of complex product features in a development team. Bach dgr in Comp Sci, Engg,… https://t.co/hsB2fBmqO4 https://t.co/TSLWrYgYba]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ICT Technician: Overview Provides technical and end-user support of computer software and related equipment. Responsibilities Troubleshoot computer and basic telecommunications hardware and software to ensure that issues are investigated and resolved.… https://t.co/sOjlXArxYE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Batteries Still Suck, But Researchers Are Working on It: Technologists have devised a variety of ways in which lithium batteries can be tweaked to improve battery density, and maybe more importantly, battery safety. https://t.co/txEBzrd3ut https://t.co/maSTiZgW9m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ENGINEER: PLM: ENGINEER: PLM (Product Lifestyle Management) Research, design, evaluate, install, operate or maintain systems &amp; processes used to ensure mechanical products &amp; equipment meet requirements. MS in Mechanical Eng or equiv. field. 2 yrs exp as… https://t.co/KmW1hsJv49 https://t.co/etTQNbxHyz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[School shootings in the US outnumber other G7 nations: School shootings are a reality in America, an average of one a week just this year alone. https://t.co/NN3qzRLBfJ https://t.co/6KVCFfnXDC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer: COMPUTER/IT Senior Project Consultant-Development for SAP Labs, LLC (South San Francisco, CA) under suprvsn, wrk on small to midsize prjcts in dvlopmnt org w/modrte lvl of rsk &amp; cmplxty. Bach in Comp Sci, Eng, Math, Physics, Info Sys or rltd… https://t.co/tWgfL61LLS https://t.co/NuhPD2mhd0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starbucks changes its definition of a customer https://t.co/wctJ6z3HJ0 https://t.co/xFE9uS94uP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Performance Test Engineer – Requisition ID R47464: Requisition ID R47464 West Creek 8 (12080), United States of America, Richmond, VirginiaAt Capital One, we’re building a leading information-based technology company. Still founder-led by Chairman… https://t.co/MSXiUmFPNO https://t.co/WuhVEKrnMf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Lead: Global Fund Accounting Administration &amp; Shared Technology (GFAAST) serves to transform our global operating model, processes, technology, and data infrastructure to enable Fund Financial Services to scale efficiently with uncompromised… https://t.co/1pKBFVNPWd https://t.co/2iBn3BKaou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager Services – Contingent Upon Award: Location: Albuquerque, New Mexico Job type: Permanent Sector: Operations Category: Senior Manager Experience &amp; Education The Project Manager Services must have a Bachelor’s degree in Engineering,… https://t.co/kDuU71HdVL https://t.co/vCfHJbWpcT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Technical Lead: Req ID: 14989    At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The quality, integrity, and commitment of our employees are key factors in our company’s growth, market presence and our… https://t.co/UG5jkJwKjI https://t.co/dShl2GrKGq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Desktop Technician: About Us PCM is one of the fastest-growing value added direct marketers of technology solutions for business, government and educational institutions as well as consumers. We’ve built an environment that is fast-paced, growing and… https://t.co/BIajrChEM3 https://t.co/TjeJ9KgpmG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Security Policy Analyst: Clearance Level Must Currently Possess: Secret (NACLC) Clearance Level Must Be Able to Obtain: Secret Suitability: No Suitability Required Job Family: Information Technology Job Description: CSRA is seeking a Cyber Security… https://t.co/6ZddE1M2QB https://t.co/RgGB3KWZ9w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Programmer Analyst, Data Informatics: Job Snapshot Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Burlington, MA, US Job Type: Consulting Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 5/6/2018 Job Description The successful candidate will be an experienced, highly… https://t.co/0RTPCPrBbW https://t.co/qjoxwiotuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CNC Mill Set-Up Programmer: Job Description We are AAM. We have the POWER to move the world. At AAM, we’re looking for associates who push boundaries and drive solutions for the future. Innovators. Thinkers. Dreamers. Doers. No matter the role or… https://t.co/5Lts9E7E6B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jimmy Carter on world's biggest problem: Former President Jimmy Carter said that he believes the single greatest challenge facing the world is discrimination against women and girls, during a commencement address at Liberty University in Virginia. https://t.co/WNwNtTyw05 https://t.co/RQt25nkQ8L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DIRECTOR OF MATERIALS: SUMMARY Direct and oversee the operations associated with materials management to include receiving, warehousing, distribution, material handling, obsolete inventory, MRO inventory and inventory accuracy. Develop and manage the… https://t.co/RiqRsQ4Cao https://t.co/kYuoCWmfTv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manager, Site Reliability Engineering: The challenge The Adobe Marketing Cloud is a rapidly growing collection of services used by Adobe Marketing Solutions. The services are a global, software-as-a-service deployment used by Adobe’s top customers. As… https://t.co/2bm8FnlIHj https://t.co/ihvfosqyTE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solution Architect: The challenge Digital marketing is advancing at a dizzying pace and companies are turning to the Adobe Marketing Cloud, the leader in enterprise marketing software, to stay ahead. Solution Architects help Adobe Marketing Cloud… https://t.co/gesCuy731J https://t.co/2qn6Odyep6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: We are seeking a highly motivated Software Engineer to join the Enterprise Logging team which is part of IT Enterprise Monitoring.The IT Enterprise Monitoring team is responsible for monitoring the health of our applications and… https://t.co/6ugkfXj2mT https://t.co/jto7KijTvW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior BI Developer: About Blackbaud: Leading uniquely at the intersection point of technology and social good, Blackbaud provides software, services, expertise, and data intelligence that empowers and connects people to advance the social good movement.… https://t.co/89PGnmRdUs https://t.co/m0w0MMwQoe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[City reveals why it lost Amazon HQ2 bid https://t.co/axN0TWLx1m https://t.co/2pojxCGMOf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer, Creative Mobile Drawing: The challenge The Adobe Drawing &amp; Painting Applications team is reinventing digital drawing for a new generation of users and devices. We are seeking a highly motivated Software Engineer to develop compelling… https://t.co/hoALHRXsJL https://t.co/Q90eWarB7t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer with SOLR Experience (Rye): *** No one with less than 2 years industry experience will be considered. *** *** No third party candidates will be considered. *** Candidates MUST have a minimum of specific domain experience and no resumes… https://t.co/we4KHA1BMX https://t.co/0UkzHDhpBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best Weekend Tech Deals: Apple Watch, Neck Massagers, Monitors: Computer monitors, TVs, laptops, desktops, and even the Apple Watch are all on sale this weekend. https://t.co/9ARjrzB1lT https://t.co/840z8mIKZV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haircutter: Overview SmartStyle is the smart choice for so many reasons. At SmartStyle, you’ll have everything you need to be successful! Built-in traffic of more than 5,000 people a day u2013 that’s like being exposed to an entire town of people u2013… https://t.co/DbNXqNtjlk https://t.co/ssw9Abd4OW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital Applications Tester: What you’ll be doing…The Customer Experience Testing and Certification (CETC) team is looking for a highly energetic, motivated and talented individuals for testing end to end stack of applications as a part of One Fiber… https://t.co/QwcArlEAIA https://t.co/H8B9S8vweA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Specialist Electrical Vehicle Systems Engineer: For Eaton Specialist Electrical Vehicle Systems Engineer job – Engineering – Multiple Skip to Main Content – Products – Services – Markets – Support – Company – Toggle navigation – Products – Services –… https://t.co/1isGMfokqG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump really wants the (North Korean) show to go on: President Donald Trump wants Kim Jong Un to understand he really wants them to meet. https://t.co/kRTLiJG4HA https://t.co/oW64TYbch8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mom: I told my daughter, 'run, baby': A shooter has been reported at Texas' Santa Fe High School, the school district there said. The district is on lockdown. https://t.co/ABaLDAaQbP https://t.co/TI0WsTEouf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C# Developer – Financial: Looking for highly educated C# Developers that have exposure to the Financial industry. Must have a degree from a named school and have a GPA 3.8 or better. You will have 3+ years C# Backend development. You will develop custom… https://t.co/MmjfNIwzJt https://t.co/MkDh9oq7CD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Apps Developer: Senior Apps Developer Skip Navigation Raytheon – Cyber – News – What We Do – Who We Are – Global – Investors – Careers – Visit:Cyber – Who We Are – Leaders – Businesses – Corporate Responsibility – Culture – History – Diversity –… https://t.co/UnF8gl7owh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Summit of Kilauea volcano erupts: An eruption from the Kilauea volcano's summit shot ash and smoke into the air early Thursday on Hawaii's Big Island, and the resulting plume is expected to cover the surrounding area, according to the Hawaiian Volcano… https://t.co/zBcJSxgJ4r https://t.co/qUSvSmVuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales Engineer: Sales Engineer ID 2015-6104 Category Technical Support Location US-NY-New York Responsibilities https://t.co/1sgJWtc2ZR seeks a bright, self-motivated Sales Engineer (SE) to join our “startup within an established company” for our global… https://t.co/EkMMUpzH8U https://t.co/5aITZzlpmj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: VMware, Inc. has multiple openings at various professional levels in Palo Alto, CA. The following software engineering positions develop and/or execute software, testing and validation procedures, programming and documentation: Member… https://t.co/W1GrEnvQY0 https://t.co/7PRrxS4Qfg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doctor: Yanny vs. Laurel is all in your head: What are we to make of the latest perceptual debate taking over the internet, separating loved ones from each other, causing chaos, sobbing, grief? https://t.co/3EsB9gyNGl https://t.co/XzDFMtP7Fh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quotes Engineering Manager, Platform Engineering #FSQE01: Quotes Engineering Manager, Platform Engineering FactSet Research Systems, Inc., Norwalk, CT. Manage team of software engineers in Quotes Content team w/in Market Data Engineering. Minimum… https://t.co/q4y63DU8n3 https://t.co/xjViXMpngJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bike Commuter Buying Guide: 14 City Cycling Essentials: Even if you’re not a cycling pro, this stuff will help you ride to work like one. https://t.co/nrKwDCljvH https://t.co/smBYeLQUMK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Haspel's approach to terror prepared her to be America's top spy: Gina Haspel is all but guaranteed to become the next director of the Central Intelligence Agency after she gained the approval of the Senate Intelligence Committee on Wednesday and the… https://t.co/T1PuxqyARJ https://t.co/68FvqvTHFa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PeopleSoft HCM Developer: MULTIPLE OPENINGS IN CRYSTAL CITY, VA. Performs application development, configuration and unit testing for the IPPS-A project. Participates in development, integration and deployment of solutions. This role is responsible for… https://t.co/Bzd40kWjSy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Java Developer: Our Company: Altec Inc., founded in 1929, is a privately held company headquartered in Birmingham, Alabama. Altec specializes in the manufacture, sale and service of aerial devices, digger derricks, cranes and specialty equipment for… https://t.co/KjxggjR8AD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New docs out on 2016 Trump Tower meeting: The Senate Judiciary Committee has published thousands of pages of interviews with people in the room during a June 2016 Trump Tower meeting where Donald Trump Jr. was promised dirt on Hillary Clinton. CNN's Evan… https://t.co/wjAeGRwqA1 https://t.co/7mB9O1Uckl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator: PayPal, Inc. has the following job opportunities in San Jose, CA: Global Pricing SOX Operations (Req.#16-3596): Work w/ SOX (Sarbanes-Oxley) Internal Controls program planning activities for Pricing process, including materiality,… https://t.co/xXYvFCrTet https://t.co/GC2qc3afUl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network/DevOps Engineer: Network/DevOps Engineer sought by Metapro USA LLC in Overland Park, KS (and other US locations as needed) to bld &amp; dply apps using techs such as Jenkins, puppet, &amp; Maven. Domestic trvl req as needed. Apply at… https://t.co/hrsogQ8Kt7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: Transcripts give Mueller more fodder: What can we learn about the Russia probe from the thousands of pages released by the Senate Judiciary Committee Wednesday? The voluminous testimony and exhibits pertaining to the June 2016 Trump Tower… https://t.co/pChiY1cghG https://t.co/mWV4yRLqTt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Astronomers have found the fastest-growing black hole ever seen, and it's got a monster appetite: Astronomers have found the fastest-growing black hole ever seen in the universe, and they're calling this one a monster with an appetite. It's growing so… https://t.co/pwq3N5vwht https://t.co/v1RKMrRhjQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Support Staff to do Breaks 11:00-3p: Description: KinderCare Education is the nation’s leader in early childhood education. We nourish curiosity through purposeful experiences to create a future full of lifelong learners. From our National Support… https://t.co/CEyHjlxBgm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Graduation Gift Ideas: The 16 Best Gifts For Your Recent College Grad: Here are 16 of the best graduation gift ideas for the newly-minted grad in your life. https://t.co/BCojUiTadA https://t.co/aZh8e9lHUO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He just lost his second election in a matter of months: Republican state Rep. Rick Saccone is now zero-for-two in his campaigns for the US House in Pennsylvania this year. https://t.co/ki0HgMDLsG https://t.co/ICi1swCvci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Developer (.NET): The senior level developer is responsible for working as part of a collaborative development team to create working software applications based on our customers requirements using .NET and related technologies, and leading other… https://t.co/bwVz10SLlL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deputy Program Manager 2 – Systems Cyber Team:   Job Description – Deputy Program Manager 2 – Systems Cyber Team (18009430) Deputy Program Manager 2 – Systems Cyber Team Requisition ID : 18009430 Location : United States-Colorado-Boulder US Citizenship… https://t.co/Ftepl9vFiN]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>