<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Music: Riley, Scanlon, Hanley, Smith  Words: Smith https://t.co/JLQifbCeAh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BlindTasters: Alcoholism prevention poster, France, circa 1954: 'Health, sobriety: never more than a litre of wine a day'. Two years la…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Containers and their drivers" https://t.co/bbm09f8GMo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stan_chow Oh no! An English genius. Sui generis https://t.co/EKaILPfzkQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AliceFishburn: Subscribe to great journalism. It gets things done. https://t.co/bnFw1W0gBN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chapeau to @johnmcternan for taking the argument to the Corbynite left in the spirit of comradeship. The result is a very rich discussion https://t.co/32OFkl4W3h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @helenbarrett: Footballers are famed for their disastrous business sense. @VincentKompany is the exception - as he explains on @Financia…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TonyTassell: The shocking @FT investigation led by @miss_marriage into sexual harassment at a charity dinner for men at the top of the…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Men Only: Inside the charity fundraiser where hostesses are put on show https://t.co/PpLDKvDyyh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If the 1918 H1N1 virus were to break out of the facility in Atlanta it would cause around thirty million deaths" https://t.co/DettimaMxf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An appalling case: "Folie ou acte antisémite ? Neuf mois après, le meurtre de Sarah Halimi reste inexpliqué" https://t.co/ybJth8gpPK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thoroughly enjoying Geoffrey Smith's exploration of the career of Keith Jarrett  https://t.co/Dcf6RF6KL0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Silvio Berlusconi flexes his political muscle in Italy again - @TonyBarber8 on yet another comeback https://t.co/f3PILiM0ys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intermittently illuminating Dissent symposium on the uses and abuses of the term "neoliberalism" https://t.co/5Q8jToGKL0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rafaelbehr: This is good. Also sobering. https://t.co/jHKhJDwe6D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brother Jack McDuff - sanctified! https://t.co/FwOFidtVJu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_paullay @lindasgrant @TomRollinson1 With that book, it's impossible to know which one you're referring to, though I have an idea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @scott_abbie: The @FT is now offering FREE subscriptions to all 16-19 year olds worldwide. Schools can register at https://t.co/n6iclxaZ…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @londonsoc: You can now read the latest edition of the London Society Journal online https://t.co/XKw5dKdW8i https://t.co/jPUblM42Mb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @khalafroula: New FT Series
UK Privatisation Revisited https://t.co/jbkt0EPGka]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Superb piece by @Grepsul on Carillion, intangibles and the perils of sunkenness  https://t.co/nJdK7j59rK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @soniastolper: Concert de louanges outre-Manche après l'interview de Macron à la BBC https://t.co/i9CYPWP2tO via @libe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful website devoted to the work of the late Peter Campbell https://t.co/BNDjENgf2J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Superb review of book about My Lai by Max Hastings that raises profound questions about barbarism and laws of war https://t.co/KWEvKSk8a1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @olivierfaye: Une certaine idée de la refondation du FN https://t.co/TPhAkAwIcG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobertSYates Re-design is superb. Congratulations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wannwennnicht I don't think so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Giving interview in English is one thing. But stikl more impressed by comments he made on MS of Ricoeur's last book. https://t.co/DF4C3XQaRu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@davies_will Tony Travers's analysis of them as "parastatal" has always seeme to me very powerful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @henrywinter: Shame on @premierleague and @EFL for not organising a nationwide tribute to Cyrille Regis this weekend. His old clubs plan…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's the best of the FT's commentary this week on the collapse of Carillion in one place https://t.co/LxgatKo9Z8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best of enemies: Robert Tombs for @ftcomment on the long history of Anglo-French relations https://t.co/BZjkQJNQV5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alan Ryan in @nybooks says Burke would have been horrified at Cameron's decision to call the EU referendum https://t.co/ujTpG9R67p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember well his 1995-96 seminar on hospitality https://t.co/rG0WPSlFJi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This looks good: 1968, day by day https://t.co/jMRykkHlQS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GeorgeShiber: I miss Sidney

A student once interrupted him and said, "I just don't understand." 
He responded: "Why should you have th…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Unmentionable Season of Death - an utterly terrifying piece by Antony Beevor on the siege of Leningrad https://t.co/ePKBo8mFuv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @oxmartinschool: "The most impressive post-crisis effort of rethinking how macroeconomics should be done, by many of the field’s top pra…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@ChrisGiles_ on why the theory of 'constrained optimisation' won't work in the second phase of the Brexit talks https://t.co/C8BlRouG05]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SebastianEPayne @FTCakeTrolley @konditorandcook Fake news.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this the end of the age of plastic, asks design historian Penny Sparke https://t.co/QyTa8dgndX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caro says an entire section of The Power Broker on Jane Jacobs was cut. Version he gave Knopf was 1,050,000 words.  https://t.co/qsjo6hYO27]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Philip Roth on America and the "worship of jackals by jackasses" https://t.co/7d0I4qEyrR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carillion's downfall shows dumb money knows no borders - v good by @patrickjenkins_ on the Landesbanken and Schuldschein https://t.co/RW3uK6RhEA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rodrikdani: Yes. This distinction between pluralism by juxtaposition versus integration is important. I agree with Sam Bowles that we s…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @hugorifkind: I don't normally retweet stuff like this, but this long thread might be useful for anybody still wondering whether the US…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These guys - Ruby Rushton of @22amusic -are supporting Mulatu Astatke at the Barbican in March. Catch them if you can https://t.co/sOT901UUnq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @markvdvd: Applications are open for the @FT's Paul McClean graduate trainee scheme.

Insatiably curious? Audacious enough to ask for a…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@MPJVincent has been writing up a storm on the Carillion debacle  https://t.co/7OsNuVfBLw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's right. Martin's series this week on the future of macroeconomics is well worth following
https://t.co/B1HyGC2yIE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting from @WendyCarlinEcon and Sam Bowles on the need for pluralism in the teaching of economics https://t.co/p5b0ZALVoK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could 2018 be the year of fake economic data, asks @ChrisGiles_ https://t.co/GqywE3jKD5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a sorry spectacle the Parti Socialiste is at the moment  https://t.co/3xz6z3tKFs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @katie_martin_fx: Carillion: the "lawful Ponzi scheme" that was in need of a "shitometer" 
 https://t.co/4cwY4LlJv3 via @FT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thoroughly enjoyed the magnificent Ruby Rushton this evening. South London's finest https://t.co/hP9E0XMoZr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ftcomment: Watch the markets and the money flows https://t.co/ZobNK83TeH https://t.co/eVMLcc1InS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @gideonrachman: My latest column on Europe’s biggest test will come in Poland https://t.co/wZR8TZVVrx via @financialtimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Britain needs its own New Brandeis Movement to tackle the 'curse of bigness' - @jameskirkup for @ftcomment https://t.co/vI30Gnn5Sk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @prospect_uk: Carillion isn't the only firm that could fail. In 2014, @jderbyshire found similar risks with Serco and G4S https://t.co/D…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This week, @MESandbu will be devoting Free Lunch to a series of posts on the future of macroeconomics. Here's the first https://t.co/WNKTk2gwb7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MartinSelmayr: Now even WolfgangMünchau @EuroBriefing is positive about #future of Europe + German #GroKo commitment: "biggest push by…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnmcternan Sure. But the question of the size of these companies remains - as my piece, which was agnostic on the principle of outsourcing, made clear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wrote this a few years back on megafirms whose raison d'être is to win govt contracts. Seems relevant today https://t.co/DgWwkG0Bob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reading François Dosse's book, I'm reminded that Macron cited Bataille's La part maudite in his address to the congress at Versailles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeyyLowe Sending a copy of this to Marr now https://t.co/mQkgDevXDD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @johnthornhillft: ‘Convenience is the new religion in China.’ Great piece by @duncanclark on how the Chinese tech giants are forging ahe…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@richard_king @HonestJonsLDN Yes. Got that. Lovely record.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A landmark of British jazz: Joe Harriott's Free Form (acquired @HonestJonsLDN's yesterday on a rare excursion west) https://t.co/nONICtb3T9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @adam_tooze: "AlphaZero, to my joy, sacrifices” … “enormous piece activity, and black is tied up in knots”. Fascinating on the logic of…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @harikunzru: Apollinaire on the ones and twos. https://t.co/7oAWsq77Qu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pleased to have had hand in genesis of @Nicklezard's NS column almost ten years ago. Today more compelling than ever https://t.co/nXHZKjJHG2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone would think @MADarbyshire had been writing these columns for years. Here she is wryly funny on what happens when your parents leave home https://t.co/WpHu9fppB4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Daniel Lindenberg, author of Le Rappel a l'ordre, is dead - obituary by @JeanBirnbaum and Nicolas Weill https://t.co/tohSJjkJeT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ClaudiaChwalisz: "Je ne suis pas une petite chose fragile. Je ne réclame pas d’être protégée mais de faire valoir mes droits à la sécur…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TonyTassell: Japan girl band gives voice to cryptocurrencies - lovely piece by @Urbandirt on an ensemble with maid outfits, Mexican mas…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is very good: @TimHarford on how to spot a bubble (includes some myth-busting on tulip-mania in 17th-century Holland) https://t.co/uL9yGZ8I9m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now on a Melville-Delon binge (merci @adam_tooze) https://t.co/M4ibmRhGVU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IPR_NickP @GavinJKelly1 @po_qu @ftcomment Martin Wolf's latest will be grist to your mill, I'd have thought https://t.co/gSxExFJ33g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IPR_NickP @GavinJKelly1 @po_qu One to look forward to: two of the finest minds on the British centre-left (and @ftcomment contributors to boot) https://t.co/mG5l3WgqCG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KonbiniFr: Kamaal Williams, BadBadNotGood ou encore Ezra Collective... Voici 5 jeunes artistes qui prouvent que le Jazz n'est pas du to…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ftcomment: Re-nationalising utilities is the wrong answer to a real question https://t.co/puLg0qxbXN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pleased to see @GeorgeProchnik's Stranger in a Strange Land on this list https://t.co/8styZQ3j8p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent from @ChassNews on #BalanceTonPorc v Deneuve et al https://t.co/2gyvZsBMVr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lemondefr: Gallimard suspend son projet de réédition des pamphlets antisémites de Céline https://t.co/B7KQUHyWFU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@gideonrachman on how North Korea is trying to drive a wedge between Seoul and Washington https://t.co/nPGAo7gzD7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada is Britain's likeliest post-Brexit destination, argues @martinwolf_ https://t.co/lYrqG0LGkv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @resfoundation: Another absolute must-read column from Sarah O Connor - one of the Commissioners on our Intergenerational Commission htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Important series by @MESandbu on the economics of Big Tech. Today, the harm caused by untrammelled market power https://t.co/ADzubfCK3B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Grepsul: John McDonnell is right: Britain can easily nationalise water via @FT
 https://t.co/H0hAQHE4iu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@greenmiranda identifies three ways to fix UK university financing  https://t.co/zxYzvlaU4s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@johnthornhillft on technocracy and the 'revolt of the engineers' https://t.co/RxBMDXVQkQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marvellous piece by Geoff Dyer on the magnificent photographs of Gary Winogrand https://t.co/x3bjLG216c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@AndreiSoldatov for @ftcomment on how the Kremlin mastered the art of outsourcing its cyber disinformation campaigns https://t.co/Sx04vLVfGp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today in 1968 - this @libe daily series on that tumultuous year is excellent https://t.co/JhLyP8Gevp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @brownswood: L'actualité du jazz : We Out Here, London by night… et par Shabaka https://t.co/DbqrEpCEc6 via @francemusique]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andyhamamatsu That pub has a choice of *three* meads, for heaven's sake!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sally__Williams Turner Contemporary, Margate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twombly https://t.co/j4lCeD8x9d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a bout of medieval madness, my wife is now drinking mead https://t.co/wXGMUeMJ12]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the wonderful Lifeboat in Margate, with its fine selection of beers, ciders, perry and ... mead https://t.co/W9Oky5R2Z5]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>