<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. SharePoint Developer: Jobs Toggle navigation * Sign In * Sign Up * Help Career Portal * Failure Message Cannot parse, seems some issue with the profile, please create the profile manually Alert Message Job Post has been updated successfully *… https://t.co/AxXWyopHev]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Developer/Architect SharePoint/Office 365/Angular: Portal Solutions (now part of the Withum Team) Microsoft Solutions and Service practice helps organizations share what they know and find what they need by connecting people, data, and content. We… https://t.co/BTImxVny3t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Nintex Developer: Prestigious Enterprise Company is currently seeking a Developer with SharePoint and ****** experience, as well as some Nintex exposure. Candidate will be responsible for end-user computing development using the Microsoft… https://t.co/Lej8wpLtkd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Administrator:   Job Description &amp;#8211; SharePoint Administrator (18006042) SharePoint Administrator Requisition ID : 18006042 Location : United States-Georgia-Atlanta US Citizenship Required for this Position: No Relocation Assistance: No… https://t.co/iNWfZa0KX7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sharepoint Administrator UNIX/Linux Administrator (Multiple Positions): Point Administrator Atlanta, GA 15 Months Job Summary: Under broad supervision, installs, configures, and supports the client Point-based infrastructure and associated applications.… https://t.co/y05CVrWTyX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Change Manager (Greenbelt, MD): Description:The SE&amp;#38;I Change Manager will establish and manage a structured change management program on behalf of US Census Bureaus (USCB) System Engineering and Integration (SE&amp;#38;I) team. &amp;#160; Responsibilities:… https://t.co/nJ15KBP5fq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint and O365 Developer: Description: THE COMPANY Are you interested in helping solve today&amp;#8217;s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing… https://t.co/AmhJcTc6L3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Team Lead Job: Date: Mar 9, 2018 Location: Washington, DC, US Company: SAIC SharePoint Team Lead (Job Number:432851) Description: Job Description This contract position is the lead member of a SharePoint team that supports an independent… https://t.co/U1ot7bcKjy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project manager with sharepoint exp: Project manager with sharepoint exp Ref No.: 18-11897 Location: Redmond, Washington Job Description:- Position : Project manager with sharepoint exp Location : Redmond, WA Type : Contract (12 Months) a) Taking… https://t.co/8yOoAgJou1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sharepoint Developer -TS/SCI Polygraph required: Description: The Defense and Intelligence Division of Leidos has a career opportunity for a Sharepoint Developer with a TS/SCI with polygraph clearance in Annapolis Junction, Maryland. PROGRAM SUMMARY: Do… https://t.co/4yR3lOs2NX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Development Requirements Analyst Job: Date: Feb 26, 2018 Location: Washington, DC, US Company: SAIC SharePoint Development Requirements Analyst (Job Number:434441) Description: Job Description &amp;#8211; This contract position is a key member of… https://t.co/yRhoqlTd2T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Network Engineer: Description:Leidos has a career opportunity for a Senior Network Engineer in Honolulu, HI. Candidates must possess a current TS/SCI security clearance in order to be considered. The individual will be required to conduct… https://t.co/mgtq1grKuf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For Apple, Quitting Intel Won't Come Easy: It makes all the sense in the world that Apple wants to leave Intel behind. Where it gets tricky is how it gets there. https://t.co/7d9Tnk2oHp https://t.co/VfFiKGnJZi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Nintex Developer: Prestigious Enterprise Company is currently seeking a Developer with SharePoint and ****** experience, as well as some Nintex exposure. Candidate will be responsible for end-user computing development using the Microsoft… https://t.co/eTk0Ne6zDc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Developer – JavaScript SharePoint: Title Senior Developer &amp;#8211; JavaScript &amp;#038; SharePoint ========================================== EOE Statement We are an equal employment opportunity employer. All qualified applicants will receive… https://t.co/9c5PunklGu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Sharepoint &amp; collaboration: * worked on medium &amp;#8211; large size projects ($1 million +) * managed a team of 5-10 members or more * worked on a project that required them managing multiple workstreams concurrently PROJECT SPECIFICS:… https://t.co/UeGx9tqkFt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer, .Net / Sharepoint: The St Louis Fed is one of 12 Reserve Banks serving all or parts of Missouri, Illinois, Indiana, Kentucky, Tennessee, Mississippi and Arkansas with branches in Little Rock, Louisville and Memphis. The St. Louis Feds most… https://t.co/2532joTC1E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Monitoring Engineer (Greenbelt, MD): Description:The Monitoring Engineer will primarily be responsible for the overall monitoring, maintenance of the Network Operations Center. They are the first point of contact responsible for reactively monitoring… https://t.co/Lxu06spbq9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Admininistrator / Developer: SharePoint Admininistrator / Developer Location: Herndon, VA Job Code: 3200 # of openings: 1 Description Bay State Computers, Inc. is a professional services firm and a leading provider of Information Technology… https://t.co/02sxS7xeEC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: Description: The Origin program is in need of an experienced SharePoint developer to design, build, configure, maintain and conceptualize complex and detailed SharePoint sites for our customer on various customer systems.  There is… https://t.co/yPadHpS91F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint SME: SharePoint SME Location: Washington, DC Job Code: 3265 # of openings: 1 Description Bay State Computers, Inc. is a professional services firm and a leading provider of Information Technology (IT) services and products to the U.S. Federal… https://t.co/RJN9ebY065]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET / Web Developer: Would you like to perform rewarding work while contributing to the success of an established, growing company? Pragmatics, Inc. is seeking ***** / Web Developer to support a Government customer in Washington, DC. As the .NET / Web… https://t.co/77VffskOvM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Solutions Architect – Supervision Group: Job Summary Technology developer, designer, and innovator with a strong business orientation to create business-driven applications using SharePoint, Nintex and other web-based collaboration… https://t.co/Zku6h5VOYs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Project Manager: Associate Project Manager JOB SUMMARY The Associate Project Manager supports cross-functional program teams to ensure projects meet objectives and are delivered on-time. Under the general supervision of a Manager or Director,… https://t.co/G9rfyPkJkT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Inside Story of Reddit's Redesign: Goodbye, dystopian Craigslist. There's a new Reddit, and it's all grown up. https://t.co/H0Brpxm80Y https://t.co/pHNCK0twYt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Administrator/Developer: JOB DESCRIPTION: Resource 1 is seeking a SharePoint Administrator/Developer for a 6-month contract-for-hire opportunity in Chicago, IL. The selected candidate should have experience in Microsoft Technologies,… https://t.co/IefbUaE1EG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Systems Security Officer (IA Security Specialist [Journeyman]) – 16588: Description Huntington Ingalls Industries &amp;#8211; Technical Solutions Division, Integrated Mission Solutions Group (Camber Corporation) provides mission-critical… https://t.co/sHPF7Fusk7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: NETE Point Developer Rockville, MD 20852 NET ESOLUTIONS CORPORATION (NETE) is a multi-award winning company founded in 1999. NETE is a full service Information Technology (IT) company dedicated to providing value focused consulting… https://t.co/rVluNOZPQN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Configuration Management Analyst: Description: The job of the Configuration Management (CM) Analyst is to perform the necessary functions to maintain configuration control of aircraft system hardware and software configurations. PRIMARY… https://t.co/0ShsDJ6sVK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C4ISR Senior Systems Engineer: Description:Leidos has an opening for a C4ISR Senior Systems Engineer at Joint Base Pearl Harbor-Hickam, Hawaii.&amp;#160; This position requires an active TS/SCI clearance.&amp;#160; Duties:&amp;#160; The candidate will analyze and… https://t.co/2aeOSzvmO3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Architect – Chicago, IL: Job Type:PermanentDate Posted:12th February 2018Location:Chicago, IllinoisContact Name:Christopher CriscuoloTelephone:Reference:NFI272018CC2 Salary:$100000 &amp;#8211; $120000 per annum SharePoint Architect &amp;#8211;… https://t.co/YQuK00mVw8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Target Development Network Analyst 16080: Description Huntington Ingalls Industries &amp;#8211; Technical Solutions Division, Integrated Mission Solutions Group (Camber Corporation) provides mission-critical engineering and technical service to Information… https://t.co/ntM48tnPVZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Security Watch Officer: Description: Global Information Grid (GIG) Service Management-Operations (GSM-O), a Defense and Intelligence Group of Leidos has an opening for a Cyber Security&amp;#160;Watch Officer&amp;#160;at the JFHQ DODIN Operations Center on… https://t.co/GHnTNqBOqH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: Description:Leidos has a current job opportunity for an experienced SharePoint Developer with expertise in JavaScript to support our DISA customer on the GSM-O program. This position is located in Chambersburg, PA. JOB DESCRIPTION… https://t.co/4jOVjEyZlm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CND Analyst (Network Senior) – 16399: Description Huntington Ingalls Industries &amp;#8211; Technical Solutions Division, Integrated Mission Solutions Group (Camber Corporation) provides mission-critical engineering and technical service to Information… https://t.co/VOGEIn3Rmm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: SharePoint Developer Minnkota Power Cooperative is seeking qualified candidates for the position of SharePoint Developer located in our Grand Forks offices. This position is responsible for the design, development and maintenance of… https://t.co/vXOqlBiAwm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Product Team Lead: Description: The Leidos Civil Health Operations is seeking a Product Team Lead/Software Lead&amp;#160;to support a program for the FDA in&amp;#160;Rockville, MD and Baltimore, MD.&amp;#160; &amp;#160; &amp;#160; The Systems for Inspections, Recalls,… https://t.co/cyqt8Kknx1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Stop Eye Strain: Tips, Tricks, and Apps: The aching eyes, sore muscles, and headaches caused by eye strain can be prevented by following these tips. https://t.co/p8NSkVjJ5G https://t.co/LUGPpuy6km]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior SharePoint Developer: LCG is seeking a Senior SharePoint Developer to join a highly skilled Agile web development team. The team develops web applications predominantly using .Net, SharePoint, Angular JS, SQL Server and does Customization and… https://t.co/0JFD7vjRq0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer Systems Analyst Subject Matter Expert 16496: #CyberJobs #CamberIT Technical Solutions Description Huntington Ingalls Industries &amp;#8211; Technical Solutions Division, Integrated Mission Solutions Group (Camber Corporation) provides… https://t.co/tRiEfUtqdi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Systems Analyst – Division of Supervision and Regulation: The Information Systems Analyst is responsible for the design, implementation, and support of complex automated distributed systems essential to carrying out the responsibilities and… https://t.co/NlmiAH4NlV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[systems engineer: Company Description Commvault is the world&amp;#8217;s most powerful backup and recovery software in the cloud and on any infrastructure, helping companies transform their data into a powerful strategic asset. Commvault data protection and… https://t.co/61ZyzDjkQB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer, .Net / Sharepoint: The St Louis Fed is one of 12 Reserve Banks serving all or parts of Missouri, Illinois, Indiana, Kentucky, Tennessee, Mississippi and Arkansas with branches in Little Rock, Louisville and Memphis. The St. Louis Fed&amp;#8217;s… https://t.co/QWIHJUH1Q4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Project Manager: Associate Project Manager JOB SUMMARY The Associate Project Manager supports cross-functional program teams to ensure projects meet objectives and are delivered on-time. Under the general supervision of a Manager or Director,… https://t.co/QQnOUBT5Hz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint SME: SharePoint SME Location: Washington, DC Job Code: 3265 # of openings: 1 Description Bay State Computers, Inc. is a professional services firm and a leading provider of Information Technology (IT) services and products to the U.S. Federal… https://t.co/OlfuyIV4O3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: JOB TITLE: SHAREPOINT DEVELOPER LOCATION: PEACHTREE CITY, GEORGIA CLEARANCE: ACTIVE SECRET CLEARANCE CITIZENSHIP: US CITIZEN POSITION OVERVIEW: Swingtech is seeking a talented SharePoint Developer to provide on-site enterprise… https://t.co/9ZVOnC8xUf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior SharePoint Developer: LCG is seeking a Senior SharePoint Developer to join a highly skilled Agile web development team. The team develops web applications predominantly using .Net, SharePoint, Angular JS, SQL Server and does Customization and… https://t.co/lyApTvg24p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[systems engineer: Company Description Commvault is the world&amp;#8217;s most powerful backup and recovery software in the cloud and on any infrastructure, helping companies transform their data into a powerful strategic asset. Commvault data protection and… https://t.co/4p9OxnjfvO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Administrator/Developer: JOB DESCRIPTION: Resource 1 is seeking a SharePoint Administrator/Developer for a 6-month contract-for-hire opportunity in Chicago, IL. The selected candidate should have experience in Microsoft Technologies,… https://t.co/0LU3V6C1FH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Solutions Architect – Supervision Group: Job Summary Technology developer, designer, and innovator with a strong business orientation to create business-driven applications using SharePoint, Nintex and other web-based collaboration… https://t.co/vCWiGMKxnq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tech Tools to Help With Hand and Arm Injuries: For those who have recently injured or lost their dominant hand, everything from apps to bungees exist to ease the frustration. https://t.co/XdRuduuKhY https://t.co/ImP2ChNnQy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Systems Analyst – Division of Supervision and Regulation: The Information Systems Analyst is responsible for the design, implementation, and support of complex automated distributed systems essential to carrying out the responsibilities and… https://t.co/8sREB7VnRA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: InfosysMSWTPU Technology Lead &amp;#8211; US SharePoint Online / O365 &amp;#8211; Wilmington, DE Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to create and execute strategies… https://t.co/rYHU4BZe8a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: NETE Point Developer Rockville, MD 20852 NET ESOLUTIONS CORPORATION (NETE) is a multi-award winning company founded in 1999. NETE is a full service Information Technology (IT) company dedicated to providing value focused consulting… https://t.co/LwECCbvfuI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Administrator:   Job Description &amp;#8211; SharePoint Administrator (18006042) SharePoint Administrator Requisition ID : 18006042 Location : United States-Georgia-Atlanta US Citizenship Required for this Position: No Relocation Assistance: No… https://t.co/2t5mAy1Da9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Admininistrator / Developer: SharePoint Admininistrator / Developer Location: Herndon, VA Job Code: 3200 # of openings: 1 Description Bay State Computers, Inc. is a professional services firm and a leading provider of Information Technology… https://t.co/4KzEaJ9q95]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Developer – JavaScript SharePoint: Title Senior Developer &amp;#8211; JavaScript &amp;#038; SharePoint ========================================== EOE Statement We are an equal employment opportunity employer. All qualified applicants will receive… https://t.co/CRJOyzQaEA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: Infosys Engineering Services Technology Lead US Document Controller Are you looking for a change? Do you want to collaborate with some of the best talent in the industry? Are you ready to join a company whose passion is to really… https://t.co/MTYm6Lhy1C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Developer/Architect SharePoint/Office 365/Angular: Portal Solutions (now part of the Withum Team) Microsoft Solutions and Service practice helps organizations share what they know and find what they need by connecting people, data, and content. We… https://t.co/7STzmrNfck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Development Requirements Analyst Job: Date: Feb 26, 2018 Location: Washington, DC, US Company: SAIC SharePoint Development Requirements Analyst (Job Number:434441) Description: Job Description &amp;#8211; This contract position is a key member of… https://t.co/R9tQx8hL50]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Management Specialist 15385: Camber Corporation is seeking a Database Programming and Data AnalysisSpecialistto join our diverse, team-oriented company that is customer focused &amp;#8211; employee driven. The successful candidate will join our team… https://t.co/H0v8v4ndvk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. SharePoint Developer: Summit Technologies is looking for a Sr. SharePoint Developer to join our team in Washington, DC. The candidate will be responsible for the successful development, deployment, and integration of the customers SharePoint system… https://t.co/OiTiRmbDDZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With ‘Sniffs’ and ‘Licks,’ Petzbe Makes Social Media Nice Again: When people are impersonating their pets online, they tend to be really, really nice. https://t.co/6kn5dFQXYV https://t.co/IXZ3apdmlg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Target Development Network Analyst 16094: Description Huntington Ingalls Industries &amp;#8211; Technical Solutions Division, Integrated Mission Solutions Group (Camber Corporation) provides mission-critical engineering and technical service to Information… https://t.co/V4tfDGh1sO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid level Developer – JavaScript Sharepoint: Title Mid level Developer &amp;#8211; JavaScript &amp;#038; Sharepoint ============================================= EOE Statement We are an equal employment opportunity employer. All qualified applicants will receive… https://t.co/JC3qEqxSYe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Email System Administrator: Why Join Altec? If you&amp;#8217;re considering a career with Altec, Inc., there&amp;#8217;s never been a better time to join us! Our Company was founded based upon values that place the customer first, and view people as our greatest… https://t.co/cEOr45Ubt5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Collaboration Project Manager: Job Description * Manage projects related to collaboration tools adoption or migrations including but not limited to Dropbox, Box, Zoho and Office 365 suite of apps * Manage escalations pertaining to collaboration tools;… https://t.co/8AsxNUw6ID]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Nintex Developer: Prestigious Enterprise Company is currently seeking a Developer with SharePoint and ****** experience, as well as some Nintex exposure. Candidate will be responsible for end-user computing development using the Microsoft… https://t.co/2MuS5LmA5T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Solutions Architect – Supervision Group: Job Summary Technology developer, designer, and innovator with a strong business orientation to create business-driven applications using SharePoint, Nintex and other web-based collaboration… https://t.co/Lf5eeUYVaI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: Jobs Toggle navigation * Sign In * Sign Up * Help Career Portal * Failure Message Cannot parse, seems some issue with the profile, please create the profile manually Alert Message Job Post has been updated successfully * Position… https://t.co/zylRHWD2WG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid level Developer – JavaScript Sharepoint: Title Mid level Developer &amp;#8211; JavaScript &amp;#038; Sharepoint ============================================= EOE Statement We are an equal employment opportunity employer. All qualified applicants will receive… https://t.co/ufy4E26HTq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Team Lead Job: Date: Mar 9, 2018 Location: Washington, DC, US Company: SAIC SharePoint Team Lead (Job Number:432851) Description: Job Description This contract position is the lead member of a SharePoint team that supports an independent… https://t.co/gXg4z6fDVJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager CRM: The Dynamics NAV Project Manager will ensure that project teams have a full understanding of the customers requirements and the direction for a Dynamics NAV solution. In addition, they will oversee and manage the planning, design and… https://t.co/OiP2nf1ZTK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. SharePoint Specialist: Job Location: Little Creek, VA Job Title: Senior SharePoint Specialist Position Summary DRS Seeks a full time Senior SharePoint Specialist (SPS) to support the Enterprise Knowledge Management requirements for the Naval Special… https://t.co/PU8ooqr3C6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Development Requirements Analyst Job: Date: Feb 26, 2018 Location: Washington, DC, US Company: SAIC SharePoint Development Requirements Analyst (Job Number:434441) Description: Job Description &amp;#8211; This contract position is a key member of… https://t.co/ibav9pZl79]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Xbox One Spring Sale Roundup (2018): Life is Strange, Overwatch, and More: We picked the best Xbox One games and deals in Microsoft's massive 2018 Xbox Spring Sale! https://t.co/bJKCi3mC2v https://t.co/5AKYSzmCZK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agile Coach: Looking for an experienced Agile Coach to join our team supporting SSA in Woodlawn, MD MUST be US Citizen or green card holder Key Required Skills: Agile Coaching, Training, Agile Implementation experience using Scrum, Kanban, Lean, etc.,… https://t.co/mvMoEk0bzQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Consultant – Analyst/Developer/Administrator: CRI Advantage is looking for a SharePoint consultant to work with our federal client based out of Boise, Idaho. There will be some Pacific Northwest travel on a monthly basis to service satellite… https://t.co/tKtoccCBiR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Administrator/Developer: JOB DESCRIPTION: Resource 1 is seeking a SharePoint Administrator/Developer for a 6-month contract-for-hire opportunity in Chicago, IL. The selected candidate should have experience in Microsoft Technologies,… https://t.co/ZLYRi04u7h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior SharePoint Technical Developer Lead: Companyhas an excellent opportunity for a hands-on Senior SharePoint Developer to oversee a Development Team. This person will be directing a team of highly skilled developers and delivering complex internal… https://t.co/HuKEJj6ma6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Engineer: Systems Engineer Top 3 skills: Experience with F5 Local Traffic Manager (LTM), creating VIPs, Pools and iRules Strong skills Administrating and troubleshooting Microsoft Internet Information Server (IIS) IIS, Power Shell, DNS, System… https://t.co/4gFaXhAsSl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: SharePoint Developer Minnkota Power Cooperative is seeking qualified candidates for the position of SharePoint Developer located in our Grand Forks offices. This position is responsible for the design, development and maintenance of… https://t.co/J5U75Leoup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. SharePoint Developer: Jobs Toggle navigation * Sign In * Sign Up * Help Career Portal * Failure Message Cannot parse, seems some issue with the profile, please create the profile manually Alert Message Job Post has been updated successfully *… https://t.co/llscjh1oGV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Nintex Developer: Prestigious Enterprise Company is currently seeking a Developer with SharePoint and ****** experience, as well as some Nintex exposure. Candidate will be responsible for end-user computing development using the Microsoft… https://t.co/UV95vTQIy6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Admininistrator / Developer: SharePoint Admininistrator / Developer Location: Herndon, VA Job Code: 3200 # of openings: 1 Description Bay State Computers, Inc. is a professional services firm and a leading provider of Information Technology… https://t.co/zjXt0uZzqq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Administrator:   Job Description &amp;#8211; SharePoint Administrator (18006042) SharePoint Administrator Requisition ID : 18006042 Location : United States-Georgia-Atlanta US Citizenship Required for this Position: No Relocation Assistance: No… https://t.co/0DeMNWwt0k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: SharePoint Developer &amp;#8211; Programmer (DIRECT HIRE ONLY!) **LOCAL** This position will involve the development, administration and configuration of SharePoint 2016 platforms. Opportunity will allow incumbent to work on new… https://t.co/F0yXv6W3dy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint SME: SharePoint SME Location: Washington, DC Job Code: 3265 # of openings: 1 Description Bay State Computers, Inc. is a professional services firm and a leading provider of Information Technology (IT) services and products to the U.S. Federal… https://t.co/583dptte1n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pinterest Adds New 'People You Follow' Tab to Your Feed: The new "following" tab shows you pins from people you follow in reverse-chronological order. https://t.co/JqC6G26vkJ https://t.co/4ZHF5M1Fto]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Application Support Analyst: At KinderCare Education, we make it our passion to nurture a sense of discovery, joy, and wonder in every child, every day, at every one of our centers. As the nation&amp;#8217;s leading private provider in accredited… https://t.co/vKRk5ufqoJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer, .Net / Sharepoint: The St Louis Fed is one of 12 Reserve Banks serving all or parts of Missouri, Illinois, Indiana, Kentucky, Tennessee, Mississippi and Arkansas with branches in Little Rock, Louisville and Memphis. The St. Louis Fed&amp;#8217;s… https://t.co/Dsx2oXAPEV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Security Analyst: What you&amp;#8217;ll be doing: As a Security Analyst you will be trained from the ground up in security risk, remediation, vendor risk assessments, and healthcare security frameworks. This is a great opportunity to learn from an expert in… https://t.co/Rw4Cb1wfDD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Systems Analyst – Division of Supervision and Regulation: The Information Systems Analyst is responsible for the design, implementation, and support of complex automated distributed systems essential to carrying out the responsibilities and… https://t.co/FGvOp8AL1I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Project Manager: Those who join Emergent BioSolutions feel a sense of ownership about their future. You will excel in an environment characterized by respect, innovation and growth opportunities. Here, you will join passionate professionals who… https://t.co/llzpnOg3Gh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Email System Administrator: Why Join Altec? If you&amp;#8217;re considering a career with Altec, Inc., there&amp;#8217;s never been a better time to join us! Our Company was founded based upon values that place the customer first, and view people as our greatest… https://t.co/kVYJf1K6AC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer, .Net / Sharepoint: The St Louis Fed is one of 12 Reserve Banks serving all or parts of Missouri, Illinois, Indiana, Kentucky, Tennessee, Mississippi and Arkansas with branches in Little Rock, Louisville and Memphis. The St. Louis Fed&amp;#8217;s… https://t.co/lKjMjEdnwA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Team Lead Job: Date: Mar 9, 2018 Location: Washington, DC, US Company: SAIC SharePoint Team Lead (Job Number:432851) Description: Job Description This contract position is the lead member of a SharePoint team that supports an independent… https://t.co/G5QaDQsDyw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager: JOB TITLE: Senior Project Manager JOB LOCATION: Deerfield, IL JOB SUMMARY: Senior Project Manager is responsible for leading teams to deliver project(s) that span across one or more business units. Manage resources, schedules,… https://t.co/CcR10hHEOT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network and Systems Specialist: Company Description ThreatConnect arms organizations with a powerful defense against cyber threats and the confidence to make strategic business decisions. Founded in 2011, ThreatConnect (then called CyberSquared) started… https://t.co/VZIpMUgVLC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: Infosys Financial Services and Insurance Technology Lead &amp;#8211; US (.Net Technologies with Webservices/ UI) Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to create and… https://t.co/KR5HbTxE1O]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>