<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump voter: Voting for Trump my 'biggest mistake': CNN's Alisyn Camerota talks to a panel of Trump voters about how the President is doing and one man says voting for Trump was the "biggest mistake he's ever made." https://t.co/hsln1u6wOW https://t.co/qcqk6wS5jf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jr. SQL Database Administrator: Greensboro, NC 27408 #2018-26522 Description Overview The Fresh Market currently has an opening for a Jr. SQL Database Administrator at our Corporate Offices in Greensboro, North Carolina. Responsibilities – Provide… https://t.co/l3BOna26h7 https://t.co/2Wtotf4y1W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Reporting, Metrics, and Dashboard Developer, Senior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Herndon, VA Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 7/17/2018 Job Description Job Number: R******* SQL Reporting, Metrics, and Dashboard… https://t.co/uBN2a6ADjM https://t.co/mmKh93sRxD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New pay deal could make him the richest man alive https://t.co/yAZuMKc3cC https://t.co/kHuzYwhmq1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server Reports Analyst – System Analyst (II): Job Ref: ********* Employer: NTT DATA Country: United States County/State: Virginia Address: Post Date: 01/08/2018 00:23 Req ID: 25561 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board,… https://t.co/zSmTIJdC2y https://t.co/qzxOV9kJeu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reverse Logistics Specialist: User Experience Engineer (Mountain View, CA) Define the user model &amp; user interface for new &amp; existing Google products &amp; features. User Experience Engineer. #1615.33776 Exp Incl: physical prototyping; sw communication dev… https://t.co/Oeluz22jZY https://t.co/Iw85vbBzzj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL DBA: SQL DBA Ref No.: 18-30425 Location: Minneapolis, Minnesota Title:- SQL DBA Location:- Minneapolis MN Contract Role Provide DBA support on all aspects of databases administration including backup/recovery, replication, deployment and real-time… https://t.co/GFWXM2NSVh https://t.co/sV7vvcfFZP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inside the boutique behind Manafort's $48,000 lizard coat: It wasn't the $12,000 pink pinstripe suit or the $48,000 blue lizard jacket that raised eyebrows. After all, House of Bijan is often described as the most expensive men's clothing store in the… https://t.co/bcJVWz9JOF https://t.co/N3QSluVL52]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal GUI C# Developer (Winforms, WPF): Summary: CRD is currently expanding the capabilities of our products in several new areas. The Principal GUI C# Developer will work on developing the user interface and related software. We employ 170+ of the… https://t.co/GOWyawbtMG https://t.co/gwb0wFkvJ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer SME: SQL Developer SME – 18-02550 Ref No.: 18-02550 Location: Greenwood Village, Colorado Akraya is looking for a SQL Developer SME for one of our clients. If the job description below is a fit, please apply directly or call Ajay at… https://t.co/MGdIJp7zBG https://t.co/fpVkKs2GX7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gates says he and Manafort didn't report 15 foreign accounts, knew it was illegal: Rick Gates, the key prosecution witness in the tax and fraud trial of former Trump campaign chairman Paul Manafort, testified Monday he had committed crimes alongside and… https://t.co/tjG3957Ns6 https://t.co/wIsNbSShBD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MySQL Database Administrator: Requisition ID 2018-40977 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Secret Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description General Dynamics is looking for an experienced MySQL Database… https://t.co/bAEHROgNj9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spark Developer: Spark Developer Ref No.:18-11058 Location: Philadelphia, Pennsylvania Start Date: 06/21/2018 Title: Spark Developer Location: Philadelphia, PA Duration: 6-12+ Months Contract Job Description: Technical/Functional Skills : 1. Spark,… https://t.co/iYXA4BDxJS https://t.co/JDHOUMnLgT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Android developer: Los Angeles, CA Full-time $110k – $140k Posted Today If you are a Senior Android developer with experience, please read on! What You Need for this Position At Least 3 Years of experience and knowledge of: – Java – Android… https://t.co/XKWbC3jTR7 https://t.co/yFY6ahUL6q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Database Developer/Junior DBA: SQL DATABASE DEVELOPER/JUNIOR DBA THIS IS A FULL-TIME POSITION. NO THIRD PARTY CANDIDATES. NO CANDIDATE REQUIRING A VISA TRANSFERWILL BE ACCEPTED. CANDIDATE MUST BE LOCAL TO NEW YORK/NEW JERSEY AREA AND READY TO… https://t.co/pK0dRxLP8X https://t.co/22A63eaXjg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer I: SQL Developer I in Remote at Beacon Health Options Return to *********************** | Join Our Talent Network Toggle navigation – Careers Home – We are Beacon – Benefits – Featured Careers – Clinical / Quality – Customer Service /… https://t.co/OD8WuwZTfo https://t.co/UBt4GW3c6T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ABS Reporting Systems Analyst III: GM Financial seeks: ABS Reporting Systems Analyst III: Req. BS in EE, CS, CIS, MIS &amp; 5 yrs of exp in Asset Backed Securitization reporting, ETL coding and SQL. Economist II: Req. MS in Applied Stat, Applied Math,… https://t.co/90Hjd6bf0q https://t.co/d0tTaXb4g9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Project Managers: American Express Travel Related Services seeks Technical Project Managers to drive the development and delivery of technical products and solutions for our customers. Engage with product owners, business stakeholders, and… https://t.co/jU05GlJ2Vm https://t.co/TnjlFIjOTn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NFL's first male dancers will hit the sidelines: NFL fans will see history made this season, and it has nothing to do with what goes on between the goalposts. https://t.co/XH6uCUMw4E https://t.co/AY1XXiinDi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump team expected to respond to Mueller soon regarding interview: President Donald Trump's legal team is preparing to respond to special counsel Robert Mueller regarding the possibility of an interview, Rudy Giuliani told CNN Monday. https://t.co/vo2vwk7xqf https://t.co/BX6VB61IxE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Database Developer – Corptax: Senior Database Developer CSC Employer is a market leader in leading-edge commercial tax software and process solutions . Through our unique ERP solution, we unlock the value of the tax function, transforming it into a… https://t.co/iJOTheo4Ym https://t.co/w7tZiXd8I9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server DBA: SQL Server DBA Location: Herndon, VA Job Code: 3592 # of openings: 1 Description Bay State Computers, Inc. is a professional services firm and a leading provider of Information Technology (IT) services and products to the U.S. Federal… https://t.co/15Tffu4IME https://t.co/2S6OKJ7s64]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Star of TV's 'Facts of Life' dead at 92 https://t.co/6XS4cvXqtR https://t.co/V3WPlndtjS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ABS Reporting Systems Analyst III: GM Financial seeks: ABS Reporting Systems Analyst III: Req. BS in EE, CS, CIS, MIS &amp; 5 yrs of exp in Asset Backed Securitization reporting, ETL coding and SQL. Economist II: Req. MS in Applied Stat, Applied Math,… https://t.co/3eWVSA48Es https://t.co/0VjFHhyHTH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Entry/Junior Level SQL Developer: – Looking for a technologist who is interested in a career in software development, supporting data warehousing, data integrity and database management projects. – Entry level to 3 years of experience with SQL-being able… https://t.co/DbWV2WSP2z https://t.co/t184kPoDNl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everest has a serious poop problem: When climbing enthusiasts take a stab at the highest mountain in the world, thinking about their bodily waste is probably low on their list of priorities. https://t.co/ZPP0rDD6Gi https://t.co/05tzNsdcsF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior/Regular QA Automation Engineer: Project Description You will be working in a team which develops an operational risk assessment and reporting solution. You will be working with people located around the world. Our teams are self organized and take… https://t.co/OVgc7sbB9S https://t.co/fggHQBAity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Business Analyst: Job Description Senior Business Analyst Senior Business Analyst (******) About Us At HDR, we specialize in engineering, architecture, environmental and construction services. While we are most well-known for adding beauty and… https://t.co/rxHyLgkU5n https://t.co/HVomZKveyd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's attacks on LeBron fit a disturbing pattern: There's no disputing that Donald Trump's pattern of attacking well-known African-Americans as having "low IQs" or being of low intelligence is parroting the white nationalist view that blacks are… https://t.co/GkkOeQsVPy https://t.co/iQ4zLAMYvb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Engineer, RDS SQL Server: Job Description Software Development Engineer, RDS SQL Server Location: US-WA-Seattle Job ID: ****** Company: : ********** Services, Inc. Position Category: Software Development Job Description Are you… https://t.co/KLTOHKvdox https://t.co/zrVe2DEuca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server Database Administrator: SQL Server Database Administrator Ref No.: 18-31038 Location: San Francisco, California SQL Server Database Administration, Infra &amp; Data Security : IT IS_AMS_Oracle Database Administration L3 Oracle Database Admin… https://t.co/gS4rF3MYYz https://t.co/UJg9VPhOcw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: SQL Developer Ref No.: 18-32758 Location: Charlotte, North Carolina Position: SQL Developer Job Location: Charlotte, NC Job Title: Full time permanent – 7+ years of experience in SQL development with Business intelligence software:… https://t.co/Pf5dFJ12jX https://t.co/jqziat2QrH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL/SQL Programmer Level 1: PL/SQL Programmer Level 1 in Norfolk, VA | CACI International – Small Business | – Suppliers – About Us – | – What We Do – | – Media &amp; Events – | – Investors – | – Careers – | – Contracts – | – Contact Us Join Our Talent… https://t.co/Wj85Q8TYis https://t.co/xfFI9XPqIA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: Guess which countries are playing dodgeball with Trump?: Every week, I offer a glimpse of the kind of intelligence assessments that are likely to come across the desk of the President of the United States. Modeled on the President's Daily… https://t.co/VN5FVYJIrd https://t.co/IWhzIqf0Ax]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Horse-riding, gun-owning Democrat shakes up governor's race: Paulette Jordan gently nudges her horse into the Idaho field, her yellow riding gloves loosely holding onto the reins as the sun begins to set on the nearly triple-digit temperature summer day.… https://t.co/XTPeNvvHZ9 https://t.co/9r2sycvciN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETL Developer- SQL Reporting: Date posted 08/01/2018 Requisition Number: ******BR Location: United States – Connecticut – Stamford Area of Interest: Business Affairs/Development/Analysis, Information Technology Services, Telecommunications Position Type:… https://t.co/4oRrZbnFLm https://t.co/YL9fWY1Fh4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL/SQL / JavaScript: Job Snapshot Employee Type: Full-Time Location: McLean, VA Job Type: Information Technology Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 7/19/2018 Job Description Job Description Responsible for the back-end PL/SQL development and… https://t.co/8oSlNlbxQr https://t.co/nRC2Ue57qP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Developer NEXEN full stack Platform development: The NEXEN Development Team’ is a collaborative group of passionate and talented engineers based out of our Jersey City Innovation Center.’ ‘ We are actively working on designing and implementing a… https://t.co/sxLt4ArQ8R https://t.co/wW5qy5qNhw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What I learned from student journalism changed everything: I came across some old photos last week. Two photos, actually. One from 2002, when I was editor of my college newspaper at Kishwaukee College. The other from 2012, when I was the adviser to that… https://t.co/Ezco7Yea50 https://t.co/aCCyhxaJjS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Java Developer – JavaScript, Angular, Kafka, SQL: Job Description Principal Java Developer – JavaScript, Angular, Kafka, SQL The Principal Developer position in the AST Performance, Monitoring &amp; Availability Engineering Team will be responsible… https://t.co/JFBR1u8kws https://t.co/rUJzNIJhyt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Concur Client Support Analyst III: SAP Concur Client Support Analyst III Job Close By continuing to use and navigate this website, you are agreeing to the use of cookies. Accept – SAP Careers home – SAP employees – Join our talent community Search by… https://t.co/cfpPfbbBmZ https://t.co/yOTK9Ssrqz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Business Systems Analyst GRS Strong SQL: Technical Business Systems Analyst’ ‘ GRS ‘ Strong SQL Formulates and defines system’s scope and objectives based on both user needs and a good understanding of the application, business, operational… https://t.co/0mw93w5c0D https://t.co/BRcfkkgAuV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer (ROPS): The ROPS SQL Developer role is a developer who is responsible for the design, development, implementation and support of business critical backend databases, ETL workflows, and VBA applications. The SQL developer will have… https://t.co/Nmf0cLVKvq https://t.co/jbXdBbGqjO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mysql Admin: ******/Mysql Admin Ref No.: 18-33427 Location: Mc Lean – New York, New York LEAD-ADMINISTRATOR-L1 Job Description(As per hiring manager) Key skills required for the job are: MySQL Admin-L3 (Mandatory) As a Lead Administrator, you should be… https://t.co/i9H6DplHI5 https://t.co/uAohVdS3rq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russia appoints Steven Seagal as special envoy to US: Russia appointed actor Steven Seagal as a "special representative" on US-Russian humanitarian ties, the country's Ministry of Foreign Affairs said in statement on its official Facebook page Saturday. https://t.co/MsPOakjLxT https://t.co/r0i7khFcPc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NRA lawsuit says it's in financial trouble because of actions by NY regulators: A lawsuit filed by the National Rifle Association says the gun advocacy organization will have to close its headquarters, shut down its online media presence and stop holding… https://t.co/dJhGGixcDu https://t.co/CVdcxKmxM8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator: Requisition ID 2018-41782 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Top Secret/SCI Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description SUMMARY: Applicant will provide On-Site tier 1 technical support for… https://t.co/sVRsDHGLMj https://t.co/XPXq1CRCXZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL DBA: SQL DBA Ref No.: 18-33956 Location: Houston, Texas Role DBA Mandatory Technical Skills Ideally Certified DB Professional with more than 8 years’ experience with SQL. Experience should include DB design (modelling and normalisation), capacity… https://t.co/FmC1AySDAI https://t.co/vCMwwRjfaj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL/SQL Developer: PL/SQL Developer Ref No.: 18-33612 Location: tempe, Arizona Hello, Greetings for the day ! We have an urgent requirement for PL/SQL Developer in Tempe , AZ. Please let me know if you are looking for a new project. You can reach me at… https://t.co/SqydJNtCwE https://t.co/LHQUmBc5BN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teradata and SQL Developer: Teradata and SQL Developer Ref No.: 18-29976 Location: Charlotte, North Carolina Position: Teradata and SQL Developer Job Location: Charlotte, NC/ Plano, TX Job Title: Full time permanent The ideal Candidate is an expert… https://t.co/ajHamVR12b https://t.co/z5Uu1lojgS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MS SQL DBA: MS SQL DBA job | Cognizant job in Raritan, New Jersey, United StatesJob Details | Cognizant – ************* – Industries – – – Services – – – Latest Thinking – – – About Cognizant – – Careers Home – Get To Know Us – Our Core Values –… https://t.co/mWz7O20T5V https://t.co/CLfXGLUxGB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid-Level Programmer Analyst: Location: North Charleston Job type: Permanent Sector: Operations Category: Analyst Jobs We have an exciting opportunity for a Mid-Level Programmer Analyst to join our team in North Charleston, South Carolina! This position… https://t.co/ayLKcbhh4c https://t.co/T3ZTGQRJpm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Software Developer: Job Board Powered by Bullhorn Jul 12, 2018 JobsYour ProfileLogin Job #5644: Information Technology Job Code: #5644 Title: SQL Software Developer Date Posted: 06/18/2018 Job Type: Direct Hire Job Location: Connecticut Job… https://t.co/8d28yN7wqs https://t.co/0PsuPlrbDV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 marvelous places to visit in August: August can present something of a challenge when you're setting travel plans. https://t.co/r8lKDMTdiY https://t.co/rRYA30dczE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Summary: Heartland School Solutions, a business unit of Global Payments, is seeking a full-time software developer to work with one of our existing remote development teams. The position will consider both remote candidates or… https://t.co/XEw45LzNy6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is 'kompromat'?: The Kremlin has recently been accused of collecting compromising information on US presidential candidates, a tactic called "kompromat". https://t.co/GTXeTEqTgP https://t.co/eEdwicFmx8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Developer JavaScript, Angular, Kafka, SQL: Principal Java Developer ‘ JavaScript, Angular, Kafka, SQL ‘ The Principal Developer position in the AST Performance, Monitoring &amp; Availability Engineering Team will be responsible for developing a new… https://t.co/GSn3fOycei https://t.co/HmQYvOHowU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joseph Pappas reportedly had been hiding in plain sight: As police have been hunting the man they believe killed a prominent Houston doctor, their suspect in the July 20 shooting seems to have been leading a double life. https://t.co/pufLI7m3wh https://t.co/hm2t8OsBA8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Senior Developer with strong DB experience (NoSQL/Mongo): Job Ref: ********** Employer: NTT DATA Country: United States County/State: New Jersey Address: Post Date: 31/07/2018 00:10 Req ID: 16819 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right… https://t.co/reijK1adFK https://t.co/Shnvfm1IuX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Job Title: Senior Software Engineer #HAD0618 Location: Omaha, NE Job Number: JO-1806-27751 ProKarma, Inc. has multiple openings for the position of Senior Software Engineer based out of its U.S. headquarters in Omaha, NE. The… https://t.co/HydiEuqx3n https://t.co/3Ngo2SGyR9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ABS Reporting Systems Analyst III: GM Financial seeks: ABS Reporting Systems Analyst III: Req. BS in EE, CS, CIS, MIS &amp; 5 yrs of exp in Asset Backed Securitization reporting, ETL coding and SQL. Economist II: Req. MS in Applied Stat, Applied Math,… https://t.co/LnnyrIazS5 https://t.co/Q2PUudH57X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warren: Trump likes two-bit dictators: Speaking to progressive activists at Netroots Nations, Sen. Elizabeth Warren (D-MA) criticizes what she calls President Trump's "politics of division" among the working class. https://t.co/e9bLvxBdlJ https://t.co/pyNTlaCQiY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Administrator – SQL: TRAX International Careers – Home – Our Services – Our People – Our Leaders – Careers – About Us Returning Applicant? Login Now New Job Search Database Administrator – SQL Job Code:2018:0303-002 Location:Lynchburg, VA FT/PT… https://t.co/KnWeSRwX3F https://t.co/bW2YP4iWhI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior SQL Developer: Senior SQL Developer – (12839) This details all the information about the job posting. Job Title Senior SQL Developer Organizational Unit Ashley Furniture Industries , Corporate , Information Technology Location Advance, NC 27006 US… https://t.co/ngV5UP3xU1 https://t.co/NAbzM7kLUk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How much avoiding the stock market is costing you https://t.co/Poy8c3hpkZ https://t.co/MGgKd0yMeM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consultant: CONSULTING Deloitte Consulting LLP seeks a Consultant in San Jose, CA and various unanticipated Deloitte office locations and client sites nationally to: Providing human capital consulting services to clients on behalf of a global consulting… https://t.co/CCGsOVsj2m https://t.co/uA34CMSKaW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suspect in Houston killing found dead: The man suspected of killing a prominent Houston doctor in broad daylight two weeks ago has been found dead, Houston Police Chief Art Acevedo said Friday. https://t.co/XJzcS56FZ9 https://t.co/ymyBiPtU1u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Specialist Appl Support Analyst, UNIX/LINUX/Windows, SQL (Sunday — Thursday): Sr. Specialist Appl Support Analyst, UNIX/LINUX/Windows, SQL (Sunday ‘ Thursday) ‘ Overview Of BNY Mellon: BNY Mellon is a global financial services company focused on… https://t.co/xMROy6CnHV https://t.co/eEipXHAMwb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump mocked for comparing himself to Lincoln: Trump touts poll numbers higher than Honest Abe's. Oops, not so honest! CNN's Jeanne Moos reports. https://t.co/DnRR2Raio3 https://t.co/pqjUme1MlO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer I (SQL Server DBA): GENERAL PURPOSE: The SQL Server DBA Engineer provides the technical design and delivery role in the Engineering and Infrastructure Delivery lifecycles from installation, integration, maintenance, currency and upgrades of… https://t.co/NiZYXG7EOv https://t.co/ycu2dEg7cA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Intelligence Solution Architect: Business Intelligence Solution Architect Date: Jun 29, 2018 Location: Clinton, NJ, US Company: New York Life Insurance Co Apply now Start apply with LinkedIn Start apply with Facebook Apply Now EmailStart Please… https://t.co/akVYiSz57I https://t.co/poNtjoeT2D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETL Developer: ETL Developer Ref No.: 18-31345 Location: McLean, Virginia Position: ETL Developer Location: McLean VA Duration: 12 Months " – At least 5+ years of experience in developing ETL solutions using Informatica PowerCenter. – Hands on experience… https://t.co/e0jJNYfQbr https://t.co/DeVif11DMo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysis: The simple reason why Trump wants to sit down with Mueller: The New York Times has the story. It reads: https://t.co/622sZryLuo https://t.co/76MpZGE5Bg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[:: AWS DEVELOPER WITH SPARK ::: :: AWS DEVELOPER WITH SPARK :: Ref No.: 18-29483 Location: NYC, New York The required skills for the position include the following: Python experience (Scala or Java are okay too) Spark, Hive, MapReduce, NoSQL and related… https://t.co/577FxLgITs https://t.co/HnfxfhZeP7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Younger workers are making this big financial mistake https://t.co/knvBjPi9z9 https://t.co/d7JJuDFOzu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL/SQL Developer: Careers Center | PL/SQL Developer Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome page Returning… https://t.co/UgO5jsDx8K https://t.co/li2roKOXy6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAS tech Lead: SAS tech Lead Ref No.: 18-29491 Location: Tempe, Arizona Position: SAS tech Lead Location: Tempe,AZ Duration: 12 Months 1. Experience in SAS is mandatory Review the available technical, business and user documents, validate the quality,… https://t.co/lyCiyBGdF1 https://t.co/bahWskbmzI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test pilot flies huge cargo plane in a 'loop': At over 110 feet long and with a wingspan of more than 130 feet, the Lockheed Martin LM-100J is a very big airplane. https://t.co/wYJKLFfCuU https://t.co/RjB62p478r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Justice Ginsburg: Recent term 'much more divisive than usual': Supreme Court Justice Ruth Bader Ginsburg on Wednesday evening described the 2017-18 term as "much more divisive than usual." https://t.co/S9UaPhjcgy https://t.co/wdiAkV7uNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Commercial Operations Analyst, NA iTero: Align Technology is a global medical device company that pioneered the invisible orthodontics market with the introduction of the Invisalign system in 1999. Today, we develop innovative, technology-rich products… https://t.co/jiOGxYdGFB https://t.co/5d7BZ0zCOD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[KMP TMP Testing Senior Software Developer, Cloud Service Reliability: KMP – TMP Testing – Senior Software Developer, Cloud Service Reliability job description at VMware Skip Navigation MENU VMware Search Jobs – MENU – Home – Life at VMWare – Careers –… https://t.co/Lb8Gf5mNKV https://t.co/9hEabDEWcQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tech Lead Net: Tech Lead – .Net Ref No.: 18-26267 Location: Malvern, Pennsylvania – Expertise in DOT NET Architecture; Administrating and managing both Windows and Web Application using ******, C#.NET and .NET MVC. – Expertise in Relational Databases… https://t.co/swZPJY7qUr https://t.co/u2CGWSC83Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test automation Engineer: Test automation Engineer Ref No.: 18-30544 Location: Santa Clara, California 5+ years of hands-on, demonstrable Selenium/ Appium or Mobile automation testing experience . 3-5+ years of strong, demonstrable experience creating… https://t.co/UplkQvEqhL https://t.co/Ko9Gn6amZm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A history of Kim Kardashian West's clapbacks: What's worse: body shaming or a homophobic jab? https://t.co/j4wrbYke6j https://t.co/qL0SBHLd8O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UI UX Developer: Job Locations US-WA-Vancouver Job ID 2018-5207 # of Openings 1 Overview Web Developer (JavaScript) – HP Vancouver, WA We are seeking a well versed, full stack Web Developer with experience using modern JavaScript libraries like… https://t.co/9pRz8xR2DH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: Senior Java Developer $120-125K +Bonus McLean, VA Senior Java Developer will be part of development team supporting new and ongoing development efforts on suite of Pricing Applications within IT organization. Our team is made up of… https://t.co/riRogrrsSj https://t.co/Rb68lwz8U4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's call to end Mueller probe reignites obstruction question: For months, President Donald Trump has relentlessly attacked the Russia probe, and his missive Wednesday saying Attorney General Jeff Sessions should stop the investigation reignited the… https://t.co/X19mDWsKgY https://t.co/DHsc8N4SXO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server Systems Analyst Associate: Job Description Job Title: SQL Server Systems Analyst – Associate Job ID: ****** Status: Full-Time Regular/Temporary: Regular Hours: Shift: Day Job Facility: UPMC Health Plan Department: Admin Finance Location: 600… https://t.co/oTUC2oybLA https://t.co/DhMR18UwkH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Data Science Analyst: Job Description Job Title: Senior Data Science Analyst Job ID: ****** Status: Full-Time Regular/Temporary: Regular Hours: Shift: Day Job Facility: UPMC Health Plan Department: Marketing Communications Location: 600 Grant St,… https://t.co/TO4KM6JUFI https://t.co/WZTcVmrn6E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bishop says Catholic Church suffers from 'crisis of sexual morality': The sexual abuse accusations against a prominent American archbishop reveal a "grievous moral failure" within the Catholic Church, the president of the US Conference of Catholic… https://t.co/cDKpBhEpNc https://t.co/ApIvUU5hI5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Java Developer JavaScript, Angular, Kafka, SQL: Principal Java Developer ‘ JavaScript, Angular, Kafka, SQL ‘ The Principal Developer position in the AST Performance, Monitoring &amp; Availability Engineering Team will be responsible for developing… https://t.co/VQ4WO0nt4c https://t.co/sUBjtnZacA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FBI agent testifies Manafort raid was not a no-knock raid https://t.co/7vLXQpAREs https://t.co/rQJjMpBqPy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BI Developer/SQL Developer (Business Intelligence): Overview * Develop, test and deploy various ETL jobs * Participate in data conversion and data migration efforts * Create Stored Procedures, Functions and Views from scratch * Model and then implement… https://t.co/mPotgtmteM https://t.co/HLW5BxoDOD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks, GOP, the national debt is back https://t.co/nJeGQO29TF https://t.co/uYK8Au4hWg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL/SQL Developer: PL/SQL Developer Ref No.: 18-32868 Location: Pleasanton, California PL/SQL Expertise in SQL and PL/SQL programming, developing complex code unitsSolid Experience of creating PL/SQL Packages, Procedures, Functions, Triggers, Views and… https://t.co/XPpEIkKkyI https://t.co/tuRydKdma0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch a simple gesture for a teen with autism: A grocery store employee is being lauded for helping a teen with autism stock shelves in a fridge. https://t.co/cHc4ODeqtb https://t.co/vyaEABOdaU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C/C++ SQL Transaction Processing: C/C++ SQL – Transaction Processing at Conduent – What We Do What We DoWhat We Do What We Do What We Do Industries – Automotive, Aerospace and Defense – Banking and Capital Markets – Communications and Media – Healthcare… https://t.co/2WfqRt8gTJ https://t.co/PKiiaQOcSs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Intelligence Analyst: What’s the opportunity? The Business Intelligence Analyst designs and develops enterprise-wide reporting solutions as well as completes adhoc reporting requests using MSSQL and SSRS. This individual is responsible for the… https://t.co/PdkkmdGEdA https://t.co/SuYLDmZd3n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-Fox News analyst: Trump echoes Stalin: Lt. Col. Ralph Peters talks to CNN's Anderson Cooper about Trump's attack on the media. https://t.co/urkNJunWf6 https://t.co/5Xifux1mg0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Specialist Developer: Job Description Consults with internal business groups to provide appropriate application software development services or technical support. Analyzes, defines and documents requirements for data, workflow, logical processes,… https://t.co/uiEhH83Sbg https://t.co/W3GydQlMCD]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>