<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Product Security Engineer: Senior Product Security Engineer San Francisco, CA Full-time Company Description We believe the economy is better when everyone has access. When everyone has room to grow. No one should be left out because the cost is… https://t.co/ugHUXC2tkC https://t.co/mOrF4DubwU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Planning Developer: Job spec My client is one of the largest transport services organisations in Europe The purpose of this role is to support the development of business planning solutions, which meet the business needs of Data Excellence's… https://t.co/ZbwAcu0ETu https://t.co/5QuwpoFd47]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Security Lead / Consultant (SAP / SOX / JSOX / GDPR): Security Lead / Consultant (SAP / SOX / JSOX / GDPR) – Contract – Bracknell, Berkshire (with 2 days working from home). A leading IT services company is searching for a Security Lead / Consultant to… https://t.co/wFqCWwnIAB https://t.co/jmeM1zuK7K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Android Developer – Contract – Birmingham: Android App Developer – Native App, Android Studio – Contract – Birmingham I am currently looking for an Android Developer for a 6 – 12 month contract in Birmingham, you will join the Development team, which is… https://t.co/3mH19XVLMY https://t.co/ybK1nRlSGC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst – Front Office Systems – 6mth Contract – Edinburgh: Business Analyst – Front Office Systems – 6mth Contract – Edinburgh We often have Business Analyst vacancies that are quite generic, and not too focussed on any one particular business… https://t.co/P1AJPgm1mE https://t.co/oFkzvTBsSg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Support Consultant: An excellent opportunity for an experienced Application Support analyst to join a fast growing company and take responsibility for the support of a range of applications and reports, as well as working closely with… https://t.co/9OKjohLL2r https://t.co/lIcJmbqKKH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Up close and hands-on with DJI’s Osmo Pocket gimbal: I’ll admit that I’ve warmed up pretty quickly to the Osmo Pocket. The original post from earlier today is pretty skeptical, owing in no small part to the price point. And while I stand by the earlier… https://t.co/pwEw22Oved https://t.co/Egx5taCvXf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solutions Architect: ECS Group are currently looking for a Solutions Architect to join a global provider of IT Solutions based in Leeds. As the Solutions Architect you will be responsible for working with key business stakeholders to specify, design and… https://t.co/dMo66Q1sOM https://t.co/CJK2fJkjF1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PSG vs. Liverpool https://t.co/XV1O3ZyTfP https://t.co/NLNLdnI4TJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst (banking): Business Analyst (banking experience) – Dublin – €(Apply online only) per day My client are currently recruiting for a Business Analyst for an initial 6 month contract based in Dublin. As well as a proven track record as a… https://t.co/KZ42WundGj https://t.co/S0ek6HSVQc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drupal Developer: SENIOR DRUPAL DEVELOPER– 6 MONTHS + GHENT (BELGIUM) FREELANCE My client are seeking a senior Drupal developer for a long term mission in Ghent. The company are working on large projects for national and international brands and are… https://t.co/f8WzSF6LR2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pompeo, Mattis defend Saudi ties amid Senate anger over Khashoggi murder: Secretary of State Mike Pompeo and Defense Secretary James Mattis traveled to Capitol Hill for a closed-door briefing with Senate lawmakers Wednesday where they emphasized the… https://t.co/sL3RD5EMwQ https://t.co/xBdcrBNKSh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Graduate Web Developer (top Academics): Graduate Web Developer (top Academics)   React, Node.JS, Angular, Python, Django, Docker, AWS, Web Development, Graduate Graduate web developer needed for an up and coming web development agency that is one of the… https://t.co/FRzkQiXHkv https://t.co/cNZE2CyS84]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fintech Contracts Manager In-House: Our client is a fintech managed services company based in central London with an international office network. The firm is on a steep growth curve and as things have become busier they are now looking to hire a IT… https://t.co/elVmcAU39e https://t.co/1vKGlCsfzl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Net Developer: A .Net Developer is required for a small development team who’s currently transitioning to a DevOps environment. This is a great opportunity for an experienced .Net Developer to pick up skills in Continuous Integrations and Automated… https://t.co/sVGF1qGRTT https://t.co/rAtzNSXv6e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: Is the British media already turning on Meghan Markle?: It is barely six months since the wedding of Prince Harry and Meghan Markle was feted by the British press as a modern, progressive fairy tale. https://t.co/qAE6U2eu3p https://t.co/IiYc4QmUrG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: I'm working exclusively with a client within the Global Capital Market space, who are actively hiring in their London offices for a Python developer to join there ranks. Seeking a strong Python developer with solid exposure to on… https://t.co/v5E0VNDeBf https://t.co/JiRZmIhLyZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manager, Software Engineer: West Creek 8 (12080), United States of America, Richmond, Virginia At Employer, were building a leading information-based technology company. Still founder-led by Chairman and Chief Executive Officer Richard Fairbank, Employer… https://t.co/0L6RPQ1IEy https://t.co/8VBMRfzlXm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Backend Java Software Engineer – CreditWise: McLean 2 (19052), United States of America, McLean, Virginia At Employer, were building a leading information-based technology company. Still founder-led by Chairman and Chief Executive Officer Richard… https://t.co/DDInBosgk4 https://t.co/jX5s2CRKix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Cloud Engineer – (VMware): telent Senior Cloud Engineer – VMware Location: Camberley Type of Job: Permanent Ref No: V6887 Role Profile Within this position you will build and enhance the engineering and technical relationship with both internal… https://t.co/y9H8CWjKWJ https://t.co/eJc5tDV8wU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chinese gene-editing scientist defends his research, raises possibility of third baby: The Chinese scientist who sparked an international outcry after alleging to have helped create the world's first genetically edited babies, has raised the possibility… https://t.co/7rKLZoXv5q https://t.co/MGyWBWUE5h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon’s newest service uses machine learning to extract medical data from patient records: Amazon has launched a new service that uses machine learning to extract key data from patient records and can potentially help healthcare providers and… https://t.co/P4GHxY5OJw https://t.co/f1kXu54OMc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UI Engineer: Jobs | Boston Dynamics Skip to main content Menu Main navigation – Home – Robots – SpotMini – Atlas – Handle – Spot – LS3 – WildCat – BigDog – SandFlea – RHex – Jobs – News – About – Contact Jobs Boston Dynamics is Hiring Working for Boston… https://t.co/pS5ETuDEKj https://t.co/KSCFVM3Ezr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer, Big Data Platform: SunIRef:it Sr. Software Engineer, Big Data Platform – San Jose, CA – ********** Find Jobs Company Reviews Find Salaries Find Resumes Employers / Post Job Upload your resume Sign in Home whatjob title, keywords,… https://t.co/8BXnovDw9W https://t.co/HaGN5VDgPS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automation Test Architect (Exeter): Automation Test Architect Exeter (Devon) 3 – 6 Month Contract £(Apply online only)/day (Neg) Automation Test Architect needed for a 3 – 6 Month Rolling Contract in Exeter. Start ASAP in December 2018. Key skills,… https://t.co/aWjUWMjo7n https://t.co/oM26aI5Tvf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This city holds onto its crown as city with the most Michelin stars: Michelin Guide, the famed French dining bible, has confirmed what most travelers already believe -- Tokyo is the world's no.1 food destination. https://t.co/0v08PPxfWK https://t.co/5trzpl2MNh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fluent German Renewals Executive: We are recruiting for Global organisation within the IT distribution sector and they are seeking a Fluent German Renewals Executive to join their team. Salary £21k per annum, plus £7k OTE and super benefits This is a… https://t.co/D9P8OMK1JW https://t.co/IwmuICNyAp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A/V Systems Design Engineer: 26-Nov-2018 A/V Systems Design Engineer Enterprise Operations Colorado 462390BR • Experience with Design, installation, configuration, integration and testing of videoconferencing and integrated audio/visual technologies… https://t.co/aEUoh1KiNI https://t.co/zaBjGp4VFj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Architect – Professional Services: The Consultancy business is the essential core for the SCC Services providing technology consulting, architecture, design and implementation services to our public and commercial sector customers. The role of Lead… https://t.co/PjXBJwqfbN https://t.co/4wONaSqIH8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Report raises questions about pilots' actions in deadly Lion Air crash: Indonesian investigators probing the crash of Lion Air Flight 610 have recommended the airline review its safety culture while they seek to find out why the plane's aircraft sensors… https://t.co/nko759kkCH https://t.co/mzC1sqO5Wg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SCADA System Support Engineer: telent- SCADA System Support Engineer, Warwick Permanent Within our SCADA team we’re looking to recruit a System Support Engineer. This role will support the engineers within the recently created Network Operations Centre… https://t.co/bFbprdpES3 https://t.co/AqJDSrx6e9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Solutions Architect – Infrastructure – Surrey – £70k: INFRASTRUCTURE SOLUTIONS ARCHITECT – GLOBAL LOCATIONS (UK, EU, SOUTH AFRICA) Exiting opportunity to join a fast-paced, constantly evolving, ceaselessly innovating company providing… https://t.co/Dwa6n5xq2g https://t.co/nbZ5wTWQFv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sports complex is housing thousands of migrants in Tijuana. It's at least 3 times over capacity.: The sports complex sheltering thousands of Central American migrants in this Mexican border city is well above its capacity, and more migrants are… https://t.co/GqpkM8KagK https://t.co/dLd3fuJ062]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server Developer: Database Developer – Bradford – £50,000 + Bonus + Flexible working DBA, Database Engineer, SQL, MongoDB   This advanced and rapidly growing company are looking to add a SQL Server Developer to their Software delivery team based just… https://t.co/CGh4u5BHIa https://t.co/u1eG56jdB6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front End Developer: Front End Developer * Dublin * 6 month Contract * Excellent Daily Rate Great contracting opportunity for a Front End Developer to join a leading tech company conveniently located in Dublin. You’ll work on a large new project as part… https://t.co/xZhgt4NPFY https://t.co/kKKXbP46Cd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Officials release video from gender reveal party that ignited a 47,000-acre wildfire: Oh boy. A video released by the US Forest Service shows the moment when a gender reveal party in Arizona went horribly wrong, sparking a wildfire that burned nearly… https://t.co/RRCGU334aT https://t.co/n2b9Ng0aQs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Red Hat acquires hybrid cloud data management service NooBaa: Red Hat is in the process of being acquired by IBM for a massive $34 billion, but that deal hasn’t closed yet and, in the meantime, Red Hat is still running independently and making its own… https://t.co/vnarATAQCs https://t.co/Ffo4AhxDYp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital Project Manager: This great digital agency in Leeds is looking to hire a talented Digital Project Manager with a couple of years experience to join their busy team. They are a very successful agency with many years of experience behind them. This… https://t.co/IooigZwlo5 https://t.co/MqI46rdPyY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clojure Developer: Clojure Developer – Clojure /ClojureScript Fintech based in London, using Clojure and Clojurescript to create tools for financial analysts. We are developing AI-based automation tools to provide the equivalent of a cognitive assistant… https://t.co/xbQPuo4cyv https://t.co/D0DsVdnqe7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technial Support Engineer – Cork – French/German: Technical Support Engineer – Cork French or German €30-50,000 DOE Our Cork based client are currently seeking to hire a Technical Support Engineer. You will be fluent in either French or German, have a… https://t.co/r91wlW49t0 https://t.co/ReJseSpphy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man charged in Charlottesville death 'thought he was acting in self-defense,' attorney says: The trial of a man accused of killing Heather Heyer at a white nationalist rally in Virginia will include evidence that the defendant believed he acted in… https://t.co/m10ql77JNU https://t.co/f1xCWIbo64]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Engineer: 2nd Line Technical Support Engineer / Systems Engineer I am working with an industry leading telecommunications organisation based in the Ruddington area. They are in the market for an ambitious Technical Support Engineer to… https://t.co/pbzCjWaZch https://t.co/RRCD4fxuRB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The changing police narrative of why a black man was shot and killed in an Alabama mall: Hoover police can't seem to get their story straight on why an officer killed a man at an Alabama mall. https://t.co/v56zdlepYX https://t.co/4uv8bbIpGm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wintel Engineer (AD – VMWare – SCCM): Wintel / Citrix / Active Directory / VMWare / Windows / Technical Support / Unix / SCCM Role Purpose Provides technical support activities as part of service delivery provision and/or projects deployment, including… https://t.co/h12ygSfZK8 https://t.co/51bm89NjPs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Software Engineer – CSI NOVA: 111184BR Cyber Software Engineer – CSI NOVA PA – State College, VA – Arlington, VA – Dulles 111184BR Seeking Cyber Software Engineers for Raytheon Cyber Security Innovations (CSI) offices in Arlington, VA; Dulles, VA;… https://t.co/M1zXneOwrb https://t.co/6WpbkqTd3l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Graduate Software Developer: Graduate Software Developer – London – Immediate – £23k – £26k + employee perks Sparta Global is looking for graduates who want to launch their careers in tech as full stack engineers with the ability to write and test the… https://t.co/uKU4gSoSrg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ICT Information/Data Architect: ICT Information/Data Architect Worcester £49,000 The role is part of the ICT Technical Architecture Practice e.g. to identify impacts on any new proposed services. The role will also help to create a culture of perpetual… https://t.co/kybwbdc5ha https://t.co/O2wtghQSEP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former World War II codebreaker dies at 96: Baroness Trumpington, the former World War Two code-breaker and British politician, has died at the age of 96. https://t.co/pyU7qie6eT https://t.co/yOUyQYhYb7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Incident response – Home based: A multinational company with offices on almost every continent is looking for experienced incident response consultant to be based out of their London office. This is a hands on job and you’ll be tasked with dealing with… https://t.co/OvFJY87SZU https://t.co/s55wta08rN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Test Automation Engineer: SunIRef:it Senior Test Automation Engineer – San Mateo, CA 94401 – ********** Find Jobs Company Reviews Find Salaries Find Resumes Employers / Post Job Upload your resume Sign in Home whatjob title, keywords, or company… https://t.co/4D6iEfDwKr https://t.co/tj0x1SZhZP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Customer Support – Graduate Role: Are you a Graduate seeking an opportunity to apply your Computer Science Degree in your first role within a market leading business? We are proud to be supporting a Kent based business who excel at delivering a high… https://t.co/jHgb0LJDru https://t.co/4iAWqD3KZy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Specialist – Infrastructure: Overall Job Purpose To provide proactive management audit improve and architectural guidance for Data Centre infrastructure platforms and customers. This will include design configuration and support for all Data… https://t.co/Y8hygzy4zW https://t.co/slGu7Msu1k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JavaScript Team Lead – will relocate!: job detailsJob Number:1219201Job Title:JavaScript Team Lead – will relocate!Job Type:Full-timeLocation:Jersey City, NJHours:Post Date:Apr 19 2018Salary:$180K-$190KDetailed Job Description: Great financial firm is… https://t.co/7acZtsDrDr https://t.co/dUVebDlfri]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump casts doubt on UK's ability to trade with US post-Brexit: US President Donald Trump has added himself to the chorus of skeptics doubting British Prime Minister Theresa May's Brexit plan, saying it isn't clear if the agreement will allow a US-UK… https://t.co/iZN2CO4RHR https://t.co/wsdPPCqCq4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Java Engineer: Having Developed a reputation as the go-to Cloud team in London, we are searching for a Technical Lead Java Engineer to sit as the design authority for a complete re-build of the words largest airline's core platform as Java… https://t.co/gV0XYQ6al8 https://t.co/DAdmssEDWP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Desktop Support Engineer Vacancy – Central London: Our client is looking for an IT desktop support engineer, on permanent basis based in Central London. Key details * IT Desktop Support Engineer * Permanent vacancy * West End (Central London) *… https://t.co/SzwfC7dZyc https://t.co/63BNxwbuNj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal IC Design Engineer: 113586BR Principal IC Design Engineer CA – El Segundo 113586BR This position requires a U.S. person or the ability to obtain an Export Authorization from the appropriate government agency for non-U.S. persons. Senior… https://t.co/XQ5DihUDOP https://t.co/MDiAkUSDXu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer: We are currently recruiting for a leading solutions provider who are recruiting for a number of Network Engineers for their Basingstoke site. You'll be responsible for providing complex and tactical solutions to their customers… https://t.co/vz7dUM4QsP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Six bodies found at house in Japanese tourist town: Authorities have discovered the bodies of six people, including a 7-year-old girl, at a house in the Japanese town of Takachiho, a popular destination for tourists visiting the Takachiho Gorge in… https://t.co/iPSKrkZVSn https://t.co/vJ3DUsqPMi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Engineer:   Job Description – Systems Engineer (18023146) Systems Engineer Requisition ID : 18023146 Location : United States-District of Columbia-Washington US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation Assistance: No relocation… https://t.co/HxqpZ9WTQv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NET Developer – Fintech Start-Up – Manchester: NET Developer – Fintech Start-Up – Manchester (Tech stack: .NET Developer, https://t.co/QLOVMK1yTs MVC, C#, Agile, Azure, SQL Server, HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, Angular, .NET Developer, Urgent) We have several… https://t.co/okRIdUp2rW https://t.co/8SWbATdoFX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NET Developer, C#, WPF – Mobile Telecommunications – London: NET Developer, C#, WPF – Mobile Telecommunications – London (Tech stack: .NET Developer, C#, WPF, Server 2016, MVVM, Prism, TDD, Agile, .NET Developer, Urgent) Established in the early 1990s… https://t.co/39CeyKA0eQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Support Analyst – Bespoke Applications: Application Support Analyst The ECS Resource Group are recruiting for an Application Support Analyst to work for a leading online gaming/gambling organisation based in London. You will be responsible… https://t.co/jLpTgcihpi https://t.co/tMz3HE3RuA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: Has the world learned the lessons of the Holocaust? I don't think so.: The rise of the far right in Europe has brought back to the surface fears that many had hoped were gone forever. https://t.co/fEFDzFIkDv https://t.co/ZN9o0qsLQ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NET Developer – Times Top 100 Employer – Birkenhead: NET Developer (https://t.co/QLOVMK1yTs, C#, C#.NET, dot NET, Web Application Development, .NET 4.5, https://t.co/QLOVMK1yTs MVC 5, RESTful, Web API, SQL Server 2016, Knockout.js, Angular, Bootstrap,… https://t.co/sqpL2FQTMK https://t.co/r8t2z9VQrm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Program Support Assistant GS-303-7: PROGRAM SUPPORT ASSISTANT GS-303-7 The U.S. Department of Agriculture (USDA), Agricultural Research Service (ARS), Plum Island, New York, is hiring a full-time positon at the Plum Island Animal Disease Center.… https://t.co/7DeMKGgh70 https://t.co/pdMIZdyIQu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NET Developer – Fintech Start-Up – St Albans: NET Developer (https://t.co/QLOVMK1yTs, C#, C#.NET, dot NET, Web Application Development, NET 4.5, https://t.co/QLOVMK1yTs MVC 5, MongoDB, RavenDB, Scrum/Agile, IOC, Azure, SQL Server 2016, HTML5, CSS3,… https://t.co/xyeO8cW8Db]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NET Developer – Fastest Growing Social Media Firm – Nottingham: NET Developer – Fastest Growing Social Media Firm – Nottingham (Tech stack: https://t.co/QLOVMK1yTs MVC, .NET Core, Web API 2, SQL Server 2016, Agile, Urgent) Our client is on a quest to… https://t.co/G0d622l6eV https://t.co/Jyukdyjgvh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Project Manager A new role for a Project Manager has arisen with a thriving, well-invested, fast-growing specialist solutions provider in Cambridge, currently listed in the Sunday Times Tech Track 100 fastest growing UK tech Companies.… https://t.co/PVYIEjFlwo https://t.co/umWaM77Gkk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Identity Access Management #180009DP: Zurich Services (Schaumburg, IL) seeks Identity and Access Management (IAM) Consultant to manage the solutions architecture &amp; software development in the domain of identity &amp; access management/related middleware/lead… https://t.co/au1JDTNW2F https://t.co/pALtJM30rr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Exclusive: A global travel company based in London who shaping and influencing customer behaviours to drive revenue and value for clients are seeking Mid and Senior Java Developers. With offices globally and an impressive client base of… https://t.co/vOI93HDD0b https://t.co/pqIJuK7Nze]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That night, a forest flew: DroneSeed is planting trees from the air: Wildfires are consuming our forests. The institutions and technologies to keep these environments healthy have suffered decades of neglect. DroneSeed is a Seattle-based startup that… https://t.co/XgvdJEsmPm https://t.co/lBJT3AWcGf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NET Developer, https://t.co/QLOVMK1yTs MVC, C# – Global Record Label – Fareham: NET Developer, https://t.co/QLOVMK1yTs MVC, C# – Global Record Label – Fareham (Tech stack: .NET Developer, https://t.co/QLOVMK1yTs MVC, C#, WCF, RESTful, Web API 2, SQL… https://t.co/ZSnDfWDEPG https://t.co/ciAAwHx7tg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AWS launches Arm-based servers for EC2: At its re:Invent conference in Las Vegas, AWS today announced the launch of Arm-based servers for its EC2 cloud computing service. These aren’t run-of-the-mill Arm chips, though. AWS took the standard Arm cores and… https://t.co/qgEdOHbIQu https://t.co/PWSB36N5vK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PHP Developer (Full Stack): PHP Developers (Full-stack) Up to £45,000 + benefits West and East Yorkshire Interaction Recruitment are proud to be partnering with a growing software house in West Yorkshire. Our client requires two experienced PHP… https://t.co/zl3sSAyHn9 https://t.co/oEGyWyOvNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump says he was 'very tough' on GM CEO over plant closures: President Donald Trump said Monday he was pressuring General Motors over its decision to close four plants in the US because of sagging demand for sedans. https://t.co/DZZVXajPr8 https://t.co/yYe4fEbv0p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NET Developer – Amazing Opportunity – Tunbridge Wells: NET Developer – Amazing Opportunity – Tunbridge Wells (Teck stack: https://t.co/QLOVMK1yTs MVC, C#, Azure, AWS, Agile, Angular, RESTful API, Web API 2, WCF, Urgent) At this very moment our client is… https://t.co/KQP4Ztd1qJ https://t.co/pxt7JXEa3r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NET Developer – Computer Gaming Company – Southampton: NET Developer – Computer Gaming Company – Southampton (Tech stack: .NET Developer, https://t.co/QLOVMK1yTs MVC, C#, WCF, RESTful, Web API 2, SQL Server 2016, Agile, .NET Developer, Urgent) Having… https://t.co/laWnho0uH9 https://t.co/3xVZmd3C5g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NET Developer – Liverpool: NET Developer – Liverpool (Tech stack: .NET Developer, https://t.co/QLOVMK1yTs MVC, C#, Agile, Azure, SQL Server, HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, Angular, .NET Developer, Urgent) We have several fantastic new roles for .NET Developer… https://t.co/6QnBGlh6F0 https://t.co/zbCKZB5CSz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mia Love slams Trump in concession speech: Republican Rep. Mia Love sharply criticized President Donald Trump during a concession speech on Monday, saying Trump's vision of the world is "no real relationships, just convenient transactions." https://t.co/2rLGW39LG4 https://t.co/a9OcwIpqkY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Internal Auditor: Internal Auditor; Senior: Execute and occasionally lead audits, advisory and investigation projects in accordance with professional accounting standards as it relates to Real Estate Appraisals. Review reports of suspected fraud; analyze… https://t.co/Hljd5WLMhI https://t.co/HHSJyybDIw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NET Developer, https://t.co/QLOVMK1yTs MVC, C#, – Digital Download Site: NET Developer, https://t.co/QLOVMK1yTs MVC, C#, – Digital Download Site – Reading (Tech stack: .NET Developer, https://t.co/QLOVMK1yTs MVC, C#, Azure, WebAPI 2, ElasticSearch,… https://t.co/LYtuju84K7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: ENGINEERING- Juniper Networks is recruiting for our Sunnyvale, CA office: Software Engineer: Develop efficient &amp; intuitive user interface using single page application frameworks like Backbone, React JS, JavaScript, HTML5, &amp; CSS3.… https://t.co/iRvp8jUQYZ https://t.co/pGLTUdjfGr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NET Developer, https://t.co/QLOVMK1yTs Core, C# – Manchester: NET Developer, https://t.co/QLOVMK1yTs Core, C# – Global Internet Icon – Manchester (Tech stack: .NET Developer, https://t.co/QLOVMK1yTs Core, C#, https://t.co/QLOVMK1yTs MVC, Angular, Web API… https://t.co/mpmkE5ehAv https://t.co/OVgG3XYwYA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NET Development Manager – Fintech – Manchester: NET Development Manager – Fintech – Manchester (Tech stack: .NET Development Manager, https://t.co/QLOVMK1yTs MVC C#, https://t.co/QLOVMK1yTs Core, Angular, TDD, BDD, .NET Development Manager, Urgent) We… https://t.co/dPI8hVNz3F https://t.co/pPjBNd34qU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kim Kardashian West: I was high on ecstasy when I got married and made my sex tape: Kim Kardashian West may have been the designated driver for her sisters as a teen, but that doesn't mean she didn't party. https://t.co/tXLF5zAMpD https://t.co/NxrzeslPNV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer: Electrical Senior Engineer for Skyworks Solutions, Inc., San Jose, CA: Create innovative solutions for cellular mkt. Resumes: Angela Ho, Skyworks, 5221 California Ave., Irvine, CA 92617. Must ref: SJ0418SS recblid g9u3jfosczx7e1kuis1m9p8bmereug https://t.co/fo0PgFjiIc https://t.co/eLKZG3bE9n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NET Developer -Fastest Growing Social Media Firm– West Malling: NET Developer – Fastest Growing Social Media Firm – West Malling (Tech stack: .NET Developer, https://t.co/QLOVMK1yTs MVC, .NET Core, Web API 2, SQL Server 2016, Agile, .NET Developer,… https://t.co/sGXVuqWC3L https://t.co/AJ0C34qZxq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NET Developer – Global Phenomenon – Kingston upon Thames: NET Developer – Global Phenomenon – Kingston upon Thames (Tech stack: .NET Developer, https://t.co/QLOVMK1yTs MVC, C#, .NET Core, Azure, Web API 2, Angular 2, .NET Developer, Urgent) Our client… https://t.co/FXuebkBcQ0 https://t.co/8ZKepVq96A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Italian director Bernardo Bertolucci dies at 77: Bernardo Bertolucci, the award-winning Italian director of "Last Tango in Paris", has died aged 77 following a battle with cancer, Italian officials confirmed Monday. https://t.co/8d91EtZRT8 https://t.co/8IwbnxcAVA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NET Developer – Global Phenomenon – Grantham: NET Developer – Global Phenomenon – Grantham (Tech stack: .NET Developer, https://t.co/QLOVMK1yTs MVC, C#, .NET Core, Azure, Web API 2, Angular 2, .NET Developer, Urgent) Our client has created a global… https://t.co/j2ea4mYM0P https://t.co/V32mPO1RYq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UI Architect: UI Architect ******O5 With tremendous market success in our Cloud Applications, especially in ERP Cloud, Higher Ed institutions have expressed unprecedented interest in embarking a cloud adoption journey with Oracle. Student Information… https://t.co/qbUh7lndrg https://t.co/8lTpwBO7Qh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NET Developer – Computer Gaming Company – Chester: NET Developer – Computer Gaming Company – Chester (Tech stack: .NET Developer, https://t.co/QLOVMK1yTs MVC, C#, WCF, RESTful, Web API 2, SQL Server 2016, Agile, .NET Developer, Urgent) Having sold over… https://t.co/E4495LyVgx https://t.co/MfCNFibkJ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior/Principal Full-stack Software Dev Engineer (LifeLock…: SunIRef:it Senior/Principal Full-stack Software Dev Engineer (LifeLock ID Protection) – Tempe, AZ 85281 – ********** Find Jobs Company Reviews Find Salaries Find Resumes Employers / Post Job… https://t.co/2aCC1Hn5dj https://t.co/7o34ertrD3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/lEqrCJxONf Developer: Due to my clients continued growth and success, they are seeking an experienced https://t.co/lEqrCJxONf software developer to join their expanding development team in Chorley, Lancashire. The primary objective – is to… https://t.co/R8FQKkybWY https://t.co/Vhy7rhuxY0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UAE pardons British academic charged with spying: The United Arab Emirates has pardoned Matthew Hedges, a British citizen who was charged with spying by an Emirati court. https://t.co/XCbkyg9wA7 https://t.co/G96Ssd4iiS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solution Analyst – VisionPLUS: Job Title: Solution Analyst – VisionPLUS Grade: Senior Consultant Location: London (UK) – travel will be required Practice: Cards and Payments Salary: Competitive+Flexible Benefits+Bonus Working Pattern: Full Time,… https://t.co/Ej4JX9xDX7 https://t.co/NeUIY7P49d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More than 140 whales dead after mass stranding: As many as 145 whales have died after being found stranded on a remote beach in New Zealand, conservation officials said Monday. https://t.co/XLiIY2z9pR https://t.co/B2dL6tC9Fq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer – C: Software Developer – C#.NET Full Microsoft Stack   Experienced Full Stack Software Developer required with experience of working within an agile software development environment for successful software development team for a… https://t.co/TdsxfZamGw https://t.co/SRLcOwJWgh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US authorities used tear gas on migrants attempting to cross the border illegally from Tijuana, according to journalists at the scene: The US Customs and Border Protection office in San Diego has closed road and pedestrian bridges in both directions at… https://t.co/DmcsPtiwm6 https://t.co/F1dZl4Yvmc]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>