<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Integration Engineer: Costa Mesa, CA Full-time $90k – $120k Posted Today YOU ARE A passionate SQL Engineer that loves solving problems! In this role you will be analyzing and integrating data from many sources with minimal documentation. We are… https://t.co/uPZlPO50O5 https://t.co/JF06Bhb3RP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Cavs win NBA finals, NFLer could be out $9 million https://t.co/nYpDrnPWS5 https://t.co/hAb7KEjFzq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL/SQL Developer: PL/SQL Developer Columbus, OH 05-14-2018 Location: Columbus, OH For more than 18 years, CareWorks Tech has been delivering technology solutions that drive results. As your advocate, the common thread across our associates is crafting… https://t.co/2UGhoeqe07 https://t.co/1yq9n5YYUt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: Job Description This Senior Consultant position will develop and maintain analytic products including reports and simulation models for CVS Caremark customers and account teams. This position will received data from other teams within CVS… https://t.co/3aB1xcy76v https://t.co/XmAIpj8j0c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server Developer: – * Bachelor’s degree or foreign equivalent required from an accredited institution. Will also consider three years of progressive experience in the specialty in lieu of every year of education. – At least 4 years of experience with… https://t.co/OtSPkaawac https://t.co/Z1ot5f9M4o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server DBA w/ MySQL or Postgres: SQL Server DBA w/ some MySQL and/or Postgres DC Kamis is searching for a Database Administrator to fill a direct/permanent position with a company located in Washington DC. The DBA should have expertise with large SQL… https://t.co/LCUJ4uqNWy https://t.co/FrzHA2hm1E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 people narrowly escape bridge collapse: A bridge is wiped out from heavy water flow in Cuba and two people narrowly escaped the wash out. https://t.co/WW61VE5FyY https://t.co/av7oD6lKMA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Grey's Anatomy' actor: 'Whites Only' spaces still exist: For a few hours on Tuesday, thousands of Americans will suffer. They will be without their morning jolt, afternoon pick-me-up and end of day treat from corporate giant Starbucks coffee. People… https://t.co/eNdRosugxA https://t.co/bJHgPNJzsJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heckling fan taunts Steph Curry's wife: The wife of NBA star Steph Curry, Ayesha Curry, took to Twitter to address a fan who was heckling her after Game 5 of the Western conference finals. https://t.co/R09aTHuA7s https://t.co/G0eYs0xmh6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL/SQL Developer: PL/SQL Developer Charlotte, North Carolina – United States Job Start Date – 06/18/18, Posted Date – 05/25/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview Required: Minimum 5 year experience in Oracle Stored procedure development Able to write… https://t.co/Mc2Fgq7UuB https://t.co/dVPsglsWpp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Backend Software Engineer – Java / MySQL / AWS: We are looking for a highly talented Backend Software Engineer for our El Dorado Hills office. As a Backend Java Application Developer youll provide support across all of Keepers products (Consumer, B2B).… https://t.co/v8cYGlZIcC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server Admin/Developer: SQL Server Admin/Developer Ref No.: 18-28320 Location: Torrance, California Role: Sql Server DBA Location: Torrance, CA Duration: 12 + Months primary skill : DBA SQL secondary skill : Microsoft SQL Server Database Developer… https://t.co/8ljuAJYzCl https://t.co/AcexS10mGE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why some polls may be underestimating Democrats: Republicans dominated the midterm elections in 2010 and 2014 in part because voters who supported Barack Obama in presidential years voted for Republicans or stayed home when he wasn't on the ballot. https://t.co/XSMZoRdFkP https://t.co/ChWUB1UFoL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL/SQL Developer with .Net: PL/SQL Developer with .Net Ref No.: 18-28424 Location: Tempe, Arizona Hello, Greetings for the day ! We have an urgent requirement for PL/SQL Developer with .Net in Tempe, AZ or Santa Clara, CA. Please Let me know if you are… https://t.co/iwvQVOzusd https://t.co/X0zMScm7tl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The top July 4 events across the US: Although many people view Memorial Day as the American holiday that unofficially kicks off summer, it could be argued that the Fourth of July is summer's biggest, best holiday. https://t.co/hRCTaJKXLZ https://t.co/ANW9wpITE4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Program Manager: Program Manager (Sunnyvale, CA) Coordinate regional &amp; global programs for Google facilities and physical operations. #1615.28185 Exp Incl: researching &amp; analyzing key bus drivers &amp; trends in the high technology or internet domain;… https://t.co/AErmlG0s5a https://t.co/kk6kpGbwy3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Experts break down 'The Star-Spangled Banner' https://t.co/2Viid078BQ https://t.co/aSCumm7g3b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL / ETL Developer: SQL / ETL Developer – VanderHouwen 1-************ – About Us – Meet The Team – Join Our Team – Employers – Technology Job Placements – Accounting &amp; Finance Job Placements – Engineering Placements – Job Seekers – Technology Jobs –… https://t.co/U3zy09Vdgp https://t.co/69jSXdmaUM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Specialist Developer https://t.co/qZglOKK4dO, MVC, C#, SQL Server, SSRS: For BNY Mellon Specialist Developer – *******, MVC, C#, SQL Server, SSRS job – Asset Servicing – Multiple Skip to Main Content – – – – Toggle navigation – Who We Are – What We Do –… https://t.co/Shqn31oIUg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These are Trump's Fox News hires: President Trump has appointed several conservative TV pundits to his cabinet, many of whom come from Fox News. https://t.co/JSBAN8sj1s https://t.co/kCte08e5Ju]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst II(excel, SQL, Healthcare): Job ID ******* Category Data Analytics Schedule Full-time Job ID ******* Category Data Analytics Schedule Full-time Description: Position Purpose: – Analyze health management programs including: data collection,… https://t.co/C8gGwzkV6U https://t.co/OPHKH8ZKkE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MySQL DBA: MYSQL DBA LOCATIONS: PITTSBURGH, PA/CLEVELAND, OH LOOKING FOR EXPERIENCED MYSQL DBA TO ASSIST WITH ENTERPRISE MYSQL DESIGN AND IMPLEMENTATION PROJECT. * The candidate must have experience with the following technologies: * MySQL Architecture,… https://t.co/3sZUB6Vxae https://t.co/O45aFLEOHA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SSRS – SQL Server Reporting Services: SSRS – SQL Server Reporting Services Ref No.: 18-27583 Location: columbia, Maryland Key skills required for the job are: SSRS – SQL Server Reporting Services-L3 (Mandatory) As a develoer, you are responsible for… https://t.co/tvnFzPuS31 https://t.co/5WLsk0wY8B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Soccer team may need to learn to scuba dive to escape: The initial relief that greeted the dramatic discovery of the trapped Thai soccer team has given way to concern, as rescuers begin the difficult task of attempting to free the 12 boys and their coach… https://t.co/PeeMFsqmrE https://t.co/i7s7XdEfnN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server Integration Services: SQL Server 2012 Integration Services (SSIS) Ref No.: 18-22663 Location: Kalamazoo, Michigan SQL Server 2012 Integration Services (SSIS) Kalamazoo, MI 12 Months contract Job Description: Hand on experience of SSIS and… https://t.co/LxSmHRPHMC https://t.co/fSZMBWrXEH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle Pl/sql developer: Job TitleOracle Pl/sql developer – ID:31484 Duration6 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsOracle, PL/SQL, Billing LocationIrving, TX Date Posted04/13/2018 Our client, a Fortune 50, global telecommunications company is looking for GIS… https://t.co/0lXjuEosbD https://t.co/a90mo2a1Pd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CONSULTING SOFTWARE ENGINEER – SQL Server / ETL / DW: Lead SQL Server database, ETLand cube development design and development in Business Intelligence Team data warehouse and analytics environment Essential Functions: – Develop guidelines for other… https://t.co/jPdVY6f4Kd https://t.co/a38BfumRgM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MS SQL SSIS Developer: MS SQL SSIS Developer Ref No.: 18-23310 Location: Washington, District of Columbia Title:- MS SQL SSIS/SSAS Developer Location:- Washington DC Contract W2 – Candidate should have more than 8+ years of Total IT experience. – More… https://t.co/0AHD5fdr2Q https://t.co/3UrzeDbcTm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Report Writer/Report Developer – SQL/SSRS: Report Writer/Report Developer – SQL/SSRS – FirstPRO 360 Toggle navigation Menu Close – Specialties – Accounting &amp; Finance – Information Technology – Life Sciences – Medical Device Sales – Project Services –… https://t.co/z618GPhhtJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL BI Developer: SQL BI Developer Ref No.: 18-28074 Location: Redmond, Washington Role: SQL BI Developer Location: Redmond, WA Duration: Full Time Permanent Job Description Proficient in SQL BI Advanced knowledge on SSIS/ETL Packages and SSAS Knowledge… https://t.co/h0wm0eJzMD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL DBA with development experience: Requirements * 2+ years database administration experience * 1+ year database developer experience * In person interviews Requirements * Strong proficiency with SQL and its variation among popular databases *… https://t.co/3FV9oI9VmL https://t.co/89DDuSRCOP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Northeast US swelters under the worst heat wave of the year: Nearly 60 million people across the Northeastern US are under a heat watch, warning or advisory from the National Weather Service as the worst heat wave of 2018 scorches the most populated… https://t.co/uFpeIUuXHZ https://t.co/Enoe7y2hEO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Soccer team found alive after 9 days trapped in cave https://t.co/QylYJOdOea https://t.co/wq0QOruAGa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I.T.: Infoshare Systems, Inc. (Mission Viejo, CA) needs: Project Manager: supervise multiple employees, provide project mgt. throughout the life of project: Sr. Application Developer: design, develop &amp; test software solutions using JAVA, J2ee, C#.NET,… https://t.co/mVb9uv65qX https://t.co/QBCx06cJyM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Specialist Developer https://t.co/qZglOKK4dO, MVC, C#, SQL Server, SSRS: For BNY Mellon Specialist Developer – *******, MVC, C#, SQL Server, SSRS job – Asset Servicing – Multiple Skip to Main Content – – – – Toggle navigation – Who We Are – What We Do –… https://t.co/xWuBCozXh7 https://t.co/MqOwxTJ8C3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Acosta shouts questions at Trump: CNN's Jim Acosta talks about his experiences facing hostile crowds while covering President Trump's rallies and responds to critics who say he shouts questions at President Donald Trump to draw attention to himself. https://t.co/LjR0qkTTkQ https://t.co/46M5G7NgZv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exclusive: FBI seized recordings between Trump's lawyer and Stormy Daniels' former lawyer: The FBI seized recordings President Donald Trump's attorney made of his conversations with a lawyer representing two women who had alleged affairs with Trump, a… https://t.co/Ex9tJums5e https://t.co/jbU98Y9rjQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL BI Developer (SSMS) / QA ETL Testing: SQL BI Developer (SSMS) / QA ETL Testing – CareWorks TechCareWorks Tech CareWorks Tech Menu – Services – IT Consulting – Enterprise Service Management – Infrastructure – Security – Interactive – Events – Careers… https://t.co/5h8g4xcouD https://t.co/uWgLwt48nw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle PL/SQL Developer: Job TitleOracle PL/SQL Developer – ID:31809 Duration3 Months to Hire Start DateASAP Job SkillsPL/SQL LocationDallas, TX Date Posted05/25/2018 Qualifications Bachelor’s degree (BA/BS) in a related field such as information… https://t.co/NEidM6gZO6 https://t.co/Ozl8EDzBaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lawmaker calls for banning bouncy castles after girl's death: A British MP has called for a temporary ban on bouncy castles in public places after a girl was thrown from one and killed by the English seaside on Sunday. https://t.co/ZtsdogHyMJ https://t.co/oKSn7jrfJ8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Intelligence- ETL / SQL Developer II: Business Intelligence- ETL / SQL Developer II at PATTERSON COMPANIES Skip Navigation – Corporate Site – Company Overview – News and Events – Working at Patterson – Environmental Impact Sign In Search Jobs… https://t.co/jCyeSHQNK1 https://t.co/bdrWf4dbo0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL DBA: SQL DBA: 18-02378 Ref No.: 18-02378 Location: Mountain View, California Akraya is looking for a SQL DBA for one of our clients. If the job description below is a fit, please apply directly or call Dipak Badgujar at ************. If this position… https://t.co/ZzCl29Pz0t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[pl/Sql developer: pl/Sql developer Ref No.: 18-27893 Location: pennington, New Jersey Hello, Kindly review the below position and let me know if you are interested, send me an updated resume along with best time to contact. Title: PL/SQL Developer… https://t.co/xrgU0PSota]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[American tourist dies in boat explosion: At least one American tourist is dead and ten people were injured after a tour boat exploded in the Bahamas, according to the Royal Bahamas Police Force. https://t.co/Om5ZnxmR8z https://t.co/YbIjah3yEV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle PL/SQL Developer: Oracle PL/SQL Developer in North Quincy, Massachusetts, United States | Consulting at CognizantJob Details | Cognizant – ************* – Industries – – – Services – – – Latest Thinking – – – About Cognizant – Careers Home – Get… https://t.co/AgXzxGi8TS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETL Developer (SQL Server and SSIS): * This person will work with the RM Data Layer Team to assist in developing the RM data warehouse * Position will perform ELT (extract, load and transform) to bring data from many source systems into the Data… https://t.co/kYAnOKAPPX https://t.co/JYJfpxFcAI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Production Support Analyst with SQL Exp.: Production Support Analyst with SQL Exp. Ref No.: 18-28056 Location: Louisville, Kentucky Position: Production Support Analyst with SQL Exp. Location: Louisville, KY Rate: Market rate Duration: 12+Months Ability… https://t.co/WvFJl9EQ7c https://t.co/maOlP8qfGV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Data Analyst: The MSR Portfolio Management team is currently searching for a Technical Data Analyst with associate level experience with relational database structures, SQL, Visio, Excel and/or MS Access skills. Business Objects or Reporting tool &amp;… https://t.co/WObtR9vHgK https://t.co/dITve9P52H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automation tester w/Selenium, Java, SQL: Automation tester w/Selenium, Java, SQL in Quincy, Massachusetts, United States | Digital at CognizantJob Details | Cognizant – ************* – Industries – – – Services – – – Latest Thinking – – – About Cognizant… https://t.co/uSkbFtijGg https://t.co/WtJ07KtLCj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Specialist Developer – .NET, C#, SQL Server — Exchange Traded Funds: Sr. Specialist Developer – .NET, C#, SQL Server ‘ Exchange Traded Funds The Exchange Traded Funds Technology Team creates application-layer solutions to streamline and improve the… https://t.co/HAcxzEQxgU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Database Administrator: Fitness International is a well-established, respected fitness company with over 600 state-of-the-art sports clubs throughout US and Canada. Based in our Irvine headquarters, our IT department is expanding to support new… https://t.co/9trAJWigcc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Full Stack WordPress Developer: Our vision is to be the best provider of building products in the eyes of our customers, employees, shareholders, suppliers and communities. At Masonite, we understand that people are key. We are a composite of… https://t.co/MWb64EtC9D https://t.co/vOj0DrupVK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CNN anchor: Trump uses racism to appeal to base: CNN's Don Lemon breaks down President Trump's reaction to ABC's firing of Roseanne Barr over her racist tweets. https://t.co/jdvifm3N12 https://t.co/Jqu0OngNqO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer – Senior: SQL Developer – Senior Job in Scottsdale, AZ | CVS HEALTH ************* Main menu – About – About – Our Services – Retail Pharmacy – Pharmacy Benefits Management – Clinical Services – Specialty Pharmacy – Digital Services –… https://t.co/TZvFqrwIT0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL BI Developer: SQL BI Developer Ref No.: 18-28074 Location: Redmond, Washington Role: SQL BI Developer Location: Redmond, WA Duration: Full Time Permanent Job Description Proficient in SQL BI Advanced knowledge on SSIS/ETL Packages and SSAS Knowledge… https://t.co/R19NbZPA1d https://t.co/2KsXf6H6Ry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What will happen with 700 empty Toys 'R' Us stores? https://t.co/RB53lJfhxA https://t.co/a80lsMZ66Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MySQL Database Administrator: General Dynamics is looking for an experienced MySQL Database Administrator who will be responsible for ensuring the performance, availability, and security of MySQL instances. You will also be responsible for orchestrating… https://t.co/Arx6mVnxEs https://t.co/vq4l7f8To8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL/SSIS Developer: As a SQL/SSIS Developer, you will be filling a role at Huntington Bank to backup an application lead, support, assist, and enhance new vendor based applications being installed, enabling capital optimization and pricing decisions… https://t.co/p9rKmxjgUu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Country over party:' Democrats turn to military veterans to take back the House: Every time Dan Feehan shakes hands with voters in rural Minnesota, the reality of war is only as far as his right wrist. https://t.co/ALZVUpjZp0 https://t.co/tCiCpEe3hY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Informatica and SQL Server Developer: Informatica and SQL Server Developer: 18-02111 Ref No.:18-02111 Location: Burbank, California Akraya is looking for a Informatica and SQL Developer for one of our clients. If the job description below is a fit,… https://t.co/4QBMvEEITd https://t.co/D8yvg8yCdk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: SQL Developer Austin, Texas – United States Job Start Date – 06/11/18, Posted Date – 06/11/18 Primary SkillsSQLTax TermsC2COverview Phone and Inperson.. Duration – 6months. Rate- 50-55. Location Austin, TX . Client Retail Responsibilities:… https://t.co/n4vh86gEVZ https://t.co/FUi2BWGKLM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best July 4 events across the United States: Although many people view Memorial Day as the American holiday that unofficially kicks off summer, it could be argued that the Fourth of July is summer's biggest, best holiday. https://t.co/Gd1NjuRUQ7 https://t.co/K1QRyQBMIO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protest signs reveal the outrage: The hand-scrawled signs in all colors and sizes reflect the thousands of Americans participating in rallies Saturday against the Trump administration's "zero tolerance" policy toward undocumented immigrants. https://t.co/bCy8KzZmsQ https://t.co/3A7kv4bXNX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL DB Developer: SQL DB Developer Weston, Massachusetts – United States Job Start Date – 07/02/18, Posted Date – 06/12/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview Apex has an opportunity for a SQL Developer role in the Weston, MA area. This is a 6+ month… https://t.co/Ml442uEaqO https://t.co/tPbGqa55Ru]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump has world wondering what's next: President Donald Trump was in the East Room of the White House on Friday to trumpet the six-month anniversary of his tax cuts, the singular legislative achievement of his presidency so far. https://t.co/0UR9h1DK3f https://t.co/GiWluYwREf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Database Administrator: TUVAprovides turnkey solutions that offer better systems, tools, and methods to further your goals, reduce costs, and streamline operations. From requirements analysis, design, and implementation to operations and training… https://t.co/9Ff5hWPVc1 https://t.co/isTiWEGvym]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Roberts played the long game and won: For much of Chief Justice John Roberts' 13 years in the center chair on the Supreme Court, the direction of the law came down to the man who sat next to him, Anthony Kennedy, whose key vote and… https://t.co/zMPlwaIiTl https://t.co/OkKQDtmPH3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The worst NBA contracts in the last 5 years https://t.co/KIQzWAppn1 https://t.co/D1pwSr9ayv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server Database Architect/DBA Lead: Our direct client is looking for a SQL Server Architect/Lead to provide leadership, guidance, and coordination for large DBA support teams, including coordination of complex database design, development,… https://t.co/9uI1A6BwHB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Full Stack C# Developer: Company is looking for someone who has at least 8 years of programming experience with C#, *******, SQL, and JavaScript. The Developer will be tasked with keeping projects on track, reporting to management, and staying up… https://t.co/ov7ssnwsl1 https://t.co/5flmJYuWW1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This concrete (yes, concrete) is going high-tech https://t.co/I4fza5G3U3 https://t.co/Tiqk58x6jI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior SQL DBA: Senior SQL DBA Charlotte, North Carolina – United States Job Start Date – 05/16/18, Posted Date – 05/16/18 Primary SkillsSenior SQL DBATax TermsC2COverview Senior SQL DBA Any Visa from Trusted Vendors – Only These are the maximum rates… https://t.co/nURAgA6Mte https://t.co/lF5OF5UaYc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Specialist Developer – https://t.co/qZglOKK4dO, MVC, C#, SQL Server, SSRS: Job Description Specialist Developer – *******, MVC, C#, SQL Server, SSRS Provides application software development services or technical support in more complex situations. May… https://t.co/KjwoUmIBJC https://t.co/nH5LO6CNxO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Editor details suspect's threats: Former editor and publisher of the Capital Gazette newspaper Tom Marquardt discusses the threats accused gunman Jarrod Warren Ramos made against employees at the newspaper. https://t.co/R22sj8dM8R https://t.co/8XWPZcLdfB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server Business Intelligence: SQL Server Business Intelligence (BI) Responsibilities: – Providing direction on the new SQL Server Data Warehouse (DW) SQL Server BI tool – Making sure all data elements in the Enterprise Data Repository (EDR) were… https://t.co/NGN8klUOhG https://t.co/TQ2MCeLfB7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL/SQL Developer: PL/SQL Developer Malvern, Pennsylvania – United States Job Start Date – 06/25/18, Posted Date – 05/24/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview Title: PL/SQL Developer Project: Audit/Regulatory Compliance Reporting Team Duration: Long… https://t.co/ks3id6yhb6 https://t.co/LlgSKAJMPB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hannity denies tying Maxine Waters' rhetoric to shooting https://t.co/yqcnH5olHt https://t.co/9vu7rVSVk8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Axios: Trump privately threatens to quit WTO: President Donald Trump has been privately suggesting that he wants the US to withdraw from the World Trade Organization, according to a new report. https://t.co/AkMhYNRq5T https://t.co/HcbVEsJ9x3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. PHP Developer w/ NoSQL: SR. SOFTWARE ENGINEER – Permanent (No sponsorship today or in 3 years) AUSTIN, TX DIRECT HIRE – SALARY UP TO $125K – Will pay for relocation IMMEDIATE NEED for a Sr. LAMP Engineer to join our large enterprise client in Austin,… https://t.co/sfdlQr8f6X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT SQL Developer: An INFORMATION TECHNOLOGY SQL DEVELOPER is needed in the WATERLOO, IA area. This is with a strong consumer goods manufacturing company that is top in its class and offers a great work-life balance! MUST HAVE: * ASSOCIATES DEGREE… https://t.co/PhLc3EjBwa https://t.co/AnyuFX0OcG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer (For XML): Job TitleSQL Developer (For XML) – ID:31282 Duration12 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsXML, SSIS, XML Stored Procedures, SQL Queries, Consumer Facing web sites LocationTorrance, CA Date Posted05/14/2018 FOR IMMEDIATE DETAILS… https://t.co/eYGi9QWb7X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More voters want candidates who support abortion access: Registered voters are more likely to say they will vote for a candidate who supports access to abortion services, according to a Kaiser Family Foundation poll, released Friday. https://t.co/MqdEPl2PJx https://t.co/GEVklPuCiD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL DEVELOPER: Earthjustice is the premier nonprofit environmental law organization. We take on the biggest, most precedent-setting cases across the country. We wield the power of law and the strength of partnership to protect people’s health; to… https://t.co/znKwD4dloh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: Dems badly underestimated Trump: Democrats have a history of underestimating Republican presidents. https://t.co/JpUIEkwQbu https://t.co/VsGYJ3N12O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Database Analyst/Developer: Company Overview For 29 years, clients in the private and public sectors have relied upon SOS International LLC (SOSi) for critical operations in the world’s most challenging environments. SOSi is privately held, was… https://t.co/wzol6ZqYG8 https://t.co/FdwznhfPdY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Specialist Developer – https://t.co/qZglOKK4dO, MVC, C#, SQL Server, SSRS: For BNY Mellon Specialist Developer – *******, MVC, C#, SQL Server, SSRS job – Asset Servicing – Multiple Skip to Main Content – – – – Toggle navigation – Who We Are – What We Do… https://t.co/Ge1J8YLXE6 https://t.co/3MX5sjMV20]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NOSQL Developer: * Deep understanding of NoSQL and relational databases and database fundamentals, including data storage, data modeling, and data access patterns * Hands on experience with Linux system administration, including hardware and software… https://t.co/jdg2MDSk69 https://t.co/7wz4PFFosg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bolton answers to Trump-Putin meeting concerns: National Security Adviser John Bolton defends the decision for a meeting between Russian President Vladimir Putin and President Donald Trump, despite national security concerns following Russia's meddling… https://t.co/xEg1jvbgpE https://t.co/EtpoP1H2sG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: Why I'm burying a beer can in the backyard: Summer is here and Britain has a problem. For once this is not because the England soccer team is stinking out a World Cup (quite the opposite). But it's connected -- kind of. At a time when the nation… https://t.co/zzllmLyC64 https://t.co/UWPFqMW1oP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL/SSIS Developer: Search and apply for jobs at Piper Companies | Careers at Piper Companies Careers Search Jobs Connect With Us SQL/SSIS Developer Job Attributes Job Id: 19145Job Category: Software Applications &amp; ERPJob Location: Durham, NC… https://t.co/cPukx30lOC https://t.co/CPHOVYWJID]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL/SQL Developer: At least 4years of experience in Oracle PL/SQL development. At least 4 years of experience in software development life cycle. At least 4 years of experience in translating functional/non-functional requirements to system requirements.… https://t.co/plsMadAfMS https://t.co/MYa53CMOQw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Customer starts choking, Chick-fil-A employee does this: When a customer began choking on his food, a quick-thinking employee at a Chick-fil-A in Austin, Texas, jumped into action. https://t.co/281vwI8yyE https://t.co/gJCDD5I0Mw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best photos of the 2018 World Cup: The defending champions are out of the World Cup. https://t.co/tzvHYkpgGZ https://t.co/5sLpENZPFO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Specialist Developer (T-SQL, PL/SQL, Database design, objects, tuning): Sr. Specialist Developer (T-SQL, PL/SQL, Database design, objects, tuning) ‘ Developer, Application Development and Tools:’ Responsible for designing custom applications and… https://t.co/cMXOkYd5X3 https://t.co/Au5h2WFc1v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid-Level Java Developer: General Dynamics Information Technology (GDIT) has an immediate need for a Mid-level Java Developer to analyze, design, develop, implement, and support code; working under limited supervision; performing additional duties as… https://t.co/qB5Hn8iqDn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Child actor claps back at social media trolls: Ten-year-old "This Is Us" actor Lonnie Chavis recorded a message for trolls after receiving mean messages on social media about his appearance. https://t.co/uTMPLClT9R https://t.co/Xxb6lM4V4h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[28-year-old Latina is new face for Democrats https://t.co/JibMbnEHEH https://t.co/g8yDBYO1FX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL SQL Developer: PL SQL Developer in Alexandria, Virginia, United States | Management Consulting at Deloitte Toggle menu – Deloitte home – About Deloitte – – Location: United States Available in locations and languages – Students – Experienced – Careers… https://t.co/1Cs3iLtoPJ https://t.co/XbkEY04HHP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Database Administrator SurePayroll: Title SQL Database Administrator – SurePayroll ========================================= About the Organization Paychex, Inc. (NASDAQ: PAYX) is a leading provider of integrated human capital management solutions… https://t.co/Q5LDEPGoC4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server Developer: 5+ years of ETL / Data Warehouse experience 5+ years MS SQL Server experience; e.g. DDL, TSQL, Stored Procedures, Functions 3+ years MS SQL Database Administration; e.g. index, partitioning, execution plan analysis 3+ years SDLC… https://t.co/zDqFS3SOSg https://t.co/ZrjYCNEgsL]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>