<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Project Manager Water / Wastewater Engineering: Job Description Sr. Project Manager Water / Wastewater Engineering Sr. Project Manager Water / Wastewater Engineering (******) About Us At HDR, we specialize in engineering, architecture, environmental… https://t.co/nYknaYy4ff https://t.co/UHs5uPGVx9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Game Developer: Posting Details Applications will be accepted until midnight (Eastern Time Zone) on the ‘Posting End Date’ shown below. Position Information Job TitleGame Developer Applications Accepted FromPublic: Open to the public Special Instructions… https://t.co/0RcKBn0QCf https://t.co/8sAIPVh7ud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automation Programmer: Job Title Automation Programmer Requisition # PCC-US.****** Job Type Full-time Shift Type First Shift (Day) Location PCC Airfoils Douglas, GA – Douglas, GA 31535 US (Primary) Job Description PCC Airfoils, LLC, headquartered in… https://t.co/ikKQQ5ZbZd https://t.co/gdyUrdwExV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Testing Analyst Senior: Brief Description: The QA Testing Analyst — Senior for the Huntington Consumer Technology Systems is viewed as a leader within their team and actively participates with the larger team to help ensure the quality, performance… https://t.co/Q7BI5fGL0f https://t.co/YqHZWQXqU1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They baptized their children for school places. Now regret is setting in.: Ireland has dropped its "baptism barrier," which once allowed most Irish primary schools to prioritize admitting Catholic students. Some parents say the change has come too late. https://t.co/sO0306N4JQ https://t.co/qWBRvFPSII]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET / SQL Developer: .NET / SQL Developer – CareWorks TechCareWorks Tech CareWorks Tech Menu – Services – IT Consulting – Enterprise Service Management – Infrastructure – Events – Careers – Training – Contact Careers – Careers – Current Opportunities… https://t.co/rEC6im7hud https://t.co/fB1ZYEzH74]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump and White House are silent amid McCain news: When Sen. John McCain's family announced Friday that he was ending medical treatment for aggressive brain cancer, the news shook Capitol Hill and prompted support from his Republican and Democratic… https://t.co/lnWI8Pswx0 https://t.co/HybwTZnLnS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['It IS bad there': Emails reveal Trump officials pushing for TPS terminations: There was a simple explanation in October 2017 when a Department of Homeland Security official was asked why a memo justifying ending immigrant protections for Central… https://t.co/7uZ6flfxrS https://t.co/c5z4jHtSwl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, Senior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Dayton, OH Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 8/3/2018 Job Description Job Number: R******* Software Engineer, Senior Key Role: technical knowledge of software… https://t.co/Va907BuW7L https://t.co/TeaD2hFcVr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UI Angular Developer: UI Angular Developer Ref No.:18-11860 Location: Columbus, Ohio Position Type:Full Time/Contract Start Date: 07/05/2018 Must Have Skills: Angular.JS experience HTML/ CSS Angular.JS software engineering experience Familiarity with… https://t.co/eUe0EsM0AA https://t.co/w3SPtSm9G5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John McCain Fast Facts: Read CNN's Fast Facts on US Senator John McCain. https://t.co/6Ka7lJUJOA https://t.co/pZ9ogZtS3c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Business Operations Analyst Revenue Cycle Administration: Description Summary: A lead member of the Revenue Cycle Team who works with leadership to develop training curriculum and educational materials, supporting staff in their efforts to become… https://t.co/8lcLYsI7zC https://t.co/rCvwnOZHJt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meghan McCain shares photo of father during his absence from Washington: Meghan McCain tweeted a photo of her father Sunday, showing her and the Republican senator from Arizona together amid his absence from Capitol Hill. https://t.co/gSXmP6mPS5 https://t.co/5zlLzBij7n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maximo Developer: Maximo Developer Ref No.:18-03429 Location: Perrysburg, Ohio Position Type:Contract This opportunity is with a multibillion $ Global giant based in United States, Canada &amp; Mexico, with 16 different delivery centers and Regional offices… https://t.co/NMdpQvRCCi https://t.co/HWWZTnD3RY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What to know about tipping in Canada: Here's what you need to know about proper tipping in Canada, including the variations you might find among cities such as Montreal, Toronto and Vancouver. https://t.co/YdCUOIUKjd https://t.co/4SaYAcRI9K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist Intern (BS/MS Students) – Summer: Date: Aug 6, 2018 Location: Wickliffe, Ohio, US, 44092 Company: Lubrizol Corporation Lubrizol Additives is a pioneering global supplier of chemical additives technologies including additives for engine… https://t.co/6lbEfcl0c6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automation Programmer: Job Title Automation Programmer Requisition # PCC-US.****** Job Type Full-time Shift Type First Shift (Day) Location PCC Airfoils Douglas, GA – Douglas, GA 31535 US (Primary) Job Description PCC Airfoils, LLC, headquartered in… https://t.co/bFUPa1iXMM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager AECOM Hunt: AECOM is actively seeking a highly talented Project Manager for immediate employment for a project in Canton, OH. Provides overall management administration to project and assists in establishing project specific objectives… https://t.co/aoS0toqNyP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 things for August 24: David Pecker, Hurricane Lane, Duncan Hunter, Arctic ice: Here's what else you need to know to Get Up to Speed and Out the Door. https://t.co/JvJ9e8hRe3 https://t.co/JlL5cBYLGc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer-NX/Teamcenter: For Siemens Software Engineer-NX/Teamcenter job – Research &amp; Development – Milford, Ohio Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard – Toggle navigation – My Dashboard – Our Stories – FAQS – – –… https://t.co/pcb9cGakwt https://t.co/OnONk82LPv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waymo wants to test its self-driving car tech in China: Waymo, the self-driving car division of Google's parent company, Alphabet, has registered a company in Shanghai. https://t.co/Br2fTBwqAk https://t.co/UUoqx5oLWW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Java Developer: Location US-OH-Cincinnati Posted Date 22 hours ago(8/14/2018 11:44 AM) Job ID 23952 # Positions 1 Category Technology Position Type Full Time Overview Be Here. Be Great. Working for a leader in the insurance industry means… https://t.co/4Bdojicfjo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director, IT Support Services, College of Arts and Sciences: Job Title Director, IT Support Services, College of Arts and Sciences Applications Accepted From Public: Open to the public Special Instructions to Applicants Please complete the on-line… https://t.co/ZXH2EG32EO https://t.co/1HXiHfJhOH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ireland abuse survivors say Pope must face up to Church's past sins: This weekend will be a moment of reckoning for survivors around the world, as the Pope arrives for the first papal visit to Ireland in nearly 40 years amid a growing outcry over… https://t.co/N80KE5cRNS https://t.co/YaebiIHJws]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Criminal justice overhaul is tabled -- for now: President Donald Trump on Thursday tabled a criminal justice package being pushed by a group of lawmakers and his son-in-law, Jared Kushner, multiple sources said. https://t.co/VsBCIbK7H0 https://t.co/tttCHVM1UX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon bans the sale of a guidebook for 3D printing a gun: The everything store doesn't have room for a book explaining how to 3D print a gun. https://t.co/5Tgn4qzLnE https://t.co/70afFtAMKg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bolton warns Russia over election interference, denies Trump is a 'security risk': National security adviser John Bolton warned Thursday that the US will not tolerate Russian interference in the 2018 midterm elections, attempting to reaffirm the… https://t.co/GFfzaUOu5G https://t.co/XsOCH3N65k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beto O'Rourke's defense of anthem protests draws support from LeBron James: A viral video of Democratic Texas Senate candidate Beto O'Rourke discussing protests over racial injustice during the national anthem in the NFL has drawn a wave of praise and… https://t.co/H7O3QsRTqL https://t.co/nNMQpcAor1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Project Manager Sr: Technical Project Manager Sr Join a team recognized for leadership, innovation and diversity Honeywell Intelligrated – ********************* has multiple opportunities for high-level Project Managers to support major… https://t.co/QDs3hKJMjP https://t.co/bbLT95yLeZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starbucks will start paying employees to volunteer 20 hours a week: Starbucks is paying employees to give back. The company announced on Thursday that it is testing a program that will allow some employees to spend half of their workweek at a local… https://t.co/RVG0dYhCSw https://t.co/Atajz2uWuX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Safety Management System Specialist I: Are you an empowered Lead Team Partner with the drive to transform ideas into sustainable value? Arconic is seeking individuals who have a demonstrated ability to achieve results in a manufacturing environment, as… https://t.co/l2Ygz1M22a https://t.co/GGxnKnRJKB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nashville's coolest lodging has a no-glitter policy: Urban Cowboy in Nashville, the second outing for partners Lyon Banks and Jersey Banks, turns the bed and breakfast concept on its head with a stylish look and emphasis on music. https://t.co/vvXzlNsprM https://t.co/3W3LCZBNWG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Service Desk Manager: Founded in 1866, The Sherwin-Williams Company is a global leader in the manufacture, development, distribution, and sale of paints, coatings and related products to professional, industrial, commercial, and retail customers. The… https://t.co/f2Jn4Uc8W6 https://t.co/yCjw8ePQtZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Operations Data Analyst: Job ID 2018-66215 Program Posting Cincinnati-Corporate Regular / Temp Regular Full-Time Min. Exp.(Yrs) 1-3 Category Professional Non-Clinical Location Cincinnati Zip Code 45202 Official Job Title Operations Data Analyst State… https://t.co/cLhiYoZMTD https://t.co/8Y0FLuAQfA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From 'screw you' Aetna to Sweet 16, teen celebrates her surgery -- and new life: Cara Pressman had a blunt "screw you" message for Aetna after the insurer denied her minimally invasive brain surgery. After the teen spoke up, Aetna changed its policy --… https://t.co/cXVOCJfYVk https://t.co/oX3lmEtSzW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developers: Careers at ASC – ASC SoftwareASC Software 4074 E. Patterson Rd Beavercreek, Ohio ********************* +1 ************ Support Login – – – Home – About – About Us – Reviews – ASC Innovations – Solution Partners – Industry Partners –… https://t.co/arlaaWWNmK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager I – Healthcare: Project Manager I – Healthcare Tracking Code 5315-244 Job Description At Gilbane we’re building more than buildings, we’re helping create schools, hospitals, laboratories and other facilities across the United States and… https://t.co/gKT2mbPmTK https://t.co/BbkSB6fIlW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trade war: Trump's latest round of China tariffs kicks in: The Trump Administration's latest round of tariffs on Chinese goods kicked in Thursday, drawing immediate retaliation from Beijing. https://t.co/epG5gunj3t https://t.co/0siLD8FTWA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Network Engineer Job: Req #: 75447 Location Name: Home Office, Columbus Department: Information Technology At DSW, we believe in the power of shoes. We understand shoes bring out something great from within, and since 1991 we’ve been helping… https://t.co/57roiPOEjE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The national suicide hotline needs a fix -- and Trump agrees: Donald Trump's signing of the National Suicide Hotline Improvement Act last week is an important step in making mental health resources available to the many Americans who need them, writes… https://t.co/CZm8Asy8nw https://t.co/v3j4oD2sTg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Careers Center | Software Engineer Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome page Returning… https://t.co/gFhZubApIv https://t.co/Enjx7H9rUC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Abu Bakr al-Baghdadi purportedly releases message saying ISIS losses are test from Allah: For the first time in almost a year, ISIS has released what it says is a new audio message from its leader Abu Bakr al-Baghdadi. https://t.co/wHbnQk3Ys1 https://t.co/PEgrfMawu9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BrewDog's first 'beer hotel' opening in Ohio: BrewDog, a multinational brewery, is opening a beer hotel in Columbus, Ohio, where you can indulge your beer passions and then head to bed, wake up and start over. https://t.co/mORTaOsXS5 https://t.co/JUDT0u9i01]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to build a career in diversity and inclusion: Positions like "head of inclusion" or "chief diversity officer" are only growing in demand. https://t.co/x7L5RkU6ik https://t.co/Mf2pBet5TB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How crazy rich are Asia's wealthiest families?: The success of the movie "Crazy Rich Asians" is drawing attention to the region's growing wealth. https://t.co/FqaxhPug79 https://t.co/FmlvDTX6jE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front End Developer: Job Description What you’ll be doing… If you are curious about new technology and the possibilities it creates, then this job may be perfect for you. As part of the Information Technology team, you will work on new technologies and… https://t.co/kkPFyCQNm9 https://t.co/3BW4JwHaEp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The place where 1980s computers still rule: The Totally 80s Rewind exhibit in Seattle's Living Computers: Museum + Labs takes visitors back to the 1980s, the decade of the home computer revolution. https://t.co/id1tzzKMxP https://t.co/Yi3fT1b1In]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager I Healthcare: Project Manager I – Healthcare Tracking Code 5315-244 Job Description At Gilbane we’re building more than buildings, we’re helping create schools, hospitals, laboratories and other facilities across the United States and… https://t.co/KMeziNXQYV https://t.co/muQI9G1tL9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Defamation case against Christopher Steele dismissed: A Washington D.C. judge has thrown out a defamation case against a former British spy by three Russian oligarchs over a dossier alleging Russian interference in the 2016 US presidential elections. https://t.co/jBZfM6FDx5 https://t.co/CP71Q1nlTZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cohen's attorney says he has information on Trump that would interest Mueller: Lanny Davis, the attorney representing President Donald Trump's former personal attorney Michael Cohen, said Tuesday his client has information on Trump that would interest… https://t.co/rXBj72tclc https://t.co/laWtYvzI46]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The swamp slime is oozing toward Trump: Until this moment, Trump has played a game of flipping-the-script with the American people, promising he would rid national politics of the unseemly power players voters abhor, writes Michael D'Antonio. Instead his… https://t.co/83bdX1xXJw https://t.co/tEBDZPPNrM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Data Analyst (Salesforce): Founded in 1866, The Sherwin-Williams Company is a global leader in the manufacture, development, distribution, and sale of paints, coatings and related products to professional, industrial, commercial, and retail… https://t.co/s90VlhgyOz https://t.co/BMBbIPh9pR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Lead Business Analyst: Founded in 1866, The Sherwin-Williams Company is a global leader in the manufacture, development, distribution, and sale of paints, coatings and related products to professional, industrial, commercial, and retail customers. The… https://t.co/D1xvoGmQAY https://t.co/K42g3b9jNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Golden State Killer suspect to be tried in one trial in Sacramento: Suspected Golden State Killer Joseph James DeAngelo will be tried on multiple murder counts in a single trial in Sacramento, California, prosecutors said Tuesday. https://t.co/jZYo2DInnt https://t.co/xGEScz1SLA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intel protests to Trump -- quiet and loud -- gain momentum: Retired CIA analyst Gail Helt has lived her life largely in the shadows. But after President Donald Trump revoked former CIA Director John Brennan's security clearance, Helt joined almost 200… https://t.co/jy6EuTjJNB https://t.co/Ibggoa3tII]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Hybris Architect $175k: Cincinnati, OH Full-time $150k – $225k Posted Today If you are a SAP Hybris Architect with experience, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us We are one of the fastest growing companies in the country that invest heavily… https://t.co/d65E04s9GT https://t.co/I5NfWrd5gW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The rise of diversity and inclusion jobs: Demand for these positions has increased in the last few years. https://t.co/twpUE2JOeg https://t.co/MTVh0hfxsY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Egypt Fast Facts: Read CNN's Fast Facts about Egypt and learn more about the most populous country in the Arab world. https://t.co/klK0K7ykXF https://t.co/EjFzvf0vvW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electrical/Automation Engineer: About Us Gerdau is the leading company in the production of long steel in the Americas and one of the major suppliers of specialty long steel in the world. With more than 45,000 employees, Gerdau has an installed capacity… https://t.co/mHcwJkr3mI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Zealand surfers shot at while riding local waves: Three surfers say they were shot at while surfing at a jealously guarded surf spot in New Zealand's North Island, police say. https://t.co/ONVyjth0fN https://t.co/czbhp2r313]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Data Architect: Founded in 1866, The Sherwin-Williams Company is a global leader in the manufacture, development, distribution, and sale of paints, coatings and related products to professional, industrial, commercial, and retail customers.… https://t.co/THhlpcsJuQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Colorado man pleaded for family's return. A week later he's expected in court to face murder charges: Chris Watts faces nine charges, including several counts of first-degree murder of his wife and his two young daughters. https://t.co/VWnZZDMT2N https://t.co/MmXTw5aGgG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FBI asks for help finding Chinese man kidnapped in California: US authorities are pleading for the public's help in finding Tony Liao Ruochen, who is believed to have been kidnapped in San Gabriel, California last month. https://t.co/WDVE4BnWR7 https://t.co/ZC1HJnGbfP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wall Street Journal: Acting EPA head signs Trump admin proposal that would release more CO2 into the air: The Environmental Protection Agency will allow states to set their own emission standards for coal-fueled power plants, the Wall Street Journal… https://t.co/lWibTBVotK https://t.co/7nslBxr4L6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Melania Trump confirms her first big solo trip as first lady, to Africa: Melania Trump announced Monday afternoon that she will go to Africa in October for her first major solo trip since becoming first lady. https://t.co/qwfWRH1eGO https://t.co/4ucde280rt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer: J2EE Developer – CareWorks TechCareWorks Tech CareWorks Tech Menu – Services – IT Consulting – Enterprise Service Management – Infrastructure – Events – Careers – Training – Contact Careers – Careers – Current Opportunities Find the right job… https://t.co/lyZiLDqS8b https://t.co/4U6FujZSi3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Supreme Court nominee and top Senate Democrat to meet Tuesday: Brett Kavanaugh, President Donald Trump's nominee to the Supreme Court, will sit down with the top Democrat in the Senate on Tuesday, according to Senate Minority Leader Chuck Schumer's… https://t.co/GRecCQuili https://t.co/VjuO3bCAex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Analyst/Web Developer: Applicants must be eligible to work in the specified location Day Job Position Summary: – Develops and supports custom applications using Visual Studio, .NET Framework and C# syntaxes. – Incorporates source code repositories… https://t.co/Cdr42NS9Ks https://t.co/XPMPqSSOBz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going to Minneapolis and St. Paul? Here's what to see: The Twin Cities of Minneapolis and St. Paul are a fantastic destination for a vacation. Here's what to see in top neighborhoods for the best in culture, food and fun. https://t.co/JPXlebHZu5 https://t.co/chCutbXu22]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Oracle Applications Developer: Founded in 1866, The Sherwin-Williams Company is a global leader in the manufacture, development, distribution, and sale of paints, coatings and related products to professional, industrial, commercial, and retail… https://t.co/HWT5lSBRHi https://t.co/d6rrxkqtCR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advanced Software Engineer: Advanced Software Engineer Posted Date 7 hours ago(7/25/2018 9:21 PM) ID 2018-32176 Job Location USA-OH-Dayton Category Engineering-Software Employment Type Full Time Hiring Company General Dynamics Mission Systems Basic… https://t.co/hET82PccEQ https://t.co/uBOLqJXW6o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elayne Boosler: Saying 'joke' is no excuse for offensive behavior: Elayne Boosler: Stop calling "vile" statements "jokes." "No. You are not going to cloud up our art form." https://t.co/HVjXHivhnJ https://t.co/dmFb4ftCxZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer, Software Engineering (SAP LE/MM Global Supply Chain): At Cardinal Health, we are developing the innovative products and services that make healthcare safer and more productive. Join a growing, global company genuinely committed to making a… https://t.co/YQgv3peLVu https://t.co/UXUZ0V70R4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Neighboring South American countries stiffen borders as chaos in Venezuela triggers exodus: A Brazilian mob attacked Venezuelans, while Ecuador and Peru have created harsh rules for entering migrants. https://t.co/Zw8gZoI79L https://t.co/ClYYQ0sWlX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Syrians in Idlib brace for the war's final showdown: CNN goes to Syria's final rebel stronghold, Idlib, where people say they have no escape from an apparently imminent government onslaught. https://t.co/LzWVaKg2jI https://t.co/BY4MP1So0u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Research Enterprise Enablement Java Developer: now Research Enterprise Enablement Java Developer ============================================= Company Name: Kroger General Office Position Type: Employee FLSA Status: Exempt Line of Business: Research &amp;… https://t.co/81WcNy6wv1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator: Overview We are seeking aSystems Administratorto join our team in support of a mission critical customer. This position will be based at Wright-Patterson Air Force Base. The System Administrator (SA) is responsible for effective… https://t.co/UqJzqrR5n9 https://t.co/pfsbLv3O2V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reliable Sources: Rudy said 'truth isn't truth,' but he got something right: Rudy Giuliani was tapping into something real when he told Chuck Todd that "truth isn't truth" on Sunday's "Meet the Press." https://t.co/QpzwmWIchp https://t.co/Vrl5IOxri9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Registrar Services Analyst: Job Title Registrar Services Analyst Applications Accepted From Public: Open to the public Special Instructions to Applicants Please complete the online application and attach the following: detailed cover letter,… https://t.co/nyfPGNrZzM https://t.co/50P8jSBEwH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Systems Administrator: Dupont | Sr Systems Administrator in Johnston, IA – Visit – ************** – | – Create / Edit My Profile – | – View Jobs In: – EnglishFrenchSpanishPortuguese Sr Systems Administrator Johnston, IA Search Other Jobs New Search… https://t.co/zTz2IYhh9a https://t.co/rWuYeLru55]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These functional wedding bands are perfect for those with active lifestyles: Qalo's functional silicone rings are perfect for those living active lifestyles. Here, we rounded up our favorites that are all available for purchase via Amazon. https://t.co/ArCNiIsL0N https://t.co/1R6ovI1tgY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Client Project Manager: Client Project Manager Req ID #: 37345 Location: Spencerville, OH, US For 70 years, Charles River employees have worked together to assist in the discovery, development and safe manufacture of new drug therapies. When you join our… https://t.co/RnWWfuh4u4 https://t.co/9mDeT35ZYB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager II Healthcare: Project Manager II – Healthcare Tracking Code 5143-244 Job Description At Gilbane we’re building more than buildings, we’re helping create schools, hospitals, laboratories and other facilities across the United States and… https://t.co/VHYNEwuc4r https://t.co/zU9e4b1eHh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Your faith is shaken.' Pittsburgh Catholics react to report detailing sexual abuse by clergy: St. Paul's Cathedral in Pittsburgh was about half-full at 8 a.m. mass on Sunday morning when Rev. Kris Stubna stepped up to the altar to deliver his homily. https://t.co/gglaANtfQZ https://t.co/v0jiCDjEwF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Testing Automation Engineer: Applicants must be eligible to work in the specified location Description Responsible for developing, executing and maintaining automated and manual test scripts. Should be familiar with standard software development,… https://t.co/CPybaC3KIH https://t.co/kz5N8qzxLL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Inside Politics': Alleged Russian spy's charm offensive: Here are the stories our D.C. insiders are talking about in this week's "Inside Politics" forecast, where you get a glimpse of tomorrow's headlines today. https://t.co/RfCXbG65sg https://t.co/VGmz9bf3zd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Consultant, Business Intelligence Analytics (P: What Strategic Planning and Execution contributes to Cardinal Health This role is responsible for deeply understanding the business in multiple functional areas and across Business Units, as well as… https://t.co/25SrNQh18H https://t.co/GB7BVcqKoF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Technician/Engineer (Layer 1 Transport) – Columbus: Responsibilities: As a Transport Services Provisioning Engineer, you will be responsible for mission critical layer 1 networks. This encompasses gathering requirements, designing, bidding (RFP),… https://t.co/adDEhm54a2 https://t.co/LQ5aH7zc1E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump compares Mueller probe to McCarthyism: President Donald Trump on Sunday compared the special counsel investigation to McCarthyism, saying Robert Mueller made the late Sen. Joseph McCarthy "look like a baby." https://t.co/YQXOyysooi https://t.co/g9oKheVogL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hospitality Systems Administrator: Applicants must be eligible to work in the specified location Company Name: Kroger General Office Position Type: Employee FLSA Status: Non-exempt Position Summary: Provide administrative and system support in the areas… https://t.co/qCtbDkrVcG https://t.co/aj24XxYiRs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The bull market is showing signs of old age, but it's not dead yet: The epic run for stocks will become the longest rally ever this week. But is it about to end or does it still have some life left? https://t.co/d59c4rfAmE https://t.co/3QslNsyQkt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Major earthquakes strike near Fiji and in Indonesia's Lombok island: Earthquakes struck near two popular vacation destinations Sunday, one rattling the South Pacific islands of Fiji and Tonga, and another striking Indonesia's Lombok. https://t.co/AT2AVDrn4p https://t.co/LpvmPTgDS6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embedded Developer (Device Connectivity): Our direct client located in Twinsburg is looking for an Embedded Developer (Device Connectivity). Desired skills include 2+ years of experience with C/C++, Linux OS, Embedded systems development, JavaScript,… https://t.co/gmHVMtVX64 https://t.co/EI4k96NETD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['How could this happen again?' Why this Catholic abuse scandal seems worse than 2002: If the Catholic sexual abuse scandal that came to light in 2002 slowly unspooled through news reports, Pennsylvania's grand jury report landed like an atom bomb,… https://t.co/e0u0VXWIPS https://t.co/7Kn0aFuGK7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Software Developer: Java Software Developer – Diverse Lynx – Blue Ash, OH | ********** Loading.Server error, please try again laterSorry! It looks like you are in private browsing mode, which is not supported. Please switch your browser mode. Java… https://t.co/k5iHsdhbw9 https://t.co/IAdEHc9G5V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man who crashed car outside UK Parliament charged with attempted murder: A 29-year-old man who deliberately drove a car into a crowd outside Britain's Houses of Parliament has been charged with two counts of attempted murder, the Metropolitan Police in… https://t.co/Yu5IqItwn1 https://t.co/SsQ6aOBdzp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager/Senior Project Manager, IT: Location: Dayton Job type: Permanent Sector: IT &amp; Communications Category: Senior Manager Location: DAY PSA Corporate HDQ (DAY-PSAH) Additional Locations: None Requisition ID: 20867 Overview Join us for a… https://t.co/y9HJR4yssr https://t.co/G8SmDECW89]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kofi Annan protected us from our worst instincts: I was profoundly privileged to work for Kofi during his two terms as UN secretary general, writes Jeffrey Sachs. Kofi opened up the doors of the UN to the people of the world. https://t.co/hvFLjeOazN https://t.co/AYyuK26DAk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Relax, binge watchers. Netflix is not adding commercials: Netflix is setting the record straight. https://t.co/uIwIQQSGKQ https://t.co/03UgKYBxFX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NY Times editor says Trump's 'enemy of the people' mantra endangers journalists: The executive editor of The New York Times is "deeply concerned" by President Donald Trump's treatment of the news media, he told CNN, adding that Trump's approach… https://t.co/XlkOrEWO54 https://t.co/ct4S3coDow]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>