<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA["Give all to love; Obey thy heart..." - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Today you are You, that is truer than true. There is no one alive who is Youer than You." -  Dr. Seuss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love is, above all, the gift of oneself." - Jean Anouilh [please consume wisely]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://twitpic.com/r4lav - winner of Gratitude contest! @AbintraCenter message me your address to receive "Attitudes of Gratitude" book]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love has no other desire but... to wake at dawn with a winged heart & give thanks for another day of loving." - Kahlil Gibran]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Appreciation is a wonderful thing: it makes what is excellent in others belong to us as well." - Voltaire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love is a command to rise to one's highest potential, the best and noblest vision of ourselves. Love is a reward MORE: http://big.ly/e6LR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tinybuddha: "In true dialogue, both sides are willing to change." ~Thich Nhat Hanh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["People who want the most approval get the least and people who need approval the least get the most." - Wayne Dyer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love and compassion are necessities, not luxuries. Without them, humanity cannot survive." - Dalai Lama]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["With love and patience, nothing is impossible." - Daisaku Ikeda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Small acts, when multiplied by millions of people, can transform the world." - Howard Zinn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You can give without loving, but you cannot love without giving." -Amy Carmichael]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The hunger for love is much more difficult to remove than the hunger for bread." - Mother Teresa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The way to love anything is to realize that it might be lost." - G K Chesterton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The great tragedy of life is not that men parish, but that they cease to love." - W Somerset Maugham #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RumiQuotes: Lose yourself, lose yourself in this love. When you lose yourself in this love, you will find everything. #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Loving people live in a loving world. Hostile people live in a hostile world. Same world." - Wayne Dyer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["All the ill that is in us comes from fear, and all the good from love" - Eleanor Farjeon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When you think that someone or something other than yourself needs to change, you’re mentally out of your business." - Byron Katie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The risk it takes to remain tight inside the bud is more painful than the risk it takes to blossom." - Anais Nin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When the power of love overcomes the love of power the world will finally know peace" - Jimi Hendrix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In love, everything is true, everything is false; it is the one subject on which one cannot express an absurdity." - Nicholas Chamfort]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We must learn to speak with love again." - Thich Nhat Hanh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Between whom there is hearty truth there is love..." - Henry David Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To fear love is to fear life." - Bertrand Russell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I want to kiss you forever and a day for the beauty that is in you" Marlene Dietrich to Ernest Hemingway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["every time I ever put my arms around you I felt that I was home" Ernest Hemingway to Marlene Dietrich]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Letter writing is the only device for combining solitude with good company" - Lord Byron]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I would like to go through life side by side with u, telling you more & more until we grew to be 1 being together" James Joyce to his wife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In an age like ours, which is not given to letter-writing, we forget what an important part it used to play in people's lives." -  Broyard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I am always conscious of my nearness to you, your presence never leaves me." Johann Wolfgang von Goethe to Charlotte von Stein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To send a letter is a good way to go somewhere without moving anything but your heart." - Phyllis Theroux]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[[quotes this week are in honor of the (nearly lost) art of writing love letters. what would you write in a #LoveLetter ?]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love sought is good, but given unsought is better." - William Shakespeare, in Twelfth Night]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @QuakerQuotes: Too often we underestimate the power of touch, a smile, a kind word, a listening ear… – Leo Buscaglia #FF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Marriage is not a noun; it's a verb. It isn't something u get. It's something u do. It's the way u love ur partner every day" - de Angelis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There is only one kind of love, but there are a thousand different versions." - La Rochefoucauld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Real magic in relationships means an absence of judgment of others." - Wayne Dyer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I love to be alone. I never found the companion that was so companionable as solitude." - Henry David Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["All alone! Whether you like it or not, alone is something you'll be quite a lot." - Dr. Seuss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Beauty is a heart that generates love and a mind that is open." - Thich Nhat Hanh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The course of true love never did run smooth." - William Shakespeare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Women need real moments of solitude and self-reflection to balance out how much of ourselves we give away." - Barbara de Angelis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RumiQuotes: Be still! Be quiet! Find acquaintance with silence. Go inside, delve into your heart. Take a day off from the clamor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love at 1st sight is easy to understand;it's when 2 ppl have been looking at each other for a lifetime that it becomes a miracle" Amy Bloom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love's something even the most perfect assemblage of words can't describe.Stop scaling or putting it into numbers.It doesn't work-OliverMetz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you love somebody, tell them." - Rod McKuen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love is a valentine with lace all around the edges." - Charles Schulz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you cannot love yourself, you have no chance to love another person." - Matthew Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The more anger towards the past you carry in your heart, the less capable you are of loving in the present." - Barbara de Angelis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Because of a great love, one is courageous." - Lao Tzu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love is the greatest refreshment in life." - Pablo Picasso]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[modern Romeo & Juliet play tweeted in real time http://www.suchtweetsorrow.com]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love and doubt have never been on speaking terms." - Kahlil Gibran]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love is merely a madness...." - William Shakespeare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It is not how much you do, but how much Love you put into the doing that matters." - Mother Teresa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The only true gift is a portion of yourself." - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wintry8 you're very welcome! thanks for reading. keep growing and diving deep....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Immature love says 'I love you because I need you.' Mature love says 'I need you because I love you.' - Erich Fromm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Simply put, you believe that things or people make you unhappy, but this is not accurate. You make yourself unhappy." - Wayne Dyer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RumiQuotes: 


In the lover's heart is a lute which plays the melody of longing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Hearts are not had as a gift but hearts are earned..." - William Butler Yeats]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Don't cry because it's over. Smile because it happened." -  Dr. Seuss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love is at once more animal than friendship and more divine ..." - George Santayana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love is but the discovery of ourselves in others, & the delight in the recognition." - Alexander Smith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To love deeply in one direction makes us more loving in all others." - Madame Swetchine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love is all we have, the only way that each can help the other." - Euripides]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There is but one genuine love-potion: consideration." - Menander]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To get the full value of joy you must have someone to divide it with." - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When you love, you bring freedom to the person you love. If the opposite is true, it is not true love." - Thich Nhat Hanh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love dies only when growth stops." - Pearl S. Buck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It is easy to halve the potato where there is love." Irish Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love's the ability & willingness 2 allow those that u care 4 2 B what they choose 4 themselves w/o any insistence that they satisfy U" Dyer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To write a good love letter, u ought to begin w/o knowing what u mean to say & to finish w/o knowing what u have written" - Rousseau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["For a community to be whole and healthy, it must be based on people's love and concern for each other." - Millard Fuller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love is like a blazing flame, golden and full of warmth." - Ben Oliver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Genuine sincerity opens people's hearts, while manipulation causes them to close." -Daisaku Ikeda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Man is truely great when he can act from his passions." - Benjamin Disraeli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I'd rather lose myself in passion than lose my passion." - Jacques Mayol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love always brings difficulties, that is true, but the good side of it is that it gives energy." - Vincent van Gogh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @blahangel: Lets all not forget: there is always something to be grateful for...so easy to get trapped in negative thoughts. #love]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To love for the sake of being loved is human; but to love for the sake of loving is angelic." - Alphonese De Lamartine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To love is to receive a glimpse of heaven." - Karen Sunde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Mankind must evolve ... a method which rejects revenge, aggression, & retaliation. The foundation of such a method is love" MLK Jr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RumiQuotes: Gamble everything for love, if you are a true human being. Halfheartedness does not reach into majesty. Rumi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love is a sacred reserve of energy; it is like the blood of spiritual evolution." - Teilhard de Chardin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NoteFromTheUniv "To be loved like you've never been loved, you must love like you've never loved!" ~ The Universe (www.tut.com)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In seperateness lies the world's great misery, in compassion lies the world's true strength." - Buddha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I have found men who didn't know how to kiss. I've always found time to teach them." - Mae West]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @QuakerQuotes: Let us try what love can do to mend this broken world – Rabbi Sharon Kleinbaum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Death can not stop true love, it can only delay it for a little while."from the movie "The Princess Bride"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Those who are needy of love hide from themselves what's already there." - The Universe (www.tut.com)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @QuakerQuotes: If we have no peace it is because we have forgotten that we belong to each other – Mother Teresa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If a guy doesn’t know what he wants, he generally doesn’t want what he’s got..." - Christian Carter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wintry8 but show him how independent & awesome you are, with or without him. love yourself 1st, & treat him the way you want to be treated]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wintry8 if he's not who you want him to be (affectionate, etc) it's going to be a difficult marriage for you both...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[become a fan of our Facebook page for longer Love Quotes to share: http://www.facebook.com/LoveQuotations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There is always something left to love, and if you ain't learned that, you ain't learned nothing." - Lorraine Hansberry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Don't forget to love yourself." - Soren Kierkegaard]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>