<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Civil Project Manager: Job Information: Civil Project Manager Job Email Opening Title Civil Project Manager Category Civil Engineering Description As a Civil Project Manager you will be responsible for business development and marketing activities as… https://t.co/HCEWXBF0Af https://t.co/W3ToCAjfDw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Linux-System-Administrator-w–Hadoop: Carries out moderately complex information systems and/or information technology tasks within more than one discipline, such as application support, database administration, software quality assurance/quality control,… https://t.co/378cvRwpxu https://t.co/9qY5AdPLCE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big Data Architect, Senior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Stafford, VA Job Type: Design, Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/22/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest… https://t.co/YYPxxXZCFY https://t.co/N0znhZGt3M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketing Operations Analyst II: The Loyalty &amp; Analytics Department has an opening for a Marketing Ops Analyst I. This position is located in Pleasanton, CA. Position Purpose The Loyalty &amp; Marketing Analytics Team is a business group at Albertsons, LLC… https://t.co/YV02XGQkBA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analyst, Network Security: NETWORK SECURITY ANALYST Responsibilities/Qualifications Associate degree or equivalent work experience, Bachelor’s degree a plus. Minimum 1-2 years experience with networks, network management technologies, or experience… https://t.co/3tapwyZlO5 https://t.co/K1g0D1vraV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Systems Specialist: Quality Systems Specialist (Entry Level) Jobs in Oklahoma City at Boeing Skip Navigation SearchMenu – News – Investors – Employee/Retiree – Merchandise – Suppliers – Features &amp; Multimedia – Commercial – Defense – Space –… https://t.co/MHQrX7TdRp https://t.co/zXHPgwewka]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Administrator: Connection Services has a fantastic opportunity through our technical staffing division in Washington, DC. We are looking for a System Administrator. This is a long term contract opportunity with immediate start. Hours: 10AM-6:30PM… https://t.co/K8YdVdsBb1 https://t.co/3w4C9fjzZ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[500 Tennessee zipline visitors fall ill: An investigation continues into what has caused hundreds of visitors to a Tennessee zipline destination to suddenly develop gastrointestinal illness. https://t.co/pAKrlpJX8j https://t.co/taYHI7ov8r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[User Experience Front End Developer: User Experience Front End Developer Description at City National Bank| Jobs and Careers at City National Bank Skip Navigation – Financial Information – Careers Home – Locations – Contact Us – News &amp; Insights – about –… https://t.co/huY8hqv7bZ https://t.co/RXnWMI1iCr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer II: Scientific Research Corporation is an advanced information technology engineering company that provides innovative products and services to government and private industry, as well as independent institutions. At the core of our… https://t.co/lllUvNi5s5 https://t.co/ttPThX0ABT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior DevOps Engineer: Job Description LocationSan Jose – CA, US LevelBachelor Experience5-10 Experienced Available since5/9/2018 Functional areaResearch &amp; Development, Electrical Engineering, Mechanical Engineering BackgroundInformation Technology,… https://t.co/MlCJzKwOOV https://t.co/Nxn7EmLmKp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales Operations Analyst: About ANGI Homeservices: HomeAdvisor and our sister company, Angie’s List, have combined to create the largest home services marketplace in the nation. We connect millions of homeowners across the globe with home service… https://t.co/GmUm6Q7uoC https://t.co/SoHijtBaBJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Job Description Today’s warfighters and intelligence analysts are overwhelmed with data and tasks from a variety of unmanned vehicle systems. Our software helps the warfighter become more effective and efficient in operating… https://t.co/PBdo6m7Z8Z https://t.co/7uz6ThGoYS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior UI/UX Architect: MetroStar Systems Careers ========================= Senior UI/UX Architect Web Design Arlington, Virginia Apply MetroStar Systems is looking for a Senior UX Architect that is passionate about making technology and data intuitive… https://t.co/yueDQxs5cN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Engineering Specialist – Inside Sales: Application Engineering Specialist – Inside Sales Tracking Code REQ_UT_AESPEC Job Description Job Summary Provides technical sales support to customers, and field sales engineers by offering application… https://t.co/08YFmeUUAM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He walked away from millions to play for 1-11 team https://t.co/UhAKMNCf11 https://t.co/5zyK62pS0P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Analyst: 17848BR Business Systems Analyst General Atomics San Diego California General Atomics (GA), and its affiliated companies, is one of the world’s leading resources for high-technology systems development ranging from the nuclear… https://t.co/rUWV8d8izl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid .NET Developer – WITS: Mid .NET Developer – WITS Ref No.:18-00124 Location: Columbia, Maryland Position Type:Full Time Experience Level: 5 Years Start Date: 06/28/2018 Mid .NET Developer – WITS FEi is a leading IT company specializing in Federal and… https://t.co/J577F6coMY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Web Developer: Description Infoblox Inc. seeks an IT Web Developer 4 in Santa Clara, CA, to assist with the creation and maintenance of Infoblox’s digital efforts MS in comp, sci., or related and 1 yr. exp. in IT related fields req. Send res. to M.… https://t.co/687hxLrfJa https://t.co/oXY07ttxb0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Katy Perry and Barack Obama were hit hard by Twitter's follower purge https://t.co/wLjoZ1iSGB https://t.co/pZArl7p2sJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gadget Lab Podcast: Panos Panay on Why Microsoft Made the Surface Go: Microsoft's chief product officer, Panos Panay, tells us why the company made the Surface Go. https://t.co/YPQUverM95 https://t.co/bxq3vWpndO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[40% of Americans can't cover a $400 emergency expense https://t.co/FMO4wnW9le https://t.co/ahnmJSq3Xl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology: MARKETING Interested candidates send resume to: Google LLC, PO Box 26184 San Francisco, CA 94126 Attn: A. Johnson. Please reference job # below: Account Strategist (Multiple Positions); Mountain View/Palo Alto/ San Bruno, CA; Perform market… https://t.co/PBhRtMCE3B https://t.co/OLBO9JSy4K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Performance Engineer: Job Description What you’ll be doing. Customers expect our networks to perform at a high level all the time. That’s where you come in. You will investigate, evaluate and resolve network and data performance issues to ensure… https://t.co/h1g9SwBZ9Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: Careers Center | .Net Developer (Support)/ ESRI Geomapping Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome… https://t.co/rUxFTRYGfW https://t.co/Hy2qX1bjX9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dell G7 15 Review: Mucho Muscle for Your Money: A budget gaming laptop with a few flaws, but gobs of brawn. https://t.co/i110VSkQom https://t.co/h4SXc21gMV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BPM Developer: BPM Developer Denver, Colorado – United States Job Start Date – 07/23/18, Posted Date – 06/14/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview Client Onboarding is a mission critical application which will be used daily by tens of thousands of… https://t.co/n1EHTXPBRF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Operations Specialist Admissions New Student Enrol: Job Description Position Information TitleSystems Operations Specialist DepartmentAdmissions &amp; New Student Enrol (8102) LocationMain Campus Position Summary The University of Arizona is seeking… https://t.co/tA9i33oCBL https://t.co/lhSF827G3Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[58 immigrant kids reunited as government slowly reconnects families: Fifty-eight immigrant children under the age of 5 have been reunited with their parents after being separated at the border, the Trump administration said in a Thursday evening filing. https://t.co/XnbRKuIlAd https://t.co/sIsnLxz3Ic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Network Engineer: Requisition ID 2018-40692 # of Openings 3 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Top Secret/SCI Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description Contract: I2TS 3 Position: Sr Engineer, Network – Network Engineer… https://t.co/fc4J5iJaH6 https://t.co/ZBbpaxFSuw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Tools and DevOps: Location: Missouri Job type: Permanent Sector: Operations Category: Engineers Jobs Overview: * Training and Professional Services (T &amp; PS) is seeking a software engineer with a passion in development tool chains and… https://t.co/ScOi0vGelh https://t.co/Q7LQQ86aFg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Laboratory (TSL) Manager: **Technical Support Laboratory (TSL) Manager** Locations:Newark, Delaware Job Family: Engineering New Search Apply English (US) **Job Description** **Division:** Siemens Healthineers **Business Unit:** Services… https://t.co/OzZp9pDCuv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software QA Engineer: O2 Technologies, Inc. in Irvine, CA is seeking Software QA Engineers to monitor, analyze &amp; test sftwr during dvlpmnt in order to ensure quality. No trvl; no telecomm. Job duties are proj-based &amp; performed @ unanticipated sites w/in… https://t.co/HmSIuv5EbD https://t.co/1ZXVFGvFCC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where to watch New York's annual sunset show: It's a magical moment that can leave viewers awestruck: The sun aligns perfectly through spaces between carefully constructed monolithic structures to cast an amazing beam of light. https://t.co/xkhVtvO8Si https://t.co/jMdJkSgdXm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[180- Operations Analyst Lead: OVERVIEW Provides professional expertise in national defense functional disciplines or areas with a focus on military Command, Control, and Intelligence (C3I) and combat support; interoperability of military tactical and… https://t.co/R754CNXo1H https://t.co/cjfJyCCLft]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Data Domain LLC (a Dell Technologies company) is seeking a Sr Software Engineer Specialist at our Santa Clara, CA facility to provide technical expertise by independently determining and developing approaches for solutions to a wide… https://t.co/v8ZJeAhsas https://t.co/G9lwjS2d3n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Data Analyst Digital Analytics: Job Description What you’ll be doing. – Lead cross functional teams across sales, operations, analytics, and IT, to deliver complex strategic and tactical insights. – Leverage technologies (Adobe Analytics,… https://t.co/14IJVRfiy9 https://t.co/7IVE88ysuU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Performance Engineer: Job Description What you’ll be doing. Customers expect our networks to perform at a high level all the time. That’s where you come in. You will investigate, evaluate and resolve network and data performance issues to ensure… https://t.co/lcxMd73gA6 https://t.co/q4gt8ZAc1e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['I think they like me:' Trump says he's popular in UK: US President Donald Trump has shrugged off protests planned across the UK ahead of his arrival there Thursday, claiming he is very popular in Britain because of his hardline stance on immigration. https://t.co/DZn4wZGAKi https://t.co/isvMwTzUMi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior DevOps Engineer-Data/DBA: Job ID 2018-3652 Location US-CA-San Jose Category Network Operations About the Job Senior Devops Engineer Come join us and be part of our team as a Senior DevOps Engineer – Data/DBA focused on Kubernetes. 8×8 is in… https://t.co/8lnYuqb1d7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JAVA Software Developer: JAVA Software Developer in Chantilly, VA | CACI International – Small Business | – Suppliers – About Us – | – What We Do – | – Media &amp; Events – | – Investors – | – Careers – | – Contracts – | – Contact Us Join Our Talent Network… https://t.co/nnK6aYDJqG https://t.co/xcBXEpcS5I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Devops Engineer: Devops Engineer Ref No.:18-02926 Location: Renton, Washington Position Type:Contract Position: Devops Engineer Location: Renton, WA Job Description: – CI/CD pipeline design and implementation (Gitlab CI/CD or Jenkins or bitbucket… https://t.co/nio9NnhjGK https://t.co/8gER7R19DC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Tom Petty music coming: A four-CD box set of previously unreleased material by Tom Petty and the Heartbreakers is set to be released in September, SiriusXM announced Tuesday. https://t.co/PiCpfcInj0 https://t.co/RCUVbfxNpu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solutions Design Engineer: Tampa, FL Full-time $90k – $130k Posted Today If you are a Solutions Design Engineer with experience, please read on! If you are interested in joining a growing company that definitely cares about providing a great working… https://t.co/jweBBJLi7Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Analyst (USMC JPED): Job Description BAE Systems is currently seeking multiple full-time Systems Administrators to support the U.S. Marine Corps Intelligence, Surveillance, and Reconnaissance Enterprise (MCISRE) in Quantico, VA. Candidates will… https://t.co/foFDLtOZHb https://t.co/k3E3rFDWiL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, Mid: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Washington, DC Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 7/4/2018 Job Description Job Number: R******* Software Engineer, Mid Key Role: Perform complex analysis, design,… https://t.co/bTDXfkamLd https://t.co/DxGy6JvEUt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseline 8 or Baseline 9 Navy Aegis Computer Network Technician (ACNT) Trainer, CSCS DET Mayport: Requisition ID 2018-43628 # of Openings 1 Job Function Technical Operations (TechOps) Security Clearance Level Secret Full/Part Time Full Time Job… https://t.co/X8VV7csZgW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's secret NATO strategy https://t.co/6cDowSvvzS https://t.co/1TDk4wKMAQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TITLE SENIOR CNO DEVELOPER LEVEL 2 (RS): Careers Center | Senior CNO Developer Level 2 (RS) Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply… https://t.co/8TOoKSmTVT https://t.co/Cy4VdtqxnF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer Windows Kernel: Who We Are Malwarebytes is the next-gen cybersecurity company that millions worldwide trust. Malwarebytes proactively protects people and businesses against dangerous threats such as malware, ransomware, and exploits… https://t.co/7izROB02Cm https://t.co/1VL4MOQN6S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best Wireless Headphones for Working Out (2018): Bose, Sennheiser, Beats, and More: Looking for a pair of sturdy, sweatproof, wireless buds to help you rock your inner jock? We have you covered. https://t.co/ibmWnOwBBE https://t.co/VD96qZUZOP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETL Developer: ETL Developer Ref No.: 18-00387 Location: Herndon, Virginia ETL Developer We collaborate. We create. We innovate. Intrigued? You’re a business professional with an innate curiosity that thrives in a dynamic and Agile environment. You… https://t.co/7mBoPuiHGW https://t.co/tlqdpI6n4N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front-End Web Developer: MetroStar Systems Careers ========================= Front-End Web Developer Web Development Suitland, Maryland Apply MetroStar Systems is looking for a Front-End Developer that can create engaging web applications that solve user… https://t.co/Oi6LrsvBwo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Careers and Culture – Polaris Alpha -Software Developer Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job.… https://t.co/bSxF1Fjx6n https://t.co/Nd2s2EjzFp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer (mid level): Calance Job Opening – Network Engineer (mid level)Job Openings | Calance IT StaffingJob Openings – Calance Calance Creating Customer Alliances – Job Openings – By Job Title – By Date Created – By State – For Employeers –… https://t.co/qoFI7XY3bK https://t.co/XQETPYAVZC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer, Mid: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Herndon, VA Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/22/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management and… https://t.co/rN9QSAItTA https://t.co/5BgKyTVk23]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Engineer Senior Staff: Req ID : 432683BR Job Code/Title : E1465:Systems Engineer Sr Stf Job Description : This position will support the SBIRS program System Engineering team in all phases of development to include Deficiency Reporting,… https://t.co/BEeXlhA7VV https://t.co/jaORcI6pm7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Senior System Administrator: Requisition ID 2018-39770 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Secret Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description SUMMARY: Applicant will provide one-on-one Tier 3 level technical… https://t.co/yjMDjLk1ES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. System/Software Developer (Big Data/Java/Web): Requisition ID 2018-37764 # of Openings 7 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Top Secret Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description ***Only applicants with a Top Secret (TS)… https://t.co/61gRk79Nzl https://t.co/F4Z3ealpxl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst: Data Analyst (SEO) Job Description As a Data Analyst on our SEO (search engine optimization) team, you will leverage your deep experience in data analysis and data mining to drive significant organic search traffic and user engagement… https://t.co/ylrfSqertP https://t.co/BpUJhlK8ZV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Software Engineer Specialist: Data Domain LLC (a Dell Technologies company) is seeking a Sr Software Engineer Specialist at our Santa Clara, CA facility to provide technical expertise by independently determining and developing approaches for… https://t.co/CFwc0S2CXX https://t.co/fq2zzfLjP4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reese Witherspoon is one step closer to Oprah-dom with new DirecTV deal: Hello Sunshine is saying hello to a new deal that will give the Reese Witherspoon-led media company a new platform for its female-driven content. https://t.co/t48dwkMmAi https://t.co/ALr1Ju0ZUY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Cerner Skip to main content Skip to main navigation Skip to footer – Your Career Path – Client Services – Clinical – Corporate – Engineering &amp; Technology – Sales, Marketing &amp; Strategy – Students &amp; Graduates – How We Hire – Our… https://t.co/BwBvGuJRnC https://t.co/dYi08xata7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(Entry-Level / New Graduate) Software Engineer – .NET / C# / Java: (Entry-Level / New Graduate) Software Engineer – .NET / C# / Java at PETSMART Skip Navigation – Saved Jobs – ************ – – – – – – – #lifeatpetsmart – About – Home Office – Retail… https://t.co/pFUF3gAonB https://t.co/jTSR5JC1al]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Web Developer: Lead Web Developer Job Description Are you passionate about software? Are you constantly pushing yourself to learn new technologies to develop better, faster and more efficient applications? Then CoStar is the place for you. Everyone… https://t.co/HJmYVTh0oP https://t.co/VnkoR4arFc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Developer III: Requisition ID 2018-41116 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Top Secret Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description ***ONLY applicants who possess an Active Top Secret Clearance need apply***… https://t.co/Hko9zF2deA https://t.co/9OOejSxKS8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst II – Order to Cash / Finance: School Specialty is the industry’s largest provider of educational products, services and programs including Classroom Supplies, Arts products, Special Needs Resources, Math, Science, Reading, Physical… https://t.co/X1AwTGqzjt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principle UX Designer: MetroStar Systems Careers ========================= Principle UX Designer Web Design Reston, Virginia Apply MetroStar Systems is looking for a Principal UX Designer to lead our award-winning UX and Design teams. In this role, you… https://t.co/4F1vCJpdl7 https://t.co/wDfYGx5Jd6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager: Posting Information Position Information Position TypePermanent Staff (SHRA) Is this an internal only recruitment?No Position TitleBusiness Officer – Advanced Working TitleSenior Project Manager Position Number******** Vacancy… https://t.co/rjMcPJPYNT https://t.co/MMufrhShbS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Employer helps businesses fight cybercrime, protect data and reduce security risks. With cloud and managed security services, integrated technologies and a team of security experts, ethical hackers and researchers, Employer… https://t.co/CaVqg7LTP1 https://t.co/LcrICdWNU4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Manager, Digital User Experience US: Job Description We envision a Luminex solution in every lab around the world seeking to obtain timely and confident answers. We aim to lead with transformative solutions that uniquely accelerate reliable answers… https://t.co/5e3XSwiYDJ https://t.co/9rqu8wQJuQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama education secretary slams Trump administration moves on affirmative action: Former Education Secretary John King Jr. expressed dismay that the Trump administration is "going backwards on civil rights issues" following the rollback of Obama-era… https://t.co/xZB0BFuzu4 https://t.co/yRWl3LjrjH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Flight Test Engineer: Lead Flight Test Engineer (Mult. Pos.) (Learjet, Inc.; Wichita, KS): Oversee &amp; cnfrm test aircrft configuration for flight tests, incl. testing instrumentation. Perform tech’cl revw &amp; procssng of spcfc aircraft test plnng docs,… https://t.co/KwXMqawSYb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why treating Novichok exposure is so difficult: What should a medical professional do when faced with a patient poisoned by a nerve agent? https://t.co/DKrzG4GNub https://t.co/AtewSxair9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[APPLICATIONS DEVELOPER III: Applications Developer III, Sprint Corporation, Overland Park, KS. Responsible for development and production support for Sprint’s Network Centralized Access Management systems for Sprint’s telecom network. Apply at… https://t.co/7kdL9jgTdi https://t.co/mmeHwncHg4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aerospace Job Fair: Moog Aircraft Group in Torrance is HIRING Come Attend one of our upcoming Career Fairs AEROSPACE ENGINEERING OPPORTUNITIES Tuesday July 10th, 2018 @ 4pm 8pm 20285 Western Ave., Torrance, CA 90501 AEROSPACE ENGINEERING OPPORTUNITIES… https://t.co/9Cmqk9sQhb https://t.co/RLyAddJtAR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republicans agree immigration affects their political future. They don't agree on how.: Republicans in Washington are nearly unanimous that addressing the issue of immigration is essential to their political future. But they remain deeply divided as to… https://t.co/z1uBUc5yld https://t.co/mYZNMQVnmi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator Senior: Requisition ID 2018-42595 Category Info Technology Position Type Regular Full-Time Department INFO SAN/Linux/ESX Post End Date 5/22/2018 Overview Under general supervision, the Systems Administrator Senior provides accurate,… https://t.co/cfBZpahn4o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Riese &amp; Müller Load Review: The Minivan of Bicycles: Groceries, toddlers, and tools all fit in the cargo box of the Riese &amp; Müller Load. https://t.co/WrI3x0KkgP https://t.co/KA3lTMY9NP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Analyst: Who We Are Malwarebytes is the next-gen cybersecurity company that millions worldwide trust. Malwarebytes proactively protects people and businesses against dangerous threats such as malware, ransomware, and exploits that escape… https://t.co/fL9fw9t9ER]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C++ Consultant: C++ Consultant Ref No.: 18-27602 Location: Cincinnati, Ohio Title: C++ Consultant Location: Cincinnati, OH Job Role Summary: A software developer with 3+ years of experience architecting heterogeneous software solutions involving C/C++.… https://t.co/4XzOATzhZZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Civil / Structural Engineer: Civil / Structural Engineer Posted Date 1 month ago(5/23/2018 4:30 PM) ID 2018-31472 Job Location USA-VA-Herndon Required Clearance Secret Category Engineering-Hardware Employment Type Full Time Hiring Company General… https://t.co/YuydUcukh3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TITLE SENIOR CNO DEVELOPER LEVEL 2: Careers Center | Senior CNO Developer Level 2 (DS) Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a… https://t.co/FdqgLuptAT https://t.co/CtS8QGkWJF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Datastage, Oracle, Unix: Job Search Results Home Home Language English Franais Espaol Sign inRegister Email: Password: Forgot your password? Sign in Please enter your registered email address, and we’ll email you a link to reset your password right… https://t.co/7x7fXyFAx3 https://t.co/Ai26zjhDzS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Commercial Construction: Job Description ******** JOB SUMMARY The purpose of this position is to lead individual, multi-disciplined real estate project solutions for clients, with direct accountability for project delivery.… https://t.co/MtwaLbX4z9 https://t.co/A1ff4ywWrd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NYT: US threatened nations to stop breastfeeding resolution: The United States threatened nations in an effort to blunt a World Health Assembly resolution supporting breastfeeding this spring, The New York Times reported Sunday. https://t.co/GN4sa8Wjyp https://t.co/XpGAbulWvp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Diplomatic disconnect spells trouble for US-North Korea: Less than a month after President Donald Trump talked about opening "a new chapter" between the US and North Korea, the relationship between the two nations has taken a tense and hostile, but… https://t.co/Uhh04aqe4R https://t.co/Eixjb0njyc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manufacturing Project Manager: We’re using cookies to give you the best experience possible of **********. Read more about the cookies we use and how to change your settings: Essity B 218.8 (-2.3 SEK) on 09-Jun-2018 16:19 Select region Global site – USA… https://t.co/kGsdrkERrm https://t.co/No3S38DcnM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Team Lead/Principal Developer – Insurance Accounting: For BNY Mellon Team Lead/Principal Developer – Insurance Accounting job – Information Technology – Jersey City, New Jersey Skip to Main Content – – – – Toggle navigation – Who We Are – What We Do –… https://t.co/F5Wu800LKR https://t.co/GiWNc7CT7T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the Age of Despair, Find Comfort on the ‘Slow Web’: Traumatized by the news? Enter the peaceful world of train rides, city walks, and hikes on YouTube. https://t.co/c7xQnIAW43 https://t.co/nCvHzNWZSY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. QA Engineer: Sr. QA Engineer Pasadena, California – United States Job Start Date – 06/25/18, Posted Date – 06/12/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview Complete Description: Senior Quality Assurance Engineer needed for the functional and automation… https://t.co/4rUwTTmAPH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer, Video Technology: Job Description Job Description This position will be a member of the team responsible for the design, development and implementation of the infrastructure support system for all of Video Technology. This position… https://t.co/i3SFoHaFrb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump admin expected to halt some payments under Obamacare program: The Trump administration is expected to stop some payments under the Affordable Care Act's risk adjustment program, potentially shaking up insurance markets, The Wall Street Journal… https://t.co/vz1Yn38IGB https://t.co/dxU42hmiXv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer, Senior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Alexandria, VA Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/21/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management and… https://t.co/LTNREIATcN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Analyst: Business Systems Analyst: 18-02413 Ref No.: 18-02413 Location: Tempe, Arizona Akraya is looking for a Business Systems Analyst for one of our clients. If the job description below is a fit, please apply directly or call Sandeep… https://t.co/HfKAQdDihU https://t.co/4m4lurpzF8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineering Project Manager: Job Description BAE Systems is seeking a talented, experienced Software Engineering Manager to join our C4ISR Systems rapidly growing work force. If you are someone who wants to make a difference and be part of a… https://t.co/WoyJta4ABO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Administrator: – System Administrator Job Locations US-San Francisco | US-DC-Washington, DC | US-TX-Dallas Req No. 2018-4385 Category Sales Company Overview With a powerful combination of Digital Experience, Cloud Networking, and Cloud Edge… https://t.co/JruEm9IX2g https://t.co/H3QRrvh6d0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer/Analyst – Medical Products Manufacturing: Programmer/Analyst – Medical Products Manufacturing Job in Marion, NC | Baxter Skip to main content – English – Investors – Careers – News &amp; Media – Partners &amp; Suppliers – English – Our Products &amp;… https://t.co/7gEmxu5qru https://t.co/9QHGrxSixu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US destroyers sail through sensitive waters between China and Taiwan: In a move that could heighten tensions between Washington and Beijing, two US Navy destroyers have sailed through the Taiwan Strait, a US Navy official has confirmed to CNN. https://t.co/CE2DRyfnWc https://t.co/vTEBuiJyCf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UX/Visual Designer – Web: 6/7/2018 UX/Visual Designer – Web Tracking Code 10918 Job Description WHAT YOU LL DO: You ll spend quality time with your nose buried in a MacBook Pro but you ll also collaborate with our creative leadership, designers, and… https://t.co/bGXDcsO0TQ https://t.co/sQdSlFqCRM]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>