<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @aravosis: For me, Kelly’s attack on Frederica Wilson was the lowest blow. It showed us something of his character, and it wasn’t pretty…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John #Kelly Says #Trump Isn't Up To The Job Of Being President https://t.co/JkhLNA1Fyn via @politicususa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @StrategicThghts: Had to laugh when year end quiz panel on #CBC The House couldn’t name the #bcliberal leader. They finally guessed his…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over to @senatemajldr who will soon own the #Shutdown if he can’t work with #dems on veto proof bill. @realDonaldTrump is on tape in Oval Office taking full credit for shutdown. Now #Trump can’t claim it’s not him on that tape. https://t.co/OUY9zSEaAC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @maggieNYT: Lindsey Graham Suggests Syrian Troop Drawdown Will Take Longer Than 30 Days    https://t.co/VaoHc4T6MR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion | #Trump is incompetent, impulsive and amoral. Heaven help us all. https://t.co/hSlkgzQGAu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[George #Conway on report #Kelly said #Trump wasn’t up for top job: ‘You don’t say’ https://t.co/OvaG7AEjAP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LindseyGrahamSC also believes in the tooth fairy. He’s lost credibility since becoming an apologist for #Trump. #Syria #SyriaWithdrawal https://t.co/C9mE9UApqp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“ #Trump is pulling a cabinet and #WhiteHouse staff behind him that is replete with benchwarmers and third-stringers.” https://t.co/YpszBI3SEa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“But the government on Wednesday made two things clear: Prosecuting such crimes is and should be a priority, and #Trump’s tweeted claim about his innocence holds less water than we might have thought.” https://t.co/VRyJ2t46SI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“American Media Inc., the parent company of the National Enquirer, has agreed to cooperate with federal prosecutors in New York, the Department of Justice announced in a statement on Wednesday.” Might reveal other #Trump secrets. https://t.co/LnyLquq5Ty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like @realDonaldTrump wouldn’t be #POTUS if Election laws not broken. Hard to believe #Trump didn’t know. https://t.co/PW34u1PweG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheViewFromLL2: Eventual Trump tweet: "What the Fake News Media won't report is that the reason everyone around me constantly does crim…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jaketapper: Also: “AMI further admitted that its principal purpose in making the payment was to suppress the woman’s story so as to pre…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jaketapper: US Atty for SDNY reveals "AMI admitted that it made the $150,000 payment in concert with a candidate’s presidential campaig…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Year of the Woman just roared in #Trump's Oval Office @CNNPolitics https://t.co/klxVfVUwM9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion | #Trump’s departure from reality is a national security threat https://t.co/acm4CwP31j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Bear in mind that #Trump had already started telling people that #Ayers would succeed John #Kelly as chief of staff, so Ayers’s decision was doubly humiliating. “ https://t.co/qZvZLBnro5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Trump’s Judicial Nominees Take Heat but Largely Keep Marching Through Senate   via @NYTimes https://t.co/V5fqwDBxKo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine how dull the news cycle would have been today if @realDonaldTrump hadn’t done a fantastic imitation of @AlecBaldwin. Might have had to give attention to climate change, Paris agreement, Saudi Arabia and Yemen, or other real stuff. Of course substance is beyond #Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @thehill: Arctic lost 95 percent of oldest and thickest ice over last 33 years https://t.co/qS4XhBJEcS https://t.co/DgUecchhQI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From #Trump’s rants and Tweets he appears to love to watch @donlemon, Hope @realDonaldTrump enjoyed tonight’s intro :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘This has spiraled downward’: #Democrats introduce #Trump to divided government https://t.co/oTHGOIK8Hn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WoodfordCHNL: 2/2 @bcliberals House ldr @maryforbc also advises @BCLegSpeaker in writing that she is requesting the special prosecutors…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WoodfordCHNL: 1/2 @bcliberals House ldr @maryforbc has again put serious questions in a letter to @BCLegSpeaker on the #bcleg controver…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MeetThePress #cnn #msnbc @maggieNYT Please ask #Trump what happens in a #ShutDown, who gets hurt. https://t.co/S8WcIT8S3I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It would be really good if anyone could get @realDonaldTrump on tape explaining exactly what would be affected in a shutdown. Safe bet is #Trump doesn’t have a clue and would drive reality checkers into overdrive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senators dumbfounded by #Trump vow to shut down government https://t.co/IRI4EdUEer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rolandparis: Correct. Canada is fulfilling the terms of its treaty obligations and upholding the rule of law in good faith, and paying…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SethAbramson: Uh... did the President of the United States just *threaten America with civil war* if federal prosecutors refer him for…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NancyPelosi showed today that she’s a leader, @realDonaldTrump showed he belongs on reality TV and not in the #WhiteHouse as #Trump #POTUS https://t.co/OFkNNd5Ex3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @engageBC: Check out this list of work the @bcndp government has undertaken to make life better for people. We can invest in people and…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonder if @nbcsnl has to pay royalties when @realDonaldTrump auditions a skit. As I watched #Trump I thought #SNL had changed to Tuesdays. https://t.co/yfysRMOz3a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysis | Congresswoman to Google CEO: Why when I search ‘idiot’ do I get pictures of #Trump? https://t.co/QsbOnqOydE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Trump4future Never believe the spin from Trump and Fox News. No one wants “open borders” claimed by Trump. https://t.co/wAYd5Jqw10]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @voteprbc: Is this you wondering where your ballot is? If it is TODAY IS THE LAST DAY TO REQUEST ONE. Do it online, by phone or in perso…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Trump expressing unhappiness with Mnuchin: report https://t.co/24pCtnTpC0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @INTEGRITYBC: Wally Oppal defends Speaker, says he's being treated unfairly https://t.co/mfSb2p6TbF #bcpoli #vanpoli #bclp #bcndp #bcgre…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great news for @realDonaldTrump. Will it help #Trump to attack this judge. https://t.co/AbKSLWS5HV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch #Trump just offer to ship nukes :( https://t.co/ch9JSnQgWB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is @senatemajldr thumbing his nose at @realDonaldTrump? Looks like #Trump can’t deliver and #McConnell putting #POTUS in place. https://t.co/Z4KFv7OhDy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@primetimecrime @CIA Do you really think rogue opperators dismember #Kashoggi without direction from #MbS? That’s not how #Saudi works. #Trump saying he doesn’t care, we’ll see how many #GOP follow him down this abandonment of global leadership.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Trump brushes aside #CIA assertion that crown prince #MbS ordered killing, defends him and #Saudi Arabia https://t.co/Bejvj4cDrJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EvanLeeson: @StrategicThghts @nspector4 The house voted to suspend them. They were not suspended by Plecas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nspector4 Suggestion he be Sargent went no where, unfortunate #Plecas made suggestion which is most damaging to him, not Mullen. Everyone isn’t at peak under pressure, really need prosecutors’ reports. They better indicate shocking alleged offences or Plecas et al will wear it. #bcpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NicholasSimons: Meet Mr. Squeaker. #bcpoli https://t.co/gljp8Zvw8z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nspector4 We can’t say for sure until we know nature of potential charges and what advice was given to #Plecas re his authority to suspend Officers. Assume he’s not an idiot and has good reason for actions. Time and law suits will tell. #bcpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nspector4 Anyone whose been around #bcleg for last 35 years knows and likes Craig James. That makes commentary hard as most sympathetic to friend they trust, assuming #Plecas not totally incompetent he knew that. Looking forward to prosecutors’ reports. #bcpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nspector4 @jjhorgan Who could name the Clerk or Sergent, #bcliberals see opportunity to go after “traiter” #Plecas. Unless they’ve all lost their senses and want to award Officers with millions in damages, there has to be something very serious behind this. We’ll see. #bcpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marissenmark @keithbaldrey Looks to me like #Plecas floated a bad idea which went no where as #bcleg management committee unanimously said no and appointed next down chain as would be expected. #bcliberals making far too much of something that went no where except for their hatred of #Plecas #bcpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marissenmark @keithbaldrey We do have to keep in mind that the primary interest of the #bcliberals and their syncophants is to get rid of #Plecas who they see and treat as a traitor. Given extraordinary treatment of Clerk &amp; Stg, assume #bcleg is nuts or there’s a very serious investigation. #bcpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not that @realDonaldTrump cares about facts but #Trump should know from 1999 to 2008, only 0.151% of Ninth Circuit Court decisions were reviewed by the Supreme Court, two other Districts had more cases overturned, numbers too small to mean much except for deflecting #POTUS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing that #Trump became #POTUS without respecting the rule of law. Could someone tell @realDonaldTrump that despite his love of autocrats, the Constitution protects folks from him. https://t.co/FqBOUtBGvG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tlehskwii: Go in person and vote today. Tomorrow is your last day to vote in person. It's super easy and the best way to ensure you bal…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BowinnMa: Many thanks to the @WCGCE (Chartered Engineers Pacific) for hosting me for a 2-hour lecture on the Integrated North Shore Tra…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#bcpoli #pr4bc Some wil let their neighbours decide and then complain. Not too late to have your say. https://t.co/YdwcH71nUh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @thehill: Author Stephen King tells Iowans to vote out Steve King: "I’m tired of being confused with this racist dumbbell" https://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Tweet is from #Trump #POTUS who will have to work with whatever #Congress voters give him. Does his hateful rhetoric lay a good groundwork for working across aisle next year? https://t.co/0SZgVyp5Gn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for information on slime in Red River Cereal. Ate it for years but lately cooking produces a disguesting inedible slime. https://t.co/4i5yXohRtC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today I spoke to three folks &gt;60 who could vote in #midterms. One didn’t know there was a vote Tuesday, other two weren’t interested in voting. Does #Trump or #Dems win if apathetic are the majority? Hard not to scream when I encounter people like this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Trump Administration Spares Corporate Wrongdoers Billions in Penalties https://t.co/7F7R36NYNH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘HAPPY THANKSGIVING TO ALL!’: Rhetorical bedlam erupts as President #Trump speaks to the world from Mar-a-Lago https://t.co/riHCAhklkX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next week is the last of the scheduled #bcleg sitting days until Feb 2019. https://t.co/mLb37g6ZAx Hopefully the two special counsels will complete their work by then. Must assume release of details on suspicions would jeapordize investigation. #bcpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tomfletcherbc: Mullen appears to announce ex AG Wally Oppal has been added as second special advisor to @BCLegSpeaker. That’s it #Bcleg…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jtferrier: Breaking news - people standing in a hallway #bcpoli https://t.co/sxGCemkrzX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mikelecouteur: BREAKING: @SenateCA is ready to have a RARE weekend sitting to deal with the Canada Post back to work legislation IF it…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PattyOLimerick: No. A murderous spoiled prince is. https://t.co/8av7GOcSCQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CBCtanya: Motion adopted in BC Legislature: Kate Ryan-Lloyd, current Deputy Clerk, will serve as Acting Clerk of the Legislative Assemb…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Justice Roberts’ Rebuke of #Trump Is a Warning Shot https://t.co/nEWvxDZWz1 via @thedailybeast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. will slow in 2019, may enter recession in 2020, economists forecast https://t.co/CqYvdEI9Qy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @suestroud: @MoveUPTogether @PeterKellyBC And if you can't guess this is really what is behind the #BCLibs attacks on the speaker. #bcpo…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LeyneLes: Govt house leader mike Farnworth confirms speaker wanted to name his friend /adviser as acting Sgt at Arms. Answer was “a ver…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @atrupar: REPORTER: Mr. President, what are you most thankful for?

TRUMP: "For having a great family &amp; for having made a tremendous dif…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Trump Says He’s Thankful for Himself This Thanksgiving https://t.co/PWA0yzwVjZ via @thedailybeast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Trump politicizes Thanksgiving call with troops to attack migrants, judges @CNNPolitics https://t.co/iaR4cv8t50]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NBCNews: President Trump is at his Florida estate for the Thanksgiving holiday, marking the 215th day at a Trump property since taking…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keithbaldrey No change except patience to allow investigation to conclude without further defaming the officials. #bcpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@keithbaldrey Speaker and other MLAs must not jeapordize investigation. None are so stupid as to not realize drama of escourting officials out by police. Big price to pay if reputations wrongly damaged. Need patience for what must come out. #bcpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Press gallery at #bcleg tight with officials as are long serving MLAs. Have to presume steps need to be taken to protect investigation and evidence. At their pay grade, it will be an expensive mistake if charges not laid and successfully prosecuted. #bcpoli https://t.co/qLPwFe6AyM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @InklessPW: I prefer to begin with the little things, like using my real name on Twitter. https://t.co/QjYY6omzrN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Acting Attorney General Matt #Whitaker got $1.2 million from nonprofit that won't disclose its donors https://t.co/nSYcmjNmCu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nytopinion: The only thing standing between Trump and his plan to prosecute Clinton was Donald McGahn. Think about that. https://t.co/g…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @washingtonpost: Analysis: Exaggerating economic numbers is nothing new for Trump. Doing so to give the Saudis cover is. https://t.co/J2…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Republicians have another opportunity to say they aren’t puppets of #Trump. 

Who in the #GOP will defend the courts against authoritarian attack?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysis relevant to #Trump’s attack on Chief Justice : Are 80 percent or 0.1 percent of the 9th Circuit Court’s decisions overturned? https://t.co/1BAk4zJUSX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While #Trump acts as apologist and diversion for murdeous #MbS as usual he ignored facts on US oil imports by country: https://t.co/3t9C4CJDJN https://t.co/3s0Fd7QNkD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OutFrontCNN: "This is not about America first. This comes out to Saudi first." - Former Director of National Intelligence James Clapper…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EdKrassen: Global warming also causes extreme winter conditions.  If you picked up a book you would know this. https://t.co/YauZTuMQ8g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OutFrontCNN: Trump doubles down on criticism of federal judges

@ErinBurnett: "While the President is playing politics to convince Amer…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Trump doesn’t care if he undermines rule of law and trust in the judiciary. @realDonaldTrump rudely criticizes everyone but autocrats. https://t.co/Ul2ID3Cgb4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shocking - truth irrelevant to #Trump as he spins for murderous #MdS. https://t.co/osZNm2AHee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @washingtonpost: Analysis: The warning offered by a Filipina journalist targeted by her country’s president https://t.co/J9dmajWhNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @katiederosayyj: Speaker Darryl Plecas raised concerns in January about clerk Craig James &amp; Sgt-at-arm Gary Lenz, which is why he hired…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CNNSitRoom: “This never happens. You never see Justice Roberts speak out like this," CNN's @LauraAJarrett says. “Attacks on judges aren…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch #Trump engage in ever more bizarre distractions as #Mueller closes in. An indictment against his son will make @realDonaldTrump even crazier. https://t.co/Vl5rsCtyqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MeetThePress: .@neal_katyal: "I'm not aware of anything like it in our lifetime," on Trump's tweet going after Chief Justice Roberts. #…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MeetThePress: On Trump going after Chief Justice Roberts: "The adjectives you think about when you think about the chief justice are re…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MeetThePress: WATCH: Trump’s attacks on Roberts "are the actions of authoritarian governments," @neal_katyal says on #MTPDaily

https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RadioFreeTom: This headline is accurate. Let that sink in. https://t.co/43phXaVz0M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BruceBartlett: You have to go back to FDR's first term to find such an extraordinary pissing match between the president and the Suprem…]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>