<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[When I see Charlie Brooker is presenting #Film2017 https://t.co/N35HVp3gqR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How they haven't thought of doing this until a few years ago is beyond me, a great programme.  #TheToughest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Claudio Ranieri is sitting somewhere in Italy watching this. #LeiLiv https://t.co/PxyGHBITG1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@suzietwinkie haha cheers. I had that in drafts for about 10 years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who's the nicest of all engineers? The sound engineer of course.  #roomtoimprove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ahhcuppatea we could try it but that means I have no tea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ahhcuppatea I can't I make tea during the break.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deecf I'd rather have my pringles if I'm being honest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I spend most of the episode on twitter I only ever see the start and end of #roomtoimprove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@deecf overdraft and Lisa the ice queen QS don't exist in the same world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine going food shopping with Lisa, 'no you can't have them pringles' we only have a budget of €89.45 #roomtoimprove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is how we sound to foreigners after a few pints.  #raydarcyshow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Luke I won't be your stepfather.  #FirstDatesIRL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He said the C word on tv. A stern letter to RTÉ is written as we speak. #FirstDatesIRL https://t.co/gLbEzwwaJb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haha he said he had a flower for her but it was actually a bag of flour. The absolute mad thing.  #FirstDatesIRL https://t.co/93IoskgTlY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#stormdoris absolute carnage in Naas after Storm Doris. It's gonna take some effort to clean this up. https://t.co/p6E8RJ3GW7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lemar loves a good 50/50 challenge #MCIASM #UCL https://t.co/hTiZ5aNl90]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We might be paying too much for electricity and gas. Well I never.  #cblive https://t.co/k04k0kKi4Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Regardless of religion every child has the right to an education. It's not about religion it's about basic human rights.  #cblive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love the way the Iona institute milf makes up stuff for the craic #cblive https://t.co/MLdzCIBiGF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#pintbaby several pints into his session starts getting all philosophical and shit. https://t.co/7oVzluyRI7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dermo loves windows #roomtoimprove https://t.co/fFkYZi0Yhf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['I'm don't pointing the finger at anyone' says Dermot 'don't fuck with my windows' Bannon. It has all the hallmarks of bannon #roomtoimprove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dermot 'don't fuck with my windows' Bannon, as he'll now be known as #roomtoimprove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three guarantees in life 
1. Taxes
2. Death 
3. Dermot Bannon arguing with people on  #roomtoimprove about the colour of a kitchen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brian D'Arcy should head to Coppers for the night l, that's sure to cheer him up a bit. Btw he's a top top guy a decent skin.  #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never go Dutch on a first date, you tight git.  #FirstDates https://t.co/xTgjNgjlEj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dessie's new gaff is the biggest thing to happen to Westmeath since the 2004 Leinster final.  #RoomToImprove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I bet ya Crystal Swing send nudes to each other.  #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That United starting line up has scored 12 goals all season. #MUFC #MANCHE https://t.co/TFqHUqPsWs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ben Foster in the last few minutes of the game #wbaliv https://t.co/iFxfDztjvN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tubridy and the rest of these lads are a bunch of geebags #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When's the acid house late late special? #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HillaryClinton: 3-0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big Sam watching the Cabaye goal #CRYARS https://t.co/wuXFk0qRiq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Joey7Barton: On Steve's birthday as well! 😂😂 🇪🇸🇪🇸🇪🇸]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's 80% in the U.K. And 6% in Ireland because no one in power gives a fuck like everything else that doesn't benefit them.  #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How I'm gonna be on Thursday nights until First Dates come back.  #FirstDatesIRL https://t.co/yK6eUeDq5y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone on First Dates #FirstDatesIRL https://t.co/zpnboof9bN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She's one of those girls who popped her cherry at 18, so like most girls then #FirstDatesIRL https://t.co/3DnjNpVbru]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @hectorirl: What a disgrace ...Give this team &amp; these players whatever they need &amp; what they deserve .. RT &amp; show your support for the l…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the 8th day god created Emily #pointless https://t.co/yY7jG6W23n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We all know this will be the actual view from the apartments in Cherrywood. #dontbelievethehype #IrelandsPropertyCrisis https://t.co/qVc4b5k6jM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ireland 2007 property bubble it'll never happen again. 2017......... and it's happened again #IrelandsPropertyCrisis https://t.co/B2rs2uNM0e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read about how angels really love and care for you, only €24.99 in Easons and all good book stores. #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The poor auld unemployed angels lost their jobs due to cutbacks in the sector. Fucking recession lads. #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MLSaperstein It's bringing tears to my eyes just thinking of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MLSaperstein He looked so happy then. https://t.co/RLHbYYrsk7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He went into hospital and came out and got a fresh 1991 look.  #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tubridy after saying chi-Ching to an Asian chap. #LateLateShow https://t.co/kxD1ASzour]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jaysus Kurt Cobain makes some brutal music these days.  #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shane Ross walking into work on learning of the secondary strikes today. #busstrike #buseireann #irishrail #DublinBus https://t.co/8jFq3MqHpl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here comes the coming out stories #FirstDatesIRL https://t.co/SpAJPpFV3x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you realise George Hook is on the telly more since he retired from being on the telly #CuttingEdge https://t.co/2nKmxn5UGI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AddictionsPMC they locked Keano in a closet until the Welsh team left. Health and safety regulations and all that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FirstDatesIRL the lad from Galway and his hair https://t.co/Tj3co8cqqC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emily has me like #FirstDatesIRL https://t.co/KHZdWfO7gt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every time Fidelma Healy Eames opens her mouth. #CuttingEdge https://t.co/S8MB5BKpQv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I get all my protein needs in my daily snickers and chicken fillet roll. #CBLive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ray Shah is to nutritionists what Trump is to presidents. A shitehawk.  #CBLive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like seen Arsenal lose, simply to watch Arsenal Fan TV meltdowns. They are glorious blud.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's Robyn from How I met your mother, doing working in Dublin Zoo #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love @Paulmcgrath5 his book 'Back from the Brink' is possibly the best football autobiography ever. #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking at Eamon Dunphy's eye I can only think of this scene #RTEsoccer https://t.co/0lDs1MKIGs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Expect hipster priest to turn up in Walford punching Danny Dyer's nut in, in the Queen Vic #Redwater]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bit of a shite turn out for the funeral considering the wake was held in a barn with a band and loads of people there  #Redwater]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lets ride a horse in a churchyard for absolutely no reason at all  #Redwater]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A pissed up Eamon Dunphy is a great Eamon Dunphy #RayDarcy #raydarcyshow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People may mock Eamon Dunphy but at least he speaks the truth and doesn't sing from the hymn sheet like some commentators #raydarcyshow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I might pop in next door to see how they're getting on, that's what this like sitting in someone else's gaff #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mary Black has turned into the pissed up auntie at a wedding. Fair play to her #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nathan Carter on the Late Late Show. I'm Shocked #LateLateShow https://t.co/gvsPAjgOXM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enda Kenny is funnier than Oliver Callan doing an impression of Enda Kenny.  #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you realise Lucie will be back on Monday #pointless https://t.co/JAt4Qsv1Cm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear Pointless 
No one likes chemical elements
PS Rebecca is weird and Lucie has some fine baby bearing hips.  #pointless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lucie works in a lingerie shop #pointless https://t.co/IMT1YjPRQI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Dad is gayer than your Dad #Firstdates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How I feel watching urban trend setter boy and bricklayer Molly #Firstdates https://t.co/wFTwjOpLB5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I genuinely thought Patrick was there to meet a lad. #FirstDates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A united Ireland would mean having Ireland's Call as the national anthem. Nah you're  grand. #cblive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jahspark Take me to church?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The priest is going off to listen to some Mumford &amp; Sons while drinking some craft beer to get his head around the news #Redwater]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A hipster priest probably too hipster to say an auld mass.  #Redwater]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is why we didn't give you any points in the Eurovision we knew what was coming #Redwater]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's gonna be a fight in the pub, it wouldn't be Irish stereotyping without it.  #Redwater]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How'd you know we're from London? I think the strong cockney accent would be a giveaway off where you're from.  #Redwater]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@innocent You're cool, I do have this to drink and by then I'll have forgot about it https://t.co/yJXJiEUgsD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@innocent I'm never drinking your delicious smoothies and juice ever again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Portugal right now #Eurovision https://t.co/UYno4D63lR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the UK expect points off Ireland and get nothing off us #Eurovision https://t.co/bCW3CBIer0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His converse are cheaper than his plank of wood he was selling in Dunnes #truefacts #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never Forget  #LateLateShow https://t.co/4Y3Gd9EJGN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He said that was a comedy act but but but it wasn't funny #LateLateShow https://t.co/XpN1TYMSuu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is like a prequel to the Hunger Games just a matter of time before these young people start bating heads #TopTable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd love to know what league Dunphy thinks is the strongest he doesn't rate EPL,La Liga, Serie A,Bundesliga or Ligue 1 #rtesoccer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#rtesoccer Is it Blackie Connors or Diego Simeone boss. #ucl #AtletiRealMadrid https://t.co/4GnvT0qLH1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @carterjwm: HELP ME PLEASE. A MAN NEEDS HIS NUGGS https://t.co/4SrfHmEMo3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can see the exact moment where the Welsh lad's heart broke. She was brutal #FirstDates https://t.co/5Wsztz9Teo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This old geezer is tearing me up stop being so sweet and sad.  #FirstDates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the bouncer won't let you into the nightclub https://t.co/awPzY0X5pi]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>