<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: 'I was told not to touch him or bond with him because that was for his other moth - https://t.co/XLBYV0Ufi7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Column: 'We are required to provide a sick cert to cover the period of absence to - https://t.co/yspE15hBYD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tammybangs Or uphill and looking forward to the views. Can't wait to try one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Stand-off between gardaí and locals at protest against clinic which 'treats sex  - https://t.co/hZGRbftCka]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Lyme disease: 'I became a shadow, housebound, a virtual recluse' - https://t.co/tLvlFGMjw4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Here's how to ensure your home renovation stays bang on budget, according to a bu - https://t.co/rd4SY1hRq9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Showers throughout the week, but heatwave-level weather to return for the weekend - https://t.co/fwHRqe1ikF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Irish Water hopes new restrictions in Dublin will help avoid 'widespread outages  - https://t.co/TjKCrOCLA5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Gerard Craughwell on his combative Twitter personality and what he thinks of Mich - https://t.co/SKyjRJiGdH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Poll: Should the minimum wage be increased by 25% to €11.90 an hour? - https://t.co/flNtFzaij8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: 450 migrants stranded at sea as Italy and Malta argue over who should take them - https://t.co/BoagZo1sFr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: A beauty therapist sacked for friending clients on Facebook has been awarded €1 - https://t.co/Gx1ynYr0N5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: The first space tourist flights could happen over the next year - https://t.co/NEmI3YjKQB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: 'Setting guidelines around relationships at work is a wise and obvious next step  - https://t.co/4eIat54MWg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Poll: Should Revenue collect the TV licence fee? - https://t.co/OSTNJR0ybh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Kindness: Change your life and make the world a kinder place - https://t.co/LbGcboS4bO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: British minister resigns over lewd messages to women  - https://t.co/xNkHC2mpQ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Leo wanted the HSE to save money by re-using crutches, but was told it was a non- - https://t.co/r2uQxwwxDY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Fine Gael senator calls for 'drunk tanks' at city Garda stations - https://t.co/N5a4t3jnG5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Fine Gael senator calls for 'drunk tanks' at city Garda stations - https://t.co/N5a4t3AZ4F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Roseanne nominated for two Emmys despite being cancelled over star's racist tweet - https://t.co/he2IDc4UOt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Magic mushroom lab discovered in Dublin - https://t.co/K2lE0JIigM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Affordable housing: 'Taxing high end real estate transfers could fix the problem' - https://t.co/srO9X1KNK6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Taoiseach says he'll consider law banning convicted sex offenders from using dati - https://t.co/C81UhcE2VE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Young woman found not guilty of dangerous driving causing the death of four frien - https://t.co/RwHv0xQ7q4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Trailer Watch: Which movie should you go see this weekend? - https://t.co/i9mIPcIdkJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Ireland to be the world’s first country to divest public money from fossil fuel - https://t.co/5WyBwHEmka]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Vodafone apologies after network goes down in many parts of country - https://t.co/hGXkZcUU6K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Poll: Should vending machines selling unhealthy foods and drinks be banned in sch - https://t.co/tiCTAamgce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Gardaí took angle-grinders to some bike locks in Dublin today (but they'll pay t - https://t.co/ZxoVrei6oj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Delivery driver arrested at Mountjoy Prison after phones, sims, tablets and stero - https://t.co/rFt8ZAreS9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Covert surveillance sees fish enforcers crack down on illegal salmon netting in D - https://t.co/PbVro5XBxS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: TDs are off on their summer holidays today - https://t.co/RavPPGKEwt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: 'A setup': Stormy Daniels arrested in strip club for allowing someone to touch he - https://t.co/rdAjytLxPy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: The North's fire service dealt with a call every 48 seconds last night - https://t.co/PmHXSCbZc4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Mexico earthquake unearths a temple dedicated to an ancient rain god - https://t.co/BWqhu2NEAB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Poll: Should vending machines selling unhealthy foods and drinks be banned in sch - https://t.co/tiCTAa4FkG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Thai cave rescue 'nearly ended in disaster' after water pumps failed - https://t.co/4omEOevGFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Mary Lou McDonald: 'Leo asked where I was in the Dáil yesterday. I'm in Palesti - https://t.co/TG2Mb0NT21]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Poll: Do you think Ireland is ready for a no-deal Brexit? - https://t.co/TC89TRFCEE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: New rules could ensure gift vouchers are valid for five years under Irish law - https://t.co/dN5YZr8MiZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Irish Cancer Society calls on HSE to stop referring patients' debt to collection - https://t.co/0qeWm9jPzq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: 'A deliberate act': Gatwick Airport flights remain suspended after drones flown  - https://t.co/bUFlEywQBR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alpine_ink @jayasax 😂 Apparently in Denmark they drink wine, so who knows?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MeSpoonie @ghoulcabin 🙄This exact mood, but for Danish 😅]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ghoulcabin So true, I barely made it tonight, topping up my DL streak at 23:30 in a panic because I couldn't get online earlier. Then I see this 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Former 'singing' priest jailed for 3½ years for indecent assault - https://t.co/bZYECldMUU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie:  Dublin City Council is going to spend €1.6 million to remove chewing gum - https://t.co/VBpXvTSBHf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: 'It's like a scene out of The Wire': Building on Dublin housing site stopped afte - https://t.co/y7GrdC2CiG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Toy Show, turkey and Santa Claus: This year's Christmas stamps have been unveiled - https://t.co/QNQYZbwhWk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: 'Incomparable' pink diamond aiming to sell for €44m could smash record at Genev - https://t.co/MMi319qoK6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: 'Europe must take our fate into our own hands': Angela Merkel calls for future cr - https://t.co/SbBTwsfO8F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Alcohol ads with pro-drinking comments on Facebook 'boost desire to drink' - https://t.co/Tx3uaFCjko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: 'There's a risk we'll remember this whole episode as a case of two bad, and one g - https://t.co/FjBRbdlJjl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Poll: Would you fix a dash cam to your car for an insurance discount? - https://t.co/ppl9MwWYG7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: 'A toxic wasteland': Hundreds of people still missing after California wildfires - https://t.co/yrQKESqATp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Dublin city councillors to vote on extending pedestrian 'green man' time - https://t.co/VHAdTor4ax]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Peter Casey's former PR firm says it has nothing to do with Traveller video he tw - https://t.co/MKSDW9jbJ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: New river rules seek to protect native Irish crayfish from plague-carrying alien  - https://t.co/VYBXcci1Gt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Plans rolled out for continuous bus lanes in Dublin - but property owners to lose - https://t.co/npDGR20DeE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: FactCheck: Who got it right between Higgins and Ní Riada in the debate over spea - https://t.co/sETL4WYYlL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: New self-lubricating condoms can reduce infection risk and withstand '1,000 thrus - https://t.co/pR8hkFOAav]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Latest poll has Michael D Higgins with nearly twice as many votes as rest of cand - https://t.co/4t5FFqx7iJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Gavin Duffy: 'Can I apologise there are three candidates from the Dragons' Den?' - https://t.co/z9RKNp7X6U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: 58 fairy penguins killed in suspected dog attack in Australia - https://t.co/vH86Dw7eEO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Poll: Would legalising cannabis work in Ireland? - https://t.co/0LUMbk6JRJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: 'Appalling' and 'reckless': Presidential candidates round on Casey over Traveller - https://t.co/LUlebdp1Wi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: 'Appalling' and 'reckless': Presidential candidates round on Casey over traveller - https://t.co/LUlebd7qxI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Potential conflict between cyclists and pedestrians cited as College Green plaza  - https://t.co/HMay5vsjPk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Potential conflict between cyclists and pedestrians cited as College Green plaza  - https://t.co/HMay5vaIqK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Parents Panel: What's the right age for a smartphone? - https://t.co/HkgxczHVuy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Worried about your pet being frightened this Halloween? Experts advise on how to  - https://t.co/Ks8e6OjvFl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Decongestants 'should not be given' to young children with colds - https://t.co/lmnkrHhOJh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: 9 tried-and-tested tips for getting the kids to stop whining* - https://t.co/WkJ3C812IK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: 'Shocked and disappointed': DCU society suspended from hosting social events over - https://t.co/WFQTtIXkib]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: FactCheck: How does President Michael D Higgins pay for his dog grooming bills? - https://t.co/rZSNMwtMdS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Hostage-taker detained after commandos storm German rail station  - https://t.co/Po3RbvtdAu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Rough sleeping banned in Hungary as new homelessness law comes into force - https://t.co/f2oKs8lIOm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Names of 796 Tuam Babies written on white sheets and brought to Galway church - https://t.co/BOdpH6T0KD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Visitors the surprise winners as they queue up to cash in on currency-ravaged Tur - https://t.co/srMkODCHd3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: 'The market was misled': Suspended sentence for Drumm for role in illegal loan sc - https://t.co/HnZaEftVy7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Adrienne Corless: 'It looks like the consultation facilitators dug deep to find r - https://t.co/yuZPEZ0oVA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Air hostess awarded €30k damages against Ryanair after falling down plane stair - https://t.co/3it0qZtEwZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Gardaí took angle-grinders to some bike locks in Dublin today (but they'll pay t - https://t.co/ZxoVrezHMT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Paramedic assaulted on Dublin bus by man he was treating - https://t.co/snVO5kniwx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: All 12 boys and their coach rescued from flooded Thai cave - https://t.co/m6qjUipKtw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Shift to HPV testing 'could eliminate cervical cancer in Irish women in a generat - https://t.co/pB284dQkRC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Should Michael D Higgins seek a second term as President? We hit the streets to a - https://t.co/gWUId1EPvH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: 'End of an era': Irish Times completes takeover of the Irish Examiner - https://t.co/jfoahqfqDX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Advice column: How to lower your car insurance premium - https://t.co/BujGwbS1Mn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Ireland set to ban plastic microbeads as Cabinet approves drafting of new law  - https://t.co/oAMe1MFYAg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Investigation after garda submachine gun found in Dublin city centre by member of - https://t.co/JG0AiL6yPt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just commented on @thejournal_ie: Confirmed: Michael D Higgins says he WILL seek a second term as president  - https://t.co/Hd5MA7QWX1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Together4yes: Dr Marian Dyer, one of the GPs signed up to our petition, speaks about her experiences dealing with patients who, for the…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @gaffneyciaran: Boarding a 13 hour flight from Buenos Aires to London. London to Dublin tomorrow. No one at airport knows what my repeal…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@plantingtheoar @AilidhNoor @IrishCoastGuard It says they got another man to help pull them all back out, while they were ringing 911 from the beach.  One of the two was swept out again and then they were all thrown forward onto the beach and struggled out with the fourth man helping. Happened in Brittany.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zoederrick @IrishCoastGuard The second time I watched it, I thought they went onto the beach because they saw him walking around and thought they'd join him. They followed him. Frightening power in that water.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jim_knipe @IrishCoastGuard Disabled person on the beach, happened to be filming, it's on YouTube. They shouted a warning to the three before the wave came in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@orchidsbudget @JanetOS_ I don't even know what the legal situation is regarding surrogates. Read about it in England. Not here. Curious, that. However, surrogacy abroad seems to be a voluntary act.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @gardainfo: This lovely fella looking for his owner.
Can the owner or anyone with info pls contact Tallaght Garda station on 01-6666000…]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>