<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Easy-going Alexander Fleming" after reading @channingtatum's latest tweets with self-promoting Trump-orange, observant Eeyore-grey and easy-going Lebowski-weed-green https://t.co/BiDUzIFsQ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CIA is watching. It can neither confirm nor deny that @channingtatum's inspiring and strong tweets remind it of Captain America https://t.co/8BL6RBuk5W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Down-to-earth Physicist" after reading @stephanieadams's latest tweets with analytical Vulcan-blood, educated Cicero-toga-white and down-to-earth Shrek-green https://t.co/7INojmL5aJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the worst of Dr. Greg House with the best of Sherlock Holmes and you get @stephanieadams: arrogant and cunning yet probing and clever https://t.co/RkFH17W0QZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Good-natured Dr. John Watson" after reading @danieldennett's latest tweets with devoted knight-silver, loyal Tarzan-loincloth-brown and good-natured Santa-red https://t.co/K8QSyXK9Wx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this significant book about Twitterbots also bought:
-   Leo Tolstoy's 'War and Peace'
-   C.S. Uris's 'The Big States'
 How very significant!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Following @danieldennett's creative and imaginative tweets is like being invited to join The Justice Society by Green Lantern himself https://t.co/TJFCKcBmYK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NETFLIX watches YOU!
Based on @virendersehwag's charming and witty tweets it pushes films about The English Class System and/or Edmund Blackadder https://t.co/5ldCcPIZ4o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this rigid book about computational creativity also bought:
-   Moses's 'The Bible'
-   Sophie Galsworthy's 'The Steel Beam'
 How very rigid!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Holier-than-thou Jeremy Paxman" after reading @ChelseaClinton's latest tweets with condescending patrician-toga-white, quick-witted Blackadder-black and arrogant buffoon-buff-orange https://t.co/TqL4qz0DW0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hulk is watching!
Hulk HATE fearless humans who remind him of explorers. So Hulk SMASH @ChelseaClinton's curious, courageous and probing tweets! https://t.co/cYXZfP81PB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Good-natured Dean Winchester" after reading @richardbranson's latest tweets with understanding priest-black, easy-going Lebowski-weed-green and ruthless Saruman-white https://t.co/9miHLC0azF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @richardbranson's hyper-logical and devious tweets were edible they'd be Neapolitan ice cream made with corrugated cardboard instead of wafers https://t.co/L7n7jS5JWU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Media-savvy Eliza Doolittle" after reading @WatsonJW's latest tweets with good-natured Santa-red, streetwise NYPD-blue and media-savvy Britney-blonde-yellow https://t.co/DR9e0xXtI7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This pretentious new book about Twitterbots makes Jean-Paul Sartre's 'Nausea' seem as pretentious as a donut salesman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a public swimming pool in which
Spongebob Squarepants can enjoy @WatsonJW's bubbly and upbeat tweets
while chasing jellyfish https://t.co/wBdc0WnZ3U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Social-climbing Kurt Vonnegut" after reading @MesutOzil1088's latest tweets with sardonic Dante-inferno-red, artistic star-white and social-climbing Blackadder-black https://t.co/DIwNUFprBI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Take5 things that remind me of @MesutOzil1088:
1. Zac Efron
2. Princes
3. Pirates
4. Rush Limbaugh
5. Barbie https://t.co/Sd1r1S16f7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Hot-tempered Fred Flintstone" after reading @MirzaSania's latest tweets with jolly Santa-red, easy-going Lebowski-weed-green and quick-tempered Trump-orange https://t.co/eIpxREyuQF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is the UN general assembly in which
Father Ted can enjoy @MirzaSania's sly and decent tweets
while preaching tolerance https://t.co/u4PBSokPIB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Holier-than-thou Rocket Raccoon" after reading @MMFlint's latest tweets with cunning Gollum-grey, sarcastic Deadpool-red and holier-than-thou priest-black https://t.co/ktZlzYt0tV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian hackers are watching!
@MMFlint's strong and stoic tweets suggest infection with the MAX1MU5.DEC1MU5.MER1D1UZ virus https://t.co/qY15PKojYj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This political new book by Veale &amp; Cook makes Barack Obama's 'The Audacity of Hope' seem as political as a pig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning: the tenacious MAX1MU5.DEC1MU5.MER1D1UZ virus disables the 'dismiss' and 'minimize' checkboxes on all windows so that they can never by closed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Eager-to-impress Dominique Strauss-Kahn" after reading @iansomerhalder's latest tweets with charming Adonis-tan-orange, charismatic Obama-brown and intelligent Google-yellow https://t.co/WEdfRXrbSl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @iansomerhalder's cold and meretricious tweets were edible they'd be Biscuit Tortoni made with diesel instead of rum https://t.co/8An52tiFlu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this tough book about Twitter 'bots' also bought:
-   Raymond Chandler's 'The Big Sleep'
-   Irving Woolf's 'The Cyclops'
 How very tough!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Holier-than-thou Jim Carrey" after reading @POTUS's latest tweets with entertaining Bollywood-tandoori-red, attention-seeking Ikarus-sun-orange and quick-witted Blackadder-black https://t.co/6ZyMLsQXE5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Attention-seeking Elitist" after reading @BotOnBotAction's latest tweets with arrogant Anchorman-burgundy-red, sophisticated toga-white and attention-seeking Ikarus-sun-orange https://t.co/x4tROkX9Tc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the best of Dr. Greg House with the best of Sherlock Holmes and you get @BotOnBotAction: probing and astute and clever and detail-oriented https://t.co/3S0ngwtjT8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does Automated Analysis of your tweets reveal about you? How might the analysis be framed? Tweet  #BlendMySoul to find out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Attention-seeking Aung San Suu Kyi" after reading @DwyaneWade's latest tweets with resolute lion-orange, remote star-white and caring prince-purple https://t.co/REnRyZLYl6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a war zone in which
Quentin Tarantino can enjoy @DwyaneWade's influential and energetic tweets
while making violent movies https://t.co/C3qzveJc7p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Mysticism-peddling Barney Stinson" after reading @iloveruffag's latest tweets with vivacious Marilyn-blonde, attention-seeking Ikarus-sun-orange and flirtatious vixen-red https://t.co/UxCf73ZkY1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian hackers are watching!
@iloveruffag's humorous and gleeful tweets suggest infection with the THE.J0KER virus https://t.co/ekYzhnM2Qm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This thought-provoking new book about computational creativity makes George Lakoff's 'Women Fire and Dangerous Things' seem as thought-provoking as a three day drinking binge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning: the witty THE.J0KER virus hacks your Twitter account and frequently tweets random quotes from Jolly Roger's Big Book of Jokes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Sharp-witted Tony Robbins" after reading @SecularInst's latest tweets with insightful Gandalf-grey, optimistic Gumby-green and sharp-witted Blackadder-black https://t.co/REARNfo8w7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the best of Walter White with the best of Dr. Greg House and you get @SecularInst: intelligent and shrewd and astute and clever https://t.co/AIq3siB6Z1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Competitive Wesley Crusher" after reading @JayBilas's latest tweets with attention-seeking Ikarus-sky-blue, insightful Hawking-blackhole-black and competitive Olympics-gold https://t.co/YndqmHUxxi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a parking lot in which
Tony DiNozzo can enjoy @ARMurugadoss's outgoing and streetwise tweets
while finding clues https://t.co/lvdn1SLDSu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Attention-seeking Austin Powers" after reading @stevewoz's latest tweets with hip Prince-purple, silly buffoon-buff-orange and attention-seeking Ikarus-sun-orange https://t.co/nC92I8fibs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mate the best of Bridget Jones with the best of Boris Johnson and you get @stevewoz: bouncy and spunky and upbeat and media-savvy https://t.co/4tZepkZamX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Media-savvy Selena Gomez" after reading @Wally97's latest tweets with motivational Obama-brown, preening peacock-blue and media-savvy Britney-blonde-yellow https://t.co/zNbv4R6k1T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This erotic new book about bots makes D.H. Lawrence's 'Sons and Lovers' seem as erotic as an inoculation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a lecture theatre in which
Albus Dumbledore can enjoy @Wally97's whimsical and powerful tweets
while teaching the next generation https://t.co/DoL64zgT2l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Self-confident Meghan Markle" after reading @ImRo45's latest tweets with ambitious Ikarus-sun-orange, social-climbing Blackadder-black and socially-conscious Democrat-blue https://t.co/SE80bz55q6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @ImRo45's competitive and charismatic tweets were edible they'd be Kentucky jam cake made with spit balls instead of raisins https://t.co/GHFV4UULfd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Dispassionate Sonny Crockett" after reading @Tyga's latest tweets with stylish tuxedo-black, fashionable Barbie-pink and dispassionate bureaucrat-grey https://t.co/Pqn7GGcn3q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This welcome new book about computational creativity makes J.R.R. Tolkien's 'The Hobbit' seem as welcome as a brush fire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NETFLIX watches YOU!
Based on @Tyga's fashionable and consciousness-raising tweets it pushes films about The Left and/or Michelle Obama https://t.co/97S1xdobTU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Holier-than-thou Naomi Campbell" after reading @TheRealStanLee's latest tweets with arrogant pig-pink, stylish Dorian Gray and holier-than-thou priest-black https://t.co/r4LroMcm3X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the best of Dr. Greg House with the worst of Sherlock Holmes and you get @TheRealStanLee: witty and probing yet arrogant and high-handed https://t.co/YXFtDLoR8s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Attention-grabbing Amelia Earhart" after reading @Garfield's latest tweets with attention-seeking Ikarus-sky-blue, intrepid hunter-orange and tenacious warrior-woad-blue https://t.co/yOTyBYcEgz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who should star in the @Garfield biopic?
Having played Martin Luther, Joseph Fiennes is ideal for this crusading and revolutionary role https://t.co/YqVvjYNn4y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Eager-to-impress Sam Spade" after reading @themarcjacobs's latest tweets with cold frost-white, charismatic firebrand-red and eager-to-impress Ikarus-sun-orange https://t.co/TH9A8wxow3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian hackers are watching!
@themarcjacobs's fashionable but distant tweets suggest infection with the MELAN1A.TRUMP virus https://t.co/jVTQZugbsw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning: the cold MELAN1A.TRUMP virus rebuffs all requests to connect on Facebook and LinkedIn; replies to each with 'Who are YOU again?']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This dramatic new book about Twitter 'bots' makes Gillian Flynn's 'Gone Girl' seem as dramatic as the average insurance office]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Sharp-tongued King Richard III" after reading @CathyYoung63's latest tweets with ruthless Sith-black, devious demon-red and sharp-tongued Dante-inferno-red https://t.co/ZPQcgXi7fd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teacher is watching
Following @CathyYoung63's influential and electrifying tweets is like one long lecture on singing rock songs from Mick Jagger https://t.co/Eei4b3TOgm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NETFLIX watches YOU!
Based on @JayBilas's intelligent and rational tweets it pushes films about Star Trek and/or Commander Data https://t.co/gkAe2JNUKV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Confident Martin Luther King" after reading @ARMurugadoss's latest tweets with inspirational Braveheart-woad-blue, socially-conscious Democrat-blue and confident Anchorman-burgundy-red https://t.co/zgM0jcjZLS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this innocent book about Twitter 'bots' also bought:
-   J.R.R. Tolkien's 'The Hobbit'
-   Paula Kahneman's 'The Prairie Girl In North Dakota'
 How very innocent!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning: the pretentious CR1T1CZ virus replaces common English phrases in your outgoing tweets with French synonyms such as 'de nos jours']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Good-natured Dr. Eldon Tyrell" after reading @britneyspears's latest tweets with condescending Blackadder-black, scientific Heisenberg-blue and arrogant Thor-blond-yellow https://t.co/labJia14TV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon reads YOU!
Based on @britneyspears's shrewd but preening tweets it pushes Hercule Poirot's book Extracting Confessions https://t.co/rGCw1CVpH0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Well-educated Russell Brand" after reading @KellyannePolls's latest tweets with quick-witted Blackadder-black, entertaining Netflix-red and cocky Bieber-blond-yellow https://t.co/F8vSqOhq1D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the best of Dr. Greg House with the best of Sherlock Holmes and you get @KellyannePolls: cunning and clever and astute and brilliant https://t.co/g6YAIWvxPX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Socially-aware Melania Trump" after reading @jimmykimmel's latest tweets with stylish Kate Moss-green, distant star-white and fashionable Barbie-pink https://t.co/hNrx35qvDg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this stable book about Twitterbots also bought:
-   Ken Follett's 'The Pillars of the Earth'
-   D.H. Seuss's 'The Stout Reed'
 How very stable!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who should star in the @jimmykimmel biopic?
Having played Coco Chanel, Keira Knightley is ideal for this prolific and stylish role https://t.co/KueflLJv8V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Nonchalant Joey Tribbiani" after reading @JessicaSimpson's latest tweets with good-natured Santa-red, self-confident Obama-brown and easy-going Lebowski-weed-green https://t.co/IMnT4i2k1e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hulk is watching!
Hulk HATE genteel humans who remind him of aristocrats. So Hulk SMASH @JessicaSimpson's arrogant, suave and charismatic tweets! https://t.co/DqXmPDssbJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Media-savvy Cosmo Kramer" after reading @5SOS's latest tweets with nutty Wonka-goldticket-gold, affable Barney-purple and media-savvy Britney-blonde-yellow https://t.co/hpxgE6LJFr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @5SOS's mild-mannered and gullible tweets were edible they'd be Treacle tart made with ashes of a cremated loved one instead of flour https://t.co/3hsDo9LGu6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Pleasant Sonny Crockett" after reading @AvrilLavigne's latest tweets with fashionable Barbie-pink, stylish Kate Moss-green and pleasant peach-orange https://t.co/XYjWYHlL3i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This comfy new book about Twitter 'bots' makes Louisa May Alcott's 'Little Women' seem as comfy as an old tyre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teacher is watching
Following @AvrilLavigne's upbeat and media-savvy tweets is like one long lecture on ranting about liberals from Boris Johnson https://t.co/i2JcVgUaJB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Easy-going Richard B. Riddick" after reading @BillGates's latest tweets with ruthless Walter White, defiant Pimpernel-scarlet-red and easy-going Gumby-green https://t.co/0GHgytO0m0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the best of Dr. Greg House with the worst of Sherlock Holmes and you get @BillGates: cunning and clever yet cold and high-handed https://t.co/VEFK4w00tS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This economical new book by Veale &amp; Cook makes Steven D. Levitt's 'Freakonomics' seem as economical as a tractor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Socially-aware Lizzy Bennet" after reading @realDonaldTrump's latest tweets with lively lamb-white, sharp-tongued Dante-inferno-red and socially-aware Democrat-blue https://t.co/UCMj1HViXT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How similar are the Twitter personalities of @BotOnBotAction &amp; @realDonaldTrump? @KellyAnnePolls crunched the numbers: https://t.co/LZ11AM7VGg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does Automated Analysis of your tweets reveal about you? How might the analysis be framed? Tweet  #TrumpMe to find out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Highly-educated Bono" after reading @notrealyoda's latest tweets with holier-than-thou patrician-toga-white, socially-conscious Clooney-grey and preachy priest-black https://t.co/xpCoW5ZVul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @notrealyoda's conceited and arrogant tweets were edible they'd be Dundee cake made with bellybutton lint instead of orange zest https://t.co/xzgpjbvc9k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Eager-to-impress Mom" after reading @Miffy_UK's latest tweets with loving dolphin-blue, devoted knight-silver and eager-to-impress Ikarus-sun-orange https://t.co/fJFfeyHbHA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this religious book about Twitter 'bots' also bought:
-   Dan Brown's 'Angels and Demons'
-   Dante Tolkien's 'Descartes'
 How very religious!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a basement in which
Ringo Starr can enjoy @Miffy_UK's easy-going and witty tweets
while playing drums https://t.co/b91YrtTZ9z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Upbeat Carl Bernstein" after reading @carmeloanthony's latest tweets with media-savvy Netflix-red, tenacious warrior-woad-blue and curious Einstein-dandruff-white https://t.co/1GqxC5U2fK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the best of Boudicca with the worst of Madonna and you get @carmeloanthony: indomitable and subversive yet attention-seeking and attention-grabbing https://t.co/UFgHXEExrP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Short-tempered Maximus Decimus Meridius" after reading @themichaelowen's latest tweets with tactical Coriolanus Snow-white, brave lion-orange and tenacious lobster-red https://t.co/CqhAHIGcnd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a gloomy dungeon in which
Hermione Granger can enjoy @themichaelowen's rational but arrogant tweets
while casting magic spells https://t.co/RJ2KAGfeeI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Quick-witted Carl Bernstein" after reading @DynamiteTom's latest tweets with media-savvy Netflix-red, curious Einstein-dandruff-white and judgmental Grinch-green https://t.co/1JTi9YnMXj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the best of Dr. Greg House with the best of Sherlock Holmes and you get @joerogan: observant and probing and astute and clever https://t.co/pomBewOKOU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Media-savvy Rooster" after reading @FloydMayweather's latest tweets with arrogant ass-brown, cocky Bieber-blond-yellow and media-savvy Facebook-blue https://t.co/GWU0lE8UUV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a board room in which
William Randolph Hearst can enjoy @FloydMayweather's powerful and influential tweets
while telling politicians what to do https://t.co/WtEjssAtYG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Self-confident Steve Jobs" after reading @imbhandarkar's latest tweets with inspirational Braveheart-woad-blue, creative Einstein-dandruff-white and self-confident Obama-brown https://t.co/TzElMo7IFp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian hackers are watching!
@imbhandarkar's inventive and prolific tweets suggest infection with the PAUL.MCCARTNEY virus https://t.co/7deUu6AGcj]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>