<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[A lot of people love Oreos. So their manufacturer is making money. That means more dividends for shareholders. Maria Bartiromo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Selecting a Strategy Consulting Firm  http://t.co/QxWoPu5byt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its not so much about the shoes, but the person wearing them --&gt; Adriana Trigiani, Viola in Real Life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gin and Titonic Ice Cube Tray - Add the Titanic To Your Drinks http://t.co/KfcAzLzBAH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attitude: It is our best friend or our worst enemy. - John C. Maxwell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would you say a parachutist is a fall guy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A shoe without sex appeal is as barren as a tree without leaves. - Rita De Acosta Lydig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious What Went Wrong T-shirt - Love It!  http://t.co/QkfRsNn14L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Mike Clifford - A One-Hit Wonder  http://t.co/KCRoT3zxHw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't pay good wages because I have a lot of money; I have a lot of money because I pay good wages. - Robert Bosch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One person with courage makes a majority. - Andrew Jackson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL Offensive Business Cards - Everyone Needs a Stack of These! http://t.co/LlUbqTuGtA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love This Nerds Candy Juniors Tunic Tank Dress with Nerd Glasses - Dig It! http://t.co/ivCeEzXCDV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Increasingly, the mass marketing is turning into a mass of niches - Christ Anderson Author of The Long Tail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Mary Hopkin  http://t.co/0qvfLUCUfU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He who opens a school door, closes a prison. - Victor Hugo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret of success is constancy to purpose. - Benjamin Disraeli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone who lives within their means suffers from a lack of imagination. - Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Schnauzers  http://t.co/NqCjB5LGA5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The human body is the best work of art. --&gt; Jess C. Scott]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why did I want to win? Because I didn't want to lose! - Max Schmelling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We worked 80 hour weeks for 30 years to keep from having to get a real job. - Tom Lemon's comment on the rigors of being a drag racing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool Garages and Flooring Types  http://t.co/DKiQXQGssV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It will work. I am a marketing genius. - Paris Hilton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to WordTracker SEO Tools http://t.co/Dt3SK9FOnD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no psychiatrist in the world like a puppy licking your face. - Ben Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Star Trek  http://t.co/XCQrKLWteb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool All Wood Watch! http://t.co/bnlaOsuZOO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Rose Royce  http://t.co/kRMdfVYIzA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women need food, water, and compliments.  That's right.  And an occasional pair of shoes. Chris Rock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it weren't for baseball, many kids wouldn't know what a millionaire looked like. - Phyllis Diller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Ketchup  http://t.co/0QXYKJWhrU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science fiction writers foresee the inevitable, and although problems and catastrophes may be inevitable, solutions are not. - Isaac Asimov]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Crosby, Stills and Nash   http://t.co/9T27NpZjTx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for great resources on Beer?  Check out our top 10... http://t.co/fEoEdsRxRz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only undertake what you can do in an excellent fashion. There are no prizes for average performance.- Brian Tracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't do any vulgar movements.  -  Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop praising a woman, she'll think you don't love her.  Keep it up and she'll think she is too good for you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's like saying Prada's are just shoes, or vodka is just a morning beverage! - Karen, Will &amp; Grace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm shooting a commercial for safe sex. How ironic. Because I don't have that.   Tila Tequila]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The numbers are cursed. Dude, don't look at me like that, I'm not crazy. This is real. Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Experience is not what happens to a man. It is what a man does with what happens to him. - Aldous Huxley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lifetime of training for just ten seconds. - Jesse Owens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketing is what you do when your product is no good. - Edwin Land]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I could have played another year, but I would have been playing for the money, and baseball deserves better than that. - George Brett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's basically the same, just darker. - Alan Kulwicki, on racing Saturday nights as opposed to Sunday afternoons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagination is more important than knowledge. Knowledge is limited. Imagination encircles the world. - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I won't be a rock star. I will be a legend. - Freddie Mercury]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't buy a nice car and get rich you get rich and buy a nice car - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After the third flip, I lost control - Don Roberts after crashing in the Jade Grenade at New England Dragway in 1975.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Health and Mana Video Game Inspired Earrings with Key Charms!  Cool! http://t.co/iDHAP1yMMK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome!  Spongebob Squarepants I Love Nerds Green Juniors T-shirt! http://t.co/UtJufDIG1P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money, if it does not bring you happiness, will at least help you be miserable in comfort. - Helen Gurley Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am convinced that every boy, in his heart, would rather steal second base than an automobile. - Thomas Campbell Clark]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Humour. It is a difficult concept - Saavik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Brief History and Introduction to Bitcoin  http://t.co/Ytku3O480r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To confine our attention to terrestrial matters would be to limit the human spirit. - Stephen Hawking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Players have been bought, sold and exchanged as though they were sheep instead of American citizens. - John Montgomery Ward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome kayaking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the paddling lovers in your life!   http://t.co/TeDNzjmCY5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very very cool a complete working model of SpaceX rocket - awesome tech!  http://t.co/FyyEg8pVL7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Powerful Tools For Your Internet Marketing Program    http://t.co/RhKttX83Rl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Card playing is no more expensive than any other game where you hold hands.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Budweiser  http://t.co/JGMIFnlaiq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes I can't figure designers out. It's as if they flunked human anatomy. --&gt; Erma Bombeck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Paul Simon - His Biography  http://t.co/pBujkY9aHP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harness The Power of Twitter for Business to Business Internet Marketing  http://t.co/XPPo5Emrpc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whenever you are asked if you can do a job, tell "˜em, "˜Certainly I can!' Then get busy and find out how to do it. - Theodore Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have always felt I was more accurately a Hard Rock musician.  - Geddy Lee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dress shabbily and they remember the dress; dress impeccably and they remember the woman. --&gt; Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The whole fleet knows this man tried to stab me through the neck. And you missed! Butterfingers! - Gaius Baltar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A wife doesn't mind seeing a man make a fool out of himself as long as some other woman isn't helping him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Design is a constant challenge to balance comfort with luxe, the practical with the desirable. - Donna Karan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, I think we're the greatest rock 'n' roll band in the world.  - Joey Ramone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Awesome Transformer 4GB USB Drives! http://t.co/S4jOj6a786]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Totally cool LEGO Star Wars R2D2 Awesome --&gt; http://t.co/sH3LqkwLB9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stiletto, I look at it more as an attitude as opposed to a high-heeled shoe. - Lita Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every boy should have two things: a dog, and a mother willing to let him have one - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His pockets always outlast his suits...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Ankle Watches – Is This the New Place to Wear a Watch?  http://t.co/mHCOQJVQ7x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hops Holster 12 Can Ammo Pack - Beer Anywhere!  http://t.co/k6EIay7ECo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we're growing, we're always going to be out of our comfort zone. - John Maxwell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boys are Whatever, Shoes are Forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gin and Titonic Ice Cube Tray - Add the Titanic To Your Drinks http://t.co/KfcAzLzBAH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome - Hopside Down Glass - Upside Down Beer Bottle Glass - Cool! http://t.co/j39eTyGXpA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I started out writing much more science fictiony stuff and writing about science fiction. - Neil Gaiman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The roots of education are bitter, but the fruit is sweet. - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's so nervous he keeps coffee awake]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes many a tumble to keep us humble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[E.T. phone home - E.T.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today fitness equipment is something we take for granted - ever wondered about its history?  Read more --&gt; http://t.co/HwKoCjfodc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating Introduction to Marmalade Insurance: How to Select an Insurance Agency  http://t.co/uydevbbeWc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought Europe was a country? Kellie Pickler, on "Are You Smarter Than A Fifth Grader"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About BMX Biking Born from Freestyle Motocross  http://t.co/ssrHITpTE9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our Review of Amazon’s Popular Kindle Reader  http://t.co/eYc2lGZqGZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In 1905 Albert discovered Relativity, in 1906 he invented Rock and Roll.  - Yahoo Serious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've never heard a Jay-Z song.  Miley Cyrus on Jay-Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate most of what constitutes rock music, which is basically middle-aged crap. - Sting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Foghat  http://t.co/dCBheZQhfl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of White Castle  http://t.co/r7Nq9thHFG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't put it on YouTube.  Beyonce Knowles, after slipping onstage during a concert performance]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>