<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Different Types of Major League Pitches  http://t.co/fHqG5CWw2X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reputation is the other fellow's idea of your character]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About BMX Biking Born from Freestyle Motocross  http://t.co/MYkOdOJzMH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dog maybe a man's best friend but a horse made history... - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Brady Bunch is an American sitcom classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/3WCBaNJgDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I could turn and live with animals, they are "¨so placid and self-contained,"¨I stand and look at them long and long. - Walt Whitman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just started my INSANITY: 60-Day Total Body Conditioning Workout DVD Program - wish me luck!  http://t.co/5wNQF8F4kW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Paul Simon - His Biography  http://t.co/1Y7uISLLGi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not anti-social; I'm just not user friendly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A canter is the cure for all evil. - Benjamin Disraeli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the History of Adobe Photoshop  http://t.co/vhoAAF1pTA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's like saying Prada's are just shoes, or vodka is just a morning beverage! - Karen, Will &amp; Grace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Everly Brothers  http://t.co/OcDHQUzKiG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Bert Kaempfert  http://t.co/9pesQVCEWo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome tennis t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the tennis lovers in your life!   http://t.co/1aYDrAFMio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Flea and Tick Control For Your Pet  http://t.co/5rUPmKmjO2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome kayaking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the paddling lovers in your life!  http://t.co/3UioYSSoC6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Best Tips Given for Facebook Pages Geared for Business  http://t.co/LoUnoxy75k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The internet has turned what used to be a controlled, one-way message into a real-time dialogue with millions - Danniel Sacks, Fast Company]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You teach best what you most need to learn. - Richard David Bach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Redrum. -  Danny, The Shining]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To win without risk is to triumph without glory. - Pierre Corneille]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome kayaking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the paddling lovers in your life!  http://t.co/eUmjlwt4yZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The History of Rolex Watches – The Start of Something Great  http://t.co/oUTsMjmCuW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Media are tools.  Real time is mindset.  David Scott - Marketing Strategist - Author of The New Rules of Marketing and PR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter what, the very first piece of social media real estate I'd start with is a blog.  Chris Brogan - New Marketing Labs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DC Comics Ultimate Character Guide http://t.co/9u4igGFwiq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Each man has his own vocation; his talent is his call. There is one direction in which all space is open to him. - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My wife is such a terrible cook the police made her register her stove as a deadly weapon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Blue Oyster Cult   http://t.co/60HjUpFLFa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Chuck Berry  http://t.co/jsYFmGzZQo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Biking Guide BMX Review  http://t.co/Sq7fo4g89I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read How to Use LinkedIn for Your Company   http://t.co/W6chqd3gqM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Amazing and Mesmerizing SciFi &amp; Space Artwork  http://t.co/dYonionoLA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Help with Planning Garage Flooring  http://t.co/SJnBNPIAU7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tom Cruise is rumored to wear them - shoe lifts - read their fascinating history... http://t.co/DyXcbHS5HE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Kinds of Strategy Consulting Firms to Avoid  http://t.co/hrC7fjbHem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The good Lord gave you a body that can stand most anything. It's your mind you have to convince. - Vincent Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't put it on YouTube.  Beyonce Knowles, after slipping onstage during a concert performance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Ivory Joe Hunter  http://t.co/ns9jOcLLQ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Are the Major Kinds of Insurance?  http://t.co/kcaBmeBdXK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's no need for a piece of sculpture in a home that has a cat. - Wesley Bates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Confucius say it is better to be looked over than overlooked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the American Hamburger  http://t.co/2LvllJdAMy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smoking kills. If you killed, you've lost a very important part of your life. Brooke Shields]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Top 10 Burger Chains in the US  http://t.co/t3DhUoDDeW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Johnny Ace: A Life of Unfulfilled Dreams  http://t.co/QJbqHgdtVb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plano Texas is an up and coming area of Dallas - read more here!  http://t.co/UdLxD6RJUD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Best Camping Destinations  http://t.co/YX7Q0MNhH0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this gallery of the top 10 Asian beers!  http://t.co/y5W8EKrgtz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Allman Brothers Band  http://t.co/sG3cUZJfm2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The trick is to stop thinking of it as your money - IRS auditor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Skeeter Davis  http://t.co/j4OW4lwtME]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are inclined to think that if we watch a football game or a baseball game, we have taken part in it. - John F. Kennedy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read Great Outdoor Camping Equipment Tips  http://t.co/67xtNQpxuh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to Douglas Adams  http://t.co/G80jhGggUr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dog has lots of friends because he wags his tail and not his tongue. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You want to fall in love with a shoe go ahead. A shoe can't love you back, a shoe can't hurt you too deeply either. - Allan Sherman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lose Weight WITHOUT Dieting (Animal Kingdom Workouts)  --&gt; http://t.co/sqc51M6lKx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still have my feet on the ground, I just wear better shoes. - Oprah Winfrey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the great department store of life, baseball is the toy department. - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Politicians should read science fiction, not westerns and detective stories. - Arthur C. Clarke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Learning Tool for Kids - Snap Circuits Jr - Hands On Learning All About Circuits http://t.co/3JLQD4hA4U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The pessimist sees difficulty in every opportunity. The optimist sees opportunity in every difficulty. - Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Lettermen  http://t.co/xiapIxQhXS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is the only major sport that appears backward in a mirror. - George Carlin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Brownsville Station  http://t.co/XKO3ZWWYdB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Buddy Holly  http://t.co/HQQjcASu6P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We worked 80 hour weeks for 30 years to keep from having to get a real job. - Tom Lemon's comment on the rigors of being a drag racing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read Great Outdoor Camping Equipment Tips  http://t.co/LzSNF6lfw2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the The Early History of Beer  http://t.co/FAY3Kn7fXj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But I'm a rock 'n' roll singer; that's my livelihood, my occupation.  - Little Richard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not a marketing person. I don't ask myself questions. I go by instinct. - Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is a skilled game. It's America's game - it, and high taxes. - Will Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips for Using Facebook Pages for Your Business  http://t.co/x7peFoFJgN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Star Trek Enterprise Pizza Cutter! http://t.co/vXpBT7nqG2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometime the best thing to get off your chest is your chin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Eating Gluten Free  http://t.co/rYXNEh79w0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm on a 90-day wonder diet. Thus far, I've lost 45 days. - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Overview of the X-Files  http://t.co/OPtngOfN4o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding the Right Fitness Gadgets  http://t.co/3npPvLAlcJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does Food Dye Cause Hyperactive Behavior in Children?  http://t.co/LMNAtvnYu0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Experience is a hard teacher because she gives the test first, the lesson afterward. - Vernon Law]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Chuck Berry  http://t.co/4QlUyO6EjI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's later than we think and most of us aren't even thinking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Ride - La Vibora at Six Flags Over Texas in Arlington  http://t.co/nQqFumHl1z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two things are infinite: the universe and human stupidity; and I'm not sure about the the universe. - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone can steer the ship when the sea is calm. - Publilius Syrus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Pat Benatar  http://t.co/ZiqLLOGQKG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be successful, the first thing to do is fall in love with your work. - Sister Mary Lauretta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think too little, you are sure to talk too much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL Offensive Business Cards - Everyone Needs a Stack of These! http://t.co/gGu1QG6LGz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doctor, giving prescription to a patient "Let me know if this stuff works. I'm having the same trouble myself."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lend your friend $20, if he doesn't pay you back then he's not your friend. Money well spent - Ted Nicolas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Paul Davis  http://t.co/GMJyfMQW3w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About How Technology Has Helped Seniors to Make Great Strides in their Lifestyle  http://t.co/QQ9OgvmEtZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be nice to geek's, you'll probably end up working for one - Bill Gates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sign on a greenhouse: Fresh flowers just out of bed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The way you can understand all of the social media is as the creation of a new kind of public space - Dana Boyd, Social Media Research MSFT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The eternal silence of these infinite spaces fills me with dread. - Blaise Pascal]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>