<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bexhill2Bexhill @sontagdaily @Spooniehacker @chronicinclude @sineadgleeson It's out early March I think (I read a proof)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Bexhill2Bexhill @sontagdaily @Spooniehacker @chronicinclude You would probably really appreciate Constellations by @sineadgleeson.It's a collection of linked essays focusing on gendered  experiences of pain, illness, the body &amp; perhaps most of all (for me) different ideas of what is left behind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As soon as I can I'm going to Dalkeith in search of a birling oak tree that someone posted a picture of on Instagram. Evidence perhaps of life as computer simulation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[dialogue https://t.co/N176Gj4ECv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thelightoutside @manoghosts I'll bet. I've been thinking about it a lot recently as @DarraghMc was looking for experiences, he might be interested in this. At least you didn't have to stay at hers!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thelightoutside @manoghosts I'm blocking you Stuart. I WILL NEVER SLEEP AGAIN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wish I still lived in Walthamstow &amp; could see this https://t.co/cLSz2LnXLB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to reading this &amp; speaking to Blue about her Lone Women experiences for the new @wildernessflash website which will be ready very soon. Follow for updates. https://t.co/N7q0uUodIu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[pronounced as two words https://t.co/fRcwkW8gVf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bazzanagnagnag Hope it goes well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bazzanagnagnag Well done, Barry, that is definitely a step forward.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[bias https://t.co/Ifm0udiwY9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @womensart1: Joan Eardley, Catterline in Winter, 1963 #womensart https://t.co/B8k9jurLLv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GoldFlakePaint A wee bit nervous about this one but very much looking forward to reading everyone else's. Thanks for running it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amycutler1985 Ha, yes. Do you have the outfit to match?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @wildernessflash: I spoke to LOTS of women who shared their thoughts &amp; experiences re going to gigs alone, getting there, being there, g…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lostcont Thank fuck for that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lostcont Haha, that actually made me laugh out loud so unfortunately you win.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lostcont I have ALREADY scrubbed St Kilda off my map. You're next, McHenry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lostcont Bloody nuisance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[grey of seduct https://t.co/QUeab2PSM0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Monsterlander @IMcMillan And irl I'd imagine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IMcMillan thanks for sharing my stuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@natlyon Definitely, I guess true artists often are when they don't just play the game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[coalesce https://t.co/ImdFUKR6BF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@natlyon Cheers, Nat. I think The Horizon Just Laughed is a great album in any year actually.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I spoke to @damienjurado for this as part of albums of 2018 &amp; also to LOTS of women about their thoughts &amp; experiences re going to gigs alone for an experimental nonfiction piece, Watched. https://t.co/FPcY7tP2ed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@songbrookes Hope it feels less ominous than that looks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@walkingheads @lissertations PS I know Alissa via @wildernessflash but missed this. Thanks. Quite chuffed to be the best of the old :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@walkingheads @lissertations Ha, I just read the link (&amp; now understand what a ping back is), it's interesting to see it summarised by someone else with the added conclusion of "cars are awful"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@psychojography Very]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joannaofottawa Good answer!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pat_M_Barrett It is. Although perhaps controversially I actually love A Walk Across the Rooftops a teeny bit more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pat_M_Barrett Nice association. Love that album.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JBueno_UKCP I'm not saying. That's for you to decide :-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if I gave you the word would you keep it https://t.co/UOYS8Mrqd6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Miinsky Thanks very much, that's really nice of you to say so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GPatterson76: https://t.co/2IiHtkOCLZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LukeTurnerEsq The Weary by @kathrynjoseph is also about this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@godwinafaith You've been everywhere! I've not been for 30 years. Was just looking over today, mulling... X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kramawoodgin Thanks, Mark]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[lines of between https://t.co/hxSl8e36Cx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[mull https://t.co/znBQTg19Dg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[mutate of larch fever]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[unmuddle https://t.co/J1oJkwPsiv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RealEarthMother @lostcont Aw, thanks, Jo x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[perpetuate https://t.co/vX3P8Zzmzo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[tang of tip https://t.co/wQM2o8ESZd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've been invited to show this piece at a festival taking place later this year. If you'd like to input it's still open. Also interested in the sounds of outside with a dog if happy to have included
Film Project: Space of Doglessness https://t.co/xkZQiWEqAR via @wordpressdotcom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HooklandGuide Wishing you better soon, David. Have some tree magic https://t.co/IVHUM8Tdie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lostcont Merle Haggard of the ranch world?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lostcont I can see your mind thinking of a new series of procrastination there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EBCopywriting At least you make notes...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EBCopywriting Thanks, Felix. Hope all good with you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[dialogue https://t.co/3Tyi3cBuK3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ryleywalker @aquadrunkard Craig from Aerogramme is @sloopcraigb, he's just made a new record as well. You'd probably like it, Ryley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@northseacrashes Although also think of all the good day trips]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@northseacrashes Haha when you put it like that FUCK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@northseacrashes Yes. I thought that was three years ago!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@northseacrashes I was 10... low key birthday this year...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feel free to sing Bauhaus in response, Brian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saw a cormorant earlier &amp; it made me think of this that me &amp; @lostcont did last year.  https://t.co/mEL1IVzYeR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GoldFlakePaint: Issue 2 launches on-or-around January 25th!

There's a big interview piece with ~ the secret thing we're not allowed to…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@S_Carden @WednesdayErskin It is. She provokes thoughts by stealth &amp; then annihilates anything superfluous. Gallowayesque but Erskine. I'm hoping she goes back to art, music &amp; attitude tweets soon though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[there is no taut of isolate https://t.co/eRsD5oG2Kg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justin_wiggan Yes, I reckon so]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justin_wiggan In an artificial/tech way?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justin_wiggan Sounds very interesting but I think I'm going to have to read up on it properly as had to just look up haptic!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justin_wiggan What is /are stonetones, Justin?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sally__Williams Fife is beautiful, plus you get to come over the Forth bridges which is always great view wise, you should check it out!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sally__Williams Yes, I'm lucky I live just across from the beach. Also, thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sally__Williams Where do I live? In a place called Burntisland (pronounced as 2 words) in Fife, just across the water from Edinburgh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Leathley_P My mum got me it, was an excellent surprise as I didn't know they did them. Definitely need to get rid of the TD though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Paulinlatorre Sympathy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LittleBigSpoon Are you in Edinburgh or Sheffield?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LittleBigSpoon Same]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LittleBigSpoon hello stranger, how are you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also, if Frys could give me extra original or even orange instead of Turkish Delight in the selection box next year I'd appreciate it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sunk of unend https://t.co/BI1qd63u4i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if i gave you the word would you keep it https://t.co/nlt0o8qPMd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[acts of almost https://t.co/b3Mr6TJYeC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[acts of call https://t.co/TlICkjRxvc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok, to save her from having to go on about her book Sweet Home constantly, I'm telling you  @WednesdayErskin  has many skills, one of which is the ability to properly convey sarcasm with underlying almost there kindness &amp; hurt. Not  easy, but she makes it seem it. Loads to enjoy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brianrooney15 Ah ok, that is glaringly obvious now you've told me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brianrooney15 You've lost me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @bothyproject: OPEN CALL OPPORTUNITY! We're delighted to announce our inaugural programme of funded residencies @bothyproject supported…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[spin https://t.co/3eXECUo9LY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WednesdayErskin Of course.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've heard all of this &amp; it is beautiful. Also unexpectedly catchy for experimental ambient/drone https://t.co/vMHJUoCyRw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WednesdayErskin Kind of relieved about that. Thank you. Want to join my band the Mutual Luvvies?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WednesdayErskin read your book, loved your book. Your door is safe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brianrooney15 And you, Brian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NiamhMacCabe Sorry, just saw this. Thank you and to you x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@godwinafaith Thank you. Happy New Year to you too. Maybe get to see you this year x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@crossmansusanna It was. Although actually it was me and the dog &amp; hundreds of birds so was pretty noisy within the stillness. Was great. (Ignore me singing the Banks of the Ohio at the start) https://t.co/CdKRzWaBJE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[extract https://t.co/YdYpPWCDkY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@crossmansusanna I was the only one out there, came back in the dark]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[daub of after https://t.co/c2EqNFTDGd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beatgozon (I actually don't) :-). Happy New Year Jeff, and thank you for all your positivity to me and my stuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NiamhMacCabe Wouldn't mind that road trip. All the best to you, Niamh. Going to have to look up Keelogyboy]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>