<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @davidakaye: this is an interesting idea and should be thought through industry-wide https://t.co/YzfAzG1uro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @davidakaye: who put out the fire, who held the arsonists accountable, &amp; who rebuilt the foundations and the structure itself. let’s not…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @accessnow: Together with 37 consumer organisations, NGOs and internet companies, we just sent a letter to the Council urging them to ad…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @UNHCRInnovation: One refugee's path to changing master narratives around refugees: “I tell them no, I’m not an exception. I’m an except…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rankingrights: @rj_gallagher of @theintercept reports that Google's Project Dragonfly is so secretive that it shut out its own privacy…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @freedomonthenet: In November, @SMEX hosted its #BreadAndNet conference on digital rights in #MENA. @accessnow shares their reflection:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pressfreedom: Join CPJ in its #JusticeForJamal campaign. Share why journalism matters to you on social media using the hashtag https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @IndexCensorship: At a time when fake news is causing more strife than ever before, here’s your guide to spotting falsehoods before you…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @davidakaye: all governments should support @mariaressa &amp; @rapplerdotcom &amp; appeal to the #Philippines govt &amp; president duterte to drop t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MalJayaram: We have a few travel stipends to offer selected applicants: if you're in the region &amp; need help getting to Singapore, we ma…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CornellaEmily: @JuliaAngwin thought you would be interested in this article detailing more of FB's algorithmic injustice: https://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rich_wing: It's examples like these that show why we need far greater transparency from platforms about the algorithms they use. https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RonDeibert: Israeli Software Helped Saudis Spy on Khashoggi, Lawsuit Says https://t.co/Qr7YSQh4Zt #Khashoggi @oamaz7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @connectedrights: Will Facebook finally allow users real appeal rights? https://t.co/ap40MIiXjt https://t.co/VWjqYOVsuI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @eyywa: Activists are leading an unprecedented fight against Google's attempts to build a smart city in Toronto. The outcome of their st…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rasmus_kleis: Facebook will work w/French regulators on hate speech, as @EmmanuelMacron suggests states and companies must "learn to re…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Info_Activism: How Google and Amazon Got Away With Not Being Regulated https://t.co/qlSyS92fQ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Info_Activism: End intellectual property - Copyrights, patents and trademarks are all important, but the term ‘intellectual property’ i…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @IFEX: Over 80 IFEX members and other groups have joined @EFF and @Article19org in sending an open letter to Mark Zuckerberg, calling on…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @accessnow: No matter what you call #internetshutdowns or the form they take, there are no facts to show they "work" for their intended…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LetaHong: A Chinese feminist started this petition demanding the release of kidnapped students and workers in China. Please consider si…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AnandWrites: Hey Siri what's neoliberalism?

Neoliberalism is the world's most valuable company getting a tax break from a state that c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EFF: "Facebook fundamentally thinks they're doing a good job with content moderation and they could not be more wrong."  https://t.co/V…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EFF: EFF supports legislation to create “information fiduciary” rules, which outline the duties of loyalty and care companies that coll…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @zeynep: "The Saudi-led war in Yemen has pushed millions to the brink of starvation." 
One of the richest countries in the world has bee…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @daphnehk: It’s crazy enough that this UK law would criminalize viewing vaguely defined “terrorist content” online. But it also has no i…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join me for this investor webinar on Tuesday!! https://t.co/E1V6mrBByO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @goodID4all: Privacy-by-design: the technology is ready. "The economics are not there" is the typical answer we get... Of course it is n…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @accessnow: Apple is making decisions that implicate fundamental rights, and the more #transparency it can offer, the better. (Yes, we'r…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rankingrights: Next Tuesday
10:30 am - 11:30 am EST

@rmack will provide an overview of RDR, the 2018 Corporate Accountability Index an…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @daphnehk: Woohoo! OTI just released its best practices for meaningful (and standardized/comparable across platforms) transparency repor…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was in Paris on Saturday. Intermittent rain, didn’t notice meaningful wind, nothing that a standard umbrella and raincoat can’t handle even on a long walk. https://t.co/DMFw5yVGIX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @globalvoices: A Conversation with Gyani Maiya Sen, one of the last speakers of a dying Nepali language https://t.co/qMmirbeRwq https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nytopinion: Russia’s meddling in U.S. elections is not a hoax. It’s the culmination of Moscow’s decades-long campaign to tear the west…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @eolander: This is the kind of headline Chinese media strategists definitely want to see more of in their effort to shift the narrative…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can’t miss this one! My hubby is one of the speakers!! https://t.co/IAIioInvtw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MarechalPhD: I’m hearing a lot of ppl argue that bias in AI is good b/c it allows us to see the bias in the human-generated training da…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WolfieChristl: Wow, this is absurd: "Prior to this DPIA, Microsoft assumed the telemetry data were not personal data".

Very interestin…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @zararah: Wonderful news: the NHS has stopped sharing data on migrants with the Home Office — congratulations and thank you, @libertyhq…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @theGNI: At #IGF2018 .@Patrik_Hiselius outlines @TeliaCompany's principles and tools for pushing back on network disruptions w/ #economi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MarechalPhD: Due process and platform accountability in the era of automated decision-making start with the right to appeal content rem…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AmosToh: Yes! @jhybe @APC_News and @irenepoet @citizenlab do critical inter-disciplinary work that exposes root causes of digital right…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @techonomy: "I don't think the platform's complexity and rich nuance is understood by the developers of the platform" - @sanjanah on whe…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honored to have been able to present @rankingrights at the @ParisPeaceForum as a project leader. Thank you for organizing this great event and hope to see everybody again next year. https://t.co/w0fcOcxK9e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me and the other winning members of the @rankingrights team at our ⁦@ParisPeaceForum⁩ booth! Thanks ⁦@sambucabral⁩ and @brouilas for your hard work explaining the project to so many people over three days!! https://t.co/XGnaUVYXu0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to this tomorrow. https://t.co/TwrtkTkHYs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @netizenrights: A Grim Reality for Internet Freedom in Asia https://t.co/qofO6jKWoG 
via @Diplomat_APAC #Asia #NetFreedom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proud that @rankingrights participated in the drafting of this letter in addition to being a signatory. https://t.co/D8wSMGqK9H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MarechalPhD: .@nicsuzor mentions @rankingrights as an example of decentralized accountability mechanism -- see our 2016 article on this…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PaxWorld: “Companies need to treat gender diversity like the business imperative it is.” —@SherylSandberg https://t.co/B35ftBM1Jg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OpenNetGlobal: Thrilled we managed to get @KathleenNdongmo’s participation remotely. She recommends working on regional stakeholder eff…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @vitaliymoroz: Whatsapp was named as a platform to spread misinformation during Brasil elections, since it is encrypted, it's hard to tr…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rankingrights: We are proud to have been one of the chosen winners. Please note that this is the correct twitter handle for Ranking Dig…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rankingrights: Wow we were unexpectedly chosen today as a featured project by the @parispeaceforum! Our founder and director @rmack was…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @privacyint: We filed complaints against 7 companies that, despite exploiting the data about millions of people, are not well-known and…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @theGNI: 5:20 pm #IGF2018 roundtable in Salle X: GNI members @CIPESA, @Patrik_Hiselius / @TeliaCompany, &amp; @UsamaKhilji / @BoloBhi share…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WolfieChristl: "A year ago, their playbook was self-regulation, now "they want a federal law that is weak". The "180-degree turn to emb…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you so much!! We are so proud and grateful for your support. Wish the whole @rankingrights team was all there to be recognized. We weren’t expecting to be one of the selected projects!! https://t.co/wOIUErmReG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EileenDonahoe: We need governance innovations for our global digital ecosystem to match the dynamism of technology, while protecting co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SarahLJorgensen: CNN sues President Trump and top White House aides for barring @Acosta - the whole story here with lots of great backg…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EFF: Today, EFF and over 70 other groups told Mark Zuckerberg: It's time Facebook create standards that allow ALL users to appeal when…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @xeni: * SINEMA WINEMA *

Arizona, @KyrstenSinema is your new Senator.
 
• First Democrat to win that race in decades.
• First woman to…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for sharing your experience and wisdom! https://t.co/nKhe3mVpgv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rankingrights: We are at Day 3 of the #ParisPeaceForum 

It has been a great conference so far, and we are excited to have more convers…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @hiattf: The Trump administration seems to be abetting a Saudi coverup of the Khashoggi murder. Congress cannot go along. A WaPo editori…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @amatwyshyn: My  op-ed up for @WSJ on the Internet of Bodies.  #InternetofBodies #IoB https://t.co/ikKsMifeHy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @privacyint: Companies that exploit data about millions of people MUST be challenged. 

YOU have rights over your data, including the ri…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @davidakaye: sharing with everyone but an independent &amp; credible investigative team that the #UN could easily set up - and with all this…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FlorenceBonnet: Facebook to give special access to French regulators as part of a call from French president to tighten regulation of t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @normative: Trump so routinely gets away with gestures of symbolic disrespect a hell of a lot more egregious than kneeling during an ant…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @stevewaygood: Excellent FT write up on the Corporate Human Rights Bechmark @RankBHR 2018 Results. Some good progress by @ENI @adidas an…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AuschwitzMuseum: "We must take sides. Neutrality helps the oppressor, never the victim. Silence encourages the tormentor, never the tor…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Neutrality = collaboration https://t.co/vpHoQFUUp5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you for your leadership on this @jilliancyork ! https://t.co/qWGbjjiMuE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EileenDonahoe: Next generation deepfake digital disinformation  - - is about to hit our democratic discourse.  To combat it, the Transa…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @why0hy: Just once, I'd like a politician to give a quantified, clear, evidence-based justification for referring to something as "best…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @globalvoices: Is Jair Bolsonaro another Rodrigo Duterte? It's more complicated than you think https://t.co/lqnuAjqjPo "It's (not just)…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jayrosen_nyu: There's coverage. There's skeptical coverage. And there's, "if we cover this at all, we will be conceding that it's a thi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great session thanks to @gbengasesan @JulieOwono ! https://t.co/0U3HKyjXfR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Info_Activism: Freedom of Expression - On the International Declaration on Information and Democracy, a word of caution to move forward…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mariaressa: After a few hours of sleep, am back and thank you for all the messages of support! It's been a challenging two and a half y…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rasmus_kleis: I opened "information disorder" session today at #IGF2018 @intgovforum @igf2018paris, and was asked to provide quick over…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RankBHR: "Human rights is an area of increasing concern to investors."

- Financial Times (@Ftfm) on our 2018 results released today ht…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations! https://t.co/YGSdhLjsce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @accessnow: Some important considerations for freedom of expression as states move forward with the International Declaration on Informa…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @IndexCensorship: Demonising the media: Threats to journalists in Europe. Burned in effigy. Insulted. Menaced. Spat at. Discredited by t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EFF: Data scientist Cathy O'Neil (@mathbabedotorg) on risk assessments in @NYTOpinion: "It’s tempting to believe that computers will be…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @davidakaye: for those gathering in solidarity at #parispeaceforum consider that there remains no int’l or credible investigation of the…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Info_Activism: Visualising Information for Advocacy a book about how advocates &amp; activists use visual elements in their campaigns 160-p…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GlobPeaceIndex: The United States accounts for 40% of global military expenditure in 2017, despite decreasing its military spending by…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @freedomonthenet: This year, #Turkey ranks among the countries with the highest number of content removal requests sent to Twitter and F…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @IndexCensorship: Europe: Willingness to smear journalists in order to warp the public’s right to information is the true threat to medi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @brianstelter: Axios: "House Democrats plan to investigate whether President Trump abused White House power by targeting — and trying to…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@goldkorn We shall see. Maybe send in some of the people who used to cover China..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@billt Indeed!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AgnesCallamard: We will indeed persist; demand accountability for his despicable murder; demand and get human rights protection for all…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stay and fight for your right to ask tough questions they don't like. If somebody is shut down or kicked out for asking a question everybody should keep asking the same question. https://t.co/ldWofebPA0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @hallaboutafrica: On today's 100th anniversary of World War I ending, a salute to the many African warriors who fought in Europe for col…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @opengovpart: "Lack of compromise will lead us to a lack of peace. It requires courage to go to your own people when you're in political…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @hallaboutafrica: 1 of 3: On today's 100th anniversary of end of World War I, Africa's sacrifice must be told. 2 million Africans were f…]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>