<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Kitty Kallen  http://t.co/8es1nZrHBu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Trust Me I'm A Nerd Mens Sweatshirt - Awesome http://t.co/Jl2jg7M1HF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read a Review of Heaven is For Real  http://t.co/w5FWGJgkg1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You will never change your life until you change something you do daily. - Mike Murdock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The key to wisdom is a knowledge of our own ignorance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One Family’s Adoption Stories  http://t.co/98j5h3RF3f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I had never seen much of Star Trek, or any other science fiction, before I was cast. But Seven's wonderful. - Jeri Ryan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Publishing Management with HootSuite  http://t.co/0rkGnWymPy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the largest life insurance companies in the US!  http://t.co/ekxdQymwlu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Adding Solar Power for Heating Pool  http://t.co/ar6wCJIotp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make it so! - Engage! - Captain Picard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of Little House on The Prairie Episode - "In the Big Inning"  http://t.co/9yZZpgqUNw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Crosby, Stills and Nash   http://t.co/BOjG0KXklw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adoption - Initial Stages - Part 1  http://t.co/aQ2B95s1ZO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Questions to Ask a Lawyer Prior to Hiring Them  http://t.co/bM6UWr3Nlr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cooking - A Simple Way To Bond With Kids  http://t.co/wiWvIoe4Zz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Major Shoe Retailers  http://t.co/99zdpSNa1T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read about the Emerging Private Space Industry  http://t.co/LAy1FpGoa0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Guide – Business to Business Internet Marketing Tips  http://t.co/AMu3wBBMot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the largest life insurance companies in the US!  http://t.co/ekxdQymwlu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Star Wars  http://t.co/FnuVjvQm4n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rock is so much fun. That's what it's all about - filling up the chest cavities and empty kneecaps and elbows.  - Jimi Hendrix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[London Weight Loss Salon sign: "We value the pound."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every day, in every way, I am getting better and better. - Emilie Coue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Looking Glass  http://t.co/FIMFWRYsrW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a rock and roll singer.  -  Adam Ant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the dressing room, I always put on my right shoe first. Same thing for my right wristband. -  Mary Lou Retton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I speak my mind. I never mind what I speak!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aerodynamics are for people who can't build engines. - Enzo Ferrari]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn the Keys to Using LinkedIn for Your Company  http://t.co/F0XTzgireS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The whole purpose of education is to turn mirrors into windows. - Sydney J. Harris]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome basketball t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the basketball lovers in your life!   http://t.co/upILpwyJZs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Why You Should Consider a Creative Writing Degree  http://t.co/hIcF15gl2Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One way to get thin is to re-establish a purpose in life. - Cyril Connolly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The entrepreneur always searches for change, responds to it, and exploits it as an opportunity. - Peter F. Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ability is the art of getting credit for all the home runs somebody else hits. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WOW - Very Cool A Sticky Note Wrist Watch! http://t.co/tebbyBS7i8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Magic texting glove with conductive yarn finger tips for iPhone, iPad and all touch screen devices - 4 colors  --&gt; http://t.co/kyphKes7Je]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future belongs to those who believe in the beauty of their dreams. - Eleanor Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one gets very far unless he accomplishes the impossible at least once a day. - Elbert Hubbard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I was president of the good old U.S.A., I'd turn the churches into strip clubs and watch the whole world pray.  Kid Rock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dogs come when they're called; cats take a message and get back to you later. - Mary Bly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't put it on YouTube.  Beyonce Knowles, after slipping onstage during a concert performance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Platform Shoes  http://t.co/GhyM2473KB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Health and Mana Video Game Inspired Earrings with Key Charms!  Cool! http://t.co/g3F2c1wTqd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not anorexic. I'm from Texas. Are there people from Texas that are anorexic? I've never heard of one. And that includes me. Jessica S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rock and roll is here to stay. - Neil Young]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exciting History of Baseball  http://t.co/CzxEapGkNG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Ab Carver Pro is very very cool...  http://t.co/QFgnfymeuH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SEO and Web Marketing – Harness the Power of Google Analytics  http://t.co/htljhxxoDQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life started getting good when I started making money. Balthazar Getty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No heaven will not ever Heaven be; “Unless my cats are there to welcome me.” - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The quality of a leader is reflected in the standards they set for themselves. - Ray Kroc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eat, drink and be merry, for tomorrow ye diet. - William Gilmore Beymer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flattery, like perfume, should be smelled, not swallowed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just got my Google Chromecast HDMI Streaming Media Player - SO COOL - http://t.co/h4enMF11WX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this gallery of the top 10 Asian beers!  http://t.co/N9oI2HrylD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its not so much about the shoes, but the person wearing them --&gt; Adriana Trigiani, Viola in Real Life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome marriage t-shirts &amp; gear - give the gift of marriage!  http://t.co/TCBCi4MsVF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would not invest in any shoe that is too trendy. - Rachel Roy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes make me happy. - Actress Lauren Conrad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting Your Creative Writing Degree Online  http://t.co/WClR9AIXJw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yah! I'm on the "Starts tomorrow" diet!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can accept failure, but I can't accept not trying. - Michael Jordan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Jackson Five  http://t.co/y73FrSyId1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no black magic to successfully attracting customers via the web.  Rand Fishkin, Founder SEOMoz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is a Creative Writing Degree for You?  http://t.co/Y8j4gRcx0W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Cool Types of Garage Flooring  http://t.co/NW9FQP3icg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DotNetNuke 6.0 – A Big Leap Forward  http://t.co/8MUJnRD9YK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who dares to teach must never cease to learn. - John Cotton Dana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is what you get from reading the small print in a contract. "experience " is what you get from not reading it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome marriage t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the lovers in your life!   http://t.co/WiRZ5jhE7b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes are just made from leather, rubber and cloth - read about exotic shoes... http://t.co/pU24eroHF3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah, well. The Dude abides. - The Dude, The Big Lebowski]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good pitching will beat good hitting any time, and vice versa. - Bob Veale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just as soon as some people get up in the world they immediately start looking down on others. . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Jefferson Airplane  http://t.co/KSYN54gYSY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surviving a failure gives you more self-confidence. Failures are great learning tools.. but they must be kept to a minimum. - Jeffrey Immelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dogs have owners, cats have staff. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science fiction writers foresee the inevitable, and although problems and catastrophes may be inevitable, solutions are not. - Isaac Asimov]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snow and adolescence are about the only things that disappear if you ignore them long enough]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The less a man knows --  the more he tells it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Help with Picking Garage Cabinets  http://t.co/BdEcl3cAEg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These Messenger Bags are stylish and practical - cool! http://t.co/syKSW45jZf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hokey religions and ancient weapons are no substitute for a good blaster at your side, kid. - Han Solo, Star Wars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Kalin Twins  http://t.co/l9jWJmWKCU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only place where success comes before work is in the dictionary. - Vidal Sassoon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Lynyrd Skynyrd  http://t.co/CozK28JUwo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not let what you cannot do interfere with what you can do. - John Wooden]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome camping t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the camping lovers in your life!   http://t.co/9to2wbie2j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you can leave two black stripes from the exit of one corner to the braking zone of the next, you have enough horsepower. - Mark Donohue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's hard to win a pennant, but it's harder losing one. - Chuck Tanner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your Attorney Search: The Advantages of Flat Rates  http://t.co/z3udN9xRsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating history of Baseball Cards!  http://t.co/6Hn3Y6CyvI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop praising a woman, she'll think you don't love her.  Keep it up and she'll think she is too good for you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketing is too important to be left to the marketing department. - David Packard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagination is the key to my lyrics. The rest is painted with a little science fiction. - Jimi Hendrix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most beautiful thing in the world is a ballpark filled with people. - Bill Veeck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't go into details, I've already told you  more than I overheard myself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you wish to grow thinner, diminish your dinner. - Henry Sambrooke Leigh]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>