<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Business Systems Analyst #KS-01: Senior Business Systems Analyst – Service sought by ICU Medical, Inc. in San Clemente, CA: Work with business to document requirements &amp; assist in the development of designs for implementation.   recblid… https://t.co/6EbiPvL0My https://t.co/yRwnIJl7V6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer II # 22525: Software Engineer II (Plymouth Meeting, PA) sought by Accolade, Inc. Interface w/ end users to gather, understand &amp; translate requirements into Agile delivery process.  recblid 6004zd3zpxqb8vsspfwv34oetns3um https://t.co/gCCEpYZyWX https://t.co/iCgF7fohI8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Site Reliability Engineer: 100252BR Site Reliability Engineer CO – Aurora, TX – Richardson, VA – Dulles, VA – Sterling 100252BR Raytheon Intelligence, Information and Services (IIS) has immediate openings for Sr. DevOps Engineers and Site Reliability… https://t.co/CzRSb5c1bG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Quality Assurance Engineer: Why naviHealth? naviHealth is the result of over a decade of dedicated visionary leaders and innovative organizations challenging the status quo for post-acute care management solutions. We do healthcare differently and… https://t.co/feQ6Hkz66e https://t.co/YLvs3rsUKU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China's Xiaomi posts $1 billion first quarter loss ahead of blockbuster IPO: HONG KONG (Reuters) - Chinese smartphone maker Xiaomi recorded a first-quarter net loss of 7 billion yuan ($1.09 billion) ahead of its blockbuster initial public offering,… https://t.co/E1BmouD7BE https://t.co/u4iHMGyYce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer x 2: Description MUST HAVE: COUPLE YEARS OF EXPERIENCE IN BOTH AREAS * C++ * C# ?PROJECT: Their grain analyzing computer is already written in C# and C++ but they need someone to be able to sustain the existing design and also get it… https://t.co/M4ZJ0E8tHA https://t.co/i8s38MDzBw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer — TS/SCI Required (Java): An analytics and data solutions company that delivers customized solutions to clients, is seeking a qualified Sr. Software Engineer with TS/SCI clearance to join their growing team. This person will be… https://t.co/qobGxCiwwz https://t.co/iXSEDp1MAB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rights group hits Amazon, Foxconn over China labor conditions: NEW YORK (Reuters) - A U.S. watchdog group criticized https://t.co/s2foRsMat5 Inc and contract manufacturer Foxconn over what it described as harsh working conditions at a plant in China that… https://t.co/BS9sntIpSf https://t.co/fSN0sNxXbj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Internet Gold examining sale of controlling stake in Bezeq: JERUSALEM (Reuters) - Internet Gold - Golden Lines said on Sunday it was considering offers to sell part or all of its shares in B Communications, through which it controls Israel's largest… https://t.co/znXmKeoouF https://t.co/So4w1W8zby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer: General Dynamics Information Technology (GDIT) has an immediate need for a .NET Developer to analyze, evaluate and develop new and existing web/database applications; working under limited supervision; performing additional duties as… https://t.co/nS3m28p9Ro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Sr. Developer – Java / Scala / AngularJS: Are you a highly skilled software engineer with a passion for creating great user experiences? Are you excited about building products that will be used by millions of people each year? Do you love… https://t.co/TcjIzgmX91 https://t.co/Ov0FEhLebA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia forms task force to guard elections from cyber attacks: MELBOURNE (Reuters) - Australia has established a security task force to guard against cyber attacks and interference in elections, the government said on Saturday, amid concerns foreign… https://t.co/t4gPq0bcyL https://t.co/XuT45ixRKh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Program Manager: About GoDaddy GoDaddy powers the world’s largest cloud platform dedicated to small, independent ventures. With nearly 17 million customers worldwide and over 75 million domain names under management, GoDaddy is the place people… https://t.co/nzQka5vGuU https://t.co/3yiBLIyE1y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Process Applications Specialist: The Office of the Chief Administrative Officer (CAO) provides operations support services and business solutions to the community of 10,000 House Members, Officers and staff. The CAO organization comprises more… https://t.co/tLxxJ4T7AG https://t.co/Lob15IJr9K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jacksonville Project Manager / Inspector / Sales: We are looking for a loyal, driven and self-motivated individual who wants to move up on their own and make more money while helping homeowners. Our Project Managers learn our proven processes and… https://t.co/kBezISNU4M https://t.co/tpBkgbhEYi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[French emergency room tests virtual reality path to pain relief: PARIS (Reuters) - The very thought of visiting a hospital emergency department is stressful enough for many people, even without the discomfort or pain of an examination or treatment. https://t.co/0ctk6VSRD6 https://t.co/L1b5VJUCDW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dot Net Developer: – Bachelor’s degree or foreign equivalent required from an accredited institution. Will also consider three years of progressive experience in the specialty in lieu of every year of education. – At least 4 years of experience in… https://t.co/hwTjzBxi87 https://t.co/BxkjTKd4i1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Manager: We are seeking a Customer Support Manager to become an integral part of our team! You will be responsible for supporting top tier clients, some of the biggest names in the world, with unique needs. In addition, you will be… https://t.co/DtWJ643EHV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dot Net Developer: – Bachelor’s degree or foreign equivalent required from an accredited institution. Will also consider three years of progressive experience in the specialty in lieu of every year of education. – At least 4 years of experience with… https://t.co/gdy8V4YhoN https://t.co/VKNntrSj9r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China's ZTE chairman apologizes, pledges reboot after U.S. reprieve: source: HONG KONG (Reuters) - The chairman of China's ZTE Corp apologized to staff and customers on Friday after the technology firm agreed to pay a $1 billion fine to the United States… https://t.co/Mk0CBM5PVQ https://t.co/k6SGEsLaX6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Application Support Engineer: Careers Center | IT Application Support Engineer (Operations) Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to… https://t.co/bXASics8tP https://t.co/l45Cfclw2z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cash Applications Specialist: GENERAL PURPOSE OF THE JOB:This position accurately posts cash deposits to patient accounts and general ledger accounts to ensure department goals and objectives are achieved. ESSENTIAL DUTIES AND RESPONSIBILITIES:The… https://t.co/bhK3PZWPI1 https://t.co/VG7coL8ZTf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Engineer: FULL STACK ENGINEER The Senior Full Stack Engineer will be responsible for the development, testing, and implementation of innovative customer-facing native mobile and web applications and willsupport Front End responsive web sites… https://t.co/MUzgGnxU9b https://t.co/0w0kSGvY0a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. reaches deal with China's ZTE: Commerce Secretary: (Reuters) - U.S. Commerce Secretary Wilbur Ross said on Thursday Washington had reached a deal with ZTE Corp that would lift a ban on buying from U.S. suppliers, allowing China's No. 2… https://t.co/ZFIaC4KM9w https://t.co/HlQOn0zRcH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital bank Revolut to offer customers fee-free share trading: LONDON (Reuters) - British digital-only bank Revolut said on Thursday it is building a commission-free trading platform on its app, its latest bid to use technology to undercut traditional… https://t.co/rYuGmtFnwb https://t.co/iq4n8swx6M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer II – Spectrum Enterprise: CLIENT REFERENCE CODE: ******-1 About Employer Enterprise Employer Enterprise, a part of Charter Communications, is a national provider of scalable, fiber-based technology solutions serving many of America’s… https://t.co/VucucgTdsN https://t.co/cUu45e1oyL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Specialist: *We are unable to sponsor for this permanent Full time role* Prestigious Global Firm is currently seeking a SharePoint Professional with both administration and development skills. Candidate will be building, supporting and… https://t.co/h84NQfzkLl https://t.co/bTRkoiVxWp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alphabet shareholders reject diversity proposal backed by employees: MOUNTAIN VIEW, Calif. (Reuters) - Alphabet Inc's shareholders, including top executives, voted down several proposals on Wednesday, defeating campaigns to tie pay to diversity goals and… https://t.co/kOS7h02N4h https://t.co/gKjSM8Jp7B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fitbit CFO quits to join autonomous vehicle startup: (Reuters) - Wearable device maker Fitbit Inc said Chief Financial Officer William Zerella will leave the company next week to become the finance chief of an autonomous vehicle technology startup. https://t.co/GmpajDL53W https://t.co/TLSghyzubZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Architect – Residential: Saratoga, CA Full-time Compensation Unspecified Posted Today Based in Saratoga, CA, we are an award winning, high-end residential Design/Build Company that builds complex projects. Due to growth, we have an immediate need… https://t.co/MKRHDG6mQp https://t.co/0BP1RfqDvz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full-Stack Software Developer: Requisition ID ******* Job Family US-NY-New York Posting Description Aon is looking for a Full Stack Web Developer As part of an industry-leading team, you will help empower results for our clients by delivering innovative… https://t.co/Etg3DErUJJ https://t.co/IQ0tjLQQhV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MS Software Developer: Job Description M &amp; S Software Developer (17414) Introduction: The Johns Hopkins University Applied Physics Laboratory (APL), a national leader in scientific research and development, located midway between Baltimore and… https://t.co/aGGo8bBHz8 https://t.co/EbSYDRqfJC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EU states, lawmakers agree to cap price of intra-EU calls: BRUSSELS (Reuters) - European Union governments and lawmakers have agreed to cap the price of calling from one EU country to another, seeking to score another political victory with citizens… https://t.co/QpW3DmVZrl https://t.co/bTqsMJjrax]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Data Analyst – Requisition ID R46737: Requisition ID R46737 East Shore 2 (12025), United States of America, Glen Allen, Virginia At Capital One, we’re building a leading information-based technology company. Still founder-led by Chairman and… https://t.co/aUACnKwhiG https://t.co/DyyHq3IJ9z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft launches program for women returning to work: SAN FRANCISCO (Reuters) - Microsoft Corp is stepping up its hiring of women seeking to rejoin the workforce, following a rash of complaints about sexual harassment and gender discrimination at the… https://t.co/JmDg8Go63u https://t.co/ACTzCqjaJg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goldman Sachs backs card issuing, processing startup Marqeta: (Reuters) - Goldman Sachs Group Inc has joined a $45 million investment round in Marqeta, a U.S. fintech company offering technology businesses can use to issue payment cards, the startup said… https://t.co/nHleg0DIff https://t.co/j64cM4p1s0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HFC Performance Engineer, HFC/OSP Engineering: HFC Performance Engineer, HFC/OSP Engineering at Cox Communications Skip Navigation – Careers Home – Call Center – Sales – Early Career – Join Our Talent Community – Blog – Manage Your Profile – Cox… https://t.co/WrsM5BIdcL https://t.co/zCD6z1qayh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TITLE SOFTWARE ENGINEER LEVEL 3 (SS): Careers Center | Software Engineer Level 3 (18) (SS) Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply… https://t.co/AJldYxU7B1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist: What you’ll be doing. If you are curious about new technology and the possibilities it creates, then this job may be perfect for you. As part of the Information Technology team, you will work on new technologies and find ways to meet our… https://t.co/txfcEguxDp https://t.co/WO0cP1YxHL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Project Manager (45974) Job Type: Full Time FTE/Bi-Weekly Hours: 1.0/80 Shift: Days Hours in Shift: 8 Location: Palo Alto, CA Req: 45974 Job Description Job Summary This paragraph summarizes the general nature, level and purpose of the… https://t.co/kGDyLhgVkt https://t.co/JbS4lklfFc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior UI Engineer – JavaScript: 17492BR Job Description and Requirements We are currently hiring a JavaScript Developer to work in Black Duck’s Hub UI Team. In this role, you will report to the Engineering Manager and will be based in our Burlington, MA… https://t.co/TOPVsuWcNc https://t.co/J1peKIVTdQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Washington state sues Facebook, Google over election ad disclosure: SAN FRANCISCO (Reuters) - The state of Washington said on Monday it had sued Facebook Inc and Alphabet Inc's Google, accusing the technology companies of violating state campaign finance… https://t.co/9POwPWboYS https://t.co/m8QcnbBs3D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: SOFTWARE DEVELOPER Design Oracle data marts for d/warehouse. Support existing ETL, Informatica, Kettle (PDI) feeds. Use Oracle, SQL, PL-SQL,AWR reports, Elasticsearch (Kibana); Agile, Waterfall, code review, Git, Jira, Jenkins, etc.… https://t.co/rx9MmezcjA https://t.co/Sct6VauadS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[France's BlaBlaCar bets on Russia's ride-sharing culture: ST PETERSBURG (Reuters) - Russia has overtaken France as the biggest market for French ride-sharing startup BlaBlaCar, a growth driven by long distances between Russian cities and a culture of… https://t.co/zas4eiWZM0 https://t.co/WBaS8QzQz6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Account Development Manager: Use Data To Build The Next Generation Of Sales Professionals: Periscope Data’s mission is to provide the fastest data visualization tool on the market. As a Senior Account Development Manager, you will be responsible… https://t.co/YD446oWYNO https://t.co/qi8QcPO3oB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla's Musk laments Singapore electric vehicle stance: SINGAPORE (Reuters) - Elon Musk, chief executive of U.S. electric vehicle (EV) maker Tesla Inc, defended his view that Singapore was not supportive of EV ownership after a commentary in the… https://t.co/EMvZLYGwHs https://t.co/twr0mcPIpw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SR DEVELOPER – IT: SR DEVELOPER – IT Requisition #: ****** Atlanta, GA OVERVIEW Delta Air Lines has an opportunity for a Senior Developer to work on its mainframe software application development for the travel, airline and reservation industry. In a… https://t.co/p1xVdC5Hmo https://t.co/Fb9tk4bdhF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Project Manager – Plainfield, IL (USA): Logoplaste is currently seeking to recruit an Associate Project Manager, to join the HQ Team in Plainfield, IL (USA). Reporting to: Project Management Director This position provides overall Project… https://t.co/viLhLOJmys https://t.co/frlLcrHqLB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Product Manager: Senior Product Manager at Magic Leap, Inc. Sunnyvale, CA The AI group at Magic Leap is looking for an experienced Product Manager with a background in human-centered product development or design. You will be working alongside the… https://t.co/9zJCAulUKm https://t.co/0Qukrd80n2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Water/Wastewater Project Manager: SNC-Lavalin’s Atkins business is one of the world’s most respected design, engineering and project management consultancies. SNC-Lavalin’s Atkins business has been providing infrastructure planning, engineering,… https://t.co/fSkZg1fYfL https://t.co/EVV8ok0GUl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Automated Tester, Senior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: El Segundo, CA Job Type: Engineering, Information Technology, Science Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 5/24/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to… https://t.co/3al9PESKf1 https://t.co/33DO1TAzkh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fingerprint Cards announces new cost cuts amid weak market, price pressure: STOCKHOLM (Reuters) - Swedish biometrics firm Fingerprint Cards on Monday announced a new round of big cost cuts on the back of weak market conditions for capacitive sensors for… https://t.co/DvxoVgWwwX https://t.co/fWie0cWhTQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Cloud Developer: Java Cloud Developer ==================== Req #: ******_80010Location: Aurora, CO USJob Category: EngineeringSecurity Clearance: TS/SCIClearance Status: Must Be Current Job Description Make a Difference! BIT Systems, a CACI Company,… https://t.co/pQy503f1IA https://t.co/66eCyMdwYC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IAM Developer: Jobs Toggle navigation * Sign In * Sign Up * Help Career Portal * Failure Message Cannot parse, seems some issue with the profile, please create the profile manually Alert Message Job Post has been updated successfully * Position Title –… https://t.co/IzWz1BfbDB https://t.co/E5i02lnM28]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software and stealth: how carmakers hike spare parts prices: LONDON/PARIS (Reuters) - Carmakers including Renault, Jaguar Land Rover and Peugeot have boosted revenues by over $1 billion in the past decade by using sophisticated pricing software,… https://t.co/pDQByx9Mi8 https://t.co/QQG8zYN7di]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Job Description Tracking Code PRGVAB-10 Job Description We are looking for a software developer to work on projects to support customer solutions and deliver cutting edge designs in audio, video and visual display/processor… https://t.co/jAbTARtxue https://t.co/dWob9KFZ2v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior DevOps Engineer: 605 is looking for experienced devops engineers who can help us build a devops culture, with infrastructure automation owned by the whole engineering team. Our work is in optimizing advertising and programming for the television… https://t.co/a0ZJXQZU6F https://t.co/pTZ6e2ZucF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Were looking for a talented back-end software engineer at Cache Ventures to help develop and manage our growing products. As we grow, we want to continue hiring dedicated and passionate people who share the same beliefs we have about… https://t.co/0K0FjA6r2k https://t.co/OoD54QTAii]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Technology Project Manager, Mid: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Bethesda, MD Job Type: Management Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 5/23/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest… https://t.co/oIC5iMLRpj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Specialist Systems Engineer/Programmer – Electronic Communications: WE ARE BNY MELLON!’ BNY Mellon is a global investments company dedicated to helping its clients manage and service their financial assets throughout the investment lifecycle. Whether… https://t.co/OBCTbAX5AL https://t.co/z8ZzZYIJqs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House says Trump nominates Geoffrey Starks to FCC: WASHINGTON (Reuters) - President Donald Trump named Geoffrey Starks as his pick to become a member of the Federal Communications Commission for the remainder of a five-year term ending June 30,… https://t.co/tIf2j3B2z4 https://t.co/GWZA3TVj97]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical – Staff Instructor Manager: Staff Instructor Manager (multiple positions) sought by General Electric Company in San Ramon, CA to provide product tech training to internal, partner &amp; customer audiences. Reqs Bachelor’s deg, or foreign degree… https://t.co/1hiF7ohfyI https://t.co/8z1fnNbsd1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple to debut phone-to-phone augmented reality: sources: SAN FRANCISCO (Reuters) - Apple Inc next week will debut tools to let two iPhone users share augmented reality while limiting the personal data sent to its servers, two people familiar with the… https://t.co/LkeREbsPuE https://t.co/WFjufABSfh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer: Engineer: Bendix Commercial Vehicle Systems LLC, Engineer 2, Test, Irvine, CA. Design, develop and test automation, intelligent systems, industrial systems control, and coordinate and provide engineering support to conduct standard and… https://t.co/9U0p5vHduT https://t.co/AqZNGtZict]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Mobile Developer: We are changing the way people communicate around the world! Our technology enables customer service to engage specialized services providing live collaboration solution utilizing real-time audio, text, and video. As a… https://t.co/GDOGyFw1ux https://t.co/JjdDASyO9i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World's top wealth fund backs activist proposals at Facebook meeting: OSLO (Reuters) - Norway's $1 trillion wealth fund backed a wide range of activist shareholder proposals at Facebook's annual meeting on Thursday, including a measure to improve the… https://t.co/0jfuiBYCa8 https://t.co/eIGKTUJuGu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Systems Engineer: 109814BR Principal Systems Engineer VA – Chantilly, VA – Herndon, VA – McLean, VA – Reston 109814BR Raytheon Intelligence Information an Services, a leader in CNO/CNE, is seeking quality Senior Systems Engineers who are… https://t.co/gI4E6TthVH https://t.co/NwwMRHFFXA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Las Vegas, NV Full-time $90k – $120k Posted Today If you are a Project Manager with experience, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us We are a rapidly expanding Commercial General Contractor specializing in $500K – $5M construction… https://t.co/4QbG9q7QxH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Program Operations Manager, DellEMC: Program Operations Manager, DellEMC Job Location US-CA-San Francisco Req No. 2018-2380 Category Vendor Relations/Marketing Overview Are you an expert with DellEMC products and services? Is Marketing your passion? As… https://t.co/jytnMVuXKU https://t.co/Pqix99lGrY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Senior Developer with strong DB experience: Req ID: 16819 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The quality, integrity, and commitment of our employees are key factors in our company’s growth,… https://t.co/9e6sLey4DT https://t.co/Gv4K8Br8HQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google's 'Reserve' tool winning converts, taking search to next level: SAN FRANCISCO (Reuters) - Alphabet Inc's Google is drawing thousands of new customers to gyms and salons each month through an appointment-booking tool released last year, Reuters has… https://t.co/ZXd2BcbvhV https://t.co/k5z4x57Blw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Software Engineer: CBRE Company Profile About CBRE (NYSE: CBG): At CBRE, you are empowered to take your career path into your own hands. Enjoy workplace flexibility in a global organization with tremendous scale. Work in an inclusive and… https://t.co/oMS181eOgU https://t.co/WEsnCkTI16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nordic countries oppose EU plans for digital tax on firms' turnover: BRUSSELS (Reuters) - Finance ministers of the European Union's three Nordic countries have urged their partners to shelve a plan to tax large corporations for their digital turnover,… https://t.co/Gm7ERjn5b3 https://t.co/1zOvvPJGfp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: LinkedIn Corp. has openings in our Mtn View, CA location for Software Engineer (All Levels/Types) (SWE0518MV) Design, develop &amp; integrate cutting-edge software technologies; Manager, Site Reliability (6597.1170) Oversee a team of… https://t.co/5LydJ3idFR https://t.co/QF0lByzIkY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waymo to get more than 60,000 cars from Fiat Chrysler for robotaxis: (Reuters) - Fiat Chrysler Automobiles NV will add up to 62,000 more cars to Alphabet Inc's autonomous driving unit Waymo, the companies said on Thursday, as part of Waymo's plan to roll… https://t.co/QKSOSwS0uX https://t.co/60uSc3jSv0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All Source Intelligence Analyst: Req ID 92497BR Business Title All Source Intelligence Analyst Group MCIS Location USA VIRGINIA Reston Clearance Level Needed TS/SCI Category Intelligence Job Duties and Responsibilities Currently, ManTech is seeking a… https://t.co/dtxtS9Y5w7 https://t.co/fzhf10HNpZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Telegram says Apple has prevented it from updating since April: MOSCOW (Reuters) - Apple has prevented the Telegram messaging service from updating globally ever since Russia ordered Apple to remove the service from its stores, Telegram's CEO and founder… https://t.co/5cAPIPjKIv https://t.co/GMRjsogXx1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid-Level Software Engineer, Python: Req ID : 430773BR Job Code/Title : E1074:Software Engineer Stf Job Description : Are you looking for an exciting career as a Software Engineer at one of the top Aerospace and Defense Companies? A fulfilling position… https://t.co/8zQ6BNjPrs https://t.co/RHJjD6DRa8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr–ERP-Analyst—SAP-Supply-Chain—Richmond–Va: Sr. ERP Analyst – SAP Supply Chain – Richmond, Va 501 South 5th St Richmond, Virginia, 23219-0501 United States How you will impact WestRock: – Work as an effective team member in various situations as… https://t.co/ySO3j3xgfj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java UI Developer: Java UI Developer Ref No.: 18-21323 Location: Des Moines, Iowa Role Description- We are looking for an experienced IT configuration analyst to be part of a high-performing team, where innovation and collaboration are key. Our ideal… https://t.co/LoBSklESlf https://t.co/Q2Z4SddhtO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon cuts Australia from its U.S. site to avoid sales import tax: SYDNEY (Reuters) - https://t.co/s2foRsMat5 Inc said on Thursday it will force Australians to use its Australian website instead of its much larger U.S. site from July 1 to avoid a new… https://t.co/8rmJ2kRmoe https://t.co/MvAkUjCtG2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Security DevOps Engineer: Job Description What you’ll be doing… Do you have one foot planted in the security realm, the other in DevOps automation, and the third in the AWS cloud? When someone mentions an AWS service, is the first thing you think… https://t.co/tyF3rOCCu1 https://t.co/lD1eZue2QM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer, Chip Design: Samsung Austin Semiconductor LLC has multiple openings in San Jose, CA: Engineer, Chip Design Methodology to design, develop and/or test verification tools for graphics chips in conjunction with hardware product development for the… https://t.co/g2Dm1K4fPE https://t.co/39pC0EvSUP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. judge dismisses Kaspersky suits to overturn government ban: (Reuters) - A U.S. federal judge on Wednesday dismissed two lawsuits by Moscow-based Kaspersky Lab that sought to overturn bans on the use of the security software maker's products in U.S.… https://t.co/d02BYvycGB https://t.co/AlwHpd0mBX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mapbox partners Microsoft, Intel to provide self-driving car maps: (Reuters) - Mapping startup Mapbox Inc said on Wednesday it is teaming up with Microsoft Corp, Intel Corp and Softbank Group Corp's ARM Holdings chip unit to deepen its push into… https://t.co/qN3VChH9k0 https://t.co/fnbvJh2dm0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology: TECHNOLOGY Interested candidates send resume to: Google LLC, PO Box 26184 San Francisco, CA 94126 Attn: A. Johnson. Please reference job # below: Solutions Consultant (Mountain View, CA) Define feature sets for implementation of Google… https://t.co/6nFgwCY97l https://t.co/NCkH2e4loe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook's size no barrier to deals in new areas: executive: RANCHO PALOS VERDES, Calif. (Reuters) - Facebook Inc believes it could acquire other large companies without running afoul of antitrust enforcers if the world's largest social media network… https://t.co/00UU4dhrl4 https://t.co/51p12JcHon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering: ENGINEERING: Synaptics, Inc. has multiple openings in San Jose, CA. Software Engineer: build up chained secure flash boot flow on ARM v7/v8 architecture SOC Senior Software Engineer: design multimedia framework incl. AVIN, VPP, VDEC… https://t.co/6ZCQh5G8Wj https://t.co/tJCOqE2lmD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Venture firm Atomico signs up ex-Uber and Google managers: LONDON (Reuters) - Atomico, which runs Europe’s largest independent venture fund, has hired former managers from Google and Uber to help drive international expansion for its portfolio of more… https://t.co/RcK1uJEQHv https://t.co/J611sHPjgd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consultant: AVIATION The Boeing Company in Seal Beach, CA seeks Authorized Representative to conduct compliance findings against structural repairs on the 777 aircraft fuselage components. Position req MS degree (or foreign equiv) in Engineering, or… https://t.co/7Do8UONScp https://t.co/apVxB9wXLh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As inflation soars, Facebook drives trading in Argentina's barter clubs: SAN MIGUEL, Argentina (Reuters) - At an abandoned train station in Buenos Aires' working-class suburb of San Miguel, hundreds of Argentines gather with bags of clothes, rice, flour… https://t.co/IPI8hUdfuc https://t.co/sg3hPNkdvj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ASE Senior Software Developer: Job Description If you are a technology driven individual who loves to create cutting edge software, this is the career opportunity for you. The Advanced Solutions Engineering (ASE) directorate is responsible for conducting… https://t.co/8Hjayae5p1 https://t.co/dgdzviYhX0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer Integrator I: Purpose of JobWe are currently seeking talented Software Developer &amp; Integrator I for our San Antonio, TX (Vista Corporate Center) facility. Software Developers and Integrators (SDIs) are engaged in all phases of the… https://t.co/NQ0ObeiDxc https://t.co/0cd3qRupQ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LO Applicator Master:   Job Description – LO Applicator Master (18002493) LO Applicator Master Requisition ID : 18002493 Location : United States-California-El Segundo US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation Assistance: No relocation… https://t.co/tEwq4DauPH https://t.co/zuPMWUlZ2F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intelligent Automation (RPA) Client Executive: Intelligent Automation (RPA) Client Executive Location US-IL-Chicago Employment Type Permanent Position Description/Responsibilities (CCC/Vendor) The Intelligent Automation Client Executive is responsible… https://t.co/2DzXXPdVFb https://t.co/ujJOQ27lk3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mobike to scrap China user deposit in bike-sharing race: BEIJING (Reuters) - Mobike, one of the world's biggest bike-sharing companies, is doing away with deposits for all customers in China, amid fierce battle to win users. https://t.co/OxrmQjmxFK https://t.co/N9kwn48Jqd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Front End Web Developer: About GoDaddy GoDaddy powers the world’s largest cloud platform dedicated to small, independent ventures. With nearly 17 million customers worldwide and over 73 million domain names under management, GoDaddy is the place… https://t.co/XwkSNjWq4u https://t.co/9HqW1jDZ4r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Requisition Title Solutions Architect Global Technology Practice: Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome page… https://t.co/idBGUAPsLh https://t.co/ALkKPurgeK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager Security Solutions Cypress CA: **Project Manager – Security Solutions – Cypress CA** Locations:Cypress, California Job Family: Engineering New Search English (US) **Job Description** **Division:** Building Technologies **Business Unit:**… https://t.co/UdmS2478k1 https://t.co/nd4RXQWDc9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agile Coach: Agile Coach Ref No.: 18-29050 Location: Agoura Hills, California Position: Agile Coach Job Location: Agoura Hills, CA Job Title: Full time permanent – First level Scrum Master certification (PSM I, CSM ) and coaching experience – Scaled… https://t.co/Grz5l9l1la https://t.co/StT50JfWmc]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>