<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Building some new layers on this painting. It's coming along just fine, I am liking whats happening so far :) http://t.co/xPXURGxQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This will be finished, and on display at the Roundhouse for the SubmiT fundraiser event November 1st. http://t.co/UKR3hUkA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[workin on my fifth abstract piece. i really like where this is going. I should prob finish one of these 5 tho..ha http://t.co/gmdstc1a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This panther piece now has some tone and colour. I really dig the effects I've gotten on this layer. http://t.co/ZhqjNxiI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just sold this piece - def one of my faves of the latest batch. http://t.co/EHw2w3mO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is my design for this year's SubmiT fundraiser - these will be sold to raise funds on November 1at the Roundhouse http://t.co/vjTrIDHf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yellllllowwwww (I posted this earlier today but it disappeared !!) ahhhh http://t.co/9pyf9fL1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the start to my first painting on wood. I'm already loving the textures and colours of the surface.. http://t.co/S7Mae79D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm digging the little progress I've made to this new abstract. It'll take a bit longer as its larger, 36" x 36" http://t.co/gt1m0zpg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some new layers on this abstract painting. I am starting to really dig the layers that are building up! http://t.co/6DstpK3I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[abstract paintings are great cuz they let u take sweet angle shots :) http://t.co/dT8IFvyG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cocoramone thanks! ill get it wrapped up in a couple weeks (at most) im hoping!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this sketch of woodwards for a new experimental painting - pretty stoked http://t.co/uaZWYHe9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[experimenting with the effects of combining ink and alcohol. Take that any way you please:)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you ever seen a panther on three canvases before?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[393 Powell street, in an amazing place called octopus studios!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you are at Main and Broadway tomorrow, I will be painting @birdonawireart from 11-4, 2535 Main Street. New piece for #culturecrawl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @andreaarmstrong: 1 week + 1 day until the #culturecrawl!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Culture Crawl!!! - starts one week from today! Setting up the studio, varnishing originals, matting and framing prints #culturecrawl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@janetsmitharts hey whats shakin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two upcoming works for the culture crawl next weekend - these work so well as a set dont you think? http://t.co/V6mXvYXl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm digging this piece more and more as I refine the colour layers http://t.co/0Yxl83fm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Culture Crawl in just over a week!!
Check out the preview of my works:
http://t.co/WVpATWWe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I should show u them and discuss it at the crawl if u can make it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DusanPos that'd be great! im really stoked for the crawl-got a new series of abstract work and prints available of the most popular animals]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet!! 393 Powell street - octopus studios :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DusanPos thx! It was really fun. Chilled after with a couple artists for some wind down. What a great way to spend a work night :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DusanPos first place :) it was pretty rad there, got vibes, intimate crowd interaction and high spirits :) got
Kinda sweaty tho..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right after round 1. Damn it was hot inside, I was sweating! http://t.co/dppRafks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this is the coolest blending of senses - i love how he "listens to paintings" at an art gallery..... http://t.co/DgHgRBdz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Art Battle tonight at Raw Canvas. Lookin forward to making 20 min paintings. Here's the details, hope you can make it! http://t.co/hBejXuf1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tomorrow night im participating in an Art Battle at Raw Canvas. If you wanna come see what I will paint (in 20... http://t.co/QbLYMSFv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great, great, great night at the Roundhouse tonight. The SubmiT show was huge - cant wait to hear how much $$ was... http://t.co/oAUd8Esy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damn that was a quality cup of trail mixes :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mermaidwhimsy at which - woodwards, or the roundhouse?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[check out this painting i made of the woodwards building here in vancouver :) http://t.co/eJu6g1iK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is my submission for the SubmiT fundraiser tomorrow at the Yaletown Roundhouse. I'm happy with how it turned... http://t.co/UFexQDIu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm pretty stoked that the culture crawl is comin up soon - getting these reproductions all ready for sale :) http://t.co/LgWz0Y9K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This commission piece is all finished and well-documented now. I like the last touches, the whiskers :) http://t.co/U6LrFCHI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[just finished this latest commission ! do you like jungle cats? its painted on three canvases which i like http://t.co/MH1mwRQf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[cool studio shot :) http://t.co/vOfJWe6V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My newest painting is really coming together. Lots to finish still, but its taking shape in a bright and happy way http://t.co/7darwHqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Abstract #7 on the way. the contrasting blue/white is really exciting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is some updated progress on this abstract piece. I'm going to really push negative vs. positive space in... http://t.co/9goHwG6a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @submiTvancouver: Puppies! Read about @jonshawpainting's perfect day in Vancouver: http://t.co/WWP4k3Gi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LisaRosaPenz thanks for followin me, those are some pretty rad images you've put together !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Abstract.07
36" x 36"
Ink and acrylic on canvas
(stage one) http://t.co/SilYpcMx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhysioCS done deal mate!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@misoofilan hey rad images!! i really like the one on the couch.. !!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhysioCS hey thanks for followin! im an artist - check these out:
http://t.co/QMhQK6Gm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lately I've experimented with lots of texture, colour, new materials etc - tonight I started cutting out some... http://t.co/rSXsU9Jm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nope still here my friend!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haha this is a hilarious pic of me from the H'Arts Fundraiser two weekends ago

http://t.co/O0SjMGdP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a video of me making a painting in 20 minutes. My favourite part is 13:20 haha... http://t.co/B8L8Yp6X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks so much! Just doin what I love, I can't stop!! Haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holiday cards? http://t.co/csf387N2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Might be my favourite painting to date.

http://t.co/NpImtW8Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Upcoming show and sale at my studio! Let's hang out and I'll show you art and feed you snacks and hot beverages! http://t.co/XYUt83QE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook http://t.co/8ec7aZVF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stage Three (FINISHED) - Heavier translucent paint layers and heavier/thicker highlights. More ink work and... http://t.co/qGmafv57]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stage Two - First layer paint washes and some heavier linework http://t.co/8ybjIrdr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Piece:

Stage One - Ink Drawing http://t.co/hKmAyY5M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@artsbcdotorg amazing! i send out emails whenever i finish a new piece or have a show invite. ya ive had a good run of sales lately!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@artsbcdotorg rad! i like to share it with as many people as possible :) any feedback is grand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@artsbcdotorg hey there - thanks for the follow! have you seen my works? http://t.co/QMhQK6Gm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Olga Rybalko and I painted this at Fortune Sound Club tonight. Painting on a team was really cool. I also like... http://t.co/A62ZKas7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@findingmandy ah! It's so new it's not up yet! I'll b updating the site tomorrow or wed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@findingmandy thanks! thats the second in a new series of vancouver-urban works on wood panel. they are really shaping up well. more comin!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@findingmandy thats ok it happens every year! it was a great time, my first crawl!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New city inspired painting on wood - very stoked about this new series:

http://t.co/b7E8B9Cx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@findingmandy im getting into the art battles. a couple fundraiser shows, the crawl just happened and a new studio! couple xmas shows too!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't wait!! So much cool art stuff happening!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live Painting Battle and Fundraiser this monday night at Fortune Sound Club - I'm competing on team 2 for the... http://t.co/BGjvby1V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be live painting this monday night at Fortune - three teams of 2, one wicked competition. Details coming shortly :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's the beginning of a new urban piece on wood panel. This is definitely going to turn into a series.

https://t.co/Aida9kT2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No prob mate! Glad it's in good hands!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm working on a new vancouver neighbourhood-based piece starting tonight. I'll be finishing it Friday at the... http://t.co/XpZfvz34]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted 8 photos on Facebook in the album "Art Battle 37 @ Raw Canvas" http://t.co/ivHXODoy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[thanks everybody for comin out to the culture crawl. it was a mega-good time, very successful, and super cool.... http://t.co/MyrS2zrr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for the plug friend!! I love this studio!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[last day of the culture crawl today - im over at 393 powell street, if you can make it out to see my newest work :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks friend! Glad you like it so much!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight is the first of three days of the #CultureCrawl - you are invited to my studio, 393 Powell street, at octopus studios. Stokedddd!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YapesPaints @aCageyBee @ChristiYork @NorbergArt @fiveleftleather @CultureCrawl just wrapping up the set up tonight! lookin good in there :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @natilydenise: Fancy new archival envelopes for my fancy new pieces! #culturecrawl http://t.co/zlpHUbRP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Abstract.06 is finished! I'm really happy with the end result. I'm varnishing and hanging this piece for @CultureCrawl http://t.co/vvU5N4YB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Abstract #06 - all finished up. I'll be hanging it in my space tonight, so that YOU can come see it at the crawl... http://t.co/Nr3ZXmin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Abstract #06 - all finished up. I'll be hanging it in my space tonight, so that YOU can come see it at the crawl... http://t.co/Vk11BaQy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NoahNJBowman lookin good mate!! Busy next couple of days..:)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reproductions all ready and packed to show and sell @CultureCrawl in just three days :) http://t.co/n5LXxejI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Almost done! Come this and my other new abstract pieces at the #CultureCrawl !! Mannnnn I'm excited for this weekend! http://t.co/vmONOQvc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have my reproductions all packaged and ready to sell at the Culture Crawl. Wouldnt have gotten them done if it... http://t.co/sGah8hyk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got all my reproductions matted and packaged up for the #CultureCrawl - come and get one this weekend @ 393 Powell st! http://t.co/s30vKUGD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@katieruddell i thought i was gettin free tea..turns out it was empty tins? what a tease :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a new city piece in progress, for an upcoming show at Pendulum Gallery. Painting this tomorrow. http://t.co/Nc9hmNfQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm excited for my second opus demo tomorrow, 2-4pm, in the downtown Vancouver store]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NoahNJBowman thanks mate!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[cards cards cards cards :)

http://t.co/CB3zHPzV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MichaelTsouras: #Toronto, #TTC, #subway, #blackandwhite, #draw, #drawinglive, #portrait, #face, #Woman, #sketch, #sketchbook http:// ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 friends and I are hosting a show starting January 18th at the Gam Gallery here in Vancouver. Details here:

http://t.co/seefCjpH]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>