<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Mama always said you could tell an awful lot about a person by the kind of shoes they wear. - Forrest Gump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cowboys, Mavs, Rangers and more read about the Sports teams of the Dallas Fort-Worth Metroplex - http://t.co/FfDBhguTTa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding the Right Fitness Gadgets  http://t.co/bMzGngVFpg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Faster, faster, faster, until the thrill of speed overcomes the fear of death --  - Hunter Thompson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man with a lot of money may be a bad egg, but folks seldom take offense until he is broke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thousands of years ago, cats were worshipped as gods. Cats have never forgotten this. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yo, dudes. Got a new tourney lined up. We're playing for the last of the deodorant sticks. Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is an ornament in prosperity and a refuge in adversity.  - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep your face to the sunshine and you cannot see the shadows. - Helen Keller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome camping t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the camping lovers in your life!  http://t.co/cII1Oq6m07]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Some Very Interesting and Unusual Beers  http://t.co/6FJs6PlBIV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You cannot put the same shoe on every foot. - Publilius Syrus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[History of Mojang - The makers of Minecraft - http://t.co/PNI1JM03Fd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education costs money, but then so does ignorance. - Sir Claus Moser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Religion Both Protestant and Catholics  http://t.co/UzpkvH69VB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dis Be Da Place]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's basically the same, just darker. - Alan Kulwicki, on racing Saturday nights as opposed to Sunday afternoons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Link Building With Social Media Sites  http://t.co/V31yGNCJ9w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Adam Faith  http://t.co/QPSv6yA9Cz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Saving Money With Solar Power  http://t.co/Zfygooap6q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Dave Mason  http://t.co/pQkkESOUhn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live the Thug Life with These Temporary Tattoos! http://t.co/bHLs1GZK9H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gold Glitter Lips - Cool Look!  http://t.co/mShkbHXWcT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is that which discloses to the wise and disguises from the foolish their lack of understanding. - Ambrose Bierce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I look at modeling as something I'm doing for black people in general. Naomi Campbell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is what happens to you when you're busy making other plans - John Lennon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The difference between gossip and news is whether you hear it or tell it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like my money right where I can see it -- hanging in my closet. - Carrie Bradshaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction To http://t.co/zW5CF5HKyr  http://t.co/Saht3tusin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Media are tools.  Real time is mindset.  David Scott - Marketing Strategist - Author of The New Rules of Marketing and PR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you love sports?  Read about the great sports teams of the Northern California Bay Area!  http://t.co/o6MIzPNLWS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is not preparation for life; education is life itself. - John Dewey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sky is no longer the limit. - Richard M. Nixon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money was never a big motivation for me, except as a way to keep score. The real excitement is playing the game. - Donald Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL A Toilet Mug for your Coffee!  http://t.co/FVNHiU4hqr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So now I'm left with cigarettes, and I'm trying to scrape that off my shoe and then I'll be done. - Diane Lane]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome baseball t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the baseball lovers in your life!   http://t.co/dnj1KsxFOd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to ABBA  http://t.co/IzO7THGt35]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dream house is one that cost twice as much as you ever dreamed it would…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overwhelming underdogs. - Yogi Berra While Referring to the 1969 New York Mets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Bangles  http://t.co/bAJ7Wu6Adt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learning is what most adults will do for a living in the 21st century. - Perelman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoever said that money can't buy happiness, simply didn't know where to go shopping --&gt; Bo Derek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Politicians should read science fiction, not westerns and detective stories. - Arthur C. Clarke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know anything about music. In my line you don't have to.  - Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Options for Using Slimmers and Trimmers for Weight Loss  http://t.co/DR03JSz9iP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is like a poker game, nobody wants to quit when he's losing: nobody wants you to quit when you're ahead. - Jackie Robinson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stiletto, I look at it more as an attitude as opposed to a high-heeled shoe. - Lita Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hit the ball over the fence and you can take your time going around the bases. - John W. Raper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the History of the Periodic Chart  http://t.co/hEGLHGNP0p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Magic texting glove with conductive yarn finger tips for iPhone, iPad and all touch screen devices - 4 colors  --&gt; http://t.co/AvA3H868VW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we can't live together, then we're going to die alone. - Jack Shephard, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay, that thing in the woods, maybe it's a monster, maybe it's a pissed off giraffe, I don't know. Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the darkness of the world cannot put out the light on one small candle. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LinkedIn for Your Company Proves to be Effective  http://t.co/cC1dQnEoJB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where there is an open mind, there will always be a frontier. - Charles F. Kettering]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Bert Kaempfert  http://t.co/os3wEEWbdB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never, never, never, never give up. - Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Invest in Penny Stocks And Earn Huge Profits  http://t.co/dgXYKnuG7d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Michael Jordan Shoes  http://t.co/xLkYdWFpg4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must either modify your dreams or magnify your skills. - Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Genesis  http://t.co/HnLTna4Cjb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michael, I did nothing. I did absolutely nothing, and it was everything that I thought it could be. - Peter Gibbons, Office Space]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can do anything, but lay off my blue suede shoes - Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL - Cool - A Computer Mouse with a Spider in it!   http://t.co/kg4ZKrDSW1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to WordTracker SEO Tools http://t.co/0ZQtgNsq4F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On of life's little ironies is the fact that when you finally master a tough job, you make it look easy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Andy Gibb  http://t.co/apj9Qjfmg2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good pitching will beat good hitting any time, and vice versa. - Bob Veale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lifetime of training for just ten seconds. - Jesse Owens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman is the only hunter who uses herself for bait]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is a thousand times better to have common sense without education than to have education without common sense. - Robert Green Ingersoll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the Icebound Land by John Flanagan  http://t.co/pDS2secWbf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get up to Speed on Baseball with this Summary of Baseball Positions  http://t.co/z5XysEzYqR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must do the thing you think you cannot do. - Eleanor Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't be melancholy in fashion because people don't respond to it. - Isaac Mizrahi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Top Secrets for Using Facebook Pages for Your Business  http://t.co/ATTOmSzzvu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nolan Ryan is pitching much better now that he has his curve ball straightened out. - Joe Garagiola]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only thing that ever sat its way to success was a hen. - Sarah Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Dave Mason  http://t.co/pQkkESOUhn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Mac and Katie Kissoon  http://t.co/FUA5aq1BDf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to War  http://t.co/lQRbaMGMMe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never wear the same shoe twice. - Dion Sanders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people are like angels - always harping on something!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not the mistakes in life that are important; it's what we learn from them. - Donna Guthrie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spring is when you feel like whistling even with a shoe full of slush. - Doug Larson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never make fun of the geeks, one day they will be your boss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DC Comics Ultimate Character Guide http://t.co/wvlmm2J2zz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One is never over - or underdressed with a little black dress. - Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are going to turn this team around 360 degrees. Jason Kidd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stiletto, I look at it more as an attitude as opposed to a high-heeled shoe. - Lita Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweatpants are a sign of defeat. You lost control of your life so you bought some sweatpants. --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I see a pair of shoes I adore, and it doesn't matter if they have them in my size. I buy them anyway. - Keira Knightley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Lesley Gore  http://t.co/5mfYtndRbH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dogs are not our whole life, but they make our lives whole. - Roger Caras]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's rough to go through life with your contents looking as if they settled during shipping. - Milton Berle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We didn't lose the game; we just ran out of time. - Vince Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never argue with the data. - Sheen, Jimmy Neutron]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flattery, like perfume, should be smelled, not swallowed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this very cool bed fan - cools right under the covers! http://t.co/HKUU1s6B3e]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>