<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[A Buyer is nothing more than a solution to a Seller's problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Decluttering everything right now.   Nature abhors a vacuum.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JillSlattery: West Van detached home prices (a hot pocket of foreign investment) has dropped over 13% in 6 months. #VanRE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CKNW: Home sales drop by 39.5% in January compared to last year @Gordmac980 reports #bcre #VanRE #housing https://t.co/hyWtBqTeil https…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nationalpost: Vancouver home sales plunge 40% — and prices are beginning to follow https://t.co/TxTsh79pNC #business https://t.co/GAr80…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @georgiastraight: More than 3,000 new #Vancouver homes envisioned in draft plan for False Creek Flats industrial area https://t.co/XDMi4…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheGoogleFactz: How To Change Your Life In Just 4 Weeks https://t.co/W8APYhOUqQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beer league hockey update.   I returned from missing 2 games with a lower body injury.  We lost 4-2.   Got a helper.  #contributing #always]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @bcassessment: How do we assess properties? Watch: https://t.co/iPjyIv6G9g [VIDEO] #assessment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @I_W_M: #OnThisDay 1945: Soviet troops liberate Auschwitz. Liberation Day by Edith Birkin. #WW2 © The artist https://t.co/Ui3Qmbhk0s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BIVnews: Ivanhoé Cambridge sells Oakridge Centre to local developers
https://t.co/9GtizTzjKv  
#retail #YvrRE https://t.co/u6c36PI8DS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep. https://t.co/iUZJHhfgNX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NatObserver: Vancouver’s housing market third most expensive in the world: survey /via @globeandmail https://t.co/vxDE1I5xce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump. https://t.co/NdBc6U35wO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It my father's 80th birthday today.   Happy Birthday Theo!   You are truly the best!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now following @POTUS.  Here we go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NEWS1130: Inauguration Day: Trump to become America's 45th president
https://t.co/sWZRWMCJzZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I broke all of my New Years resolutions within the first 2 hours of the start of the year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Houston - we have a problem. https://t.co/LLd93VtA9x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @realDonaldTrump: There is an incredible spirit of optimism sweeping the country right now—we're bringing back the JOBS! https://t.co/BN…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Moving. Soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Fact: The scent that lingers after a nice rain is called "petrichor."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Yukon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting my players in place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @thegooglefact: More than 90% of people are no longer friends with someone that they once called their best friend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @derekgrech: Downtown Vancouver lifestyle for $4,688,000. #Vancouver #luxuryrealestate #luxuryhomes #vancity https://t.co/9mxcl7BL76]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HuffPostCanada: New Brunswick renames places with the word 'Negro' in them https://t.co/LRWYCjHfy7 https://t.co/jWymCHg5py]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's March, 2017.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heading back to Vancouver tomorrow night.   My timing could be excellent. https://t.co/kc18f84JHc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @realDonaldTrump: The media has not reported that the National Debt in my first month went down by $12 billion vs a $200 billion increas…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The KK. https://t.co/FASHLq4ySq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was at the Whitehorse snow sculpting contest today.  Some cool stuff. #Rendezvous https://t.co/JdB6ldsXPr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@flyairnorth misplaced my luggage on the way to the Yukon. That's a first for me.  Suzanne was awesome getting things sorted out. Thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a burlesque show in Whitehorse.   It's interesting. #Rendezvous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CTVNews: Last BlackBerry-designed phone with physical keyboard to hit stores in April https://t.co/YFTJ4Evz59 https://t.co/XMObhc87oz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Tweets2Motivate: Problems are like washing machines. They twist us, spin us, &amp; knock us around, but in the end we always come out clean…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heading to the Yukon on Friday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WhatTheFFacts: The richest man ever lived John D. Rockefeller had a fortune of $663,400,000,000 in today's money.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beer league game update. Played last night.   Tied 2-2 after OT. Jamie Benn-like @mikekermode with the SO winner.  Another game tommorow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @globeandmail: Americans buy existing homes at fastest pace in a decade https://t.co/9Tozx7QrgT from @GlobeBusiness https://t.co/ZzF2CgF…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['More' by Phish, The MORE Project https://t.co/SdCB8XdcdZ via @YouTube  Great song and montage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Effects of foreign homebuyer tax on home prices vary by region, MLS data shows https://t.co/lnA5MS6moV And it may get worse...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having gnocchi at Trilussa Pizza and Pane. https://t.co/XboDYeVNPs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GlobalBC: B.C. overdose toll at 116 for January https://t.co/66JyfWBw65]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TIME: BlackBerry now has a 0% share of the smartphone market https://t.co/JeVpbOwdsb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @VancityBuzz: It's the final call! Today is the last day to skate at #Robson Square for the season https://t.co/dWu8yAfnAi https://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Altus_Group: Altus Group and St. Francis Xavier University Announce Innovative Technology Collaboration Agreement https://t.co/qsWVwnVf…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @VancouverSun: The new tool to fight fentanyl: a nasal spray that stops overdoses in their tracks https://t.co/8EHeZlebKk https://t.co/P…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me with my nephew at Robson Sq.   First time on skates.   I never fell once.   #UncleBen https://t.co/n6vYpaVVxQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikekermode Stop hogging the scoring title.   Share the wealth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taking my nephew Sam ice skating for the first time on #FamilyDay.  #UncleBen #PowerForward https://t.co/b4Dz9lo3R3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salmon sandwich and a side salad.   I don't normally order a side salad so I thought I would tweet this out. https://t.co/LyguTYZHOR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@mkmolnar: Five minutes each for FIGHTING! https://t.co/Ro9iZMdTli".  St. Mike's boy. @SMCS1852]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A closed 7-11.   Now I've seen everything. https://t.co/NSPkNoJCfU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @thegooglefact: The expiration date on water bottles is for the bottle, not the water.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's one way to catch rain water. https://t.co/BQitxe4SCF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sounds challenging.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MaxTraining_WW: Your present circumstances don't determine where you can go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NEWS1130: No winning ticket for Friday night's $33 million Lotto Max jackpot: https://t.co/YPK5TAsNc6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheLOAWorld: You are a creator. You can create and achieve anything that you put your mind to. What you focus on expands. Focus on what…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back in the day. https://t.co/tHgDUCcBjW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ThompsonSustain: "90 percent of all millionaires become so through owing real estate." ~ Andrew Carnegie https://t.co/HBENWtZDkr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @globalnews: RCMP constables are paid $50,674 per year when they join the national police force. https://t.co/BleReNfnY9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BBHwest: Metro Vancouver hit 8-year low of new home listings in March: REBGV: https://t.co/6pRA4tM9LU  #vanre https://t.co/h4S1m1cQFl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The arm hurts like a son of a gun. https://t.co/erQawD4OIk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need a haircut.  Anyone have a recommendation for a hair stylist in Vancouver?   Do tell...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/2dTEKzt3f1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[11:11]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Current status of my elbow. Night before a big beer league game.   Game 1 of the playoffs.   Still playin'. #TheCup https://t.co/UolPDaeJIV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NEWS1130: 12 suspected overdoses reported in the Downtown Eastside area this morning https://t.co/vky1I28o13 https://t.co/6krjRxXqlO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @808investments: Missing a friend and fellow #realtor who was a ray of sunshine and laughter. Cherif Malak, rest in peace. I will miss y…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just met @jBoller40.   Solid solid guy.  One of my favourites in the NHL.  #ToughCustomer #WhatAJob #KeepGoing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Currently looking at a Vincent Chase imposter. @adriangrenier https://t.co/FCQ4B5M77w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @VancityBuzz: #BC billionaire donates $75 million to St. Paul's hospital https://t.co/N2YDKv5XCF https://t.co/AcnAxeuKwV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not bad.   And at least it's dry there. https://t.co/SUfdWVYkBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BBHwest: As Vancouver simmers, Toronto to see record-breaking luxury home sales this spring: Sotheby’s: https://t.co/d2iEb59IcF #cndre…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BBHwest: Metro #Vancouver’s cooling housing market is biggest factor for BC economy downshift: BCBC: https://t.co/rgegLoAvc8 #vanre htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @StellarQuotes: “A clever person solves a problem. A wise person avoids it.” ― Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beer league game update. Won 7-4 last game. No points. Played tonight. Lost 3-2 in a shootout. Please note that I wasn't one of the shooters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mikekermode: Ummm, Mark Methot's finger. Really? Top 20 grossest things ever. Google it. #NHL #Gross #Disgusting #NoMoreFingerTip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WatchCTVNews: LIVE as it happens: Union Jack projected onto Brandenburg Gate in Germany: https://t.co/FO3KtilrZa https://t.co/EAXq7MCV1v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @globeandmail: #Update: Police name British-born Khalid Masood as the man responsible for London's terrorist attack https://t.co/GClVVmV…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ajplus: American Kurt Cochran was killed in yesterday’s London attacks while celebrating his 25th anniversary with his wife Melissa, wh…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Fact: Never be afraid to try something new, because life gets boring when you stay within the limits of what you already knew.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The kid sis, her boy Sam, and yours truly. https://t.co/2iFuvq3rHk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@ScorpioTerms: #Scorpio's have an extraordinary memory and will not forget a thing you say.. Be careful." True.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's damp out there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yukon First Nations History.   “Part One - Strangers in Our Own Land” on #Vimeo https://t.co/akiKA1WoTN  This is heavy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm vibrating with love and light, in a world gone mad, in a world gone mad, there must be something more than this. #More]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's kinda close, no?   How does one get out? https://t.co/ZYnvBnGY4c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HuffPostBC: 'James Bond' legend Roger Moore dead at 89 https://t.co/mFrApHdiL0 https://t.co/NYmMaxg4UV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WOWPicsOfLife: Where Central Park meets the city, New York. https://t.co/X81tseBG6M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @garyhgoodridge: Money cannot buy dreams. https://t.co/hdkg8lwp4z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @westerninvestor: Downtown Vancouver building purchased in 2015 for $42 million has sold for  $107.5 million https://t.co/vNSzXvipBW #CR…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CBCNews: 4.2 magnitude earthquake hits near Yukon, B.C. border https://t.co/G5fZ7Hf6be https://t.co/YrBBZuX6dN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[11:11.    It has to be a sign...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Fact: The scent that lingers after a nice rain is called "petrichor."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The nephew.   He looks like a natural, no? https://t.co/dXmUsuqyMA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HeyBarber: Ducks win. I celebrate. https://t.co/Tzp0A7Z5iN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WTFFacts: A.M. stands for “Ante Meridiem,” which is Latin for “Before Midday”; P.M. stands for “Post Meridiem,” which is Latin for “Aft…]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>