<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Irritated with @bloomex .  E-mailed complaint 3 days ago; no reply. Phoned, then had 2 leave a msg.  This could get interesting. Stay tuned.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking at all the tweets tonight and see THE AMERICANS ARE BACK :-) and the echo, echo, echo of the past coupla days is almost gone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TaraCain There's a name for that condition, ya know ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DougJasinski Missed U. RBS took 2!; FMD; AHBL ... missing one or two awards. Media release to come.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gd to see @erinmcconnell @thelawyercoach @rebeccawcheung and others @ HELM awards . Social media campaign by boughton law won an award!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StorageWannabe So close, yet so far ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vancouver is a winter wonderland this morning! Kids (and dog) hoping school closes...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pleased to be asked to speak  at TagLaw Academy about most critical mktg 4 lawyers'  first 5 yrs w/ @thelawyercoach http://bit.ly/eOuPv5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TaraCain On arriving in Chicago from Vanc I was surprised to find nail scissors in my purse undetected.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@unmarketing Is that because you travel naked? Justaskin ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me 2! RT @MeganHamilton_: I just turned on xmas music radio station in my office... Makes me sooo happy! This will be on until Christmas!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I'm not watching 'Dancing with the Stars' because I'm respecting the privacy of Sarah Palin's family." - P. Morgan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevwrites Lining up for ferry now ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pray RT @cbcnewsbc: Vanc police confirm man armed w/knife holding boy about 3, unknown to him, at East Hastings St. community centre.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Legal Mktg Assoc Vanc chapter awards ceremony  (HELM) Thursday!  New format, new submissions. Join us http://bit.ly/ga0NA7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Banff_Squirrel: It's so cold tonight my Twitter has shrunk to 120 characters...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevwrites Hmmm... not sure the Honolulu/Christmas connection works 4 me, but if you say it's good, it's good :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This just in from a well-placed source: Google pulling plug on Google docs w/in 6 mos-8 mos. Notification to go out before all is lost.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevwrites Is there any other way to consume eggnog?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @colincameron: Why the Norton Rose 'merger' debate misses the point  http://bit.ly/fdeyWl  ll "This isn't an alliance...the group has ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me 2, Kev RT @kevwrites: Truly grateful today that I 1) work from home and 2) have a roof over my head.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[-10 degrees in Vanc tonight ... time to put out the rest of the Christmas decorations, I say. Yup, right after a glass of eggnog.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It only rains twice a year [in Vancouver]. Once for five months, and once for four months." -  Chi McBride, Van Sun, Nov 17]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OttawaLawyers  Send the dog after it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Simply beautiful RT @matwilcox: I love social media.  Watched it again and could not see one cell phone plug ...smart : http://bit.ly/bvCy18]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That Adam, such a ham RT @LMA_ANNUAL_CONF: Adam Severson  #LMA11 promo video http://www.youtube.com/watch?v=x_zYR4kja8I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sallyschmidt Can I get you a Tylenol for that  ;-)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you ever noticed how well-written the Groupon offers are? Seriously ... they highlight little nuggets of interest in everyday products.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Correction: with the holidays approaching is it wrong to shout "marketing is NOT a season" from atop a boardrm table?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With the holidays approaching it is wrong to shout "marketing is NOT a season" from atop a boardrm table?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Legal mktg colleagues, beautiful location, excellent programming, Mickey Mouse ... this is NOT a conf to miss #LMA11]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Recently back from San Antonio, Tx -- pretty city and was a good final blast of hot sunshine while we now await SNOW in Vancouver...sigh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cngrts Tara + Kathy!  Tx 4 asking me to speak. RT @TaraCain: 2010 #BCLMA Conf ended, I can only hope our next conference is as successful!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tip 4 parents w/kids: swap Halween candy 4 gift from tooth fairy. Give kids little candy, take rest 2 ofice, wrap + give gift and save teeth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StorageWannabe  Mst welcme. @coast_capital does great job advancg brand w/twitter - 'human' tweets, connect  w/mmbers, respond in real time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tx Tara! RT @TaraCain: Take a look at the twitter feed by @Coast_Capital for an ex. of a 'twitter voice' @lawyerPR #BCLMA conference]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tx Megan! Great to see you there! RT @Megan__Hamilton: Great #socialmedia tips for law firms from @lawyerpr at the #BCLMA conference]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevwrites ZOMBIES? R U kidding? EWWWWWwwww... they are fodder for nightmares!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love festive holidays, but gotta admit it ... I don't get Halloween. Please... someone enlighten me. What's to love?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The one and only! RT @sandy_wakeling: @lawyerPR That's John Becker! @TerryBecker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join me + support biz that suffered damage + looting last night w/our consumer $$...The Bay, London Drugs, Chapters, others? #vancouverriot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SkyTrainLady: CTV BC just reported SkyTrain is stalled. Clarification: Expo and M-Lines are operating normally. Pls RT.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matwilcox BC Ferries packed w/Canucks fans announced on earlier sailing today: "... and that 1 guy w/the Bruins jersey should get off now."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LindsayGriffith Love that strategy... and beautifully presented. Bravo!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test your US friendships: signed 'em up for Canucks fan club. #Canucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats! Home pg looks great - like a blog; lots of good content! RT @LindsayGriffith: new website is here!  http://bit.ly/iUjEVi !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@John_L_Daly Ahhhh... nice reassurances from a media veteran. Tx, JLD.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EJohnBecker Yeah, I thought you'd like that!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EJohnBecker  How about feeling "lucky"... to have the time to work late into the night on a client's sudden media issue :) !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@erinmcconnell Give 'em to your Translink-savvy Mom to deliver!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First time in a long time I have no upcoming presentations scheduled.  How to feel?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SusanEJacobsen: Must be on the mend RT Pogue: "Guy fell into upholstery machine, now fully recovered." @Eric_Bachman: I heard he was ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Favourite bumper sticker: "Horn broken. Watch for finger."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheresaLalonde: RT @cbcleahhendry: Anyone have an #air canada flight soon? Worried about how strike will impact u? We want to talk t ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TaraCain: Thank you for the info! RT @PassportCan: Children under 16 are not eligible for renewal must complete a new Application ht ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Class act that Steve Nash RT @WendyHartley: Here’s what @SteveNash has to say about the #Canucks http://dlvr.it/VjFz5 via @VIAwesome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hands up, who uses Campaign Monitor and loves it?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TELUS: It's #EnviroWeek! By re-tweeting this message, TELUS & @TreeCanada will plant a tree & you could win a prize. http://ow.ly/5bxB6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sept 1 BC articling students can practice law with aid of supervision. But will their work product sport a big "L" for "Learners"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toronto friends: I need a high end Toronto dwntwn restaurant w/private or semi-private room for 8 near Four Seasons Hotel. Any recmmndtions?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada Post turns up strike heat & announces 3-day work week to start next week http://bit.ly/k7MTlK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rossfishman: Big court victory for law firm consumers re online marketing and Google AdWords.  http://tinyurl.com/434gwnc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canucks game #4: afraid to watch; afraid to miss it. What to do?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Global News Reporter, John Daly, joins twitter. Welcome, John! Yesterday's CLE session inspired you?  Follow him @John_L_Daly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Van Sun's Ian Mulgrew: "Lawyers just don't understand [deadline] urgency like the media do."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Global News John Daly's  ideal story: simple, emotional, relates to people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CLEBC  Thanks for having me, CLE!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JoyVBehar: The Palin/Trump pizza summit was quite an event. When they were done eating, Trump fired the pizza maker & Sarah Palin sh ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[good reminder RT @DisneyInstitute: Be up front about the details of a new project with everyone involved to ensure a clear team vision.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The ultimate dog tease (watch his eyes!): http://youtu.be/nGeKSiCQkPw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sad to say g'bye  to Ogilvy Renault, but a hearty congrats to @NortonRoseOR  http://bit.ly/m7PMGS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the mktg front, congrats to Lise + her entire team RT @NortonRoseOR: @ogilvyrenault is retired and we now proudly wear @NortonRoseOR!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking frwd to presenting @ CLE's Lawyers & the Media June 6 w/@david_bilinsky & @NGartonJones http://bit.ly/kL9u0p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["HatTricks"  off ice: an inspired, intelligent charitable-giving model http://bit.ly/j2l4Pv Thanks @greenNgreen for the intro!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HA! The smoking gun ... RT @KevinFogarty: @matwilcox @lawyerPR Hence opposition to the right to arm bears.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smuttysteff @matwilcox Russian translation: Canada's bears R frequently stoned & bad influence on pigs, dogs & racoons. RCMP invstgating.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tres cool! RT @ogilvyrenault: To mark our combination w/Norton Rose Group, we will be opening the trading day at the TSX tomorrow at 9:30am.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matwilcox @smuttysteff She was clearly visualizing those bears... sitting ... smoking...and that damn pig. Bet the crew were bursting!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This cracked me up! RT @matwilcox: I can't stop laughing....  Cdn Press says......(MUST watch) http://bit.ly/js2JQi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EJohnBecker Oh puh-lease! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do complete strangers send LinkedIn invitations to me when we've never met? OK, so we work in same field, but so what?  What would u do?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OptinetSystems Nope. It wasn't his past experience. He was promoting another lawyer's results, from a different firm, as his own.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kevwrites It's an ad & since I got up close & personal assisting law society w/updating their marketing rules, me thinks it's off-side.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LarryBodine Yeah, but many just hang the banner and leave it flapping in the wind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lawyer runs newsprint ad summarizing a case & its successful result w/o lawyer names. Problem: not his case or his firm's.  Misleading?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats to Renee Collins Goult who recently launched Quantum Mediation in Vancouver w/a swanky new website ;) http://bit.ly/lVuksv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HIGH-FIVE! RT @david_bilinsky: Fin. Post publishd on my blog post on Computer Games - new era in legal ed  http://bit.ly/h0YfBe  #lpm #legal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Favourite quote that made me LOL re folks short on substance :  "All hat and no cattle",  courtesy @jordan_law21  #LMA11]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Mr. Harper's comments were so predictable during the debate, the instantaneous translation was three seconds ahead." - P. Morgan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lalaland999 Just discussed wine preferences with my roomie!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NancyMyrland Good on you! Do you know if we can get discount tx on site? #LMA11]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NancyMyrland Good on you! Do you know if we can get discount tx on site?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this! RT @jenniferlinn: Incase you are interested in a run/walk/workout while at #LMA11  http://bit.ly/djXM7n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Expect anything from this brand RT @holdencalgary: Great job #Westjet ! -- WestJet introduces money-saving fea… (cont) http://deck.ly/~XBowR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Didn't Jaffe just prove we're all 8 yrs old at heart? Their booth will be the proverbial conference "camp fire"-- meet ya there. #LMA11]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BAD-daddy RT @LindsayGriffith: Moving my @godaddy domains now after their CEO killed an elephant for sport. Na… (cont) http://deck.ly/~VIyll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@unmarketing Go on ... let's drag out the regrettables just for nostalgic sake. Dare you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social media, lawyers and mo-las-ses. My latest rant: http://bit.ly/hlcEnP (for everyone, but @EJohnBecker !)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just realized one of the wittiest lawyers I know is now on Twitter: @EJohnBecker  Don't say I didn't warn you :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @colincameron: RT @EJohnBecker  Becker & Company collection seminar - see Beckerlawyers.ca or the invitation at http://bit.ly/e53Jc1]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>