<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[How technology disrupted the truth https://t.co/HHQql20XT6 – nice summary on where society is with information/news https://t.co/t4kQ3FsjgD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EMYY123 Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BetaRish Good to hear! Looking forward to it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Off to the theatrical equivalent of a test match: @HPPlayLDN (tho without bringing own booze and scotch eggs)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robtcase Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber’s CEO doesn’t think self-driving cars will cost jobs, and he might be right https://t.co/tDY571uBRj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What I look for when hiring User Experience Designers https://t.co/5ZmJhIhTGb – mostly solid advice, tho LinkedIn tip feels a bit forced...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good stuff on the realities of football transfer deals and money involved https://t.co/A598GBpyOP https://t.co/Uy2woADu4f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JolyonMaugham: Thumbs up to Clinton for calling Farage what he is. Thumbs down to our politicians who failed to do the same. https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Stammy: boss: "will the slider UI work when we have more offerings in the future?"
designer: "yea, im pretty sure" https://t.co/yaWf1DG…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DaveWeasel Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jpublik: The Murdoch reach is in decline https://t.co/6ZuRR4YDPP https://t.co/Om8fhh0WEU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlexLeite Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Idanovitz Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TremblyLawFirm Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eholtzclaw Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @charlesarthur: Amazing piece. Farage, ex-money trader, sorta politician, urging people to stand up to banks and politicians https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iamsamstimpson Sure I remember—go for it! Or use our slack]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @basecamp: Silicon Valley arrogance: “I can tell you which startups will succeed, without even knowing what they do” by @dankim https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Evidence-Based UX Design Guide to Friends &amp; Family Opinions https://t.co/8dzSMS21a0 https://t.co/tdxLCD9jNy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting conceptual Google Analytics designs: Why Conversations Will Reinvent Software https://t.co/4BbPU96O4b https://t.co/KlvWbn03Qy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jburnmurdoch: I'd love to read this story about interstitial ads on mobile sites being bad, but... https://t.co/1jUFVGXvVd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Understand and use Mouse Heatmap data https://t.co/vI5vBYsSEn #ux #research https://t.co/Gw98vY0EuR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamesCorneille Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ditching the DSLR: Why a BBC journalist filmed only on a mobile phone for a month https://t.co/7f5hQpyXW4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice long read on Tim Cook and Apple's bullishness on mobile/iPhone https://t.co/n0XyEBtGqy https://t.co/HsCZWEzU6k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hillla Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@zimmermann_st Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A few handy tips in here... 10 Ideas to Help You Sell UX Work https://t.co/EY4Xv3ioUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former Facebook engineers launch Fabric, an automated personal journal of your life https://t.co/iIyZCXxqCy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ATryBox Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn to use and get the most out of Live Chat in your design research https://t.co/zY97xDG9QJ #ux https://t.co/4JmwvEHwKf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fondalo Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JackMawhinney1 Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[30 discs?? https://t.co/TPmFVcs6sh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why you should turn off 3rd party cookies in your browsers now https://t.co/zJrwreGH4q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FantasticMrFFox: “All Olympic Logos, Ordered By Quality” by @mikeindustries https://t.co/YIn020lP56]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @davidschneider: Ironically, this is the thing that's come closest to making me believe that there is a God. https://t.co/FnxlyCZxws]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good to know Trump's campaign seems to have failed as marketing exercise for his businesses https://t.co/HJXAwPZfTn https://t.co/xI3qKk0NPX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quite enjoying the BBC Sport site without CSS https://t.co/vjmLYZBZu0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get the most out of your client or stakeholder knowledge https://t.co/kCALFr7HA7 #design]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@interpropeople Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfpGcR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @IanDunt: Appalling. An invitation to aggressive Russian imperialism. https://t.co/u9eiTuT4Xd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ha! https://t.co/cyJW0h98Ez]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ID8UX: The Evidence-Based UX Design Guide to A/B Tests https://t.co/ySPikkdfck via @ishmatt #UX #UXDesign #design #usability]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Matt_Muir: This Autostraddle apology for their review of Sausage Party is *the* most 2016 thing I have read all year: https://t.co/uYnW…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What can you find out about your users from audience data? https://t.co/oBp2mh1g6C #analytics https://t.co/QCF5VN1gAm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @bill_tribble: Ahem. Good call! --- “At the end of the day, if your app is built on exploitation, it’s not truly innovative.” https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Using expert UX audits and what to watch out for https://t.co/FRG8EnFETv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CmonHarris: Gove looks like a conspiracy theorist in a horror movie who was, turns out, right all along about the killer. https://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mediaguardian Wrong cyclist guys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danrolfejohnson ... 2. make sure you're mainly testing their ability to *use* it rather than just them listing off opinions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danrolfejohnson I guess 2 things to check before doing: 1, do they reasonably match your target audience? ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laura Trott miles ahead in the overall standings but chasing down everyone else and winning sprints just for the bantz. #Rio2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @gillesoffthenet: Laura Trott is unreal. Contender for best British athlete of all time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johncutlefish Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Evidence-Based UX Design Guide to Competitor Analysis https://t.co/hmvVt6N2Ra #ux https://t.co/iiEdesWiP1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Evidence-Based UX Design Guide to Guerrilla User Testing https://t.co/BLehW2S4uO #ux https://t.co/lTGxjXtN76]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @davidtpegg: *points at Trump, points at Corbyn, gestures wildly, jumps up and down, gives up, makes cup of tea* https://t.co/lVM3BQOk3D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GOREFapp Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dan_Canetti Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @a7xweeman: *Record scratch*

*Freeze frame*

Yup, that's me. You're probably wondering how I ended up in this situation. https://t.co/T…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chris Hoy's punditry is so insightful and cliché-free. Actually thinks about every answer. Take note retiring sportsfolk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Tash_Tweet Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EddieRobson: Massive typical-off in the football today https://t.co/TScFNMCRVV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FuchsOfficial Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @murrayjame5: ALWAYS READ THE QUESTION CAREFULLY https://t.co/vnj6XXxIV8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pdtressler Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ndutton13: Report - Football clubs can now dictate what you can and can't post on social media. @CAFCofficial You're a joke. https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Evidence-Based UX Design Guide to Net Promoter Score https://t.co/4RkDA45XWT #ux #nps https://t.co/1ibwCRzoFH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jon_bartley: Deliveroo should listen to its couriers, who should be getting at least the (London) Living Wage: https://t.co/gu99QRQ8KP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A guide to using Conversion Funnels in UX https://t.co/mFxd90QKuZ #cro #ux]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IpshaChaudhary Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jjcrees: Back in 2010 @CommonsSTC found prescribing homeopathy compromised patient trust &amp; safety https://t.co/UwA7nwWMmk https://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Farewell, left versus right. The political divide now is open against closed https://t.co/tjFZvWaAas https://t.co/JmqYJVTS2q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @serafinowicz: NEW SASSY TRUMP VIDEO: Military Genius https://t.co/D8IwoEOubo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SteveGrant1983 I'm sure I am but sometimes if you want people to click a thing then only a button will do!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SteveGrant1983 Yeah I think the more general point is people are using buttons for the wrong thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fair points on why buttons shouldn’t have a hand cursor https://t.co/R0HYu630Ah https://t.co/6JC3cX0VPZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thelonelyrobot Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FootballRamble @ZeGermanFM The accessories that could come with...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(I make this the fifth version of the site I've done. Here are the other four: https://t.co/RsHzzg8Fzt)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GezzaB Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very pleased to have designed and today launched the new @FootballRamble logo and website https://t.co/y8KAZ7MvEq https://t.co/Xe78OICrUy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blimey. 'What's the harm' in the Olympics new fad of cupping... https://t.co/iA4PVqAw1Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to stay small and create a super flexible freelancing life https://t.co/tdkDPOxTlh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@galledia_ag Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Skip forward a school year and you'll basically go on to be an influential genius https://t.co/lGEw8RysYW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@engage2connect Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Science-Backed Guide to Taking Truly Restful Breaks – actually step away from the work https://t.co/PeYwZnD3Wc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @brad_frost: You can now use Apple Pay within the browser. https://t.co/S6PR7cKmz1 Big news for e-commerce.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All round solid advice on designing landing pages https://t.co/yB9XoEmcnG #ux]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plenty of actual LOLs watching Nina Conti - In Your Face at the @CriTheatre last night via @stagedoorLDN https://t.co/Vets4TyfDo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple is moving beyond smartphones to a world where you never take off your headphones https://t.co/Z9exzm76ub (if they stay in your ears)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @beggie_smalls: Uncanny https://t.co/RtOp8Up3oA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full-Focus Consulting: How I Re-Energized Myself &amp; My Business https://t.co/ft0HsmYyrL (solid tips for consulting)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mstandage: The Evidence-Based UX Design Guide to Surveys https://t.co/4RJp68Qhty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HereticHR: Wowwwwww Pete with the shutdown https://t.co/Z4xukAYIQH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great LOLs https://t.co/doEf7cZIGL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sentifi Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>