<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[12:30 Sky Commentator: Palace haven't got a hammering this season, they've only lost by the odd goal 

2:20 City 5-0 Palace #MCICRY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewGaynor like an elephant I never forget https://t.co/mhjVzCLJOp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AndyJohnson08: It's time to #EndTheStigma and talk about #MentalHealth. For every RT, I'll donate 10p to @MindCharity in @AaronLennon12…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The two waiter lads trying to get a peek of the two girls in the hotel afterwards #FirstDates https://t.co/6yMzN46XaI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The hot blonde is a lesbian  #FirstDates https://t.co/cRQMlk8krS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leo Messi watching that Ronaldo hat trick. #RMATL  #UCL https://t.co/aIy5RS1RZj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Craig Gordon during this game #OldFirm https://t.co/F9wWUxPEfU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like these 2 lads are moving in on Paul Williams and his leather jackets turf. He won't be happy at all #LateLateShow https://t.co/tPmpdoDtsz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This lad will be a great singer when his voice breaks when he's about 23 #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keyboard racists right now, watching this segment. #LateLateShow https://t.co/hK84J3qZlB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@talktoBOI Cheers, thanks for your help.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@talktoBOI It's held in ROI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@talktoBOI hi, can I cancel a direct debit online?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HGKrell I don't really care, to be honest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bloke should never wear tight white trousers, that's all I got from that segment #LateLateShow https://t.co/zN3f7BYKR3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Radiohead don't play 'Just' as part of their set #Glastonbury https://t.co/L8RqbtsGb4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EllDiva We don't deserve Thom Yorke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The face you make when Radiohead start playing the hits #Glastonbury https://t.co/qts8Xj48Bi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waiting for Radiohead to play a song I know #Glastonbury https://t.co/rkjdpbCzh1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know any of these Radiohead songs, can't understand a word Thom Yorke is singing but my God they're really good live #Glastonbury]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Green Fields of France sends shivers down my back every time I hear it but it's magnified x 100 when Furey and Dignam sing it #LateLate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@John_the_Champ Not all lesbians have cats]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@John_the_Champ I doubt there's a lot of people  who lived life as a homosexual but were actually straight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think about the amount women in Ireland in the past who never came out but instead raised a family but were miserable  #ADifferentCountry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russell, women keep leaving you cause you're a bit of a prick #FirstDates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Kelly one is a real life Janice from Friends #FirstDates https://t.co/PivMijUJpO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I loved everyone on that show. Funny, wise, loving and full of life they could teach us younger folk a thing or two #toooldfortheroad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She's some going hunting for a murderous hipster priest while carrying her new born baby around not many cops can do that #redwater]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mark's teeth are a bit shiny ain't they #firstdates https://t.co/F6rFAgOit8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gays Planes and Orange Parades #DUPMovies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FariBrad Sorry 😬]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Hunt for Gays in October #DUPMovies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Ascension of Arlene Foster By the Coward Theresa May #DUPMovies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gaywatch #DUPMovies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phlaimeaux Not forgetting Irish models in the 2000s posing to sell any old shite https://t.co/bimO7WKknA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BeWarmers: Roy Keane kicking the referee's door down after disallowing a goal #COYBIG #IREvAUS #IREAUS (@GrahamPatchell)

https://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roy Keane kicking the referee's door down after disallowing a goal #COYBIG #IREvAUS #IREAUS https://t.co/9XQgVK8R0y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why did it take Ireland until the 85th minute to start playing decent football, should have started like this #IREAUS #IREvAUS #COYBIG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Serious question, what the fuck does Glenn Whelan actually do? I never see him do anything #COYBIG #IREAUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not a fan of this long ball hoofing shite, get the ball down and play a bit of ball #COYBIG #IREvAUS https://t.co/X2e9HfCCOp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dunphy when he sees Hoolahan not starting #IREvAUS #COYBIG https://t.co/wzkQEMwF9o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YvonneCostello3 @dailyedge Haha I saw that, I'm on Lovin Dublin as well. I'm just really good at Twitter 😜]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love #TheSnapper simply because I loved it as kid and didn't really understand it but it's funnier when you actually get it as an adult]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dessie Curley is everyone's da who group up in North Dublin, absolutely spot on acting by Colm Meaney #TheSnapper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Suppose a ride is out of the question' is one of the best movie lines, actually the whole monologue is brilliant  #TheSnapper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ManUtdLens: Giveaway: Retweet and follow us &amp; @pgaskell13 to be in with a chance of winning this set of #mufc European winnning coaster…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish Colm Brophy would stop talking bollix, the Garda are clearly not ready for an attack. Sure they said it themselves #rtept]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mendelpol I recognised the mistake straight away, but just left it because I'm cool like that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gaffology Very true, I'm not British I don't live there but I can't see how anyone would vote to keep that bumbling wreck May in power.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*your not you're obviously]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you mess up your part in the school concert, but you're Dad still loves ya #BattleForNumber10 https://t.co/tTrpWr3cZC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How I felt before and after watching this match #PlayOffFinal #HUDvREA https://t.co/VAV7mOMDZF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will someone just score in injury time and end this shithouse of a match #PlayOffFinal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trying to work out what the hell is happening in #Redwater https://t.co/d1Yq8YWkNe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be honest Redwater is a load of shite it's like one of tv shows that would be on a Sky channel at 2 in the morning #Redwater]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A few local Glasgow women pictured the last time Celtic were beaten in Scotland #ScottishCupFinal #celtic https://t.co/CJjoE1D6yW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jaysus your man Peter sounds like a right proper dickhead who could do with a few slaps off the lads #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damien Dempsey's songs all sound the same. There I said it #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The lad driving by the rest of the audience in his new car later on #LateLateShow https://t.co/Uk8u0Mzodm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This girl is absolutely steamed, I love it #LateLateShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Burrell was in the ultimate friend zone with Diana.  #LateLateShow https://t.co/LB6ZCItPbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you try and discuss Climate Change with idiots #cblive https://t.co/t25j1iVIxW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dempsey_mp I wanted to write something else but I refrained from doing it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brenda Power isn't a very nice person if you're anyway different from her or don't share her views. #cblive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NaasBall Haha, I'm gonna hold you personally responsible if this doesn't happen. I'll walk down to you and shake my arm furiously at you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NaasBall Now I'll be disappointed when I go in and he doesn't say 'oh suits you sir']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NaasBall Brilliant I'm in the market for a new suit. Keep the money in Naas instead of heading down to Kildare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The GAA counting their dosh after the replay #GAA #MAYOvROS https://t.co/ZVngFo6aQn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mayo fans having heart palpitations again today, it would drive ya to drink #MAYOvROS https://t.co/Qg7JJyNsrA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some start to this match #MAYOvRos https://t.co/UBmyhEgmf6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThreeCare hi, I just got a bill there for €147.49 my charges this month are for €88.98 can you please explain where them charges came from]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wanna secure Ireland's place at the centre of the world. Good man Leo ya mad goat ya #vinb https://t.co/Sx0kNL8Pjo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do I need an alibi? Yes Ian you do you most certainly need one if you're prime suspect in a murder #DuPlantier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only thing I ever hit when drunk was my pillow but does the fact that he's a bit of a bastard make him a murderer? No #DuPlantier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If there ever was an example of keystone cops in Ireland it was the #DuPlantier case an absolute feck up of epic proportions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SkyKaveh: Marca say Neymar will sign six-year PSG deal on £500,000 a week. Total cost £352m. £196m release clause + £156m wages]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Huskies running out of RTÉ when Katie Price starts singing #Miriam https://t.co/6cLTC1GNDl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like Eamon Dunphy but bloody hell he never has a good word to say about Man Utd. Calling Lukaku the Belgian Heskey is just absurd.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wanking with tears in my eyes - Ultravox #replaceDancewithWankinasong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SkyHelpIreland hi, my broadband is down. I can't use the On Demand service or access the internet. Can you please help?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Say what you like about Aslan not making it internationally but Crazy World is the most iconic Irish song ever written. #ThisisChristy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bono what's it like to be Ireland's greatest ever vocalist? 
Bono: I haven't a clue ask Christy Dignam #ThisisChristy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnStitch3 @HayleyMcQueen @SkySportsNewsHQ Yeah but I bet @HayleyMcQueen wouldn't touch you with a barge pole you rotter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to see Michael Carrick get the captaincy at United. A great servant to the club and an all round decent bloke. #MUFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SportsJOE_UK @AndrewGaynor here's one for ya I got 39 I'm thoroughly disappointed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SergioRamos: The best tribute is to help all children like Bradley. Let's help make his legacy even greater. RIP Bradley Lowery @Bradle…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I didn't know Jeff Hendrick was mates with Douglas Reynholm from the IT Crowd https://t.co/P7iPp6DxLw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Bradleysfight: My brave boy has went with the angels today 07/07/17 at 13:35, in mammy and daddies arms surrounded by his... https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BBCSport: Manchester United have agreed a deal with Everton for Romelu Lukaku, senior club sources have told the BBC.

Read: https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SportsJOEdotie Do I get a medal? https://t.co/noU8vD2phM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Victoria_Catt If people like it, then great but it just hasn't become popular here yet maybe it will in the near future]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Victoria_Catt Yeah I live just outside Dublin the thing with country it's seen as music for people from the country and not people from the Dublin area.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Victoria_Catt Yeah, I don't know anyone apart from the older generation who like country. Everyone likes Johnny Cash but that's about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Victoria_Catt I'll take your word for it but there's a virtually non existent country scene around these parts. It's all indie and dance around here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Victoria_Catt I agree with you on the ratings part there must be a big country music scene somewhere in the country certainly not where I live anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Victoria_Catt I'm not getting at country but it's all that seems to be on it nowadays musically wise. Apart from Other Voices it's all country.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I praised RTÉ last night but not tonight, I wish RTÉ would push other genres of music the way the promote country. So one sided #NCNashville]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honestly Ireland could do with a Johnny Giles now, the best Irish player I never saw play.  #giles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RTÉ get a lot of stick but they really know how to do a documentary. This documentary is brilliant #giles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I miss Gilesy doing the punditry on RTÉ, the new lads are good but they're not Gilsey #giles]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>