<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Ben E. King - his story and music  http://t.co/XgTjdXtgo1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One family that practices population control:  the mafia!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can I build a high quality free website?  http://t.co/CKwJBIknBi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Fleetwood Mac  http://t.co/0GT6hKV0ry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Auto racing, bull fighting, and mountain climbing are the only real sports --  all the others are games. - Ernest Hemingway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Options for Using Slimmers and Trimmers for Weight Loss  http://t.co/dE2zGWwaf9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Race cars are neither beautiful nor ugly. They become beautiful when they win. - Enzo Ferrari]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome tennis t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the tennis lovers in your life!   http://t.co/RyrOR6fNKf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of England Dan and John Ford Coley  http://t.co/pI01baR2fr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time is a friend. Do not kill it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Those SEO Google Animals - Panda and Penguin - How They Affect Your Site  http://t.co/ouhsxSmXZI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool check out this Nerd Kit...  http://t.co/v8652cZhmQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about necessary foods for your prepper pantry!  http://t.co/7uskceG3jE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The object of education is to prepare the young to educate themselves throughout their lives. - Robert M. Hutchins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love any movie that has a retarded person working at Starbucks.  Chris Kattan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some of the greatest Hollywood actors are not the award winners, but those congratulating them on their triumph]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your chances of winning, I've got to believe are really, really small when you score one run in 18 innings. - Clint Hurdle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That guitar is okay but you'll never make a living with it - John Lennon's Aunt Mimi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome baseball t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the baseball lovers in your life!   http://t.co/EbYdkiGECs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An office clock is rarely stolen --  everyone watches it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Habit is habit and not to be flung out of the window by any man, but coaxed downstairs a step at a time. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Gary Lewis and the Playboys  http://t.co/wh6jzW8WuF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome disco t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the disco lovers in your life!   http://t.co/BRMCR6Pgfw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My dad is a marketing mastermind. - Serena Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Who  http://t.co/OJSRfULjd8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Bob Dylan -- His Biography    http://t.co/UeBbS3oEUO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If man is a little lower than angels, then angels should reform.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Tsingtao Beer  http://t.co/Nf0Tmt2eKK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 1 - What the heck do I have????  http://t.co/dcv7jsrCcA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagination is the key to my lyrics. The rest is painted with a little science fiction. - Jimi Hendrix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Emmylou Harris  http://t.co/Un5Ho8bRMq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He who opens a school door, closes a prison. - Victor Hugo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is a thousand times better to have common sense without education than to have education without common sense. - Robert Green Ingersoll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How To Find The Right Gluten Free Foods  http://t.co/oeszjeo1gJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Those SEO Google Animals - Panda and Penguin - How They Affect Your Site  http://t.co/TbB91Wv1Wa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lifetime of training for just ten seconds. - Jesse Owens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome biking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the biking lovers in your life!   http://t.co/oxEbkFLKrr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make Money by Tweeting, Blogging and Photo Sharing with Izea  http://t.co/dzpvs3VbR1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Early History of Hamburgers  http://t.co/CBsk9zZLEX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every boy should have two things: a dog, and a mother willing to let him have one - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most beautiful makeup of a woman is passion. But cosmetics are easier to buy. --&gt; Yves Saint-Laurent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to gShift Labs  http://t.co/jtddXPoKqK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helpful Hints for Web Building from the Experts  http://t.co/EVW6yAAmSw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I mean, we're lost on an island, running from boars and monsters -- freakin' polar bears.  Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money was never a big motivation for me, except as a way to keep score. The real excitement is playing the game. - Donald Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Firefighters recently rescued two people from an industrial clothes dryer. They were listed in stable condition but missing one sock!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good introduction to Minecraft Mods - http://t.co/LtltzILYUz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is the transmission of civilization. - Will Durant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of Young Samurai: The Way of the Warrior  http://t.co/iSVpBkBRw0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science fiction films are not about science. They are about disaster, which is one of the oldest subjects of art. - Susan Sontag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very very cool a complete working model of SpaceX rocket - awesome tech!  http://t.co/VlUw8HtFq0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stumbling is not falling. - Portuguese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do something for somebody every day for which you do not get paid. - Albert Schweitzer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women need food, water, and compliments.  That's right.  And an occasional pair of shoes. Chris Rock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about the Bay Area city of Pleasanton, California http://t.co/y95taAtEdD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I'm not back in five minutes, just wait longer. - Ace Ventura, Ace ventura, Pet Detective]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Wendy's  http://t.co/dw3bIRCpvT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd just as soon kiss a wookiee! - Princess Leia, The Empire Strikes Back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In youth we learn in age, we understand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't buy a nice car and get rich you get rich and buy a nice car - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Organizing Garage Cabinets and Storage  http://t.co/ilxnC6Y8v6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Fun! BANG! Turn it off this Lamp with a gun, and it "plays dead". Then bring it back to life with another shot! http://t.co/DP48Zs0O0P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Victory belongs to the most persevering. - Napoleon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To win without risk is to triumph without glory. - Pierre Corneille]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to Douglas Adams  http://t.co/cKH50Luzy5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's very strange writing science fiction in a world that moves as fast as ours does. - Daniel Keys Moran]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take twice as long to eat half as much. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Mott the Hoople  http://t.co/8aoRU5KBjz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Far and away the best prize that life offers is the chance to work hard at work worth doing. - Theodore Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You will never change your life until you change something you do daily. - Mike Murdock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't go into details, I've already told you  more than I overheard myself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love Cute Kids Watches - Having A Watch Can be Fun for Kids!  http://t.co/sT828A2CvS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's no secret. You just press the accelerator to the floor and steer left. - Bill Vukovich]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Major Watch Retailers and Brands  http://t.co/dIVPIStfmI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These Messenger Bags are stylish and practical - cool! http://t.co/JTZWzG82A3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pessimist: A man who thinks that all woman are bad Optimist: A man who hopes so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Bobby Darin    http://t.co/PUTdoCzCD2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Jimmy Choo  http://t.co/naTyedz0P6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Five Guys Burgers and Fries  http://t.co/oerZEabkkl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Average White Band  http://t.co/LfHHlkVT5G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I could turn and live with animals, they are "¨so placid and self-contained,"¨I stand and look at them long and long. - Walt Whitman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Middle age is after one night out you need two nights in. . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very cool 23 mile range walkie talkies!  Stay connected!  http://t.co/S0azKaFQiR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What is Chronic Lyme Disease?  http://t.co/0Pg3ntTF5y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Christian Louboutin  http://t.co/WJpju19Fbt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Experience is not what happens to a man. It is what a man does with what happens to him. - Aldous Huxley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is only a tool. It will take you wherever you wish, but it will not replace you as the driver.  Ayn Rand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I could walk a mile in ur shoes but I already know they are just as uncomfortable as mine. Lets walk next to each other instead Lynda Meyers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are three things you can do in a baseball game. You can win, or you can lose, or it can rain. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am the legal guardian over a massive shoe collection. - Linda Dominique Grosvenor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the sun refused to shine I would still be loving you. When mountains crumble to the sea there will still be you &amp; me - Led Zeppelin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A toupee is ear to ear carpeting!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rock is so much fun. That's what it's all about - filling up the chest cavities and empty kneecaps and elbows.  - Jimi Hendrix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of France Joli  http://t.co/zfae6OsP29]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Meat Loaf  http://t.co/8jrjlflOFr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Awesome Nintendo Wall Graphics! http://t.co/TJ23G39ICl]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DotNetNuke 6.0 – A Big Leap Forward  http://t.co/ZSwaiv7dUq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can a guy win a game if you don't give him any runs? - Robert Bo Belinsky after Losing 15 - 0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Harold Melvin and the Blue Notes  http://t.co/g8jMW4g6kX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Mike Clifford - A One-Hit Wonder  http://t.co/sVxIp6c8a9]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>