<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Cmdr_Hadfield: Each green dot is an Earth-crossing asteroid. 
The more we explore, the better we understand life's choices. 
https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@djskizzle @CNN Savage https://t.co/CyJcRPFGPP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ny_kia31_sports CFL bound?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @wikileaks: Hillary Clinton email reveals she knew of Saudi &amp; Qatar government funding for ISIL (ISIS) by August 2014 https://t.co/tlWxk…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BasedMonitored @Rambobiggs I've always wondered why do they bring up Admiral Akbar when someone dies?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@djboptics You can verify with a Nikon camera and poorly put together YouTube videos made by morons..duh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @wikileaks: Saudi previously threatened UK with terrorist attacks over arms sales investigation https://t.co/eJAFakxFE5 https://t.co/FUQ…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro Cream always rises to the top..not how fast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeCienkowski @KsLiberal @Davidw28x @ladybuglc @Dracalous @welshninja87 @GardenerN21 @U_Megabyte @Perdnoot @MarkHerron2 @JohnA_SEN @cootey59 @GameraInfalible @i_wish_upon_you @RedErinn @TheLexZane @bikinatroll @TakeThatDarwin @Goblin_Steroids @BenevolentPixie @DubuissonPaul @Ponteelcinturon @Mogleeone @TDesane @EvanLHarris2 @Snow_White125 @bigstewy58 @CSeaforthFinch @Mandokero @tcanham459 @BertramBaxter66 @onnlucky @WezKing @Bye_Dogma @mars_weather @JosephOMorrow1 @RCarrier_Errors @Floridaline @Lead1225 @Greg_MarineLab @Colin_bluenose @leedeeley21 @FarkyH @Morphindel @Astro_Brony1 @sience_says @Falmouth_Dai @Rebell117 @PromiseRW @SoulsSurvivor Clearly you have no clue what you are talking about.   You know enough to think you're right, not enough to know you are WRONG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump @ReviewTheEarth How about less God blessings, thoughts and prayers and more solutions and actions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joerogan  https://t.co/J3QE0Ea0Z7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hplarc12345 @ISON_Tracker @rich752913078 @WoodyWouldntHe @shotgunsusie @NomieAhmed @Woody94787674 @LilLeebe @Keys2Logic @valtolhurst @HeatherLA2010 @dimamynedd @alankirton @UnCastellsMes @mannysmammy @AlaskanRadical @JennUndercover @kayenne22 @Arsenal__COYG @brokenchains2 @EnochEarth @FlatRealm @faith4truths @DustinJuggles @siirii @BLMcCallum @jamreilly57 @MickWest @majwal7 @JimJerrolds @BookishNeptune @NothingSirius @Gr8Believer @yogazombies @djboptics @GoldfishEarth @hollyhaygood @ladybuglc  https://t.co/Va7uAWUwI2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@djboptics Fake account for the flat earth rimjobs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Make America Covfefe Again]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN Trudeau already sucking up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ny_kia31_sports https://t.co/SmCsv2vQXG looks almost a shitty as the real thing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OneStop_Sports Browns need to sign the guy who gave that hitstick to the first Giant in the scrum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OneStop_Sports Lmao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsDeanBlundell He looks almost as bad as those hookers he was banging years ago]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hplarc12345 @valtolhurst @HeatherLA2010 @NomieAhmed @dimamynedd @alankirton @UnCastellsMes @mannysmammy @AlaskanRadical @JennUndercover @kayenne22 @Arsenal__COYG @brokenchains2 @EnochEarth @FlatRealm @faith4truths @DustinJuggles @siirii @BLMcCallum @jamreilly57 @MickWest @majwal7 @JimJerrolds @BookishNeptune @NothingSirius @shotgunsusie @Gr8Believer @yogazombies @djboptics @GoldfishEarth @hollyhaygood @ladybuglc Clearly flatearthers photoshopped the picture to fit their narrative;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wikileaks A direct result of the media constantly pushing the story to brainwash the publix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PrisonPlanet https://t.co/s36oXLfoM9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jules_su @realDonaldTrump You talk about Trump being friendly with Saudi Arabia..check where Clinton's campaign funds came from]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@underdogbuild Thank.  Made in Canada has been more miss then hit recently]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@underdogbuild What would be your pick for best iptv add on for North American (us/Canada) channels..free and paid?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@underdogbuild just downloaded the build this morning.  Clean, fresh and looks great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TakeThatDarwin  https://t.co/Lh7cALrYrY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN Trump is going to drop a MOAB on some poor country to make up for that handshake]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN Probably had ISIS training..and who trains and funds ISIS again?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN See, those tiny hands are good for something after all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JulianAssange: Disgusted with MI5 &amp; MI6 facilitating extremists which appears to have resulted in the Manchester attack and many more i…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @wikileaks: Theresa May's #MI5 helped pump Muslims from #Manchester into Libya to attack Gaddafi https://t.co/3lUxf2n4xY #ArianaGrande]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FlatSlugbrains  https://t.co/LPgTdEoIck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump I guess nobody slapped his tiny hand away?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump Lmao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kylegriffin1 @maddow Do these politicians actually do anything?  Or just regurgitate talking points over and over and over..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BleacherReport: The first woman to play in the West Coast League is “ready for everything” ➡️ https://t.co/IDr1vZkMvn https://t.co/dEvb…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ProbingOmega @iamAtheistGirl  https://t.co/erNzskseEf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DRUDGE_REPORT Someone get that guy a pizza]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 minutes of brutal honesty #wakeupcall https://t.co/rpCgeVyjiC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro 71-46? Need a healthy rotation, our stars to produce and a few win streaks..not likely]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN  https://t.co/k4KKK1FAZb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @plm2211: @JulianAssange Do you believe the DNC is obstructing justice by suppressing evidence that Seth Rich was the Wikileaks source o…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheMacRanter Rich Hill the 2nd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @wikileaks: Sweden Withdraws Arrest Warrant for Julian Assange, but He Still Faces Serious Legal Jeopardy by @ggreenwald
https://t.co/v9…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BernieSanders Please move forward with the investigation..actually name sources, people of interest rather than vague accusations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joerogan episode 961 was top notch.  I hope we see more round table like discussions in the future]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro Gaining back his weight/strength]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#flatearth https://t.co/guge7MDHfX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Snowden: Try not to laugh. https://t.co/KryvtMTClM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarryDavis_ Smith Jr ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wilnerness590 Lmao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro I'm patiently waiting to see what type of team Shapiro and company eventually builds when this current construct finally slumps its way out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BarryDavis_ hate to say it but I think the expiry date on this current Jays team came a few years to early]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CharlesZenon @SNJeffBlair Been missing all season]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SNJeffBlair The drums of rebuild begin to grow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sportsnet @thehazelmae Glad Smoak is doing well...just sucks the majority of the team is wallowing in mediocrity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScottyMacThinks (3) not enough assets to facilitate a retool and to old to wait for the farm to produce replacements]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScottyMacThinks (2). Either get ahead of this rebuild (because that's what the team needs) or wallow in mediocrity and lose the chance and some return]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScottyMacThinks bang on about the Jays.  They feel like the Canuck after making it to the cup..old team holding on to long....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN Schiff is gonna milk this Russian theme right to end]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN Wish there was a vaccine for stupid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BleacherReport Career best "safe" call]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN Another member of the Catholic Church charged with a sexual offense.. shocking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SNJeffBlair CNN reporting?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@frankp316 @ari_shapiro Saunders is slow as fuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro Complete the trifecta and sign that douche bag Lawrie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ny_kia31_sports Knicks go nowhere with him as owner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewStoeten Restock for the 2022 push ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewStoeten Lol.  All I'm saying it will be interesting to see what direction the front office will take.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewStoeten Can't wait for the trade deadline.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Acosta This tweet aged well, lmao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RusicSN590 George who?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro I long for the day Jays fans are as excited about prospects in the system]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CNN: 60 London high-rise buildings fail fire safety tests after Grenfell Tower disaster https://t.co/xRCMrjOQYr https://t.co/Ezs3hpphj1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rambobiggs What does black lives matter have to do with gay pride?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN Trump says?   It was well documented in the DNC emails this happened]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro Flashes of...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro Flashes out what a 20mil player should play like...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN https://t.co/e0qwIa3Ofa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro It's the only hand Gibby can play at the moment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro Lose Stewart and add Devon White to make this poll interesting.  Devo would solve the lead off problem and add speed to the lineup.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ari_shapiro Halladay without question.  Stops losing streaks and gives the bullpen a rest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @StefanMolyneux: President Trump sells Qatar $12 billion of U.S. weapons days after accusing it of funding terrorism. This is dumb.

htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@djboptics How do you not get a hot spot from a sun being so close?  Stupid flat earth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN Was this a study in common sense?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Brasilmagic: Criticizing religion is not bigotry. You're not criticizing the followers, you're criticizing the doctrine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CheetoSantino @joerogan Participation awards to everyone..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ribs https://t.co/T67xqLrASP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@B_Xristian @iamAtheistGirl Oh... zombie Jesus.  Ok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WHEREDIDDEANGO @CNNPolitics @CNN Lol I'd still rather they actually did something then waste time praying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN https://t.co/f1kItk1cIb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN Remember that time when you said Qatar funds terrorism, then days later sold them 15 billion in arms... yeah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkAmesExiled Has he been labelled a terrorist or just a crazy liberal?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Wilnerness590: Tom Cheek would have been 78 years old today. #Bluejays #Jays #HappyBirthday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SNETCampbell: Kid below us fell and skinned his knee. So Kevin Barker gets a ball from bullpen and delivers it personally. https://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SNETCampbell Way to go Barker..class act all the way]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@B_Xristian @iamAtheistGirl Geezis..is he talking about the Time Travellers Wife?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN Has Wyden found Iraq on the map yet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNNSitRoom @CNN The senate committee leaking information to the press from private sessions is uncomfortable.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>