<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Controls Programmer (Glass and Manufacturing): Contract/Freelance Project Description Job Title Controls Programmer (Glass and Manufacturing) Job Location Toledo, OH Department TOL1843 – EGCM Glass/Mfg Controls – Toledo Position Type Contract / Regular… https://t.co/UaiiQpfJBS https://t.co/aznY9ldK1Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Croatia advances to first World Cup final with dramatic extra-time win over England - Yahoo Sports: Yahoo Sports Croatia advances to first World Cup final with dramatic extra-time win over England Yahoo Sports In the beginning, it was quintessential… https://t.co/bTrgMUMUVL https://t.co/jy6ibACsG1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UI developer: UI developer Ref No.: 18-27226 Location: Cincinnati, Ohio ROLE:UI DEVELOPER LOCATION: Cincinnati – Ohio JOB DISCRIOTION: Key skills required for the job are: Usability-L3 (Mandatory) Angular JS-L3As a Lead, you are responsible for managing… https://t.co/TrD0ElxQOO https://t.co/HqGwiNzOKD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer Ref No.:18-10623 Location: Houston, Ohio Position Type:Contract Start Date: 06/14/2018 Role: .Net Developer Location: Houston, OH Job Type: Contract Roles and responsibilities: – Resource should be strong on C# Design and… https://t.co/WAYqXteYfa https://t.co/NNoEAQv19X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Application Analyst and Developer: Location US-OH-Richfield Posted Date 3 months ago(3/30/2018 4:49 PM) Job ID 23412 # Positions 1 Category Technology Position Type Full Time Overview National Interstate is a member of Great American Insurance… https://t.co/cyfuasVTUU https://t.co/IaalpSZBje]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Manafort to be moved from jail where prosecutors say he has 'VIP' treatment - Washington Post: Washington Post Paul Manafort to be moved from jail where prosecutors say he has 'VIP' treatment Washington Post A federal judge in Alexandria has ordered… https://t.co/8XMtQ1GbiR https://t.co/OJs0ZbAAEW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Engineer in Test II: Careers Center | Software Development Engineer in Test II Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to… https://t.co/rdr1wRn6iJ https://t.co/ktSw7DOJAh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Objects Software Developer, Staff: Business Objects Software Developer, Staff Skip Navigation Fiserv Menu – Solutions – Industries – About – Careers – Where you fit in – Technology – Accounting &amp; Finance – Contact Center – U.S. Locations –… https://t.co/REDqkC8GFs https://t.co/ur1EPMWMR3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adam 'Pacman' Jones Involved in Fight at Atlanta Airport, Employee Arrested - Bleacher Report: Bleacher Report Adam 'Pacman' Jones Involved in Fight at Atlanta Airport, Employee Arrested Bleacher Report Free-agent NFL cornerback Adam "Pacman" Jones was… https://t.co/YserMtgYYN https://t.co/krgb7PkSzz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solution Architect: Search Jobs – RADcube – Technology Solutions – Enterprise Integrations – Enterprise Integration consulting – API Lifecycle Management – SaaS Integration – SOA – Application Services – Mobile Application Services – Web Content… https://t.co/EbSSnpzV0n https://t.co/QngU8QgUaW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full-stack developer: For Siemens Full-stack developer job – Marketing – Milford, Ohio Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard – Toggle navigation – My Dashboard – Our Stories – FAQS – – Siemens Careers Job Full-stack developer… https://t.co/TXpQT7NJ4z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Applications Developer: Job Description Founded in 1866, The Sherwin-Williams Company is a global leader in the manufacture, development, distribution, and sale of paints, coatings and related products to professional, industrial, commercial, and… https://t.co/020k4a0VDm https://t.co/qb1x84aUum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Performance Testing Lead: Location US-OH-Cincinnati Posted Date 1 month ago(5/1/2018 3:14 PM) Job ID 23558 # Positions 1 Category Technology Position Type Full Time Overview Be Here. Be Great. Working for a leader in the insurance industry means… https://t.co/VgM9o6W8A0 https://t.co/21ZgJdO2kg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mainframe System Administrator: Location US-OH-Cincinnati Posted Date 1 month ago(5/23/2018 2:48 PM) Job ID 23641 # Positions 1 Category Technology Position Type Full Time Overview Be Here. Be Great. Working for a leader in the insurance industry means… https://t.co/gQ1kHfNmk3 https://t.co/2KDbZNiLIz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lisa Page plans to defy GOP subpoena for her testimony, her lawyer says - CNN: CNN Lisa Page plans to defy GOP subpoena for her testimony, her lawyer says CNN (CNN) Former FBI lawyer Lisa Page is defying a congressional subpoena and will not appear… https://t.co/Zua4Azsvtm https://t.co/ZxzVFlg20F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle ERP folks with some OBIEE knowledge: Oracle ERP folks with some OBIEE knowledge Ref No.: 18-29697 Location: Cleveland, Ohio Please share profiles – Salary up to 105K. Visa and non visa both are fine. Look for Oracle ERP folks with some OBIEE… https://t.co/IQpBJJBv14 https://t.co/Dd6pw4ByBu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Software Engineer: Headquartered in Dublin, Ohio, Cardinal Health, Inc. (NYSE: CAH) is a global, integrated healthcare services and products company connecting patients, providers, payers, pharmacists and manufacturers for integrated care… https://t.co/Le1kMH9QFk https://t.co/HH1Zahbmbg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP SCM SD: NOTE: ‘AT PRESENT WE WONT REQUIRED H1 &amp; EAD RESUMES FOR THIS POSITION’ Title: ********** Position Type: 12 Months Contract Location: London, OH Skills Required: ********** Sector: Public Industry: Life Sciences Regards, Rohith Performance… https://t.co/Mu9oklKl3K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feds say just 4 of 102 young migrant kids reunited with parents as court deadline looms - CBS News: CBS News Feds say just 4 of 102 young migrant kids reunited with parents as court deadline looms CBS News SAN DIEGO -- Lawyers for the Justice Department… https://t.co/ver5BSfvj0 https://t.co/DFrUwT0OBw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: Careers | Join nChannel’s Fast Growing Team support contact nChannel – insights – case studies – pricing – connectors – solutions – overview Open Menu – insights – case studies – pricing – connectors – solutions – overview – Multichannel… https://t.co/2ahPkFhu5s https://t.co/7KZHBvNVFV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Developer-Progress: Description Founded in 1866, The Sherwin-Williams Company is a global leader in the manufacture, development, distribution, and sale of paints, coatings and related products to professional, industrial, commercial, and retail… https://t.co/LF2GS4bfI0 https://t.co/isnz7XbnLX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Pardons Oregon Ranchers Whose Case Inspired Wildlife Refuge Takeover - New York Times: New York Times Trump Pardons Oregon Ranchers Whose Case Inspired Wildlife Refuge Takeover New York Times Dwight L. Hammond and his son became a cause célèbre for… https://t.co/9ZxyRdN8VE https://t.co/HRaweyi66E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VIDEO: Man harasses woman at Cook County forest preserve, officer under investigation - WLS-TV: WLS-TV VIDEO: Man harasses woman at Cook County forest preserve, officer under investigation WLS-TV An Illinois park is investigating after a woman accused… https://t.co/FYBivPxen2 https://t.co/zfqW5Ocs4p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chicago-Area Native Celebrating Anniversary in Mexico Killed by Stray Bullet - NBC Chicago: NBC Chicago Chicago-Area Native Celebrating Anniversary in Mexico Killed by Stray Bullet NBC Chicago A Chicago-area native was killed by a stray bullet while… https://t.co/KhFGa0rZID https://t.co/KGMgymsyCO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parents, 3 Young Children, Found Shot to Death Inside Their Delaware Home - NBC 10 Philadelphia: NBC 10 Philadelphia Parents, 3 Young Children, Found Shot to Death Inside Their Delaware Home NBC 10 Philadelphia A mother, father and their three young… https://t.co/jczShome7j https://t.co/qhi4sDBz6E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Developer: Location US-OH-Cincinnati Posted Date 1 month ago(5/2/2018 3:15 PM) Job ID 23237 # Positions 1 Category Technology Position Type Full Time Overview Be Here. Be Great. Working for a leader in the insurance industry means opportunity for… https://t.co/nQ9sHItxN6 https://t.co/MUpBlwAhnO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Designer II: Job Title Web Designer II Applications Accepted From Special Instructions to Applicants This position is eligible for the following benefits: Level 3 – Sick Leave; Retirement Posting Number *******T Job Description Uses current practices… https://t.co/nlbgsrJfXr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woman beats a 91-year-old Mexican man with a brick, tells him to 'go back to your country' - Washington Post: Washington Post Woman beats a 91-year-old Mexican man with a brick, tells him to 'go back to your country' Washington Post The Fourth of July… https://t.co/Y0Hnrq5iC8 https://t.co/haYziaoyKQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Performance Engineer: At Cardinal Health, were developing the innovative products and services that make healthcare safer and more productive. Join a growing, global company genuinely committed to making a difference for our customers and… https://t.co/Tub8XWN7cm https://t.co/I54zO6QE2g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft's Surface Go tablet has a 10-inch screen and starts at $399 - The Verge: The Verge Microsoft's Surface Go tablet has a 10-inch screen and starts at $399 The Verge Microsoft is getting back into the cheaper tablet game today with the new Surface… https://t.co/Q1cVbL6M9A https://t.co/LZeJNrgCf3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Is Itching for a Fight at NATO - Bloomberg: Bloomberg Trump Is Itching for a Fight at NATO Bloomberg When Donald Trump barrels into Brussels this week demanding that NATO allies boost their defense spending, the response will be: We already are.… https://t.co/pJSuH9jLvE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Red state Democrats can easily oppose Beltway Brett Kavanaugh - CNN: CNN Red state Democrats can easily oppose Beltway Brett Kavanaugh CNN Paul Begala, a Democratic strategist and CNN political commentator, was a political consultant for Bill Clinton's… https://t.co/V0EPkgKRwl https://t.co/Af22chf3Ap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge rejects Trump request to alter agreement on release of immigrant kids - Politico: Politico Judge rejects Trump request to alter agreement on release of immigrant kids Politico A federal judge has turned down President Donald Trump's request to… https://t.co/s7udNa2CWn https://t.co/FTaum9dwfz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Job ID 2018-9179 Overview Insituform Technologies, LLC is looking for an experienced Project Manager to be based in our Columbus, OH office. Insituform Technologies LLC, a subsidiary of Aegion Corporation, is a leading worldwide provider… https://t.co/WbGZXC4Z8U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michael Cohen sending a clear message to Trump by speaking 'real truth,' sources say - CNN: CNN Michael Cohen sending a clear message to Trump by speaking 'real truth,' sources say CNN (CNN) Michael Cohen, the President's former fixer and ultimate… https://t.co/ksC1oMMqel https://t.co/o8LYNt1F4r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Detectives Running The Novichok Murder Investigation Are Focused On Finding The Nerve Agent's Container - BuzzFeed News: BuzzFeed News Detectives Running The Novichok Murder Investigation Are Focused On Finding The Nerve Agent's Container BuzzFeed News… https://t.co/SrM5FWYpmG https://t.co/KYNukcihpc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Analyst: Job Title Business Systems Analyst Requisition # PCC-US.****** Job Type Full-time Shift Type Location TIMET – Toronto – Toronto, OH 43964 US (Primary) Job Description Summary Develop interactive tools that convert enterprise… https://t.co/AY9w1uuRAc https://t.co/cbLmZ6RRcG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bookstore owner defends calling police on woman who told Steve Bannon he was 'a piece of trash' - Washington Post: Washington Post Bookstore owner defends calling police on woman who told Steve Bannon he was 'a piece of trash' Washington Post Black Swan… https://t.co/NEaBjaTh9j https://t.co/2oWr5CDxMV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David Davis resigns as UK Brexit Secretary over May's EU plan - CNN: CNN David Davis resigns as UK Brexit Secretary over May's EU plan CNN (CNN) The man responsible for overseeing the UK's exit from the European Union has resigned, citing irreconcilable… https://t.co/FDruTQn1ZG https://t.co/1e4m6vVg5X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump 'Very Close' to Supreme Court Decision, but May Wait Till Final Hours - New York Times: New York Times Trump 'Very Close' to Supreme Court Decision, but May Wait Till Final Hours New York Times BERKELEY HEIGHTS, N.J. — President Trump sought to… https://t.co/NbWwsQqfCS https://t.co/1KVMB1Zo7Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: Location US-OH-Cincinnati Posted Date 1 month ago(5/24/2018 1:14 PM) Job ID 22775 # Positions 1 Category Technology Position Type Full Time Overview Be Here. Be Great. Working for a leader in the insurance industry means… https://t.co/xnC39Xvnkl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full-Stack PHP/WordPress Developer: **Full-Stack PHP/WordPress Developer** Locations:Milford, Ohio Job Family: Information Technology New Search English (US) **Job Description** **Division:** Digital Factory **Business Unit:** Product Lifecycle… https://t.co/BxkM2jNEWs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Consultant Managed Services Fusion Middleware: – Senior Consultant Managed Services – Fusion Middleware Posted Date 2 weeks ago(5/16/2018 1:56 AM) ID 2018-2944 # of Openings 3Category Consulting Work Site – City Columbus Department Consulting… https://t.co/eTuRNZHbG6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[McConnell pursued from Kentucky restaurant by angry crowd - Chicago Tribune: Chicago Tribune McConnell pursued from Kentucky restaurant by angry crowd Chicago Tribune A group of Democratic Socialists and other angry protesters pursued Senate Majority… https://t.co/o9GAmcttoG https://t.co/ICgaa5wwHJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Admin Favored Corporations In Opposing Breastfeeding Resolution: Report - HuffPost: HuffPost Trump Admin Favored Corporations In Opposing Breastfeeding Resolution: Report HuffPost President Donald Trump's administration put the interests of… https://t.co/aQwUfgSbhe https://t.co/G541NphmrK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Justin Bieber and Hailey Baldwin's Road to Engagement - E! Online: E! Online Justin Bieber and Hailey Baldwin's Road to Engagement E! Online Justin Bieber and Hailey Baldwin's road to engagement began more than three years ago. The two have known each… https://t.co/0eYfOqueDy https://t.co/yLH8FmJtB0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 Family Members 'Wiped Out in the Blink of an Eye' in Crash - NBC 10 Philadelphia: NBC 10 Philadelphia 5 Family Members 'Wiped Out in the Blink of an Eye' in Crash NBC 10 Philadelphia A New Jersey family expressed disbelief and grief on Saturday after a… https://t.co/6gQnPDqFiY https://t.co/gLSbSkKCgW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump administration deals another potential blow to Obamacare by freezing risk adjustment payments - ABC News: ABC News Trump administration deals another potential blow to Obamacare by freezing risk adjustment payments ABC News The Trump administration… https://t.co/mY1zuOtP16 https://t.co/n7e7cVpzkk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Acquisition Control/Automation Engineer: Lubrizol Additives is a pioneering global supplier of chemical additives technologies including additives for engine oils, driveline applications, gasoline and diesel fuel, other transportation related fluids… https://t.co/jFE4ppCtPj https://t.co/iPF89cYkLi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Jersey couple killed after home explodes; officials investigating cause of blast - Fox News: Fox News New Jersey couple killed after home explodes; officials investigating cause of blast Fox News An elderly couple died Saturday morning after an… https://t.co/lP9ueUVkZY https://t.co/KnAkplZNqI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Research Enterprise Enablement Java Developer: Apply now Research Enterprise Enablement Java Developer ============================================= Company Name: Kroger General Office Position Type: Employee FLSA Status: Exempt Line of Business:… https://t.co/ObDTMm3Ry9 https://t.co/XOWmoZV3q6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anti-gun violence protesters shut down part of Chicago freeway - CBS News: CBS News Anti-gun violence protesters shut down part of Chicago freeway CBS News Last Updated Jul 7, 2018 4:27 PM EDT. CHICAGO -- Thousands of anti-violence protesters marched… https://t.co/4wsOAyVIzJ https://t.co/6SCYnaYWGS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Insider Attack' Kills US Service Member in Afghanistan - New York Times: New York Times 'Insider Attack' Kills US Service Member in Afghanistan New York Times U.S. troops in Farah province, Afghanistan, in May. One American service member was killed and… https://t.co/LsObKrsYxE https://t.co/76D2lXNa2s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Irate' man arrested for threats against Trump supporters, local politician - New York Post: New York Post 'Irate' man arrested for threats against Trump supporters, local politician New York Post A Long Island man was arrested Friday for threatening to… https://t.co/slF2lAJ6jQ https://t.co/TVDGeIfDB2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hurricane Beryl heads for Caribbean islands; separate tropical depression forms near Carolinas - USA TODAY: USA TODAY Hurricane Beryl heads for Caribbean islands; separate tropical depression forms near Carolinas USA TODAY Beryl, a tiny, compact storm… https://t.co/Nt9BBWSxBl https://t.co/XPIFzi1KdN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst Salesforce PLM: **Business Analyst – Salesforce – PLM** Locations:Milford, Ohio Job Family: Information Technology New Search English (US) **Job Description** **Division:** Digital Factory **Business Unit:** Product Lifecycle… https://t.co/dqG9DSxzfX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Trump administration separated families. Reuniting them is a giant mess. - CNN: CNN The Trump administration separated families. Reuniting them is a giant mess. CNN (CNN) The family separations saga has revealed failures of governance, competence and… https://t.co/NqTxxg4tKi https://t.co/G0w5dB5mqG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All-time temperature records set throughout Southern California, including Los Angeles - Washington Post: Washington Post All-time temperature records set throughout Southern California, including Los Angeles Washington Post 10:40 p.m. update. As… https://t.co/X2LdeI9Nvr https://t.co/fbDIdhP7J2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Both sides seek to 'clarify' as Pompeo holds second day of North Korea talks - Reuters: Reuters Both sides seek to 'clarify' as Pompeo holds second day of North Korea talks Reuters SEOUL/TOKYO (Reuters) - U.S. Secretary of State Mike Pompeo began a… https://t.co/z84T1KN7dt https://t.co/MuLpsJxqqD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UI/UX Developer # JN: – Like us on Facebook – Follow us on Twitter – Connect with us on LinkedIn – Instagram – Watch us on YouTube – Visit our page on Glassdoor – Our Blog RSS Feed – Home – Employers – Overview – IT – Engineering – Professional –… https://t.co/8LghUBo2lK https://t.co/PlW9qpeh26]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fast-moving fire in San Bernardino National Forest forces town to evacuate - Los Angeles Times: Los Angeles Times Fast-moving fire in San Bernardino National Forest forces town to evacuate Los Angeles Times The worst of this week's heat wave hit Southern… https://t.co/aVelgZnPf3 https://t.co/zhZYf0Dm0y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#IDAdam, the white man who called police on a woman at their neighborhood pool, loses his job - Washington Post: Washington Post #IDAdam, the white man who called police on a woman at their neighborhood pool, loses his job Washington Post The temperature… https://t.co/3WOLitkLkF https://t.co/e6GFJGk6fI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java/J2EE Developer Ref No.: 18-32344 Location: Columbus, Ohio Hello, Greetings for the day ! We have an urgent requirement for Java Developer in Columbus, OH. Please let me know if you are looking for a new project. You can reach me at… https://t.co/vQWHrDCpB8 https://t.co/DMcoSfCmM0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's War With Harley-Davidson Has Divided America's Bikers - New York Times: New York Times Trump's War With Harley-Davidson Has Divided America's Bikers New York Times A move by the company has put one of the country's most iconic brands in the… https://t.co/RDP7TJYXRg https://t.co/1dPOh2IKOc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NASA spacecraft rockets toward sun for closest look yet - https://t.co/edWcbmDM2h: https://t.co/edWcbmDM2h NASA spacecraft rockets toward sun for closest look yet https://t.co/edWcbmDM2h A NASA spacecraft rocketed toward the sun Sunday on an… https://t.co/20vIotEFUd https://t.co/kospUwKIvm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['She's a lowlife': Trump blasts Omarosa following bombshell claims in upcoming tell-all book - Business Insider: Business Insider 'She's a lowlife': Trump blasts Omarosa following bombshell claims in upcoming tell-all book Business Insider President… https://t.co/5BkWgdluMy https://t.co/i6T8cFT0jZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EAS cloud developer: EAS cloud developer – DB2 (CM8) Ref No.: 18-33696 Location: Dublin, Ohio Must-Have Strong Experience with IBM DB2 Content Manager (CM8), Cloud application development (Spring Boot, Microservices, Angular) Good-to-Have Case Manager,… https://t.co/omYExhbSlg https://t.co/DTztu3ryBN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PowerCenter Developer: PowerCenter Developer Columbus, OH 08-09-2018 Location: Columbus, OH For more than 18 years, CareWorks Tech has been delivering technology solutions that drive results. As your advocate, the common thread across our associates is… https://t.co/5mjy3f1Gzf https://t.co/yVgQwxv3Bw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VS Naipaul, Controversial Author And Nobel Laureate, Dies At 85 - NPR: NPR VS Naipaul, Controversial Author And Nobel Laureate, Dies At 85 NPR Perhaps best known for his novel A Bend in the River, V.S. Naipaul was a controversial figure in the literary… https://t.co/SnEbxTkSWD https://t.co/yh9MzYLrDl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Says Sessions `Scared Stiff and Missing in Action' on Russia Probe - Bloomberg: Bloomberg Trump Says Sessions `Scared Stiff and Missing in Action' on Russia Probe Bloomberg Donald Trump accused his own attorney general of being “scared stiff and… https://t.co/4EGquHiPrC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Charlottesville riddled with barriers, security and flowers on 'Unite the Right' anniversary - USA TODAY: USA TODAY Charlottesville riddled with barriers, security and flowers on 'Unite the Right' anniversary USA TODAY CHARLOTTSVILLE, Virginia – A year… https://t.co/cAsAhsKZEh https://t.co/lO7BfNaSkR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['It's still hard to look at' - Washington Post: Washington Post 'It's still hard to look at' Washington Post CHARLOTTESVILLE — Ryan Kelly had been working all day when he heard a car rev its engine and saw a flash of metal speed by. He didn't know what… https://t.co/7Jp8TnWc0E https://t.co/5oqJqofur9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Airline employee steals plane from Seattle airport, crashes and dies - CNN: CNN Airline employee steals plane from Seattle airport, crashes and dies CNN (CNN) An airline employee stole an otherwise unoccupied passenger plane Friday from the… https://t.co/4x3D2Tm1X6 https://t.co/UZyfv3PmEm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Technician: Job Title Network Technician Requisition # ******.1 Job Type Full-time Shift Type First Shift (Day) Location PCC Airfoils – Mentor, OH Mentor, OH 44060 US (Primary) Job Description NETWORK TECHNICIAN Maintain, repair, and upgrade… https://t.co/atuPEugmK5 https://t.co/uAaYaGDxMZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Omarosa Manigault Newman says she refused hush money, pens White House memoir calling Trump racist - Washington Post: Washington Post Omarosa Manigault Newman says she refused hush money, pens White House memoir calling Trump racist Washington Post… https://t.co/3aQcCeUtUc https://t.co/fpwZLH8eeG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager II – Higher Ed: Job Description Tracking Code 5158-244 Job Description At Gilbane we’re building more than buildings, we’re helping create schools, hospitals, laboratories and other facilities across the United States and throughout the… https://t.co/9d88HCZu27 https://t.co/22dwUEUlYC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tensions Between Turkey and US Soar as Trump Orders New Sanctions - New York Times: New York Times Tensions Between Turkey and US Soar as Trump Orders New Sanctions New York Times ISTANBUL — A worsening dispute between the United States and Turkey… https://t.co/KBCFkgk7nv https://t.co/t5Rnkxyb0v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kansas Governor Hires a Lawyer for Contested GOP Primary - Wall Street Journal: Wall Street Journal Kansas Governor Hires a Lawyer for Contested GOP Primary Wall Street Journal Kansas Gov. Jeff Colyer dug in for a legal fight over this past week's… https://t.co/JbGzPpx3n3 https://t.co/qZ2V4N5PRT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Manafort trial Day 9: Manafort got $16 million in loans from bank whose CEO wanted Trump administration post - Washington Post: Washington Post Paul Manafort trial Day 9: Manafort got $16 million in loans from bank whose CEO wanted Trump… https://t.co/ZOAkHytpHj https://t.co/ZY2pghKPLS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Security Engineer: Network Security Engineer Ref No.: 18-32427 Location: Dublin, Ohio ROLE: Network Security Engineer II LOCATION: Tulsa,Oklahoma – Security, MPLS, Internet, Ethernet, and Managed Services signal flow – CNIA- SEC / JCNIP- SEC,… https://t.co/0l25ULMMHl https://t.co/IiNPmdu9hb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laura Ingraham tries to walk back her 'demographic changes' monologue — but doesn't apologize - Washington Post: Washington Post Laura Ingraham tries to walk back her 'demographic changes' monologue — but doesn't apologize Washington Post Fox News host… https://t.co/ruy9QBttSZ https://t.co/0Cf00wPknv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Representative Tier I: Windstream is seeking entry level Specialist’s for Tier I Repair. Our Specialist will assist Windstream Broadband Internet customers with troubleshooting and incident creation to resolve customer trouble. In this… https://t.co/GMRe9JgvlK https://t.co/9bC6i8X0cT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At least 4 killed in Canada shooting; a suspect is in custody - CNN: CNN At least 4 killed in Canada shooting; a suspect is in custody CNN (CNN) At least four people have been killed in a shooting in Canada, police said Friday. The shooting took place in… https://t.co/rOL8qoyuiJ https://t.co/Wwxh5x1Aty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teamcenter Developer: Teamcenter Developer Ref No.: 18-33561 Location: Cincinnati, Ohio Job Title* Teamcenter Developer Relevant Experience (in Yrs) 6+ Yrs. Technical/Functional Skills Must have hands-on experience working with Teamcenter 9 &amp; beyond –… https://t.co/FLePu6NEFH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Big Data Developer: Senior Big Data Developer : Job Description Roles and Responsibilities: 1. Gathers requirements from stakeholders, designs the solution aligned to requirements, platform(s) architecture and infrastructure. 2. Engages with… https://t.co/yL7aYb3B5v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Samsung Galaxy Note 9 will bring a longer battery life -- and Fortnite - CNNMoney: CNNMoney Samsung Galaxy Note 9 will bring a longer battery life -- and Fortnite CNNMoney The world's largest smartphone manufacturer unveiled on Thursday the Samsung… https://t.co/m2Ffa2HelF https://t.co/ihjoWzrMfY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nearly 33000 juveniles arrested over last two decades labeled as gang members by Chicago police - Chicago Tribune: Chicago Tribune Nearly 33000 juveniles arrested over last two decades labeled as gang members by Chicago police Chicago Tribune Nearly… https://t.co/bIx0YgragP https://t.co/7UZ3BzY3cO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saudi Students Fret Over Future After Order to Leave Canada - Wall Street Journal: Wall Street Journal Saudi Students Fret Over Future After Order to Leave Canada Wall Street Journal Saudi Arabia's diplomatic row with Canada has upended the lives of… https://t.co/eZ4w3dSnmy https://t.co/KncUNCe3Cs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer EDI: Software Developer – EDI / Cincinnati , OH Overview:Seeking a Software Developer to build and maintain Microsoft BizTalk 2013/2016 applications, and C# .NET applications for use within an EDI/SOA environment. Along with modifying,… https://t.co/6RSxyxoKFX https://t.co/TXZgNgJ0Gg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brother: No signs of struggle in Iowa woman's disappearance - ABC News: ABC News Brother: No signs of struggle in Iowa woman's disappearance ABC News The brother of a missing University of Iowa student's boyfriend says there were no signs of struggle at… https://t.co/Bh5yhZmjBN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Latest: Progress made on California's largest wildfire - Fox News: Fox News The Latest: Progress made on California's largest wildfire Fox News LAKEPORT, Calif. – The Latest on California wildfires (all times local):. 8 p.m.. Firefighters are making… https://t.co/6g5VHWolmt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Ref No.: 18-29433 Location: BlueAsh, Ohio Position: Java Developer Job Location: BlueAsh, OH Job Title: Full time permanent Mandatory Technical/ Functional Skills: – 4+ (8+ years for senior level) years experience with Java… https://t.co/YBjSpVz5HI https://t.co/eq1foWX4ei]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Willow Creek Church's Lead Pastor and Board of Elders Resign - New York Times: New York Times Willow Creek Church's Lead Pastor and Board of Elders Resign New York Times The lead pastor and the entire board of elders resigned on Wednesday night from… https://t.co/qLSdBu9yaJ https://t.co/wBaAQiUuU9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Target Digital Network Analyst 3: ABOUT EMPLOYER: Employer delivers innovative solutions to critical challenges facing the nation and the world. As a premier provider of integrated services for the U.S. government, we support the Department of Defense,… https://t.co/xs8mGzvR0O https://t.co/Gyl23cm3do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-cheerleader pleads with officer after allegedly driving drunk not to arrest her because she's white - KTRK-TV: KTRK-TV Ex-cheerleader pleads with officer after allegedly driving drunk not to arrest her because she's white KTRK-TV A woman seen speeding… https://t.co/q9mBJQyMoX https://t.co/WPSmByKeg3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China retaliates with tariffs on $16 billion worth of US imports after Trump's latest trade hit - Washington Post: Washington Post China retaliates with tariffs on $16 billion worth of US imports after Trump's latest trade hit Washington Post China said… https://t.co/fFB864THv6 https://t.co/eDf2byE0Lv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['I'm a white, clean girl': DUI suspect is the picture of entitlement - New York Post: New York Post 'I'm a white, clean girl': DUI suspect is the picture of entitlement New York Post A boozed-up South Carolina woman pulled over for blowing past a stop… https://t.co/Hgu7jHxt7D https://t.co/Y9AMIzLzEz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2018 primary election: 9 things Michigan voters should know - https://t.co/hOM4qsSATq: https://t.co/hOM4qsSATq 2018 primary election: 9 things Michigan voters should know https://t.co/hOM4qsSATq Millions of Michigan residents will be heading to the polls… https://t.co/aErJFSS1wc https://t.co/U2UUovSMmT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Service Desk Supervisor II: This position assists in the oversight of the day-to-day operations of the Corporate Service Desk. It is responsible for providing complete and competent technical support to the end users, for providing technical… https://t.co/YmlxsfNiyh https://t.co/2hei83d3q0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, Senior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Dayton, OH Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 8/3/2018 Job Description Job Number: R******* Software Engineer, Senior Key Role: technical knowledge of software… https://t.co/6KfCqfgcXY https://t.co/9Yoadu88f8]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>