<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA["Our limits may not be where we think they are." -Chrissie Wellington at #IMKona awards ceremony]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes your "PR" has nothing to do with time, but what you #conquer inside]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“You cant get much done in life if you only work on the days when you feel good.” ~Jerry West #running #quotes via @running_junkie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Did you know that running uphill, at race pace; will strengthen your legs better than any weight training you could do?" via @JeffGalloway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To go fast, go alone; to go far, go together. -Warren Buffett via @CharityIdeas #run #endure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The big secret in #life is that there is no big secret. Whatever ur #goal, u can get there if u’re willing to work. -Oprah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Coach said we do what's hard, to make us hard, which makes us hard to beat.” via @gosonja #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Choose to persist without exception." - Andy Andrews #run #distance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've grown certain that the root of all #fear is that we've been forced to deny who we are. ~Frances Moore Lappe via @iheartquotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Belief is a dream's accelerator and doubt its speed limit. #run #believe (via @AffirmationSpot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We are designed to #run - and we increase our chance of daily #happiness when we do so." via @jeffgalloway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You have to believe in yourself when no one else does; that makes you a winner right there." -- Venus Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love and respect to the Men and Women who keep our country safe. We run for you! Happy Memorial Day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“You will never succeed beyond your wildest #dreams unless you are willing to have some wild dreams.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Passion is energy. Passion is desire. Passion makes you smiles when nobody is watching.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think something can never happen then you are forgetting what life is all about #miracles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It doesn't matter whether you come in first or last. It matters that you started and gave it all your #heart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Faster isn't always better. Remember where you came from.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The more I #practice, the luckier I get. -Jerry Barber]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't Settle.... So keep looking until you find it. Don’t settle.” Steve Jobs #inspiration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Running and #life are much the same. A fantastic support system of friends or family can make a big difference]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Different people in your life for different reasons. Goodness can come from multiple sources. Take time on your runs to be #thankful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Get busy living, or get busy dying" Shawshank Redemption #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Everything seems #impossible, until it's done." Nelson Mandela]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Running shirt on the back said... If you see me collapse, please hit 'Pause' on my garmin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It does not matter how slowly you go so long as you do not stop.~Confucius #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We acquire the #strength we have overcome. ~Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["And you can #dream, so dream out loud."
U2 via @LJ3000]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The block of granite which was an obstacle in the pathway of the weak, became a stepping-stone in the pathway of the strong ~ Carlyle #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Running makes me feel alive, appreciate my legs, and the friends that run with me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest healing therapy is friendship and love - H. Humphrey AND #running]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only one doubting you is you #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you think something can never happen? Nope I don't either #run #goals #life #change #dreams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The #heart has its reasons, which reason does not know." -Blaise Pascal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Running is a balance of physical exertion, enhanced mental awareness and spiritual peace. (via @JeffGalloway)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saucony slogan: "Maybe #strong is just what you have left when you've used up all your weak."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My #heart has a way of making my legs go]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“You will never succeed beyond your wildest #dreams unless you are willing to have some wild dreams.” via @Kattemie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If everything seems under control, you're just not going #fast enough." ~ Mario Andretti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want 2 become the best #runner you can be, start now. Dont spend the rest of your life wondering if you can do it" Welch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man who dares to waste one hour of time has not discovered the value of #life. ~Charles Darwin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Hope is a #good thing, maybe the best thing, and no good thing ever dies” Shawshank Redemption]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the midst of regular #life, running is the touchstone that breathes adventure into my soul -Kristin Armstrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Life is meant to be lived. Take risks. Feel passion. Discover love. Run free.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When you do something positive, even if no one else knows it or sees it, you are making a difference.” via @MiraclesGoddess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who #dream by day are cognizant of many things which escape those who dream only by night - Edgar Allen Poe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some have natural talent, others make up for it with tremendous heart #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surround yourself with people who believe in you, encourage you &amp; help you exceed your #dreams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Often hear someone say I’m not a real runner.We are all #runners, some just run faster than others.I never met a fake runner via @BartYasso]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never give up on something that you can't go a day without thinking about.~Unknown #life #goals #dreams #love]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["One is hardly sensible of fatigue while he marches to music." -Thomas Carlyle, Scottish writer and historian via @zumadog]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laziness is an option #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was born to run #thanksmom Happy Mother's Day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Ever have that problem where the treadmill doesn't go #fast enough for ya?....... No me neither.” via @Mirindacarfrae]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You can't get fit in one workout, just as you can't live your life in one day." -Johnny G #running #quotes via @running_junkie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know you're an #ultrarunner when you don't finish on the same day as the winner.” via @TheTrailJogger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To uncover your true potential you must first find your own limits and then you have to have the #courage to blow past them ~ Picabo Street]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you are not willing to risk the unusual, you will have to settle for the ordinary." -Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“There's no magic to running far or climbing Everest. Endurance is mental strength. It's all about heart.” Bear Grylls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["dont quiet them. embrace them. its natural, normal &amp;shows how much you care. when the gun goes off they will be gone!” via @chrissiesmiles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Some people think about making it happen and others make it happen!" #DO #IT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To dare is to lose one's footing momentarily. To not #dare is to lose oneself ~ Kierkegaard via @CharityIdeas @LJ3000]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Most mistakes in a #race are made in the first two minutes, perhaps in the very first minute." - Jack Daniels]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Keep some room in your #heart for the unimaginable." -Mary Oliver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We were meant to live an extraordinary #life. Don't believe anything less. Never settle for ordinary.” via @JoshCox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What excites you? What makes you dream? #run #life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Don't underestimate anyone around you. Everyone has the #power to surprise anyone at any point of time.” via @Kcancer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The way to know #life is to love many things. ~Vincent Van Gogh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not quench your #inspiration and your imagination; do not become the slave of your model. Vincent Van Gogh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“A true #friend sees the good in everything, and brings out the best in the worst of things.” Sasha Azevedo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The only one who can tell you 'you can't ' is you. And you don't have to listen." - Nike #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never give up on something that #you can't go a day without thinking about.~Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we did the things we are capable of, we would astound ourselves. -Thomas Edison #run #achieve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No rules, change happens, embrace friends, challenge norm, live life #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My daddy is faster than your daddy #HappyFathersDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To all the dads who know how to get their run on #HappyFathersDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, you CAN do it. Did someone tell you, you can't?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Discover your gift and give it away]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Punish me, make me #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Don't let fatigue make a coward of you."- Steve Prefontaine #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["For me, like so many others, #running is the answer. Out on the road it is just you, the pavement, and your will" John Bingham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Do these shorts make my ass look fast?" ~ #running shorts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The joy was in the act of #running and in the journey, not in the destination." John Bingham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Start it, run it, push it, sweat it, grunt it, laugh it, finish it #marathon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never underestimate the power of dreams and the influence of the human #spirit - Wilma Rudolph]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Few of us know what we are capable of doing…we have never pushed ourselves hard enough to find out– Montapert #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I'll lean on you and you lean on me and we'll be okay." - Dave Matthews Band #friends #runningpartners #life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["But if you never try you'll never know...Just what you're worth" Fix You by Coldplay #inspire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I run because it's my passion, and not just a sport. - Sasha Azevedo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I run marathons #yes #for #fun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I live a life of my own design. I go with the flow that's uniquely mine. via @AnnTran_]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["They who have #conquered doubt and fear have conquered failure." - James Allen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Skill to do comes of doing." Ralph Waldo Emerson via @CharityIdeas #train]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To settle is a choice, you can choose to run after your dreams #life #running]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people say they don't have enough time to train. Others make it happen #noexcuses #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Believe that you're young enough, old enough, strong enough &amp; so on to accomplish everything you want to do" John Bingham via #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be positive, ignore the critic, follow ur heart, invest in your passions, believe in ur dreams &amp; get busy making them reality~ by @JoshCox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A hero is someone who has given his or her life to something bigger than oneself. ~Joseph Campbell #charity #runners]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only disability in life is a bad attitude. -Scott Hamilton (via @rnrgirl) #run #train #marathon #endurance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A river cuts through rock, not because of its power, but because of its persistence" ~Jim Watkins #run]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>