<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't think and hit at the same time. - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overheard:  "I don't mind going to work.  It's that long wait to go home that bothers me."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So my degree was in political science, which I think was - the closest I could come to marketing is politics. - Steve Case]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was your operation expensive? "No, the doctor gave me cut rates."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The History of Rolex Watches – The Start of Something Great  http://t.co/hZhVgqbuDM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Popular Places and Activities in Europe  http://t.co/azXVUEyA0Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is an admirable thing, but it is well to remember from time to time that nothing that is worth knowing can be taught - Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1,000 Incredible Costume and Cosplay Ideas http://t.co/ihpfBep9wu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Europe – Best Places to Tour  http://t.co/KJRs75ZUnO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Julius LaRosa  http://t.co/vUbw0Qj5EB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Clear Lighted Skateboard with green LED Lights  http://t.co/XOew6Rh1hg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of the hilarious "I Love Lucy" episode - The Kleptomaniac  http://t.co/JQVAyepZfR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion is not necessarily about labels. It's not about brands. It's about something else that comes from within you. - Ralph Lauren]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Frustrations of Youth Pitching  http://t.co/U5VYUc1G8d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He who laughs last, didn't get it!!  :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is simply the soul of a society as it passes from one generation to another. - Gilbert K. Chesterton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you chase two rabbits, both will escape. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Beautiful Canadian Rockies Tour  http://t.co/Ywk9Aovm1V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The Music of L.T.D.  http://t.co/GCdSVF0e9P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Tips on Using Other Websites for Link Building  http://t.co/oXEFxtCzLp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Love Unlimited  http://t.co/8uNDYRTmQL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't get too caught up in making money or having a job, get excited about the fact that you can design your life. Darren L. Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Planning for an Ash Scattering Ceremony  http://t.co/YcGjXsfglL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awww How Adorable! A Smile Star Design - Color Changing - LED Light Toss Pillow! http://t.co/OYlJKyCekL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ELVIS - The King - One Person's Thoughts  http://t.co/1O5C9eFV6c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So now I'm left with cigarettes, and I'm trying to scrape that off my shoe and then I'll be done. - Diane Lane]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do something for somebody every day for which you do not get paid. - Albert Schweitzer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lot of people love Oreos. So their manufacturer is making money. That means more dividends for shareholders. Maria Bartiromo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I believe you are your work. Don't trade the stuff of your life, time, for nothing more than dollars. That's a rotten bargain - Rita  Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read Great Outdoor Camping Equipment Tips  http://t.co/WutUP7NCGe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laser Tag anywhere - cool guns and app make it easy to play anytime!  http://t.co/vOqRqhq5F6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You win some, you lose some, you wreck some. - Dale Ernhardt Sr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Amazing and Mesmerizing SciFi &amp; Space Artwork  http://t.co/z46XN6lvWe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opportunity is missed by most people because it is dressed in overalls and looks like work - Thomas Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most beautiful makeup of a woman is passion. But cosmetics are easier to buy. --&gt; Yves Saint-Laurent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He had a forward spring... And an early fall...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God gives us the ability, but rock 'n' roll was created by men.  - Little Richard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must either modify your dreams or magnify your skills. - Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Ankle Watches – Is This the New Place to Wear a Watch?  http://t.co/5FGzGM0lyF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Videos Games and Fitness with Wii and XBOX  http://t.co/Sr230s5vPA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is Ununpentium?  http://t.co/FFZZLuyjHb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where everything is possible miracles become common place, but the familiar ceases to be self-evident. - Eric Hoffer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotta love this Minecraft wall torch - http://t.co/RL3ZnTHk6E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is where you &amp; I are different. Because this is all I want to talk about. Letterman to Paris when she didn’t want to talk about jail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All men are born free and equal, but most of them get married.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your Attorney Search: The Advantages of Flat Rates  http://t.co/Eip7tO2yp4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious What Went Wrong T-shirt - Love It!  http://t.co/iQRG9H1wRi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's very strange writing science fiction in a world that moves as fast as ours does. - Daniel Keys Moran]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The Official How I Met Your Mother Premium Grey Silk Suit Jammies http://t.co/t8gTBGTFlZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Johnny Ace: A Life of Unfulfilled Dreams  http://t.co/9MkKpjmf7D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes are like friends, they can support you, or take you down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The whole purpose of education is to turn mirrors into windows. - Sydney J. Harris]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Return the shoes?! I can't talk to you when you're being hysterical! - Gabrielle, Desperate Housewives]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 3 - My Visit With Dr. McFadzean  http://t.co/8EiF6wE8cJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women need food, water, and compliments.  That's right.  And an occasional pair of shoes. Chris Rock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Google Webmaster Tools  http://t.co/csw9is8iEu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Coors Beer  http://t.co/TmgaLr4lNT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best way to show appreciation for a favor is to enjoy it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no room in baseball for discrimination. It is our national pastime and a game for all. - Lou Gehrig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 6 - Follow-up Appointment  http://t.co/hqq7jvSlBb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The eternal silence of these infinite spaces fills me with dread. - Blaise Pascal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dog has lots of friends because he wags his tail and not his tongue. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is better than poverty, if only for financial reasons. - Woody Allen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What people forget is that every movie that gets made keeps making money for somebody FOREVER. Dave Thomas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read The Story of the Dramatics Classic Rock Group http://t.co/iPYA0oS163]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I live by a simple philosophy: Wear fine shoes and enjoy the best luck. - Qiana Markham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome James Bond t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the 007 lovers in your life!   http://t.co/xXb3hqqmVn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good-bye, Broadcast.  Hello, Conversation.  Shel Israel - Co-Author Naked Conversations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction To http://t.co/oDCQQf5FLd  http://t.co/uUb8zyvug4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1,000 Incredible Costume and Cosplay Ideas http://t.co/ihpfBep9wu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the sun refused to shine I would still be loving you. When mountains crumble to the sea there will still be you &amp; me - Led Zeppelin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Condolence:  something that aches when everything else feels so good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Awesome Transformer 4GB USB Drives! http://t.co/mvdUYFTXQq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Corona Beer  http://t.co/TMNF4HZbij]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These Yoda Lights Must You Have!  Wonderful Geek Gear! http://t.co/CXxPP0pDyZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We thought you was a toad! - Delmar, O Brother Where Art Thou?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret of success is constancy to purpose. - Benjamin Disraeli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need to tie some kerosene rags around his ankles so the ants don't eat his candy #$@ - Dale Earnhardt speaking of Mark Martin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Five Guys Burgers and Fries  http://t.co/WxVc58hnAq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So what is Bitcoin and the Bitcoin block chain exactly? http://t.co/RPhbMgR2hA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you ain't making waves, you ain't kickin' hard enough - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome kayaking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the paddling lovers in your life!  http://t.co/f5HWaAAicf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't tell you what I had for breakfast, but I can sing every single word of rock and roll. - Patty Duke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Chordettes  http://t.co/TnDhMzpVO7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Left Banke  http://t.co/Uriy42dZB6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Tab Hunter - 1950s idol   http://t.co/LKmBjxIa7x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surviving a failure gives you more self-confidence. Failures are great learning tools.. but they must be kept to a minimum. - Jeffrey Immelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Questions to Ask a Lawyer Prior to Hiring Them  http://t.co/rgC9j6yOpt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life begins when we first realize how soon it ends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't speak ill of your predecessors or successors. You didn't walk in their shoes. - Donald Rumsfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought Europe was a country? Kellie Pickler, on "Are You Smarter Than A Fifth Grader"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The law gives a man the right to open his wife's mail, but not the nerve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He had a forward spring... And an early fall...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Put on your red shoes, and dance the blues. - David Bowie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome basketball t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the basketball lovers in your life!   http://t.co/arQS9net7V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sky is no longer the limit. - Richard M. Nixon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The universe, as far as we can observe it, is a wonderful and immense engine. - George Santayana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every day, in every way, I am getting better and better. - Emilie Coue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live daringly, boldly, fearlessly. Taste the relish to be found in competition - in having put forth the best within you. - Henry J. Kaiser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So exactly what is an atomic clock?  http://t.co/gegjCED6WS]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>