<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer/Architect: Description:Join a fast growing, solutions driven, dynamic organization and take your experience to the next level! Leidos has an immediate opportunity for a Systems Engineer to provide engineering support to the Airspace… https://t.co/Rdf5mlcurY https://t.co/EyVQkbQ5IE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Quality Engineering Manager (Software Testing): For Current Gilead Employees and Contractors: Please log onto your Internal Career Site to apply for this job. Job Description Specific Responsibilities and Skills for position: The Software Quality… https://t.co/JkqM2NaEA4 https://t.co/gBoTM0aaQn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hidden Alexa Commands, Cell Phone Tracking, and More Security News This Week: Hidden Alexa commands, cell phone tracking, and more security news this week. https://t.co/HyfWS8OEua https://t.co/qwTQcpFWPH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Project Manager – Buffalo, NY (26881): Requisition ID 26881 – Posted 04/16/2018 – IT / IS – United States – New York – Permanent Position Summary  Responsible for the overall direction, coordination, implementation, execution, control and completion… https://t.co/XwmWlYr1Ef https://t.co/rLRbZDi1rb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Implementation Specialist: Implementation Specialist We’re WELL and were the modern communication platform for the $3 trillion healthcare industry. Using WELL, patients engage with their healthcare teams on their schedule and based on their preferences.… https://t.co/SH3piYI9Lm https://t.co/hkxaOcZ6oL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test Data Architect – Seattle, WA: Test Data Architect Seattle, WA Full Time Position 12 15 Yrs Job Description: Should have minimum 12 to 15 years out of which Performed the role of Test Data architect or specialist for a minimum 4 years Have led and… https://t.co/Em31g8cwNR https://t.co/tUbSGT3UoH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ISC, Desktop Support Services: ISC, Desktop Support Services, #15435BR, Greenwood Village, CO, USMenu ToggleMenu Hide Home Life at Travelers Who We Are What We Do Why Join Travelers Community Involvement Diversity Locations Experienced Professionals… https://t.co/SJGny6RVUh https://t.co/KcjqijjpqT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HTC Vive Pro Review: An Expensive VR Upgrade: HTC’s Pro-grade headset is the most immersive VR system out there, and you probably shouldn’t buy it. https://t.co/sFrKNvjoJp https://t.co/phiskFuWkc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shipboard Installer: Description: The Defense &amp; Intelligence Group of Leidos has an immediate opening for a Shipboard Installer Field Technician based in San Diego, CA with extensive travel.  JOB SUMMARY:Shipboard Installer in support of the U.S. Navy… https://t.co/CIwcULGkai https://t.co/vS8jZZjiMU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developers – Mid to Sr. Level: Description:If you are a qualified Software Developer with a security clearance in the Omaha/Bellevue or surrounding areas and are interested in working a rewarding environment, we would like to meet with you!   … https://t.co/TWQWOtWBkj https://t.co/IHGzg5hrjN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Protection &amp; Control Engineer: Description: Lead Protection &amp; Control Engineer    Novi MI Leidos is a trusted and future-focused solutions provider. Utilities consistently come to Leidos for reliable power expertise, as reflected through our work… https://t.co/y7sBkvtwjq https://t.co/dKdZh8IzQ5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Facebook Binds—and Shatters—Communities: If a platform can provide community, we’ll gladly give up privacy—as we have throughout human history. https://t.co/hK0zQG9TlU https://t.co/kH5PAs9Fn0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VMWare Engineer: Description: The candidate will be a member of the engineering team responsible for the technical planning, system integration, verification/validation and support for total systems prior to being deployed to the production network. … https://t.co/7PAVtOAoGl https://t.co/FN777gzcks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Engineer: Description:The Civil Health Operation is currently seeking a System Engineer to support a large healthcare contract in Baltimore.   JOB DESCRIPTION: The candidate will be a member of an Operations Team providing support for all aspects… https://t.co/uDPDvkF5F5 https://t.co/LxwHBX3y6Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AWS Cloud Architect: Description:The Defense &amp; Intelligence group at Leidos has an opening for an AWS Cloud Architect. This group is migrating to the Cloud. They are standing up a new Cloud environment and looking for the expertise to migrate and… https://t.co/nK31tG77zM https://t.co/TggAg1Y3cp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boston Dynamics' Robot Dog Will Be Available Next Year: The secretive company has long been research-focused, but that doesn’t mean it hasn’t been thinking about what consumers want out of SpotMini. https://t.co/nUpjXVlbOu https://t.co/2nrT8jAVRq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solution Delivery Manager: Solution Delivery Manager What We Are Looking For In support of our key value of “Delivering Applause,” we are looking for a unique individual to build trusted advisor relationships with our customers, help those customers… https://t.co/nNFIWbaSUZ https://t.co/wsOK4RvMjP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Principal Systems Engr: 113438BR Sr Principal Systems Engr VA – Hampton 113438BR Raytheon Intelligence, Information and Services (IIS) is seeking an Enterprise Platform Operations IPT Lead to join our team in support of the Air Operations Center… https://t.co/i0SEqhK0ud https://t.co/jQajAzLQjQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advisory Financial Services Oracle Accounts Payable: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more… https://t.co/PVzDyyQ3cl https://t.co/28nSO0g4Zn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer Analyst – .NET: Programmer Analyst – .NETVDH66559667 *Richmond, VA*Resource will be part of the Messaging team and will be working on development of VERIP Phase II, Message tracking application phase II, LOINC codes filtering criteria by DSI… https://t.co/u4to7xj3se https://t.co/gcuhxxMSfj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce RDC Sr. Associate: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about us at… https://t.co/6P9hZkvvFF https://t.co/p0fPOMaSaQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Psychology of Amazon’s Echo Dot Kids Edition: The new Echo Dot Kids edition encourages kids to be polite, but psychologists and ethicists want parents to ask deeper questions than *will Alexa make my kid a jerk?* https://t.co/ftiAxFLwJD https://t.co/BphThYJw0C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Office 365 Achitect Manager – Consumer Market: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about… https://t.co/l47PMAzlzX https://t.co/2QVRDczSpb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Governance Information Architect, Taxonomist Sr. Associate: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify… https://t.co/cfvKFRWbe8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inside the Arena Where Drones Battle a Wall of 1,300 Computer Fans: In Caltech’s fancy new drone arena, the machines face terrifying atmospheric disturbances, all to help shape the future of flight. https://t.co/SPHgrB39Es https://t.co/XO5ivZRpEL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Photo Was Made With Radiation From Vintage Dishes: Peter Shellenberger uses old Fiestaware and Ektachrome film to make his autoradiographs. https://t.co/f24ak1flRE https://t.co/Z9Bk82Qo7k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Assurance Engineer: Req ID : 407865BR_5 Job Code/Title : E2541:Info Assurance Engineer Asc Job Description : Provides security engineering designs and implementation in all aspects of Information Assurance and Information Security (InfoSec)… https://t.co/yi21luKFiJ https://t.co/IeHvZxLjlK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GPS System Test Engineer: Trimble  is recruiting for a  GPS System Test Engineer to fill an opportunity in Sunnyvale, CA. Trimble is the market leader in precision high-performance GPS systems. We are seeking a self-motivated GPS System Test engineer… https://t.co/RkppdfWvwv https://t.co/W8jqoe4AUu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Process Analyst 3, Cost Management_Clearance Required:   Job Description – Business Process Analyst 3, Cost Management_Clearance Required (17012838) Business Process Analyst 3, Cost Management_Clearance Required Requisition ID : 17012838… https://t.co/IFnTc5wOX1 https://t.co/CmVi9H5N2R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Threat Analyst-Aberdeen Proving Grounds: Threat Analyst-Aberdeen Proving Grounds Aberdeen APG, MD SRI International is looking for a Threat Analyst to support a large contract in the APG area in support of the US Army Communications Electronic Command… https://t.co/oPDIAhzZP4 https://t.co/azi6rzafYn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer Software 3:   Job Description – Engineer Software 3 (18006320) Engineer Software 3 Requisition ID : 18006320 Location : United States-Colorado-Aurora US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation Assistance: Relocation assistance may… https://t.co/1soxM43vNl https://t.co/mJf29EECoa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lots of Doctors Recommend Weed Without Understanding It: Half of oncologists who recommended marijuana did so without feeling they had sufficient knowledge of the drug. https://t.co/R5i9gwORJh https://t.co/CKimqKMcUc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Network Communications Technician: Senior Network Communications Technician   Position Title Senior Network Communications Technician Announcement Summary Fayetteville Technical Community College is seeking qualified applicants for this critical… https://t.co/yy2UnnY8SK https://t.co/WrDHTTWc1k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AI Isn’t a Crystal Ball, But It Might Be a Mirror: Using algorithms to predict crimes has created a biased system: Better to use AI for looking inward. https://t.co/5Mvg7gDrzp https://t.co/jFrStF5vUa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Network Engineer: Applications are being accepted for the following vacancy on the Non-Teaching Professional staff of Hudson Valley Community College, 80 Vandenburgh Avenue, Troy, New York. Senior Network Engineer  HV-NTP-903 In order to be… https://t.co/Pum4Iaqz0e https://t.co/R49FisSQot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facial Recognition Tech Is Creepy When It Works—And Creepier When It Doesn’t: It's a powerful tool, but recent incidents have shown that there's no winning with facial recognition. https://t.co/bm1uBrlfCn https://t.co/sJG9CAv7qs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager-Health Care Construction: The Project Manager leads, directs and coordinates the day-to-day management of the healthcare project. ESSENTIAL DUTIES AND RESPONSIBILITIES Cultivate a high performance team through supervision, training,… https://t.co/jFiateES3Z https://t.co/q0ZBVPCaWg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Tornado's Secret Sounds Could Reveal Where It'll Strike: Tornadoes seem to emit sounds the human ear can't hear. That could help scientists develop better early detection systems. https://t.co/0SvsZxZDr1 https://t.co/iecFTtE56D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Mobile Developer: We are changing the way people communicate around the world! Our technology enables customer service to engage specialized services providing live collaboration solution utilizing real-time audio, text, and video. As a… https://t.co/iVkskyrZbY https://t.co/1iFTXHpCIw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Python: Python Developer – Springfield, VA -Looking for a full-stack Python Developer to help develop a project which will support Intelligence Agencies efforts to patrol the Dark Web. -Project will include prototype design all the… https://t.co/IQxKiRij1Y https://t.co/AOoZryqZ2c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Service Desk Analyst I: IT Service Desk Analyst I position available! The IT Service Desk Analyst I is responsible for providing support to end users on a variety of technical and computer related issues. Responsible for the continued upgrade and… https://t.co/XIUhSDONQa https://t.co/2fzFBa9kwi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did the Owl Do It? Unpacking the Weirdest Fan Theory About Netflix's 'The Staircase': A bizarre idea that never made the cut turns Netflix’s new-again docuseries into a true hoo-dunit. https://t.co/FiCuoosHWN https://t.co/HWxRRgWNro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Assistant #2769: Morris Area School District #2769 has an opening for a full time, year round, Technology Assistant. Job responsibilities include PC setup, troubleshooting and repair as well as providing technical support to district students… https://t.co/IMebjOWxiv https://t.co/zM0Mf1A2bn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FULL STACK DEVELOPER: Austin, TX Full-time $90k – $130k Posted Today If you are a FULL STACK DEVELOPER with experience, please read on! We are based in Austin, TX and are a cutting-edge technology platform that is disrupting the insurance and financial… https://t.co/P5EvEMS9cI https://t.co/8PjiBUejMc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: Search Display ****************************************************************************** &amp; siteid=5368 &amp; PageType=JobDetails &amp; jobid=******* ****************************************************************************** &amp;… https://t.co/FK2SAIt5bK https://t.co/CKVEuNKBYp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C++ Developer: C++ Developer Ref No.: 18-25449 Location: Charlotte, North Carolina Title:- C++ Developer Location:- Charlotte NC 1. Should possess strong technical skills to develop software using C++, Oracle PL/SQL and Unix Shell scripting. 2. Should be… https://t.co/aiseEE6gWU https://t.co/zuxVoI2m9O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer: COMPUTER/IT SAP Labs, LLC seeks a Senior Developer at our San Ramon, CA location to be responsible for development focusing on design, coding, testing, quality assurance of complex product features in a development team. Bach dgr in Comp Sci,… https://t.co/tx7MJkzdD3 https://t.co/46lTOUpgwQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Engineer: Engin 4, SW Devel &amp; Engin Comcast Cable Comm, LLC, Wayne, PA. Prvde tech leadrshp w/in team resp for develop &amp; manage Online Mgmt Syst Reqs: Bach in CS, Engin or rltd; 5 yrs exp dev enterprse-scale web app SW using C#,… https://t.co/MfZX6KkzAM https://t.co/LlZOJyQi7I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Engineer – Level II: ABOUT THE COMPANY: Are you a motivated individual who loves technology? Do you thrive in a fast paced environment? Love learning new technologies? Getting hands on experience? Have a great work ethic and… https://t.co/wG3SGbRg4E https://t.co/6613DUocb4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A War Over Bike Shares Is Shaking Up Seattle: Residents are divided over whether the city's dockless bike share program is revolutionizing transit—or creating an unwieldy, dangerous mess. https://t.co/vJSnz1IEgV https://t.co/0OjXuRvNTy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: About Wellist: Wellist gives healthcare leaders the tools and insights they need to improve patient experience by addressing unmet social needs across the care continuum. Wellists Integrated Patient Experience Solutions combines… https://t.co/EEej5Mzt3C https://t.co/GyVaiYRbat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Bubble Artisan Might Blow Up, But She Won't Go Pop: Melody Yang knows that bubbles are a lot like us—they need water, air, and a loving touch in order to thrive. https://t.co/vtfiGtm7pJ https://t.co/F964OAcrVL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test Analyst, Mid: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Vandenberg Air Force Base, CA Job Type: Strategy – Planning Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 5/30/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest… https://t.co/BTnSCCvFMj https://t.co/85q3Mj9XW1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Intelligence Manager: What you’ll be doing… You’re able to translate numbers into compelling stories—and tailor your presentation and recommendations to the audience function and level to meet their needs. You make connections between data… https://t.co/HEGr4UGA24 https://t.co/JAYRE9WjGy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Development Engineer DMTSE Devops: Systems Development Engineer – DMTSE Devops for Amazon in Herndon, VA 20170(map) DESCRIPTION The Developer Management and Tools System Engineering (DMTSE) team is looking for seasoned DevOps with CICD… https://t.co/w3rFTmpIhh https://t.co/xYEh0Am4sM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Potential Pitfalls of Sucking Carbon From the Atmosphere: A new method makes negative emissions more of a reality than ever before. https://t.co/MLLgMscVAY https://t.co/7VnGLGVsLm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Manager: Oracle America, Inc. has openings for Software Development Manager positions in Redwood Shores, CA. Job duties include: Apply knowledge of software architecture to manage software development tasks associated with… https://t.co/IhSpxqlgYS https://t.co/bFQLFp475L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Pro-Eating Disorder Posts Evade Filters on Social Media: A new study shows how sites like Instagram and Pinterest struggle to moderate pro-ED content—or even keep recommendation algorithms from surfacing it. https://t.co/j2UC074Yq5 https://t.co/Xqhnfg2IjT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer Analyst / Software Engineer: COMPUTER Miri Infotech Inc. seeks Programmer Analyst/ Software Engg. In Fremont, CA for design, develop, test &amp; support s/w projects in C#, https://t.co/VRgV5s9nrl, https://t.co/rSrpRctS32, SQL, HTML, XML.… https://t.co/26jRbFrANR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solutions Consultant: Computer: Solutions Consultant (Boulder, CO) Function as the internal or client-facing Google product expert. #1615.19545 Experience Includes: C++, C#, CSS, HTML, Java, Javascript, Perl, Python, Shell, or XML; SQL, relational… https://t.co/n6e56KgOyZ https://t.co/9x6Pt3UBUs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT-Assistant Vice President: IT-ASSISTANT VICE PRESIDENT (Research Triangle Park, NC): Support mission critical trading &amp; credit risk management applications utilizing Openlink Endur, C#, Java, J2EE, JMS, MQ, SQL, PL/SQL, AVS, Unix shell scripts &amp; XML.… https://t.co/wcXBiegRvd https://t.co/QJ3GdTbMK4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LA Is Doing Water Better Than Your City. Yes, That LA: With climate change on the horizon, Los Angeles is rushing to pull water from surprising sources. The goal: aqueous independence. https://t.co/LqcuzmaRHS https://t.co/RIGytsBEkD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Account Manager: Technical Account Manager Job Location US-CA-San Francisco Req No. 2017-2184 Category Engineering/Professional Services Overview The Technical Account Manager’s primary focus will be on cutting-edge AV solution design,… https://t.co/HfADnulHl7 https://t.co/XXsDryXkuF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watson Health – Client Experience Center Engagement Leader: Job Description At Watson Health, we empower leaders, advocates and influencers in health through support that helps them achieve remarkable outcomes, accelerate discovery, make essential… https://t.co/C6P0J6u6cw https://t.co/EXG8y7GnbE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feds Bust Dozens of Nigerian Email Scammers, but Your Inbox Still Isn’t Safe: The arrest of dozens of alleged Nigerian email scammers and their associates is a small, but important, first step toward tackling an enormous problem. https://t.co/uuPSzfkdbx https://t.co/IhCxuCqMJJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst: **CLIENT UNABLE TO SPONSOR AT THIS TIME*** ***PLEASE NO C2C VENDORS*** We are seeking a Senior Business Systems Analyst (BSA) to own solution definition and manage requirements for agile software projects. BSAs are responsible for all… https://t.co/psbADJ2O09 https://t.co/dDNsAIWrF4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Administrator: DBA Oklahoma City OK The Database Administrator will serve as a computer specialist in an Oracle Database Administrator role with the client. The role will support a variety of Oracle-specific solutions including, but not limited… https://t.co/Etqhdr7Ovq https://t.co/1CBzJZJ0r0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With a 'Lite' App, Uber Moves to Win Over India: Uber Lite should make the ride-hailing service easier to use in emerging markets where service is spotty and data is limited. https://t.co/FCn1pZypFu https://t.co/IqllKeXifk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Security Architect #80259P: IT Services (ITS) at Iowa State is seeking applicants for a Security Architect. This position will help define, architect and oversee implementation of security of campus systems including network and endpoint devices. This… https://t.co/UP3IYbcyga]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Center Specialist #80236P: Information Technology Services at Iowa State University is seeking qualified applicants for a Data Center Specialist. The Data Center Specialist will be responsible for supporting ISU’s data center infrastructure, and… https://t.co/pK1guXEym0 https://t.co/5dzebQkHtm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering: COMPUTER/IT Senior Developer for Ariba, Inc. (Palo Alto, CA) to install &amp; maintain critical sys’s running red Hat Enterprise Linux &amp; Suse Linux employing enterprise cluster apps in 24×7 datacenter environ. Bachelor’s in Comp Sci, Eng’g,… https://t.co/DA2iqO8MpP https://t.co/gi9BpIHCL0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AI Made a Movie With a 'Silicon Valley' Star—and the Results Are Nightmarishly Encouraging: Benjamin, as the AI is known, assembled 'Zone Out' from thousands of hours of old films and green-screen footage of professional actors—in 48 hours. https://t.co/Dj1oMkNHMW https://t.co/MaNSjjnrwF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. ERP Analyst – Finance: Sr. ERP Analyst – Finance 3169 Holcomb Bridge Rd, Jefferson Plaza Norcross, Georgia, 30071 United States The opportunity: WestRock is currently recruiting for a Sr. ERP Analyst – Finance reporting to Director, Center of… https://t.co/scbxKJLRUt https://t.co/6By3zJDf7f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Estimator – Heavy Civil, Pipeline, Trenching: San Francisco, CA Full-time Compensation Unspecified Posted Today If you are a Estimator with experience, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us – Competitive base salary DOE – Full Benefits! – Fast… https://t.co/bJ6CdNaJft https://t.co/wiimtFB9L2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Engineer – Heavy Civil, Pipeline, Trenching: San Francisco, CA Full-time Compensation Unspecified Posted Today If you are a Project Engineer with experience, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us – Competitive base salary DOE – Full… https://t.co/EGjf1xy9ao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inside Anduril, Palmer Luckey's Bid to Build a Border Wall: How the Oculus founder, along with ex-Palantir executives, plans to reinvent national security, starting with Trump's agenda. https://t.co/JeOlEw1Ils https://t.co/dmeNHpUcw0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Software Engineer Automotive: Ready to turn the wheel in the _AUTOMOTIVE _industry with a _HYPERGROWTH STARTUP_? MULTINATIONAL AUTOMOTIVE MANUFACTURER has already established connected car technologies abroad and are on the verge of the biggest… https://t.co/YV2deGtO3R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How a Uranium Hunter Sniffs Out Nuclear Weapons: Every bit of uranium ore has a chemical fingerprint specific to its source on Earth. Track the metal, and you can track the ne’er-do-well who took it. https://t.co/xXopMyzW9f https://t.co/dIVf4SXXGa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Directors, Analytics &amp; Research: Directors, Analytics &amp; Research The Travelers Indemnity Company has openings in Hartford, CT, for Directors, Analytics &amp; Research. Directs variety of statistical analysis, including data mining, predictive modeling &amp;/or… https://t.co/Yg4XOZVNwc https://t.co/1Z6ZxIuvYs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Westworld' Recap, Season 2 Episode 8: The Great Ghost Nation Mystery: Turns out many of those fan theories about Westworld's warriors were way off the mark. https://t.co/Ll7qf8QJCe https://t.co/Dqwf9S5s8K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Lead: Technical LeadPhoton Infotech, Inc.Dallas, TX Photon Infotech, Inc. has opening for Technical Lead (Participate in the design review with the development team &amp; provide review comments. Identifying gaps in the backend core services layer… https://t.co/RimLccQthW https://t.co/muEVn7wyWv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Compliance Operations Analysts, Member of Technical Staff, Sr. Technical Recruiters: VMware, Inc. has multiple openings at various professional levels in Austin, TX. The following software engineering positions develop and/or execute software, testing… https://t.co/lTnwRyCLuK https://t.co/4Gj7dhoLPj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Communications Specialist: IT Services (ITS) at Iowa State is seeking applicants for a Communications Specialist. This position will develop written and visual communication strategies for the ITS business unit. Responsibilities also include managing the… https://t.co/Vtt2dX9EHo https://t.co/oXHh6AyBjq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With Cortex, Land Rover Takes Self-Driving Cars Off-Roading: Land Rover always delivers capability and convenience, and that means teaching its cars to drive themselves where the roads don't go. https://t.co/8x5OXgj5RT https://t.co/2yGz5zvuHw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Portfolio Data Analyst: – Portfolio Data Analyst Job Locations US-WV-Parkersburg Posted Date 1 day ago(5/14/2018 1:23 PM) Job ID 2018-3528 # of Openings 1 Category RetailMarket/Branch Wood Responsibilities JOB SUMMARY: The Portfolio Data Analyst conducts… https://t.co/G90qIAyGsO https://t.co/iJpk69l2ma]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales Engineer, Marking &amp; Coding for LATAM:   Job Description – Sales Engineer, Marking &amp; Coding for LATAM (38719) Job Description  Sales Engineer, Marking &amp; Coding for LATAM-38719 Description   Company: Hitachi America, Ltd. Division: Industrial… https://t.co/5pq2GCHXPW https://t.co/0k1XN9pbK0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automation Tester 3:   Job Description – Automation Tester 3 (18007941) Automation Tester 3 Requisition ID : 18007941 Location : United States-Virginia-Alexandria US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation Assistance: No relocation… https://t.co/2QBXWvSQjv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of Us and the Dream of a Research Diversity Crusader: The billion-dollar, 10-year All of Us initiative promises to sequence and study the health of 1 million Americans. But will they represent the diversity of the country's population? https://t.co/HJyWusAC6E https://t.co/7wHrdHZIWt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staff Network Engineer: Job Description What you’ll be doing… Staff engineer with skills appropriate to Tier II-level incident response and change management activity. Assists senior engineers with the implementation of efficiency and automation… https://t.co/wXDYgAsTY9 https://t.co/rcgYDSZLTL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Brought 'Sense8' Back—and What Killed It in the First Place: Weird, risky sci-fi has an uphill battle, and it's going to take a very long time until that changes. https://t.co/2sN7SoDoBb https://t.co/7EuMctuWEU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer in Test, Automation Framework: Software Engineer in Test, Automation Framework | Tesla Tesla, Inc – Model S – Model X – Model 3 – Roadster – Energy – – Shop – Shop – Tesla Account – Sign In More – News – Inventory – New Inventory – Used… https://t.co/CkbHMRXU2B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Solo: A Star Wars Story' Should Have Been Two Movies: A second film could've explored where Han Solo got his cynical, jaded attitude. https://t.co/GMQOEjL7ES https://t.co/Xjlqf5LFP4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can You Spot the Hidden Images in These Psychedelic Landscapes?: Terri Loewenthal uses self-made reflective optics to compose scenes that look like double exposures but are actually single shots. https://t.co/JtQytzQbPZ https://t.co/jqYach8IRr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: LawnStarter [*************************** is looking for a Senior Backend Engineer to join our growing product development team. LawnStarter is a fast growing startup with an engineering team that prides itself on high energy,… https://t.co/q6TkfVLhQg https://t.co/NNGeKZUG8l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 Weekend Tech Deals for Father’s Day Gifts: Get a head start on your Father’s Day shopping. https://t.co/3uZMHlpCWl https://t.co/xiHj57gCVh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lyft Redesigns Its App—and Strategy—for the Age of Sharing: Believing sharing is key to its longterm success, the Uber rival is doing everything it can to get more people into fewer cars. https://t.co/fBR6hHbI9o https://t.co/QqiVcXcA8G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Britannica Insights Is a Chrome Extension to Fix False Google Results: Encyclopedia Britannica released a Chrome extension designed to fix Google's sometimes inaccurate "featured snippets." https://t.co/26V6CzeOQl https://t.co/WtCW0gFSx1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solution Architect: Job Opportunity: Solution Architect Job Location: Charlotte, NC (headquarter) with work-at-home option available for all cities through-out the U.S. Duties: Produce integrated or converged designs across multiple solutions, supporting… https://t.co/zOHiz6Ovw9 https://t.co/wJo8nbxkTY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Security Architect #80259P: IT Services (ITS) at Iowa State is seeking applicants for a Security Architect. This position will help define, architect and oversee implementation of security of campus systems including network and endpoint devices. This… https://t.co/tTe7JAH4vL https://t.co/WoRgCyv7Ns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Airbus Rattles the Beluga XL in the Name of Safety: Before it can make its maiden flight this summer, the enormous, glorious cargo plane must survive the static ground vibration test. https://t.co/dzHXVwDMjG https://t.co/R9fZe8aUqf]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>