<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[We (San Francisco) have football weather during baseball season, and baseball weather during football season. - Herb Caen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Race cars are neither beautiful nor ugly. They become beautiful when they win. - Enzo Ferrari]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He was born with a silver spoon --  but  never made a stir with it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Asked a woman in an art store, "you don't consider this horrible thing art, do you" "No madam" replied the dealer, it's a mirror.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's so nervous he keeps coffee awake]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clarity trumps persuasion.  Dr. Flint McGlaughlin - Director MECLABS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of McDonald's  http://t.co/8rLbDV5xRH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read an Introduction to Sonic Drive-In  http://t.co/VOU5F1CG3e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is one AMAZING Kate Upton poster - gorgeous http://t.co/9USvfJwfO3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You think dogs will not be in heaven? I tell you, they will be there long before any of us - Robert Louis Stevenson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A teacher affects eternity; he can never tell where his influence stops. - Henry Brooks Adams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of John Lennon  http://t.co/IGmJQeyQYR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Trade School Programs  http://t.co/xAk7FvIxzw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The probable reason some people get lost in thought is because it is unfamiliar territory to them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They just couldn't live without each other --  so they got married and discovered they could]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never threw an illegal pitch. The trouble is, once in a while I toss one that ain't never been seen by this generation. - Satchel Paige]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The internet has turned what used to be a controlled, one-way message into a real-time dialogue with millions - Danniel Sacks, Fast Company]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marriage lets you annoy and aggravate one special person for the rest of your life.  What a joy LOL!!  :&gt;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is a social process. Education is growth. Education is, not a preparation for life; education is life itself.  - John Dewey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's like saying Prada's are just shoes, or vodka is just a morning beverage! - Karen, Will &amp; Grace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introducing to the SEO Power Suite  http://t.co/5lCQzMPSHb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consider the Tuba an Amazing Instrument  http://t.co/Bpjb7OmyqT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're either making money or you're not. If you're not making money get out of the business. Meredith Whitney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the God Particle – Higgs Boson – On the Run  http://t.co/zzA4KfM0tO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My advice if you insist on slimming: Eat as much as you like - just don't swallow it. - Harry Secombe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cocaine is God's way of saying you're making too much money. - Robin Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He ran out of talent about halfway through the corner. - Buddy Baker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who Needs a Boyfriend to Snuggle With This Pillow! http://t.co/Kky5CydClw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know money is the root of all evil if you would like to find out more - just send me $10 - DM me ASAP !!  :&gt;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Amazing Big Bag Of Science! http://t.co/COVJ6WPOts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be back - The Terminator]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A classic TV sit-com - the fascinating history of Andy Griffith - they didn’t get along with sweet Aunt Bee?  http://t.co/ikNMlXGkaG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love science fiction. - Pam Grier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Book review of the Inheritance series – Eldest By Christopher Paolini  http://t.co/tgosU5IDTB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Habit is habit and not to be flung out of the window by any man, but coaxed downstairs a step at a time. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Three Styles of BMX Bikes and their Uses  http://t.co/Xt3TWHWHlz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You had me at meow - Wall Decal - theband4: You had me at meow cute funny cat dog pet vinyl wall quotes... http://t.co/QkUzV2JHjC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So say we all. - Battlestar Galactica]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How To Find The Right Gluten Free Foods  http://t.co/8eGz6LQPyM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schools to NOT Get Your Creative Writing Degree At  http://t.co/h1ur0HbZw2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education costs money, but then so does ignorance. - Sir Claus Moser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really &amp; truly you can never have 2 many pairs of shoes. You need a pair for every mood &amp; everyone knows women have lots of moods. Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome fine wine t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the wine lovers in your life!  http://t.co/MEWo8G9nnV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Politicians should read science fiction, not westerns and detective stories. - Arthur C. Clarke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To err is human, to forgive, canine - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the Devine RPG Minecraft Mod - http://t.co/vBgpHrAVS4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Media are tools.  Real time is mindset.  David Scott - Marketing Strategist - Author of The New Rules of Marketing and PR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science fiction is not predictive; it is descriptive. - Ursula K. LeGuin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of McDonald's  http://t.co/8rLbDV5xRH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Harmless Version Of the Original Russian Roulette - Great for Parties! http://t.co/89t1oakjd2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About BMX Biking Born from Freestyle Motocross  http://t.co/MIkYdiIhoa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Windows has detected you do not have a keyboard. Press 'F9" to continue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it's too close to bother to buckle your seat belt it's close enough to walk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool iPhone 4 Review  http://t.co/9AaRruJXSE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the top science fiction books of all time!  http://t.co/mMTH3bpU7o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Different Types of Ashes Scattering Services  http://t.co/DU7CR2B0D7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool Geek Tech - Mini USB Fan - Keep cool at your desk! --&gt; http://t.co/LSbnmb87qM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All men are born free and equal, but most of them get married.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Silver Plated "Privates" Scratcher - For the Busy Executive http://t.co/rSdcOvVvIP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Jackson Five  http://t.co/8ammM0weMy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to that hilarious sit-com Three’s Company - http://t.co/KDJrc6QZHj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even on the most solemn occasions I got away without wearing socks and hid that lack of civilization in high boots --&gt; Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top Films of the 1950s - theband4: http://t.co/vPd4UttJ7z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The right man is the one who seizes the moment. - Johann Wolfgang von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first and the best victory is to conquer self. - Plato]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome disco t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the disco lovers in your life!   http://t.co/eaQTlFH9va]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Benefits of iPads for Seniors  http://t.co/XRtRu7r0JE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Heineken Phone Case --&gt; http://t.co/ScP43HAfFL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to Tumblr Blogging  http://t.co/JvuublNrR4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet - very cool mechanical pin clock - very unique - http://t.co/xzobtG4Frj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of John Lennon  http://t.co/IGmJQeyQYR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who think they know everything are especially annoying to those of us who do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Brief History and Introduction to Bitcoin  http://t.co/EnNI37yOMQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Hire a Strategy Consulting Firm?  http://t.co/WN1f1SWjPy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which Is Better -- A Cat or A Dog? - theband4: Like a dog-and-cat fight, this debate has been going for... http://t.co/YNvFy0kCwX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top Films of the 1950s - theband4: http://t.co/tfsqola1Ox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You had me at meow - Wall Decal - theband4: You had me at meow cute funny cat dog pet vinyl wall quotes... http://t.co/ZqfhXhZ9V2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Far and away the best prize that life offers is the chance to work hard at work worth doing. - Theodore Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes transform your body language and attitude. They lift you physically and emotionally. - Christian Louboutin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The scenery was very beautiful. But I did not see the Great Wall. - Yang Liwei, China's first astronaut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 8 - North Texas Lyme Support Group  http://t.co/S0omHH363W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Strategy Consulting Firms to Avoid  http://t.co/yA8TooptkI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do women want? Shoes. --&gt; Mimi Pond]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Create your own Ice, Chocolate, Jelly in the shape of Han Solo in Carbonite!!!  http://t.co/NWoJTZm9Re]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome ping pong &amp; table tennis tshirts &amp; gear - get something for the paddle lovers in your life! http://t.co/NAC8YZG14J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest lie you can make is to lie to yourself. - Matt Zotti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your body is the baggage you must carry through life. The more excess the baggage, the shorter the trip. - Arnold H. Glasgow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The noblest search is the search for excellence - Lyndon B. Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Interesting Burger Facts and History  http://t.co/p7NfAn1yi2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apollo: I will not serve under a man who questions my integrity. Adama: And I won't have an officer under my command who doesn't have any.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Radiation Detection Equipment - Providing the Equipment Necessary to Protect Those That Protect Us  http://t.co/do93krlQ4w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money cant buy happiness, but it sure makes misery easier 2 live with!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good teaching is one-fourth preparation and three-fourths pure theatre. - Gail Godwin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Clash  http://t.co/wqnUbCIRkM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Celiac Disease And Gluten Free Foods  http://t.co/WZSzPf8cNC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would you say I have a plethora of pinatas? - El Guapo, ¡Three Amigos!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Remote Control Inflatable Flying Shark! AWESOME! http://t.co/nYNH3N7uVa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Car sickness is the feeling you get when the monthly payment is due. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome gardening t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the gardening lovers in your life!   http://t.co/7X8M2B1kuH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read a Review of Heaven is For Real  http://t.co/wwUDArK7wA]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>