<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Or sort of, anyway. "The Global X Guru fund was up 47 percent in 2013, a year when the average hedge fund returned 9.3 percent."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One interesting question about spoofing is: How easy is it to spot?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He said the environment at Post has improved and that he’s friends with many of the employees.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which, I mean. You can see why "nonono my boss made $276 million; I only made $9.4 million" would not be a super-sympathetic argument.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People are worried about bond market liquidity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hedge fund advertisers 
like hedge fund advertising
. There's a hedge fund, I guess, called Topturn Capital.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(That is: About $8.5 billion worth of investor money, in about 30 pots, providing credit protection on $98 billion of notional. )]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They'd almost have been crazy not to manipulate Libor. Though, as always, it would have been better not to do it in writing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now it's trying to sell the mines at a loss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“THESE NO LONGER EXIST!” OK. First of all: This is bad PowerPoint. Too much text.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be fair, no one expects negative CDS trades any time soon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But for companies? Baofeng is up over 1,600 percent since its IPO.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When there is only one venue, we find that the Last Look option reduces quoted spreads.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OK. There's also an international ranking, in which Ivey Business School at Western University in Ontario comes out on top.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The trick is for the regulation to be right, not tough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And: "Bond traders miss out in bankers’ pay rise."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We can build a product for you that will give you peace of mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is sort of rough on JPMorgan, since much of the point of the settlement was to keep those draft complaints out of the public eye.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do retail investors who say they want to buy an IPO draw that distinction? And do they change their minds that often before pricing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taleb and Today’s Fragile Bond Market" is the headline here, and the argument is that "markets are fragile when they are crowded."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe, but the direction of the governance failures is inconsistent.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Winding down an investment bank with a big American investment banker in charge of the group is going to be challenging,” the person said.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consider the various bills recently introduced in Congress trying to codify the ban on insider trading.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's possible that bankruptcy rules are priced into credit, but a lot of this stuff seems pretty marginal for pricing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So there is an argument that delaying the public reporting of large trades will improve liquidity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nobody announces a murder indictment by saying that murder is harmful. People know that murder is harmful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And if everyone thinks those people are "predatory," then, well, one option is to just pretend that they're not there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They expect never to see their money again, so they won't go looking for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["This changes everything," says a lawyer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's not expecting a numbered list of 22 reasons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can understand why -- it literally advertised that it was a Bitcoin Ponzi scheme! That was the name!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Narcissists have no self-worth, so they need a status symbol outside themselves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who gets to define insider trading? There's no law against insider trading.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While we're on the subject of Wells Fargo, here is the story of some Wells Fargo employees who are protesting sales quotas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The Justice Department could pursue settlements with large U.S. regional banks when these settlements are over."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And somehow neither the issuer, nor the underwriters, nor the buyers of the bonds notice that this isn't true.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you like listening to sensible and thoughtful 25-minute podcasts about bond market liquidity, there you go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People are worried about bond market liquidity. "The Next Meltdown?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Others, however, say the amazing part is that the bank was able to get away with it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And a lot of people have criticized Valeant's accounting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The "typically reported management fees" would be the net 125 basis points (165 - 50 x 0.8).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This campaign has puzzled me a bit, since shareholders don't, qua shareholders, care.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But there's no particular reason to think that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There will be 
bonuses of some sort

It's that wonderful time of year when financial services employees speculate about their bonuses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That threat focused their minds, and that focus led to a deal -- and a 50+ percent profit for Pershing Square in less than a year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're abandoning so much of investment banking, I suppose your investment bank will be worth less.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Bloomberg View colleague Barry Ritholtz has further criticism of hedge funds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you bought GoPro in the IPO, you do not look like a sucker. So why object to the waiver?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(We call it "wrong-way risk," or just, like, sell some shares?)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baofeng is up over 1,600 percent since its IPO. That IPO raised 214 million yuan at a market capitalization of 856 million yuan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(Think of the alicorn as Uber, for not dying of poison.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cliff Asness on HFT
. Asness and his crew at AQR Capital Management have a very interesting and thorough defense of high frequency trading.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's going to be a rough hundred years at Barclays.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Con: If you grind the banks down to nothing then you don't have banks any more, and didn't you want banks?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So it did, and then something something something money laundering, it's a bit of a mess.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is not an equivalent movement on factory conditions, but there's something even odder.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I wanted to be the one making decisions," says 29-year-old Stanford grad Alex Gelman.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And, refreshingly, it doesn't mention the sort-of-insider-trading stuff at all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I remain skeptical of the idea that it is unusually hard to prove white collar crimes, but you do need some proof.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It "has been a complete mess from the very beginning," according to a former bidder for the contract to operate it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unicorns. With the slow death of bond market liquidity worries I'm auditioning other recurring features for this space.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For another, the mere threat of activists seems to be enough to win the banks (also presumably paid) anti-activist assignments.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In other tax news, the IRS won't give identity-theft victims copies of the fake tax returns filed in their names.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All I can come up with is financial journalists; is that the target audience here?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Currency markets are being investigated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UBS sold the funds, the funds lost value, the investors sued, and the tape recordings of that sales meeting came out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*** So he stopped the deal, which was scheduled to close yesterday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Valeant tried to be friends with Allergan for a few days.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's one thing to have a rogue employee secretly getting confidential information from a regulator.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you even know that Goldman Sachs owned coal mines?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you received a misdirected e-mail that created a material risk to Goldman Sachs's financial performance, do let us know in the comments.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things are bad, if you're in the oil business.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I actually find it kind of weird that Mercuria agreed a dollar price for the business without negotiating whether Masters comes with it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone else lives in a culture that retains a strong primitive belief in the possibility of financial magic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now it's perfectly reasonable to dislike the practice of breaking trades.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The more you regulate banks, the more expensive it is to comply with the regulations, and those costs don't grow linearly with size.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The partnership agreements disclose the management fees, the existence of monitoring fees, the rebate structure, etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why own lots of shares and short a few shares?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Active vs. passive. One weird thing that you could worry about is that index funds have a tragedy-of-the-commons element to them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So if you were long with client money this morning, sorry!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 
stories of business
. Do other people enjoy reading the Harvard Business Review's blog as much as I do?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Though there is the issue of, how do you claw back a bonus if it's already been spent?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sharp permanent drop in asset prices is scary. A sharp temporary drop in asset prices is kind of funny, honestly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RemcoLenterman 
Airbnb might be worth 
more than Hyatt
.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RemcoLenterman And of course TPG's complaint is just one side of the story and might be wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matt_levine Like Valeant, however, it too has legal issues with R&amp;O.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no reason to think this would benefit shareholders; quite the reverse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matt_levine Also probably like 90 percent of what you read on the Internet today will be false!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tracyalloway I'd imagine that Bank of New York would not want to stand for re-election at that point, though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You pay people like entrepreneurs and they will act like entrepreneurs and invent mortgage-backed derivatives.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't want to give legal advice blah blah blah but can you spot what's wrong with this e-mail?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So ... are those fees too much, or too little, or just right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's one of these platforms announced every week or two, and really one or more of them has to catch on eventually.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey those are numbers, so you can measure them, and they're going up, which mean they're good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This one is about SXP Analytics, accused of stealing trading code from Quantlab Financial.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The problem with Wall Street is that we're not paying whistleblowers enough. So the Justice Department wants to pay them more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Net income was $5.6 billion, or $1.36 a share, versus $1.39 estimates. Legal costs were 26 cents a share, why not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's illegal enough that the Internal Revenue Service can take your money without ever charging you with a crime, anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wells Fargo says the ratio clocked in at 8:1 in 2014, versus 7:1 in 2013 and 3.8:1 in 2010.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fact that Goldman could mount a legal defense here is not really the point of these tapes.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>