<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Any manager who can't get along with a .400 hitter is crazy. - Joe McCarthy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Dan Fogelberg  http://t.co/BvSGhC0NjO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flattery, like perfume, should be smelled, not swallowed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Successfully Use Other Websites for Link Building  http://t.co/2hq8e9p3nM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A horse gallops with his lungs, Perseveres with his heart, And wins with his character. - Tesio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like flying jet fighters in a gymnasium - Dick Trickle was asked what racing at Winchester Speedway was like.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anthony “Tony” Harris, CSECO President and CEO, receives an Honorary Doctorate in Engineering from Purdue University  http://t.co/g0bw2sDDfF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why worry about death, it'll come sooner or later. - Jim Dunn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Electric Light Orchestra  http://t.co/9o2YDgY8rC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am the best in baseball. - Reggie Jackson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Kansas  http://t.co/lAO2HQl68D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have the end in mind and every day make sure your working towards it - Ryan Allis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Tom Petty and the Heartbreakers  http://t.co/FoygOjim0U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's face it: The teeth are getting more and more British every day. I look in the mirror and see Austin Powers staring at me.  Hugh Grant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the darkness of the world cannot put out the light on one small candle. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Steve Miller Band  http://t.co/e33XkSfWf9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money was never a big motivation for me, except as a way to keep score. The real excitement is playing the game. - Donald Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana’s Lyme Journey – Part 16 – Seven Months Later  http://t.co/UXCZHqM284]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can never be overdressed or overeducated. --&gt; Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Ten Years After classic Rock Group?  http://t.co/OxTaHudXd8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the math geek in your life - the math clock... http://t.co/fR7ngIuFDm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the goodness of a good egg cannot make up for the badness of a bad egg...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opera in English is, in the main, just about as sensible as baseball in Italian. - Henry Louis Mencken]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I live in heels. Give me a pair of flip-flops and I'll trip all over myself. - Brenda Song]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The studios have been taken over by marketing people and accountants. - Joe Eszterhas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Wonderful History of Tulips  http://t.co/wdYQMCkgCr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Wendy's  http://t.co/r60lvWbzq7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have no use for bodyguards, but I have very specific use for two highly trained certified public accountants. - Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the The Burning Bridge by John Flanagan  http://t.co/Abd5ksFeLw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never realized how boring this game was.  - Homer Simpson while watching baseball while sober]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't read other science fiction. I don't read any at all. - Jack Vance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet Stay Thirsty My Friends Dos Equis T-Shirt - Most Interesting Main In the World - http://t.co/osyb54qgV1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Brief History and Introduction to Bitcoin  http://t.co/VydyWphH1D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who will wear a shoe that hurts him, because the shoe-maker tells him 'tis well made? - Algernon Sydney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Some Very Interesting and Unusual Beers  http://t.co/qjEJ48bfQI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One person with courage makes a majority. - Andrew Jackson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who think they know everything are especially annoying to those of us who do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A respectable appearance is sufficient to make people more interested in your soul --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually, I majored in marketing and I have a bachelor of science. - Wanda Sykes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotta Love It - 12 Nerd Rubber Duckies!  Makes Bath Time Fun!  http://t.co/ZH17qRC61S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Driving a car is like playing baseball. The object in both is to get home safely. - Joe Moore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet - very cool mechanical pin clock - very unique - http://t.co/HEevEklBKL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dogs are not our whole life, but they make our lives whole. - Roger Caras]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this gallery of the top 10 European beers!  http://t.co/4YXBpO6ZKq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The difference between gossip and news is whether you hear it or tell it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science fiction films are not about science. They are about disaster, which is one of the oldest subjects of art. - Susan Sontag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of In-N-Out Burger  http://t.co/qRDUMjwJID]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cinderella is living proof that a pair of shoes can change your life…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Damita Jo  http://t.co/s51rOW4EZr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overwhelming underdogs. - Yogi Berra While Referring to the 1969 New York Mets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Chordettes  http://t.co/MG0YKeSXdw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you wish to grow thinner, diminish your dinner. - Henry Sambrooke Leigh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is Renter's Insurance?  http://t.co/fUbPllEQmv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NERD POWER Pin Button - Must Wear! http://t.co/20B0KR56Vr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be Prepared!  Learn About these Bartering Resources  http://t.co/vPr4H8Lskb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our Review of Amazon’s Popular Kindle Reader  http://t.co/Dtni6sy5de]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The purity of a person's heart can be quickly measured by how they regard animals - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best possible thing in baseball is winning the World Series. The second best thing is losing the World Series. - Tommy Lasorda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rock n' roll is dream soup, what's your brand? - Patti Smith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By working faithfully eight hours a day you may eventually get to be a boss and work twelve hours a day. - Robert Frost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Who is The Grass Roots Classic Rock Group?  http://t.co/TASkon6Ub9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So say we all. - Battlestar Galactica]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Ramones  http://t.co/Of2Wj8CRPf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Totally Cool 80s Retro iPhone Case http://t.co/yqvKWEuNhZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Increasingly, search is our mechanism for how we understand ourselves our world, and our place with in it.  John Battelle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cooking - A Simple Way To Bond With Kids  http://t.co/YHiyQ1tExF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion changes, but style endures. --&gt; Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a moral imperative. - Chris Knight, Real Genius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this gallery of the top 10 Asian beers!  http://t.co/qRYlWEOI2w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Playing baseball is not real life. It's a fantasy world... It's a dream come true. - Dale Murphy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is not a technology.  It's a conversation. And it's happening with our with out you.  Charlene Li - Co-Author Groundswell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Condolence:  something that aches when everything else feels so good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A little smile adds a good deal to a faces value]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The great difficulty in education is to get experience out of ideas. - George Santayana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Donovan  http://t.co/2DsZSZXiZU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wal-mart --  do they like make walls there?  Paris Hilton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought Europe was a country? Kellie Pickler, on "Are You Smarter Than A Fifth Grader"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Corona Beer  http://t.co/Q0SHQCQDjw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome burgers and beer t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the beer &amp; beer lovers in your life!  http://t.co/oIIZv56Woz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes make me happy. - Actress Lauren Conrad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overwhelming underdogs. - Yogi Berra While Referring to the 1969 New York Mets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it bleeds, we can kill it.  - Predator]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who will wear a shoe that hurts him, because the shoe-maker tells him 'tis well made? - Algernon Sydney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Tools for Finding Good Keywords  http://t.co/hItuXBhnVC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I look at modeling as something I'm doing for black people in general. Naomi Campbell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schools to NOT Get Your Creative Writing Degree At  http://t.co/AL1oBhE017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Powerful Tools For Your Internet Marketing Program    http://t.co/Cqewgk9kTp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read Great Outdoor Camping Equipment Tips  http://t.co/TkaOzKl8Qn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I won't be a rock star. I will be a legend. - Freddie Mercury]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A girl should be two things: classy and fabulous. - Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The road to success is dotted with many tempting parking places. - Unknown Author]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The lead car is absolutely unique, except for the one behind it which is identical. - F1 commentator Murray Walker.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Peter Cetera  http://t.co/qiWZ3PusTG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Institutions that once had to go through media to deliver information are now themselves media - Andrew Nachison - Founder We Media]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to Tumblr Blogging  http://t.co/RmLGeN13eD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Mountain Climbing from Novice to Experts  http://t.co/rUoluJgziM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Jimmy Choo  http://t.co/l826dIf60J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Early History of Marvel Comics  http://t.co/vjXZvDKJiy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only thing worse than a Mets game is a Mets double header. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making the Most of Twitter for Your Business  http://t.co/OzfNocqGyF]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>