<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[... "A man never knows how to say goodbye; a woman never knows when to say it" - Helen Rowland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... Bible: "The path of the just is as the shining light, that shineth more and more unto the perfect day."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "The history of free men is never really written by chance but by choice; their choice" - Dwight David Eisenhower]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "Positive anything is better than negative nothing" - Elbert Hubbard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... Groucho Marx: "I find television very educating. Every time somebody turns on the set, I go into the other room and read a book."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "Beware when the great God lets loose a thinker on this planet" - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... Gilbert Keith Chesterton: "People generally quarrel because they cannot argue."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... William Blackstone: "It is better that ten guilty persons escape than that one innocent suffer."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... Eric Hoffer: "When people are free to do as they please, they usually imitate each other."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... No religion is a true religion that does not make men tingle to their finger tips with a sense of infinite hazard - William Ernest Hocki]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "In order to be irreplaceable one must always be different" - Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "A person starts to live when he can live outside himself" - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "Of all men's miseries the bitterest is this: to know so much and have control over nothing" - Herodotus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "Time will explain it all. He is a talker, and needs no questioning before he speaks" -  Euripides]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "You have to decide even to hesitate. - Stanislaw Jerzy Lec]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "Universities are designed for the convenience of the faculty, not for the convenience of the students" - Adam Smith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "The more you judge, the less you love" - Honore de Balzac]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "In a world of hunchbacks a fine figure becomes a monstrosity" - Honore de Balzac]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "Victory belongs to the most persevering" - Napoleon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... Edgar Watson Howe: "A woman is as old as she looks before breakfast."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... Malcolm X: "Nobody can give you freedom. Nobody can give you equality or justice or anything. If you're a man, you take it."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "Man spends his life in reasoning on the past, in complaining of the present, in fearing future" - Antoine de Rivarol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "Do not let what you cannot do interfere with what you can do" - John Wooden]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "Take your work seriously, but never yourself" - Dame Margot Fonteyn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "In human affairs, the best stimulus for running ahead is to have something we must run from." - Eric Hoffer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... Henry Emerson Fosdick: "Hating people is like burning down your own house to get rid of a rat."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "Most Texans think "Hanukkah" is some sort of duck call" - Richard Lewis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "Television is chewing gum for the eyes." - Frank Lloyd Wright]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "Hit the ball over the fence and you can take your time going around the bases." - John W. Raper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "Things don't change, but by and by our wishes change" -  Marcel Proust]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... Eleanor Roosevelt: "Justice cannot be for one side alone, but must be for both."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... Benjamin Jowett: "You must believe in God in spite of what the clergy say."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... Thomas Carlyle: "If you are ever in doubt as to whether or not you should kiss a pretty girl, always give her the benefit of a doubt."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... Doug Larson: "Accomplishing the impossible means only that the boss will add it to your regular duties."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "It is an illusion that youth is happy, an illusion of those who have lost it" - William Somerset Maugham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... William Allin: "Education is not the answer to the question. Education is the means to the answer to all questions."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "When smashing monuments, save the pedestals" - they always come in handy" - Stanislaw Jerzy Lec]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... Samuel Johnson: "Curiosity is one of the permanent and certain characteristics of a vigorous mind."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... Henry Louis Mencken: "Love is delusion that one woman differs from another."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "Advice is seldom welcome; and those who want it the most always like it the least" - Lord Chesterfield]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... Sophocles: "The soul that has conceived one wickedness can nurse no good thereafter."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "Man will never be free until the last king is strangled with the entrails of the last priest" - Denis Diderot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "Truth is the most valuable thing we have. Let us economize it" - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "What school, college, or lecture bring to men depends on what men bring to carry it home in" - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... Clive Staples Lewis: "The future is something which everyone reaches at the rate of sixty minutes an hour, whatever he does, whoever he]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... Oscar Wilde: "Men always want to be a woman`s first love - women like to be a man`s last romance."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "To the man of thought almost nothing is really ridiculous" - Johann Wolfgang von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... Thomas Fuller: "If it were not for hopes, the heart would break."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... Theodore Roosevelt: "Keep your eyes on the stars, and your feet on the ground."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... Oscar Wilde: "The best way to make children good is to make them happy."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... Herbert Henry Lehman: "You can't run a government solely on a business basis... Government should be human. It should have a heart."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... Lynn Johnston: "Not being able to sleep is terrible. You have the misery of having partied all night... without the satisfaction."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "Dost thou love life? Then do not squander time, for that is the stuff life is made of" - Benjamin Franklin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... Allan Chalmers: "The grand essentials of happiness are: something to do, something to love, and something to hope for."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "All generalizations are false, including this one" - Blaise Pascal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "To marry a woman who you love and who loves you is to lay a wager with her as to who will stop loving the other first" - Albert Camus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "Aerodynamically the bumblebee shouldn't be able to fly, but the bumblebee doesn't know that so it goes on flying anyway" - Mary Kay Ash]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "Life is a series of collisions with the future; it is not the sum of what we have been, but what we yearn to be" - Jose Ortega y Gasset]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... Carl Sandburg: "1 tell you the past is a bucket of ashes."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "The only antidote to mental suffering is physical pain" -  Karl Marx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "Speak clearley, if you speak at all; carve every word before you let it fall" -  Oliver Wendel Holmes, Jr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "The best way to keep one's word is not to give it" - Napoleon Bonaparte]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "It is not good to be too free. It is not good to have everything one wants" -  Blaise Pascal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "Trust everybody, but cut the cards" -  Finley Peter Dunne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... Benjamin Disraeli: "Marriage is the greatest earthy happiness when founded on complete sympathy."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "Think wrongly, if you please, but in all cases think for yourself" - Doris Lessing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... Stanley Turecki: "Temperament is the natural, inborn style of behavior of each individual. It's the how of behavior, not the why."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "Nothing will be attempted if all possible objections must first be overcome" - Samuel Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "Maturity consists in no longer being taken in by oneself" -  Kajetan von Schlaggenberg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "Advice is like snow; the softr it falls, the longer it dwells upon, and the deeper it sinks into, the mind" - Samuel Taylor Coleridge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "Politeness is one of those advantages, which we never estimate rightly but by the inconvenience of its loss" - Samuel Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "Go to foreign countries and you will get to know the good things one possesses at home" - Johann Wolfgang von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... Agatha Christie: "An archaeologist is the best husband any woman can have: the older she gets, the more interested he is in her."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... Stacia Tauscher: "We worry about what a child will become tomorrow, yet we forget that he is someone today."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... Dwight Eisenhower: "There is no victory at bargain basement prices."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "It is not good to be too free. It is not good to have everything one wants" - Blaise Pascal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "Politics is perhaps the only profession for which no preparation is thought necessary" - Robert Louis Stevenson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "Walking is man`s best medicine" - Hippocrates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "As long as people believe in absurdities, they will continue to commit atrocities" - Voltaire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "Only vegetables are happy" - William Faulkner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "It is not the years in your life but the life in your years that counts." - Adlai E. Stevenson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "If you treat people right they will treat you right -- ninty percent of the time" - Franklin D. Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... Sophia Loren: "Sex appeal is 50% what you've got and 50% what people think you've got."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "It is better to sleep on things beforehand than lie awake about them afterward" - Baltasar Gracian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "By all means, marry. If you get a good wife, you'll become happy; if you get a bad one, you'll become a philosopher." - Socrates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... Alexander Hamilton: "Man is a reasoning rather than a reasonable animal."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "War is one of the scourges with which it has pleased God to afflict men" - Armand de Richelieu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "A home is not a mere transient shelter: its essence lies in the personalities of the people who live in it." - Henry Louis Mencken]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "Never play leapfrog with a unicorn" - Anon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "It destroys one`s nerves to be amiable every day to the same human being" - Benjamin Disraeli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "Character is higher than intellect... A great soul will be strong to live, as well as to think" - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "The heart has its reasons that reason knows nothing of" - Blaise Pascal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "Being powerful is like being a lady. If you have to tell people you are, you aren`t" - Margaret Thatcher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "The secret of getting ahead is getting started" - Sally Berger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "Style is a simple way of saying complicated things" - Jean Cocteau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "Depend on the rabbit's foot if you will, but remember it didn't work for the rabbit" - R.E. Shay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "Beauty is the promise of happiness" - Stendhal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "Keep cool, but do not freeze" - (from a mayonnaise jar)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... "Everything you can imagine is real" - Pablo Picasso]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[... Unknown: "Little wit in the mind makes much work for the feet."]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>