<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @McSwtrvst: If you are the older twin, call your little sibling 50 times a day and say “when I was your age” then describe what you did …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @skullmandible: most cutting thing you can say is "who's this clown?" because it implies they're a) a clown &amp; b) not even one of the bet…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pharmasean: [in hell]
Me: *sneeze*
The devil: bless you
Me, waving as I float to heaven: haha, fool
the devil: DAMN YOU
Me, floating ba…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @skullmandible: *suddenly remembers conversation from eight years ago* oh they were making fun of me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @andymacneil Two for Two on that tip I sent you. But I did get the GD wrong on tonight's. Sorry even I can't be ultra perfect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm watching Late Show With David Letterman -  with Shazam.  Try it now! http://t.co/imeotaEWQ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andymacneil what? I feed you a double gift and you take a shot at my team.  They'll be fine. Even with MT as coach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andymacneil @tb @fla but I'm busy watching the leafs being the leafs and although losing to the oil still can't even tank correctly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andymacneil @tb @fla this one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andymacneil @tb @fla ok. Are you keeping an eye on what I fed you?  I think you see a Habs loss by 2 to start?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamieRatchford You'll figure it out. And remember It's St. Patrick's Day and  raise the Guiness repeatedly but none of that Shamrockerry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andymacneil @fla @tb W L L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andymacneil @tb @fla L BY 2. W by 3 w by 1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andymacneil @tb @fla LWW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Dawn_M_: Like any responsible adult I solve all my problems by ignoring them, getting drunk then going on the internet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MooreintheAM That is an excellent summation of the Obama Presidency. Taking a deep breath before action is always good strategy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WilliamRodgers: I just poured the right amount of chips, to the exact amount of dip

So if anyone needs me I'll be home...waiting on my…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reporterdonpeat @MapleLeafs How many Lost Causes is it up to now that FN's supported]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @reporterdonpeat: "I hope the @MapleLeafs win tonight" Speaker Frances Nunziata #TOpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@towhey @TorontoRobFord So Not so Fun. Not So Effective]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@towhey @TorontoRobFord And it continues. Zero strategy. Begging the question to compare the next 100 etc etc etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@towhey @TorontoRobFord The question you always skirt is: What could have been accomplished with a strategic plan and a non addled mind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[City of Gold #toronto http://t.co/HV5b0gzWJn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NHLhistorygirl and absolutely hands down the best hockey name ever ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JasonRBradwell Absolutely. Her acting skills pull emotion from the viewer. That is talent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JasonRBradwell agree. Developed is right. Ask anyone what they thought of her in the beginning. Again. Writing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JasonRBradwell Yep. Loved the scene. Is it the magic of the writing that she had two roads and chose that one. Chocolate in her pocket.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RBC: To celebrate International Women's Day, we're donating $2 to @UNACanada for every RT of this post! #RBCIWD #IWD2015 http://t.co/w8…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Food you love and food you fear: Both are expensive /via @globeandmail http://t.co/e26TCkpdVJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ivortossell I've told the moth joke because I love the moth joke. I may never tell it again. Brilliant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ivortossell: Here is Norm Macdonald telling the infamous moth joke, in a smart post about the infamous moth joke. http://t.co/z7NMfNKhha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@piya Well Tweeted. The reporting as a result of societal change is the discussions  jumping off point]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FrankConniff: New Supergirl costume is too dark and wrong for the character and not true to the original DC comic and oh god I'm so lon…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @stphnmaher: Is funny. Because it's true. RT @monique_muise: This is so dead-on I can't even handle it. http://t.co/74RZnLWpwM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reporterdonpeat But But But Those are the only Headline we are allowed to write now. Said all headline writers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Average tweet #nhltrade Contrary to report from absolutely none who knows anything @TBLightning are not trading Stamkos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@janets_idea_hub #yesitwill #ifnotsenditback]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damn it! I have no interest in a libra male “@TScpPisces: Daily Pisces: You will find out today that a Libra male has feelings for you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please just have @SteveMartinToGo host the #Oscars2015 from now on. Please]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@goldsbie Read @cathalkelly great fishing piece from sat. And I hope you brought head protection]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know what the world needs now? One magical mixtape drop from the Stones that has no studio taint to it. I know they have it in them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DeLeat. What a shot. Guts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lisztomania by Phoenix, found with @Shazam, Listen now: http://t.co/ZpolquErTx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bloodbuzz Ohio by The National, found with @Shazam, Listen now: http://t.co/Wq73xTIdr6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andymacneil @robpizzola Ha! At least you all were in there. My OH OH was casual in complete hindsight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andymacneil @robpizzola oh oh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KathyBuckworth perfect day for it. Tomorrow may be even better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Must have just missed you @KathyBuckworth at #Icefest15]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MacCocktail: “Suburbia is where the developer bulldozes out the trees, then names the streets after them.” 
― Bill Vaughn

@HV_Limo @St…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hobodiac @ivortossell but a good man for taking to the tweetwaves to inform the huddling masses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hobodiac @ivortossell obviously he sold it. Didn't work out the other end of that capitalistic equation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@anneliesf and right you are. Wasn't being partisan. My hope for LPO is slowly being eroded by cynicism]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@spaikin @anneliesf @johntoryTO So here comes the secondary Defense. " well everyone else was doing  it" Always comes after the Denial D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't you forget about me .... “@TIME: This tribute to ’80s teen movies will make you yearn for simpler times http://t.co/nei8CmCorE”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donlandrymedia @normmacdonald DId last night. Norm does twitter story form better than anyone. No storify needed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@normmacdonald This is feeling like a classic story once again coming from a classic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That escalated quickly http://t.co/IiO8VLHGkR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@InklessPW Canadians with values want CAQ leader to STFU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iTinaGraves]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tsnjamesduthie: The suit Jonathan Pitre has on:
Sidney Crosby had his tailor make it so Jonathan could feel like the players do when th…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamieRatchford @DAVIDsTEA Yes. I see the problem.There is an empty space there that needs some tea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ivortossell: Oh god, now I won't either. @kvey: I'll never get "Walk like a dog at all crossings" out of my head.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @randyturner15: The Leafs have a 9.5% chance of winning. So it's just like the regular season.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JamieRatchford: #GoHabsGo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JamieRatchford Looks like Detergent to me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight on Remotely Problems. When FF my PVR I often mistakenly hit the Last button. I need this to stop http://t.co/O5qe9yprzI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My new series called Remotely Problems http://t.co/byTAxIw2QU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KathyBuckworth I still have the Album http://t.co/IOoP4YMGPN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sunlorrie It in a nutshell Yes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sunlorrie: Senate Questions:  If U don't know you're not supposed 2 bill 2 times for the same expenses, how the f*ck can we trust you o…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @Jack_Astors  Queensway. I Somehow managed to have a real Dark and Stormy on a dark and stormy day. WOW Mark Michelle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greenwooddavis ha. Oh damn. Now I have to make some hoops. We'll figure something out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@greenwooddavis What a great game. I lost a bet on a 60 dollar bottle of wine on the Badgers. Tell Ish I made homemade BBall nets too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @bengreenman: "World's oldest person dies at 116: Gertrude Weaver had title for 5 days." http://t.co/SLfuGaxiZT Again? Why does this kee…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bengreenman Aaarghhh Again. This did not happen. The person who was known as the worlds oldest has died. Long live the worlds oldest PRSN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My daily battle with my Elevator News Screen thingy. it has very different ideas about weather http://t.co/Y6g2TFvj1z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jack_Astors Queensway. Impressive adding Fake Roses by @TheLoneBellow to the playlist. I think I'll stay for another]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @Jack_Astors Queensway. Impressive adding Fake Roses by @TheLoneBellow to the playlist. I think I'll stay for another]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@commlabs werx CUZ I direxcted it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey. Never mind these #ZaynMalik breakdowns. I heard P Diddy's got prostate issues. Changed his name to P Drizzle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andymacneil wait there's more. LOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just wondering. Can you Dirext your own mug shots. I want this one http://t.co/AlwJsEqhQX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jpags: Karygiannis' style is to ask probing, sometimes antagonistic personal questions to craft an argument that is not always clear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/RpNUYV4Sks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheToddWilliams: Galileo Galilei (1564-1642) played a major role in the scientific revolution even though he was such a poor boy and no…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheToddWilliams @McSwtrvst]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NowPlaying Houndmouth  http://t.co/RResoZr16M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please Free @FriedgeHNIC I like Kypreos. PJ can work, likeable but talks too much to compensate for limits. But Elliotte deserves more]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gmbutts plus a year Gallagher gets it done #habs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gmbutts Says the Ten Yr old #Hab fan in all of us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @gmbutts: I really, really hope Gallagher &amp; Galchenyuk are #Habs forever and ever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Raonic wins #indianwells]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andymacneil #habs all the way]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andymacneil ha. Just making an outlier early call tht if comes true makes me look like a genius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andymacneil Yeah I'm calling it. It's  Carey's year but they may not have enough]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andymacneil yeah. Well that's ok we all will be at some point during the playoffs except for St Louis fans]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KelvinWineTherm @MacCocktail with those windshield wipers slappin' time and Holding Bobbies hand in mine we sang up every song that driver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andymacneil nice. Ok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @andymacneil  Goal Diff was off but hey. I ran the table on the Habs. How'd I do on the Wings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goal Diff was off but hey. I ran the table on the Habs. How'd I do on the Wings]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>