<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[To confine our attention to terrestrial matters would be to limit the human spirit. - Stephen Hawking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Eric Clapton  http://t.co/hU44eDCDTh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am the best in baseball. - Reggie Jackson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Al Green  http://t.co/kJINnbuR8W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winning is everything. The only ones who remember you when you come second are your wife and your dog. - Damon Hill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Joe Tex  http://t.co/LudRYYz2Kc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We can judge the heart of a man by his treatment of animals. - Immanual Kant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing shocks me - I am a scientist. - Indiana Jones, Indiana Jones and the Temple of Doom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winners never quit and quitters never win. - Vince Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History Of The Hollywood Sign  http://t.co/Hqll9kPfFD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most beautiful makeup of a woman is passion. But cosmetics are easier to buy. --&gt; Yves Saint-Laurent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rule your mind or it will rule you. - Horace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Careers with a Creative Writing Degree  http://t.co/T4z0lUqMkp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you blame others, you give up your power to change. - Dr. Robert Anthony]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Better to be a geek than an idiot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to that hilarious sit-com Three’s Company - http://t.co/vbATDnuaLB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Carlos Santana  http://t.co/Yru8DX2VZJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Play is the only way the highest intelligence of humankind can unfold. - Joseph Chilton Pearce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Daddy: Mommy just backed the car over my bicycle! "I told you not to leave it in the living room!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Increasingly, the mass marketing is turning into a mass of niches - Christ Anderson Author of The Long Tail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about the Bay Area city of Danville, California http://t.co/LPyYBftmAR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Queen  http://t.co/T7t0vwQxr8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana’s Lyme Journey - Part 5 - Test Results In!  http://t.co/SJFZfmDfxl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay, that thing in the woods, maybe it's a monster, maybe it's a pissed off giraffe, I don't know. Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People who enjoy what they are doing invariably do it well. - Joe Gibbs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conversation:  when three women are talking together.  Gossip:  When one of them leaves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Biking Guide BMX Review  http://t.co/emc3kPAtEe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating history of Baseball Cards!  http://t.co/lOnd7915if]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the Icebound Land by John Flanagan  http://t.co/EKW6vnhZGV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Life Gives You Questions, Google has Answers - AJ Carpio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're either making money or you're not. If you're not making money get out of the business. Meredith Whitney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mick Jagger can't even make a successful solo album, and the Stones are the biggest rock group that ever was.  - Don Henley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am truly not one to give advice. I'm divorced and I stole my best friend's husband.  Denise Richards on Love]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to look young and thin, hang around old fat people. - Jim Eason]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Resources for Home Brewing  http://t.co/hnNB7gLxvw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Interesting Burger Facts and History  http://t.co/e27jcF8GqM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I make Jessica Simpson look like a rock scientist.  Tara Reid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagination is the key to my lyrics. The rest is painted with a little science fiction. - Jimi Hendrix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two big firms are fighting for his services, the loser gets him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The right man is the one who seizes the moment. - Johann Wolfgang von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Genesis  http://t.co/LnIwYpV6m8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The man who remarked that money isn't everything must have gone through a woman's purse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Marvin Gaye  http://t.co/MLRGAXbKOI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Paul McCartney and Wings  http://t.co/WtTinXlch6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool iPhone 4 Review  http://t.co/qetO5n3iD2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The expectations of life depend upon diligence; the mechanic that would perfect his work must first sharpen his tools. - Confucius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find Out why Facebook is great for Your Business  http://t.co/YcVnjAHFRM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do women want? Shoes. --&gt; Mimi Pond]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make it so! - Engage! - Captain Picard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reputation is the other fellow's idea of your character]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahh Fond Memories of San Antonio  http://t.co/f9bNbaIPud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[History of Mojang - The makers of Minecraft - http://t.co/ztyTzQeFTX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm shooting a commercial for safe sex. How ironic. Because I don't have that.   Tila Tequila]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Three Dog Night  http://t.co/PTN3uJcPIY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Small Dogs Can Make Great Pets - Picking the Right Breed  http://t.co/K06b9YIXCP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people are born on third base and go through life thinking they hit a triple. - Barry Switzer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome kayaking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the paddling lovers in your life!  http://t.co/XnjtSBM9gN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Geek Decision Ball - Picks FAIL, WIN, meh, 404 error, LOL, PWND and More! http://t.co/jmyLahJmDx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's easier to ask forgiveness than it is to get permission - Grace Hopper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to win at golf:  cheat!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The noblest search is the search for excellence - Lyndon B. Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys, that Chinese dude is going to get pretty crispy out here. How long are you going to keep him tied down like that? Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Donovan  http://t.co/du17wDFxu4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious T-Shirt - “I Got Your Back” http://t.co/lqQi79TVMR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cinderella is living proof that a pair of shoes can change your life…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is not the most important thing in the world. Love is. Fortunately, I love money. - Jackie Mason]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting Overview of Top 10 International Beers  http://t.co/1fgP8hj2Lx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Tips on Using Other Websites for Link Building  http://t.co/tpFx4LFeFM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first and the best victory is to conquer self. - Plato]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How To Invest In Penny Stocks  http://t.co/Wj8n02FlSA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celiac Disease Requires Gluten Free Foods - Learn More  http://t.co/GgH9ils0B4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Lewisville, Texas  http://t.co/gGi54bCqzV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Kansas  http://t.co/Jkbu3l8ON7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best use of life is to spend it for something that outlasts it - William James]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's no secret. You just press the accelerator to the floor and steer left. - Bill Vukovich]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Barbara Acklin - The Popular Singer  http://t.co/ix3gpjtwb5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Neil Young  http://t.co/2UMGC7zAMG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Guide - Four ways to keep your printing environmentally friendly  http://t.co/DbNv5VwAle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Musical Legend – Johnny Adams  http://t.co/8yY5bTxquH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pleasure in the job puts perfection in the work. - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The object of education is to prepare the young to educate themselves throughout their lives. - Robert M. Hutchins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No change in musical style will survive unless it is accompanied by a change in clothing style. Rock is to dress up to.  - Frank Zappa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Top 10 fitness gyms  http://t.co/Rr6MzVUXGH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Fitness Alternative Energy Devices  http://t.co/Adav3YOBjN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making money is not gonna change anything about what I am, except I won't answer the door. Abel Ferrara]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A successful man is one who can lay a firm foundation with the bricks others have thrown at him... David Brinkley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A successful man is one who can lay a firm foundation with the bricks others have thrown at him... David Brinkley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids LOVE These Volcano Making Kit!  Fun and Educational! http://t.co/G898GN4HfX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone who lives within their means suffers from a lack of imagination. - Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may be dumb, but I'm not stupid.  Terry Bradshaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Find Gluten Free Recipes  http://t.co/gfnd79zhbR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Empty pockets never held anyone back. Only empty heads and empty hearts can do that.  Norman Vincent Peale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WOW - Very Cool A Sticky Note Wrist Watch! http://t.co/9HhP7x6M3Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to WordTracker SEO Tools http://t.co/b8QdMhrrzY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Life Gives You Questions, Google has Answers - AJ Carpio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of the Inheritance Series Third Volume – Brisingr  http://t.co/HK50Dr1xkN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 4 - Supplements and Herbs  http://t.co/F9xStoS7l1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A toupee is ear to ear carpeting!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Why You Should Consider a Creative Writing Degree  http://t.co/wlePCVSWRi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to that hilarious sit-com Three’s Company - http://t.co/vbATDnuaLB]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>