<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Big-Dog Pet Fountain - Keeps Fresh and Tasty Water for Your Big Dog! http://t.co/iU6M84vVmx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eat, drink and be merry, for tomorrow ye diet. - William Gilmore Beymer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The last words to the 'Star Spangled Banner?' 'Play ball!' - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About GPS Technology and Fitness Watches  http://t.co/lwVbKuJG30]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once burned a lesson is learned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Creedance Clearwater Revival  http://t.co/4wyN1Sc7Ss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cowboys, Mavs, Rangers and more read about the Sports teams of the Dallas Fort-Worth Metroplex - http://t.co/Xxe7vCpnCO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 3 - My Visit With Dr. McFadzean  http://t.co/oMdNTZj9pu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He looks like a girl.  Marlon Brando on Leonardo DiCaprio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It will work. I am a marketing genius. - Paris Hilton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can wear this wonderful Unicorn Mask - bring the magic! http://t.co/IvXdyK2l0M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Firefighters recently rescued two people from an industrial clothes dryer. They were listed in stable condition but missing one sock!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Capital as such is not evil; it is its wrong use that is evil. Capital in some form or other will always be needed.  Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't compare me to my father. Our similarities are different. -  Dale Berra about his father Yogi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's human nature to stretch, to go, to see, to understand. Exploration is not a choice, really; it's an imperative. - Michael Collins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes I can't figure designers out. It's as if they flunked human anatomy. --&gt; Erma Bombeck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of America  http://t.co/TvBQ76YS1v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome darts t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the darts lovers in your life!   http://t.co/okm8w8qsJs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about necessary foods for your prepper pantry!  http://t.co/nxvWdtQQs4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think about it... Mistakes are just small steps to perfection...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Adorable Fleece Baby Carrier Cover!  http://t.co/6hWJ8nt9dv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thousands of years ago, cats were worshipped as gods. Cats have never forgotten this. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Home is where -- . You hang your head]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Air Supply  http://t.co/HZ0cVOBXq4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our health always seems much more valuable after we lose it. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One family that practices population control:  the mafia!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Building an Effective Company Blog  http://t.co/387DRPtPw9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smoking kills. If you killed, you've lost a very important part of your life. Brooke Shields]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think education is expensive, try ignorance - Derek Bok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Don Henley  http://t.co/EdsaUlDGp7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For women, shoes are the most important. Good shoes take you good places. --&gt; Seo Min Hyun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hello again, everybody. It's a bee-yooo-tiful day for baseball. -  Harry Caray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Joey Dee and the Starliters  http://t.co/Bw8hhpdoNF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Babysitter: a teenager who acts like a Grownup while grownups are acting like teenagers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Overview of the USSSA Youth Sports Organization  http://t.co/rjSIYbYhRr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't realize how strong a person really is until you see them at their weakest moment. - Unknown Author]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A cat is a puzzle for which there is no solution. - Hazel Nicholson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you tried to give rock and roll another name, you might call it 'Chuck Berry'. - John Lennon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Awesome Sony BRAVIA DAV-DZ170 Home Theater System! http://t.co/2XeUwnCeYT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is the mark of an educated mind to be able to entertain a thought without accepting it. - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A horse gallops with his lungs, Perseveres with his heart, And wins with his character. - Tesio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the animals: God has given them the rudiments of thought and joy untroubled - Fyodor Dostoyevsky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Building Experts - Get Some Free Tips  http://t.co/Q9SM01epb8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Top Science and Tech Websites  http://t.co/Qq8x7FvJEI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Selecting a Strategy Consulting Firm  http://t.co/HtEJEiYnsV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Girls are like internet domain names, the ones I like are already taken.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How To Find Best Supplies For Gardening  http://t.co/2YYcmp8AmY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Their marriage is a partnership, he's the silent partner.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Marketing Experts Reveal Tips to Success  http://t.co/CpO0chonAs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BACON shaped themed Adhesive Bandages - Love It! http://t.co/AX9sr9GllX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Cat. He walked by himself, and all places were alike to him. - Rudyard Kipling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fall seven times, stand up eight. - Japanese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Writing Company Blogs that are Effective  http://t.co/nyfMKs1fNR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have to have a lot of little boy in you to play baseball for a living.  - Roy Campanella]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the beginning, God created man, but seeing him so feeble, He gave him the cat - Warren Eckstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Janis Joplin  http://t.co/teDQlVK1JQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone who lives within their means suffers from a lack of imagination. - Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A women with good shoes is never ugly. They are the last touch of elegance. - Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Arthur Alexander – Country and R&amp;B Pioneer  http://t.co/K82Bnn4jPI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trust people and they will be true to you; Treat them greatly, and they will show themselves great. - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A house is not a home without a pet. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plastic surgeons can do almost anything with a nose these days, except keep it out of other people's business]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His timing is perfect, so is his two-timing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Ral Donner  http://t.co/lPy2R4PmOP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagination is the key to my lyrics. The rest is painted with a little science fiction. - Jimi Hendrix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids can learn over 20 optical illusions - lots of fun and great learning! http://t.co/Yq4Gqw95po]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greetings, programs! - Flynn, TRON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of DC Comics  http://t.co/0dvmxMGQVa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The great difficulty in education is to get experience out of ideas. - George Santayana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Paul Simon - His Biography  http://t.co/yDynTaCmLd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Video games for fitness is a growing trend - tie together the love of video games and the need to stay fit!  http://t.co/EkGtyoXbhB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the History of the Nautilus Fitness Equipment  http://t.co/FsqeAO0hv8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mr. Spock, the women on your planet are logical. That's the only planet in this galaxy that can make that claim. - James T. Kirk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The iPaperPad is not magical or revolutionary. It's a paper pad. A poor man's iPad LOL http://t.co/04NYjwISGL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best possible thing in baseball is winning the World Series. The second best thing is losing the World Series. - Tommy Lasorda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of the Inheritance Series Third Volume – Brisingr  http://t.co/XC8uo39T02]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read a Short Introduction to ABBA  http://t.co/knc24Rnsut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Buckinghams  http://t.co/VVGM8YRAEu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overview of Social Bookmarking Sites  http://t.co/ZaRJAa1nj2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Crosby, Stills and Nash   http://t.co/mN3NqWDYKk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Are the Different Types of Web Hosting?  http://t.co/11A9qTviKV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball has the great advantage over cricket of being sooner ended. - George Bernard Shaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Platform Shoes  http://t.co/pE2ejphP0e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction To http://t.co/g56bkHlPdq  http://t.co/HNZmZTLP5K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What --  is the air-speed velocity of an unladen swallow? - Bridgekeeper, Monty Python and the Holy Grail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Tsingtao Beer  http://t.co/q1yJBWmM2m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Increasingly, search is our mechanism for how we understand ourselves our world, and our place with in it.  John Battelle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Rod Stewart  http://t.co/0TYvMWw2A9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool Geek Tech - Mini USB Fan - Keep cool at your desk! --&gt; http://t.co/0kYGYqsSil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Blue Origin - A Profile of This Emerging Space Company  http://t.co/wGOnBG1kQd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to find somebody and you want to be married and you want to have children, don't make it a rock star. - Stevie Nicks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious Zombie Family Car Stickers - http://t.co/wgviCaRy4l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion is a form of ugliness so intolerable that we have to alter it every six months. --&gt; Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine his nerve -- .. I was all ready to refuse him, and he didn't even ask!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make Your House More Attractive With Fall Flowers  http://t.co/PQfmuVhuQo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is Horology?  http://t.co/USmVKDl0A7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Creative Writing Degree - Why You Should Consider One  http://t.co/dUq0Dzzhg4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of the animals except for man know that the principle business of life is to enjoy it. - Samuel Butler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about the Bay Area city of Danville, California http://t.co/886cHgteSo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the Chitika Ad Network - An Alternate to Google AdSense  http://t.co/n0JnpPtfzG]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>