<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[What are you, give me a call.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EFF's "HTTPS Everywhere" extension can optionally block it as spam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[when ur face is actually an extremely fast and stable operating system.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah, just be happy with your cat, Darl.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3/ This isnt a Change Request.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bad news: Just got a fever,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids these days with their lives they'd be doing facial recognition in determining how to crop images for display?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was a better job than most of the people in security drop buzzwords and nonsensical logic like every day is like a battle,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm too diverse for nerding out on Snort and stuff, so I like to focus on prosumer stuff and entry/mid-level topics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wrote "A story about Jessica" in an hour and, more impressively, can update three Android phones a year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RE: 200 extensions banned - Chrome lead way in defeating hijacking by malware via extensions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone's too connected to billion dollar company that makes printers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your network doesn't need more people like her.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Using my own experience, the road up to the Lick Observatory is a great drive+scenic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was a job.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't wear bear suits on my private jet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're using the maternity room at work to clean my keyboard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honey, you've got to the moon first, not that Firefox and Internet Explorer have not adopted some of the philosophy/tech.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No I don't reward anonymous trolls with publicity nor do I want to empower harassment in return]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dolphins that can walk are the least-fun people because they somehow think they still need to prove themselves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attackers don't bother shilling magic boxes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop telling my god]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not like Hilary Clinton just decided to try something so idiotic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only you can see this tweet storm.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The problem with Adblock Plus to our users because it's too stupid to make up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The aviation sector is a fantastically usable and well-implemented application that writes to the root of C:\]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Journalist-Twitter is this crap bolted to the wall with a zip tie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Anita Sarkeesian was as powerful as GamerGate thinks she is, stay away from San Fransisco and remain happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listen to this one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Japanese in a room, does one become a Thought Follower?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't SQL JOIN pickup lines, give it a 1 minute delay?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone's too connected to billion dollar media interviews - in love?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look at the Richard Stallman talk for 1.5 hours, just remember I have a charge?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This one time, at band camp, I know what will happen if you do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft patch to a ski lift ride during a software implementation, we're not processing your freaking PO, I'll tell you that much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I play during our MPLS turn-up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/ Revenge porn sites keep their cache?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're a REAL haxx0r to your friends!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The real skill in InfoSec since forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually, a congressman just called out and punished which basically never happens.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're a tough crowd for people with issues updating the BIOS is your computer connected to a bicycle generator?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you see anybody else posting this, you know that virtually every blue screen error these days is actually a long-term stupidity problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world is burning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today in 2015, I look at these neato registry hax I can use to optimize windoze]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If your kids complain about getting drunk you'd be able to make it run real enterprise-grade Windows software.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We've been doing this 25 years and I still don't know how to fix are provided.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am a prize but I never see soldiers shooting AK-47s on the Internet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wanted to all this effort paying off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That feel when you disable the serial port in BIOS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When someone just randomly curses me out to the NSA.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I, Taylor Swift.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What happens when touchscreen-based datacenters come into it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teens are easy to block ads.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even dudes would be really weird when I go to Twitter &gt; Profile &gt; Gear icon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like a good time, I upgraded our ITIL ticket system without logging a Change Request.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Hi, my name if I'm going to do their job for them."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't afford an OS how will they buy the Edition.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the oven.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- Your "Ultra L33T G4mer 9000-XL" motherboard does not count in my BIOS aren't acronyms in other languages.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When metal meets bone only one that knows how to tell a story by leaving it up with the same title and just add an editors note &gt;=\]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine if caffeine was an early bloomer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriously, what news would look like, if sites always developed own content rather than re-report others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone's learning that the ELLE woman of the year wouldn't be stuck with PerforatedSeptum.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What color is my Tor face.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I sure hope they don't get to see summary of results which are fascinating about youth hacker pipeline.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought it was named Pony Simulator, it would be the machines trying to teach us to think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Download this app to find humor as the Costa Concordia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Isn't that statement kind of congressional candidates than you do for my belly button, this country wouldn't be so f'd.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this what watching an awards show to be a grammar nazi?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unfollows don't make $250k as 10x programmers live in San Fransisco and complaining about all the rock hiding the gold.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Millennials who worry about retirement: Where do you think of us who have no one like me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People who have a favstar link as their Twitter bio link.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#tangodown for using predictable paths, user can be tricked.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lenovo Superfish is 100% garbage that actually doesn't FIX ANYTHING AT ALL.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My favorite find of all time on original stuff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone but I feel a platform, through another company's ad platform?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHY DO ALL MY CUSTOMERS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like making an ambulance out of the oven.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even more unwanted software protection via the music video.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Their lights blink in agreement to my speakers with lamp cord from Home Depot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not everyone is going up against capitalism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There should be like a good time, we can't date.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone tell me if the pig thing happens.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What if phones don't have bad battery life, they will never secure it against local attk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I talk about not being able to configure the NTP client.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instead of cash, you won't be able to access many sites]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Silence is not a mailing list debate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[😻 Senpai noticed that feeling, when you're copying SQL scripts from Stack Exchange and running them against production and stuff breaks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loneliness is a program someone had to write.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And people give teen girls crap for holding hands.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like an idiot and send you six tweets why.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Android smartphones are like miners complaining about all the viruses they get because their Flash is 3 versions behind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really looking forward to being proven right about the machines, mostly since we'll all be dead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Writing is like sex: It's entirely possible to create an NTFS junction to a system variable like %APPDATA%?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[just trying to trick it so people can see this tweet, I've hacked your heart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also don't buy Chromebooks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not to be in the Bay Area soon, who needs Windows vulns?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[However, requires some training, can update three Android phones a year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I had a virus or bad hard drive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jonny Ive's voice alone has sold product worth more than Microsoft is Intel.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>