<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[An army officer owns a magnet that allows him to love everything in Utah at the same time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A grandmother is aroused by the thought of labyrinths.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solve this mystery: A monk is found murdered in a circus tent. Beside him is an animated GIF and a hat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A goblin from the future appears at the coronation of a Kurdish emperor. It destroys him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sentient scrotum walks the streets of Berlin. It has come to steal electronic dance music.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An ambassador buys a tiny crystal which allows him to become a waterfall.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Tunisian psychiatrist invents a new kind of arithmetic based on the movement of fireworks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A philosopher is blowing her nose. Suddenly her nose turns into a gramophone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A poet sees a birthmark in the shape of a porcelain doll.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A secretary realises that the afternoon is controlling random numbers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A rabbi possesses a unique skill: He can sense the presence of lightning bolts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By eating a chocolate chip cookie, you can reach another dimension. It is filled with milkshakes and snowmen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A beautiful woman plays a game of checkers with a maze.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A witch believes it is her destiny to kill motherhood.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dental hygienist is reading a history of China which describes a war against clowns that took place in 2323 BC.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Welsh senator rides her horse into a haunted palace. When she emerges, she realises she is an entrepreneur from Topeka.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A safety deposit box in Calcutta contains alcoholism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On All Hallow's Eve every man and woman in Birmingham is replaced by sharks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last night I dreamt about a koala whispering in a mountain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a secret department in Twitter that is researching how to generate feelings of pride.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A caliph wishes to befriend every carrot in Mexico City.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A duchess hears of a lighthouse inside a tropical island, and plans to visit it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A stonemason is checking Grindr inside a galaxy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A coral reef appears above Wisconsin. An accountant is talking to it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thirteen college professors plan to create a world where everything is cupcakes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A stomach made of insomnia appears in Constantinople.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A mathematician finds a leather-bound book containing instructions for building a merry-go-round out of mountain ranges.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Ethiopian philosophical treatise describes a piece of rose quartz that gives you power over reality.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a 16th century Spartan prophecy that you will forget a Stradivarius violin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Athens there is a polar bear that is covered in religion instead of fur.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One night a message is written in the sky in hailstones. It reads: "Read more Hegel."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Austrian king passes a law against icebergs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A cold-hearted boy falls in love with veganism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight you will dream of a chocolate chip cookie. Inside the chocolate chip cookie is an icicle. Inside the icicle is your heart's desire.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fortune teller turns over a tarot card with a condom on it. 'Your destiny is to become a novelist,' he says to you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A panda bear can move shooting stars with its mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A queen looks at Leonardo's Last Supper and sees her dog in the background.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Mongolian busboy is eating ice cream cones.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three hundred theologians do battle against a garden.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A historian becomes rich by selling arthouse films.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A court jester realises that he is a house of mirrors. Life goes on as normal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Baghdad there is a monkey which likes to drink gin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Norwegian angel introduces a law that everyone must adopt a dingo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Irish philosopher is writing a PhD thesis about the philosophy of Kant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You receive the memories of Billie Holiday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dreadnought falls into a swimming pool filled with boiling water.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a volcano in Shanghai that feels insane.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A city is haunted by the ghost of a congressman. He keeps repeating an odd phrase: "The sexually frustrated candy apple is playing chess."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Hungarian board of directors has a meeting about arts funding that continues for 281 billion years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Siberia there is an undertaker who has a compass instead of a testicle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A eunuch discovers that society is under the spell of a universe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A forest enjoys reading the philosophy of Heidegger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An opera singer receives a strange gift from her mother: An invisible mango tree.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A time traveller jumps from the Battle of the Somme to the present. He hands you a rhinoceros and says: "Relax."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are spirited away to Indonesia. There you start a new life as an HR manager.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A mystical book describes a man made of Big Macs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Fijian sorceress photographs the end of the world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A mermaid has the power to transport you to a concert hall in Detroit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bat and a vicar are falling out of love.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A novelist discovers that racism does not exist, and is secretly pleased.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A palace goes to a costume party dressed as a dinosaur fossil.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fisherman belches. In that time, he lives for seven years as a bed bug.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A crocodile made of glass is born in Miami.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A politician is chewing gum in a mechanical forest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A stone has the power to enable caterpillars to fly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Ukrainian necromancer hears of a cathedral located inside a desert, and immediately sets out to find it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A novelist devotes her life to making a list of every murder that has taken place in St Petersburg.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A tampon falls from the sky. It has escaped from a church in Reno.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An office manager suddenly turns into a windchime. Ashamed, she flees to Kyoto.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An anthropologist gets married to Leonardo DiCaprio inside a glass island.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Burmese solicitor plants a seed. A cemetery grows from it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A clairvoyant turns over a tarot card with a broomstick on it. 'Beware of opals,' he says to you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A tuxedo causes anyone who wears it to turn into a swimming pool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A carpenter gets drunk with a silver temple.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Czechoslovakian steamship is sailing on a sea of bloodlust.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You will dream of a custard apple tonight. The custard apple will sell you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a medieval Latvian prophecy that you will play a game of dominoes with a dictionary.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A poet owns a notebook by Nietzsche on the subject of long division.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A committee of professors imagine a Coliseum into existence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Madagascan emperor hatches a plan to strangle homosexuality.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Vermont there is a snowman which is buying a used car.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You suddenly turn into Paris.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A guilt-stricken princess receives a christening gift from an angel: 19 butterflies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Sudanese poet realises that her baby is a glass library.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lizard holds up a jewellery store. It steals 13 pearls, a topaz and a magic magnetic device.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a drug dealer in Bangkok who can get you high on paradoxes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A girl sinks into a lagoon filled with lemon juice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Catalan eunuch proposes marriage to Black Friday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Somali baron goes for a walk in a golden maze. When he emerges, he realises he is a porn star from Tampa.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A shaman makes a fortune trading in sleeping in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A deeply depressed butler falls into a pool filled with lust. A salamander jumps in to rescue him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A record producer owns a pair of binoculars that give him complete understanding of information.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An admiral sees an island in the shape of a Fabergé egg.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A 40-year-old undertaker falls in love with time travel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a beach in Varanasi that is infinitely long.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A tiger whispers to a senator: "I wish I was a lime tree."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A detective novel in which the killer is revealed to be a city.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A hairdresser is cutting up pumpkins in a shopping mall. He is thinking about snowdomes. There is a seahorse standing right behind him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An HR manager turns into every monster in Venice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sous chef switches bodies with a genie.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>