<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA["The only time success occurs before work is in the dictionary." via Cameron Cashmore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju While You Were Offline: Twitter Cripples @ Replies and Also Spirits #technology #geek https://t.co/vyK53AJgoG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju 14-year-old charged in Facebook Live sex assault of teen girl - Chicago Tri.. #facebook #internet https://t.co/Ccls9RuM9H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Could Surgeons Operate Using the Internet? - Voice of America #internet #web https://t.co/cdzSts6mwc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Productive Partnerships: How a 'David' Can Partner With 'Goliath' #entrepreneur https://t.co/w6KZ4SvEBo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju The 10 most valuable brands in the world - Business Insider #branding #brands https://t.co/yjz89lQ4KW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju The Conservative Case Against Trashing Online Privacy Rules #technology #geek https://t.co/5CoqGSNkI5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Facebook Live Footage Given to Swedish Prosecutors for Gang Rape Case - For.. #facebook #internet https://t.co/dBJyj6BlRt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The difference between ordinary and extraordinary is that little extra.- Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Your internet data now available to highest bidder - Albuquerque Journal #internet #web https://t.co/XDEh1HM97d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju 3 Steps to Retaining Existing Customers #entrepreneur https://t.co/9vxM6uwfn3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Ford, Chevrolet ranked as highest-value brands in Michigan - Crain's Detroit .. #branding #brands https://t.co/ftQZg2wnfs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This 'telephone' has too many shortcomings to be seriously considered as a means of communication…... Western Union internal memo 1876]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju While You Were Offline: Um, Steve, Your Whiteboard Is Showing #technology #geek https://t.co/njoDmXozex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Algorithms are failing Facebook. Can humanity save it? - Quartz #facebook #internet https://t.co/yv7UsBQQHG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Even Apple can't make the Internet of Things tolerable - The Verge - The Verge #internet #web https://t.co/KU180hxSMZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju 6 Tips to Running a Business and Improving Your Education #entrepreneur https://t.co/iwy2JP58er]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju What Famous Brands Does Berkshire Hathaway Fully Own? - Motley Fool #branding #brands https://t.co/jiXIL5vWem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju The Bonkers Role-Playing World of Rifts Just Got Even Bigger #technology #geek https://t.co/Ur4ate7k8T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Facebook could launch two dozen 'TV-like' original shows in June - Engadget #facebook #internet https://t.co/iW7LqmLryY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You never become a howling success by just howling. Bob Harrington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju The Internet Is Using 'The Handmaid's Tale' Memes to Voice Political Opinions (H.. #internet #web https://t.co/59XUl1cPcq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju How to Reconfigure Your Sales Operations for Account-Based Selling #entrepreneur https://t.co/CeNz1NiGE9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Five Things Influencers Wish Brands And Agencies Understood - Forbes #branding #brands https://t.co/0Cpr35CP5w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adversity introduces a man to himself.- Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju George R. R. Martin Doesn't Need to Finish Writing the Game of Thrones Books #technology #geek https://t.co/2ZjPIRWHLX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Facebook Now Has an Almost Advertising-Only Business Model - Fortune #facebook #internet https://t.co/L4ydks85hR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Courage is being scared to death, but saddling up anyway." John Wayne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Taking the "E" out of Ecommerce Platforms - Multichannel Merchant #ecommerce #tech https://t.co/9rznvTciMY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Actually, Congress Did Undermine Our Internet Privacy RIghts - EFF #internet #web https://t.co/IsRgaEUJdL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Watch 'The Never Settle Show' Ep. 5: Small Business Appreciation Week #entrepreneur https://t.co/22o5JMelfp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju BaseConnect wins Cherokee Strip Business Model Competition - Enid News &amp; Eagle #competition https://t.co/9rQavoHlsK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Victoria's Secret is at a 'tipping point,' getting weaker by the day, L Brand.. #branding #brands https://t.co/ihBJ1f8Ejf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Alanis Morissette's ex-manager gets 6 years in prison for stealing $7M - Fox N.. #manager #leader https://t.co/KZRKg7piO6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The grass is greener where you water it" via Danielle Luedtke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Social Scramble: Getting to grips with Snapchat Spectacles #socialcommerce https://t.co/H3PbScJeZD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Apple's Billion-Dollar Investment Provides a Blueprint for US Manufacturing #technology #geek https://t.co/iBfh6gjvsh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Facebook shares dip from high as investors fret over costs, future profit -.. #facebook #internet https://t.co/eEbkDyjNEy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the early days all I hoped was to make a living out of what I did best. But, since there’s no real market for …………….. Les Claypool]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju 4 Legal Considerations For Ecommerce Businesses - MinuteHack (registration) (b.. #ecommerce #tech https://t.co/wshlQgjTtW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju What do Indians do on the internet? - Quartz #internet #web https://t.co/AhXzswYXLN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Want to Speed Up Your Website? Try These 5 Cloud Server Applications #entrepreneur https://t.co/HbyFgZaoX6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Lula Cakes chosen for grant competition - Centerville Daily Iowegian #competition https://t.co/86S0QkPFF7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju 3 Common Sins Brands Commit on Social - Adweek #branding #brands https://t.co/FLCCrwMQQR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“I’ve missed more than 9000 shots in my career. I’ve lost almost 300 games. 26 times, I’ve been trusted….M. Jordan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Trailer: Netflix's Heroes Team Up in Defenders. Even, Um, Iron Fist #technology #geek https://t.co/bBfJp9iB9R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Facebook First-Quarter Earnings: What To Watch - Forbes #facebook #internet https://t.co/Nw38j0xuBD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Success is liking yourself, liking what you do, and liking how you do it."  Maya Angelou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju When Should You Look To Outsource For Your Ecommerce Shop? - Forbes #ecommerce #tech https://t.co/9Fj66NfhBe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju China increases restrictions on internet news outlets - Engadget #internet #web https://t.co/cyxfaV64uO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju How to Optimize Your Videos for YouTube's Ranking Algorithms #entrepreneur https://t.co/45UkSB5jzM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Angry lawmakers say it's an 'absolute joke' that there's competition in the airlin.. #competition https://t.co/OgEGbhub3r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju How Clothing Brands Are Embracing Transparency to Meet the Growing Demand for.. #branding #brands https://t.co/gngAOkDCpZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["People often say that motivation doesn't last. Well, neither does bathing – that's why we recommend it daily." Zig Ziglar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju We Are Social's Tuesday Tweakup #30 #socialcommerce https://t.co/23JIQqDl7w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Trump's Pressure on Tech Outsourcers Might Be Paying Off #technology #geek https://t.co/LOJKQQMJYv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Facebook criticized for analyzing teenagers' feelings, accused of giving in.. #facebook #internet https://t.co/0HvSl9Da7l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're bored with life &amp; you don't get up every morning with a burning desire to do things – you don't have enough goals. Lou Holtz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju In An Ecommerce World, Retailers And CPGs Learn To Love Their Stores - AdExcha.. #ecommerce #tech https://t.co/RLnFXI7uUf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Judge argues net neutrality violates the free speech rights of … internet provid.. #internet #web https://t.co/mM156xPsT6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Arianna Huffington Joins Propelify Innovation Festival #entrepreneur https://t.co/dJSeRc2lgG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Grocery stores devote more space to fresh food, threatening big-name brands -.. #branding #brands https://t.co/4OHZCevGGR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life has no limitations, except the ones you make. Les Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju American Gods Gives 'Faithful Adaptation' All New Meaning #technology #geek https://t.co/dmSWbe5Fet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Don't blame users when violence on Facebook goes unreported - The Verge #facebook #internet https://t.co/Jau8YgMN9q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The successful man is the one who finds out what is the matter with his business before his competitors do. Roy L. Smith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju In wake of DFTZ, DHL taps Malaysia's 'booming eCommerce' sector - MIS Asia #ecommerce #tech https://t.co/RE5ncSLgpS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Tycoon: Robots, Internet kill jobs - Arkansas Online #internet #web https://t.co/TCmttnmby3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Why Office Communication is Highly Valued and Often Ignored #entrepreneur https://t.co/RJdiNNrPlV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju 'Care Van' pitch rides off with Big Idea competition - Meadville Tribune #competition https://t.co/EsUkJMjZ9n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Brands Tackle an Online Foe: The Meme - New York Times #branding #brands https://t.co/JNHD6RTmIs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Some people dream of great accomplishments, while others stay awake and do them." Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju While You Were Offline: Hey Please Don't Call Trump's New Hotline to Report U.. #technology #geek https://t.co/ufMB9a0dNs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju FCC Invokes Internet Freedom While Trying to Kill It - New York Times #internet #web https://t.co/CsYO0BUy8Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju 10 Interview Tips for Tech Companies #entrepreneur https://t.co/WuGUnAzskV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Social commerce: Why basic bots and buy buttons are not enough - Econsultancy (.. #socialcommerce https://t.co/6bJxtLgNDF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju How selfies can build – and destabilise – brands - The National Business Review #branding #brands https://t.co/hAUj3UTeTO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Neil Gaiman Wishes American Gods Wasn't Quite So Relevant Right Now #technology #geek https://t.co/EOAXKWn6DW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Family mourns infant whose murder was posted to Facebook - New York Post #facebook #internet https://t.co/vXeLAq0G4K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want your life to be a magnificent story, then begin by realizing that you are the author and everyday….Mark Houlahan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju NSA To Limit Some Collection Of Internet Communication - NPR #internet #web https://t.co/vcbzGGtkhO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju This Startup Raised $215,000 Defying Gender Stereotypes to Empower Girls #entrepreneur https://t.co/VoubA8Q8ja]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju The 10 Best-Selling Tequila Brands - VinePair #branding #brands https://t.co/1dbZHbDGvj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[”You are what you think about all day long.” — Dr. Robert Schuller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Chatbots And The Social Commerce Revolution: Event Roundup #socialcommerce https://t.co/zjKTDr1OBZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju This Month's Must-Have Gear, From Phones to Turntables #technology #geek https://t.co/xY332zyouW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Facebook Admits It's Being Used by Political Actors to Manipulate Opinion -.. #facebook #internet https://t.co/bUGPTTd4Dn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make your product easier to buy than your competition, or you will find your customers buying from them, not you." Mark Cuban]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju The Internet Is Under Attack By the US Government - Geek #internet #web https://t.co/mBjwg76zsh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju 3 Proven Ways to Stay Consistent, Meet your Goals and Realize Your Dreams #entrepreneur https://t.co/EYrZz4e5nC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Social commerce: Why basic bots and buy buttons are not enough - Econsultancy (.. #socialcommerce https://t.co/RuwUe6LqIi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Well-Rounded Brands Power Hasbro's Winning Q1 Results - Motley Fool #branding #brands https://t.co/TFoUQClzG9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eagles soar, but weasels don't get sucked into jet engines.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju For Senior Citizens, the Future of VR Lies in the Past #technology #geek https://t.co/aIbfXecVrt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Vietnam Says Facebook Has Pledged to Prevent Anti-Government and 'Offensive.. #facebook #internet https://t.co/PqB5th1FpG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if you change the way you look at things, the things you look at change. Dr. Wayne Dyer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju India's E-Commerce Market Is On The Rise - Seeking Alpha #ecommerce #tech https://t.co/m7KOUwYZJ8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Internet firms are winding up for a fight on net neutrality - CNBC #internet #web https://t.co/CuTUfZ8cCq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Why Life Is Too Short to Work Somewhere You Don't Care About #entrepreneur https://t.co/3UMjsYTdwK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju HR Onboarding Solutions Wins Business Plan Competition &amp; $25,000 - San Angelo LIVE! #competition https://t.co/sCFE0NBahk]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>