<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Application Developer: Sr Application Developer: Perform full market trading system level development life cycle management activities that perform to NFA communication &amp; security standards. Perform component and data software &amp; architecture design &amp;… https://t.co/gNvmMP9dt8 https://t.co/mFX9VWZgeS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consultant: Requisition code: XGGS18FC0518COS1 Consultant Deloitte Consulting LLP seeks a Consultant in Costa Mesa, CA and various unanticipated Deloitte office locations and client sites nationally to: Facilitate definition of requirements, use cases,… https://t.co/Y2JxqRWchU https://t.co/UCrlqjbZKp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Security Engineer: APPLICATION SECURITY ENGINEER JOB RESPONSIBILITIES * Conduct application security assessments, penetration tests and implement tools for dynamic and automated code reviews. * Ensure compliance with society, regulatory and… https://t.co/P8GgvNp9Qw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Prouction Support: Java Prouction Support st louis, Missouri – United States Job Start Date – 05/16/18, Posted Date – 05/16/18 Primary SkillsJava,Production supportTax TermsC2COverviewclient – mastercard linked in No H1B Overview As part of an… https://t.co/2qO3cTzD5O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front-End Developer: The Front End Developer will participate in the creation of sophisticated digital experiences and must have a strong understanding of front-end web development. You will work with a team of highly skilled. You are a visual developer… https://t.co/Lzyr52KuzI https://t.co/pNXKiWOlb1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Software Engineer – GO: If youre a Senior Software Engineer and looking to take that next big step in your career while working with GO, this is your chance! Do you see technical debt as your nemesis? Do you want an opportunity to be seen as the… https://t.co/tcRMXm95iz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: Ovia Health is a dynamic startup committed to making healthcare an everyday lifestyle for women. Our mobile apps – Ovia Fertility, Ovia Pregnancy and Ovia Parenting – are the leading womens health apps. We are looking for passionate… https://t.co/0WQanatb72 https://t.co/ms4JaCNEOx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UI Software Engineer: Are you an inventive software engineer? Is it important to you to hold yourself to high standards? Do you like building robust, engaging user interfaces? SignalPath might have the perfect job for you. SignalPath is designing the… https://t.co/R0z5XjTmaC https://t.co/4FzWlL7iby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Retail Salaried/ASP Positions for District 1 (Staunton, VA) Assistant Store Manager: Retail Salaried/ASP Positions for District 1 (Staunton, VA) Assistant Store Manager ===================================================================== now Date: Apr… https://t.co/OoIF9KSIf8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist 2/3:   Job Description – Data Scientist 2/3 (18005485) Data Scientist 2/3 Requisition ID : 18005485 Location : United States-California-San Diego US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation Assistance: Relocation assistance… https://t.co/txxjTgTomp https://t.co/IAbNj9rMNI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Offer-Creation-Project-Manager: Schneider Electriccreates connected technologies that reshape industries, transform cities and enrich lives.Our 144,000 employees thrive in more than 100 countries. From the simplest of switches to complex operational… https://t.co/Q2Ou598qU2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Full Stack Software Engineer: Principal Full Stack Software Engineer (Santa Monica, CA) – Home – Products – Industries – Clients – Company Create a Profile|Log In Yes No Show Details At least one job must be selected in order to apply. Refer… https://t.co/7dYIskgCic https://t.co/aZuVnngOuS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager III: Job Title: Project Manager III Requisition Number: 23164 Position Type: Full Time City: Brentwood Campus: Corporate State/Province: Tennessee Job Description: The Project Manager III is responsible for providing project management… https://t.co/uAfvNIxyak https://t.co/EhmofLM9az]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jr Software Engineer: Careers and Culture – Polaris Alpha -Jr Software Engineer Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job.… https://t.co/2lh0QPXvTp https://t.co/B3uSFLb6UI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NETWORK ENGINEER III: Network Engineer III, Sprint Corporation, Overland Park, KS. Serve as a Microwave Engineer for the cellular/ wireless telecommunications system. Remote work is authorized. Apply at https://t.co/nEegJuEls3, Req # 245305BR. Sprint is… https://t.co/Qq8m6tV4YL https://t.co/Vu62VXYqWM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full stack developer: Herndon software development firm seeks a highly quaffed motivated individual with good working knowledge of MSSQL Server, jQuery,JavaScript. C#, and VB a plus.  Seeking a self motivated, creative quick learner. ob Description: We… https://t.co/YyBHbxWZdt https://t.co/P8A6lc7smY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineers: O2 Technologies, Inc. in Irvine, CA is seeking Software QA Engineers to monitor, analyze &amp; test sftwr during dvlpmnt in order to ensure quality. No trvl; no telecomm. Job duties are proj-based &amp; performed @ unanticipated sites w/in… https://t.co/10nxcP4Lz7 https://t.co/2ze79L6MW1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager II: More than a career – a chance to make a difference in people’s lives. Build an exciting, rewarding career with us help us make a difference for millions of people every day. Consider joining the Duke Energy team, where you’ll find a… https://t.co/zVG5FztTbG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Java Developer: For BNY Mellon Lead Java Developer job – Asset Servicing – Multiple Skip to Main Content – – – – Toggle navigation – Who We Are – What We Do – Who We Serve – Our Thinking – Client Access – Careers – Investor Relations – News –… https://t.co/njFWsOl7N9 https://t.co/V22MXU9u7g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Publications Associate Manager: Req ID : 434341BR Job Code/Title : L7434:Mult Func Publications Asc Mgr Job Description : Enjoy leading a team? Have hands-on experience with proposals? Perform as a Publications Associate Manager for Denver by leading a… https://t.co/L9boYXPgfo https://t.co/gJ86C6hpIL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Security Operations Engineer: NETWORK SECURITY OPERATIONS ENGINEER This is a permanent full time role. RESPONSIBILITIES/QUALIFICATIONS * Thorough understanding of LAN and WAN with the ability to design, setup and configure Check Point Firewalls.… https://t.co/EMuSzzlD1i https://t.co/nyVsThFrmw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Project Manager Ref No.: 18-00486 Location: Charlottesville, Virginia Project Manager We collaborate. We create. We innovate. Intrigued? You’re a business professional with an innate curiosity that thrives in a dynamic and Agile… https://t.co/hleMee3VaX https://t.co/K1tKSi2EUq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Angular Developer: Angular Developer Ref No.: 18-24294 Location: Cincinnati, Ohio Job Description – Angular Developer Role – Collaborate with senior technologists and architects across the technology landscape to continually develop and expand their… https://t.co/2WyGFSo28U https://t.co/NdfRS1oUBW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Incident Response Security Analyst: Position: Incident Response Security Analyst Job Description: Job Summary; Part of Arrow Electronics Global Enterprise Services Team, the Incident Response Data Analyst will generally assist with service delivery by… https://t.co/f48SezdrTA https://t.co/XAhq1bGnNy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer Mbed Data Services: Job ID #: 12915 – Job Category: Information Technology – Employment Type: Experienced Professionals – Division: Internet of Things – Department: ISG Web Services – Primary Country: USA – Primary Location: San Jose… https://t.co/MVeRENZp6C https://t.co/PYlK1VxOcW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Software Engineer: Associate Software Engineer Role/Responsibilities The Moodys Analytics Technology Rotation Program is a rotational training program that enables recent graduates to continue to develop their technical skills, while learning… https://t.co/TTVozWWpGi https://t.co/CiEaaGQGJv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Manager: IT Manager Duties and Responsibilities * Analyze business needs presented by users/business units and recommend technical solutions with completion timeline * Maintain organizations effectiveness and efficiency by defining, delivering, and… https://t.co/cQ596M48w8 https://t.co/LEUR9zQnhG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Analyst: As part of the Business Area Business Operations organization, the Project Analyst provides direct program support to the Director of Programs, Program Managers, Associate Programs Managers, and Business Managers utilizing SNCs… https://t.co/UYbVqEDSyk https://t.co/GQzbz4l2b1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Java Developer Spring, REST API, Unix, RDBMS, Maven): For BNY Mellon Sr. Java Developer (J2EE, Spring, REST API, Unix, RDBMS, Maven) job – Information Technology – Multiple Skip to Main Content – – – – Toggle navigation – Who We Are – What We Do –… https://t.co/rgjHAVtjcR https://t.co/bx7sko7MuB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer: IGT is the global leader in gaming. We enable players to experience their favorite games across all channels and regulated segments, from Gaming Machines to Lotteries to Interactive. We have a well-established local presence and… https://t.co/OrGkl7O6Do https://t.co/PthSEJAtML]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator II: Tracking Code UASOCS-18-0244-F Job Code 18-0244 Posting Title Systems Administrator II Post Date 6/8/2018 Full Time / Part-Time Full Time Travel No Travel Required City Creech Air Force Base State NV Country US Description… https://t.co/i0xgJ5gMdh https://t.co/NUEfVvWHDA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer with Kentico: .Net Developer with Kentico Little rock, Arkansas – United States Job Start Date – 06/11/18, Posted Date – 06/11/18 Primary Skills.netTax TermsC2COverview Phone and skype. Duration- 6months. Rate- 55. Lcoation- Little rock… https://t.co/LXnwPTvnIq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IDS Analyst IV/Network Security: Req ID 95048BR Business Title IDS Analyst IV/Network Security Group MCIS Location USA VIRGINIA Arlington Clearance Level Needed Top Secret Category Cyber Job Duties and Responsibilities Become an integral part of a… https://t.co/WkSMw0mggD https://t.co/0VCDLG8VLo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java IVR Developer: What you’ll be doing. If you are curious about new technology and the possibilities it creates, then this job may be perfect for you. As part of the Information Technology team, you will work on new technologies and find ways… https://t.co/Qkvi6NwUus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Service-Desk-Analyst: GuideIT is a is a US based technology services company focused on providing value to its’ customers through technology alignment and optimization. We are currently looking for a Service Desk Analyst to join team in Wichita Falls,… https://t.co/MQfSGFTLpz https://t.co/lOjO0Sbikd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Administrator: Ref. No.: 2387 Job Title: Accounts Payable Specialist Office: WASHINGTON D.C. Practice Area: Accounting Posted Date: 09/07/2017 Job Type: Full Time Job Description: McDermott Will &amp; Emery LLP is a leading international law firm… https://t.co/6JxqOAHYE6 https://t.co/7jm8olCfqq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager, Real World and Late Phase Research: ICON named by Forbes as one of the best employers in America! ICON was the highest ranked CRO in the best large employers listing, and is amongst the top 10 companies in the ‘Drugs &amp; Biotechnology’… https://t.co/jqOg6ijOlS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Member of Technical Staff, Applications: Requisition Number 5695BR External Posting Title Senior Member of Technical Staff, Applications Time Type Full time Pay Rate Type Salary Work Shift Regular – Salaried Country United States Locations San… https://t.co/qjPhxFDlXM https://t.co/6O54SIVToe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology: MARKETING Interested candidates send resume to: Google LLC, PO Box 26184 San Francisco, CA 94126 Attn: A. Johnson. Please reference job # below: Account Strategist (Multiple Positions); Mountain View/Palo Alto/ San Bruno, CA; Perform market… https://t.co/qcCpmOzFRC https://t.co/ZCZXQ6mHs0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer positions (Mountain View/Palo Alto/San Bruno, CA) Design, develop, modify, and/or test software needed for various Google projects. Exp Incl: #JUN2018MVSBPA-J01 (Multiple Positions); C++, Java, Javascript,… https://t.co/TsLBvUnmYm https://t.co/1im9OodgFH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Washington, DC Job Type: Strategy – Planning Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 5/30/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management and… https://t.co/SRdrgRKGBN https://t.co/XSC4dcWzoS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer Applications: SUMMARY: This position’s primary role is to define, develop, test, analyze, and maintain software applications in support of the achievement of business requirements. Responsibilities could include writing business requirements… https://t.co/5a8XeAIxcH https://t.co/eknH1xgC9S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electrical Engineer- Hardware (DO-254): 18004BR Electrical Engineer- Hardware (DO-254) General Atomics Aeronautical Systems San Diego California General Atomics Aeronautical Systems, Inc. (GA-ASI), an affiliate of General Atomics, is a world leader in… https://t.co/gpCth7gMCj https://t.co/d4IYtvNL1j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Informatics System Specialist: Agilent inspires and supports discoveries that advance the quality of life. We provide life science, diagnostic and applied market laboratories worldwide with instruments, services, consumables, applications and expertise.… https://t.co/y6V8DeJ6O9 https://t.co/zuKkwBawZy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Softw Dvlpr, IBM Corporation, San Jose, CA: Write productn quality code, unit tests, test plans, QA, &amp; documentatn. Prep technl proposals &amp; proof of concepts for various networking use cases. Dvlp web UI for cloud based Load Balancer… https://t.co/TGGYE2oGLk https://t.co/kshfC5tyed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator: SYSTEMS ADMINISTRATOR If you want to take your love of computers to the next level in a fast -paced and challenging environment, we would love to have you join our talented team. You will get the chance to work with multiple… https://t.co/1XHucCggqA https://t.co/3wiFsW48BY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solutions Architect: Location US-OH-Cincinnati Posted Date 1 month ago(4/27/2018 2:15 PM) Job ID 23456 # Positions 2 Category Technology Position Type Full Time Overview Be Here. Be Great. Working for a leader in the insurance industry means opportunity… https://t.co/LmKRqt71HN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer Ref No.:18-00235 Category: ************* Location: Lanham, Maryland Position Type:Contingent Start Date: 06/01/2018 Job Req -Additional Info Shift Work?:No Work Schedule:TBD Clearance Requirement:NACI Requirements:… https://t.co/RXWtaPOBPp https://t.co/OMJNPVuIJM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Project Manager =============== Req #: ******Location: Fairfax, VA USJob Category: Project and Program ManagementSecurity Clearance: TS/SCI with PolygraphClearance Status: Must Be Current Job Description What You ll Get to Do: This… https://t.co/WGuJCMWJaV https://t.co/D6Z4gZNFOf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Security Engineer: Job Description Job Title: Network Security Engineer Rate: Job Type: Direct Hire Location: Madison Primary Skills: networking, security, firewalls, cisco, routers, switches, intrusion detection Description: Network Security… https://t.co/rJd8lMCqUg https://t.co/of5ryeLpvc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Android Development Engineer Infotainment: Do you imagine a world of zerocrashes, zero emissions and zero congestion? We do. We place our customers atthe center of everything we do and we are creating vehicles that move humanityto that goal. The… https://t.co/zsgJJMfeHb https://t.co/7r4KgwtJef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Practice Director: Practice Director Job Location US-NY-New York City Req No. 2018-2307 Category Engineering/Professional Services Overview The Practice Director manages the fulfillment of billable engagements and maintaining project profitability for… https://t.co/hpzSzdUUVN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – C/C++: SOFTWARE ENGINEER I CENTREVILLE, VA **US Citizenship required due to Federal Government Requirement** Do you want to design, develop, and deliver bleeding-edge technical solutions in the national cyber security domain? Employer… https://t.co/kQdBzaLM0q https://t.co/Ybe1yRoAII]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer positions (Mountain View/Palo Alto/San Bruno, CA) Design, develop, modify, and/or test software needed for various Google projects. Exp Incl: #JUN2018MVSBPA-J01 (Multiple Positions); C++, Java, Javascript,… https://t.co/x8lMGahHp2 https://t.co/IUwwujF6wF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electrical Engineer #SJM-0018-KE: Engineering: Electrical Engineer (MRI): St. Jude Medical, Cardiology Division, in Sylmar, CA seeks qualified Electrical Engineer (MRI). Responsible for providing engineering services to device manufacturing operations &amp;… https://t.co/urqNVyR5O1 https://t.co/MUK1lhb4e7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales Representative – Marketing Developer: Treetop Trekking Construction (TTT) builder and operator of Ziplines, Canopy tours, Aerial Adventure Parks, Treetop Trails, and Tree Walk Villages. TTT seeks a qualified candidate to serve as a Salesperson with… https://t.co/OprTAsolOM https://t.co/nYyavfgup6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MAGTF IO Sr. Principal Operations Analyst/Planning Support – TS/SCI – Doral, FL: Requisition ID 2018-42011 # of Openings 1 Job Function Program Management Security Clearance Level Top Secret/SCI Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description Provides military… https://t.co/CBaf4SnIlQ https://t.co/stRYmCNVYq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Configuration Analyst 2/3:   Job Description – Configuration Analyst 2/3 (18010643) Configuration Analyst 2/3 Requisition ID : 18010643 Location : United States-California-Manhattan Beach US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation… https://t.co/j7tjIi2Zok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Security Engineer: Information Security Engineer Job Number: 113657405 Culver City, California, United States Posted: Apr. 24, 2018 Weekly Hours: 40.00 Job Summary We’re looking to hire an Information Security professional to help lead the… https://t.co/24u9370u4G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager Fire Solutions: **Project Manager – Fire Solutions** Locations:Pensacola, Florida Job Family: Engineering New Search English (US) **Job Description** **Division:** Building Technologies **Business Unit:** Field Operations **Requisition… https://t.co/U6DkZksGPW https://t.co/zCHwrRDGyG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: O2 Technologies, Inc. in Irvine, CA is seeking Software QA Engineers to monitor, analyze &amp; test sftwr during dvlpmnt in order to ensure quality. No trvl; no telecomm. Job duties are proj-based &amp; performed @ unanticipated sites w/in… https://t.co/FLIubpCLqa https://t.co/e6QFampJz6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple News Tries to Avoid Facebook’s Mistakes With Midterm Elections Section: From now until November, every Apple News user in the US will see a curated section of stories about the midterm elections. https://t.co/wzaa070mkB https://t.co/i36npvgX1s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Representative: Technical Support Representative The Technical Support Representative will work cooperatively with the Technical Services Manager and other members of the team assisting with the delivery and management of… https://t.co/6mOTyelG2A https://t.co/1J5dOiAMYy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Overview Public Consulting Group, Inc. (PCG) provides management consulting and technology services to help public sector education, health, human services, and other government clients achieve their performance goals and better… https://t.co/z8MAWwmAXs https://t.co/EQNoo7CsRc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GIS Specialist 1: GIS Specialist 1 ================ Req #: ******Location: Charlottesville, VA USJob Category: IntelligenceSecurity Clearance: TS/SCIClearance Status: Must be Obtainable Job Description POSITION SUMMARY: Under direct supervision, performs… https://t.co/PRB1MJ01FW https://t.co/Fpo8bTvjsn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Desktop Support Technician: Requisition ID 2017-21192 # of Openings 0 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Top Secret/SCI Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description Provide Tier 2 level user and hardware support of Windows based… https://t.co/1SNJr0FD4P https://t.co/EYpKquuRi6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TITLE SOFTWARE ENGINEER LEVEL 1: Careers Center | Software Engineer Level 1 (431) (TS) Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a… https://t.co/J1w6ut9DxN https://t.co/fckECpNkCK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staff Software Engineer — Heterogeneous Computing Runtime: Job Title: Staff Software Engineer — Heterogeneous Computing Runtime – ****** Primary Location United States-California-San Jose Job: Software Engineering Schedule: Full-time Description Xilinx… https://t.co/Mzi5iolHfb https://t.co/FlXDOMMfjW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager: Send digital resume to: ************************************ Have you ever subscribed to a premium online service on your computer or tablet? Perhaps to watch your favorite TV programs, films and videos, listen to new music, or… https://t.co/IOmMAhnRMX https://t.co/l7e0TOjKFs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT ServiceNow System Administrator: ServiceNow Systems Administrator **DIRECT APPLICANTS ONLY – NO THIRD PARTIES, PLEASE ** 3 months contract to hire Oakland, Ca Minimum requirements for this position are: – 3+ years of ServiceNow development,… https://t.co/QVClvKdLSI https://t.co/JrJnEZGKfs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Multiple Engineer Positions: Multiple Openings GL PwrSolutions, Inc.Dallas, TX GL PwrSolutions, Inc. has multiple openings for the following positions at our office in Dallas, TX: Engineer – Power Systems Planning; Engineer – Generation Interconnection… https://t.co/K9VrtB7Bwq https://t.co/iRfDcGjJCJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MicroStrategy Developer: MicroStrategy Developer wanted by clothing retailer company in Conshohocken, PA. Develop reports &amp; data analyses. Develop, test, &amp; prepare documentation related to business intelligence content. Requires: BS in Computer Science &amp;… https://t.co/5WyiSwNJPo https://t.co/HUbvZkOIt1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Project Lead #ITPL: IT Project Lead (Multiple Positions) Identify requirements by establishing personal rapport with potential and actual clients and with other persons in a position to understand service requirements. Maintain computer systems and… https://t.co/Ol42MXoc6I https://t.co/d8o9i4zIDh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SR. NETWORK ENGINEER: SR. NETWORK Engineer. Bachelor’s and 5yrs exp reqd. Work loc. Arden, NC. Send resume to OceanX LLC, 1845 Brevard Rd, Arden, NC 28704recblid u92t5b3o16r5hmoz1rsqmt75ljl0jv https://t.co/WsIrD9zECe https://t.co/uvBCQZmqeN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Axiom developer: ****** Axiom developer Ref No.: 18-20303 Location: charlotte, North Carolina Hello, Hope you are doing great. This is Vishal from Enterprise Solution Inc. and I am writing to you regarding an excellent job opportunity based out of… https://t.co/PQUd2zDvjw https://t.co/69L2qHQWMj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Tech Summer Program- Software Engineering Assistant: SAP Tech Summer Program- Software Engineering Assistant Job Close By continuing to use and navigate this website, you are agreeing to the use of cookies. Accept – SAP Careers home – SAP employees –… https://t.co/7q9lZ31uSh https://t.co/oEhqJ7CoiN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GCCS Software Engineer: GCCS – Software Engineer (TS/SCI) – DMV ======================================= Req #: ******_1Location: Suitland, MD USJob Category: Information TechnologySecurity Clearance: TS/SCIClearance Status: Must Be Current Job… https://t.co/zk5imszVkC https://t.co/xfVFfdvdYf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Customer Service Analyst II: Position Summary: This position is responsible for the coordination of clerical functions for the sales support. Working independently with minimal supervision, performs relatively complex administrative duties including… https://t.co/3wlsFML7jM https://t.co/QCkJsULQ9g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Earthquake Data Scientist: Earthquake Data Scientist Palo Alto, California Data Science Full Time One Concern is a startup which specializes in Artificial Intelligence for Natural Disasters. With our team of global disaster scientists and engineers, we… https://t.co/ajLlxCARHq https://t.co/AFssjlRWBk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Requisition Title Research Statistician Developer – Statistical Quality Control: Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job.… https://t.co/id71gNrBuU https://t.co/HTRdrXEAwB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager-Public Safety Projects: Job Description Tracking Code 4793-244 Job Description At Gilbane we’re building more than buildings, we’re helping create schools, hospitals, laboratories and other facilities across the United States and… https://t.co/GtFKFdnk5b https://t.co/CBFqE943FW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Analyst/Sr Business Systems Analyst- Omaha, NE.: Business Systems Analyst/Sr Business Systems Analyst- Omaha, NE. Job no: ****** Work type: Full Time Regular Location: Nebraska Categories: Information Technnology Provides input into… https://t.co/6HrGhNRhHw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Military IT Support Analyst: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Washington, DC Job Type: Strategy – Planning Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/6/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest… https://t.co/yCoiJsXSuf https://t.co/v9MLF7oR2N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Developer: MOSAIC Technologies Group Cloud Developer Annapolis Junction, MD 20701 MOSAIC is seeking an Cloud Developer for a malware analysis modernization program in the Annapolis Junction, MD area. Job Responsibilities: Tasking includes new… https://t.co/bXyfpMlyz7 https://t.co/l8dSO5OSaL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SW Engineer QA Cloud Software: Blog Search jobs Keyword CategorySelectAdministrationBusiness PlanningCorporate AdministrationEngineeringEngineering ServicesFinanceGeneral ManagementHuman ResourcesInformation TechnologyLearning &amp;… https://t.co/RTMO0cNP7I https://t.co/ZhgqDhLbjM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer – Virtualization: Location PL-Remote Posting date 7 hours ago(6/19/2018 7:01 AM) Job ID 62404 Category Software Engineering Company Description At Red Hat, we connect an innovative community of customers, partners, and… https://t.co/G6CmOwiSKt https://t.co/jr9uIWcJPA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[166-Front End Software Developer: GENERAL DUTIES Responsible for employing agile development processes and operating in a cloud environment. Use established agile processes and tools to capture themes, epics/capabilities, user stories, features, and… https://t.co/TqrchhpWOD https://t.co/oF2wH82mFA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Java Developer: Title: Sr. Java Developer Location: Arlington, VA Position: Full-Time US Citizen Only Salary: Market Requirements:- * Total Experience required 8-10 years * Good hand on experience in Java and J2EE technologies (JMS, JSP &amp; Servlets).… https://t.co/pf2AzlOaAg https://t.co/VWNP6nOj9O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network and Systems Specialist: Company Description ThreatConnect arms organizations with a powerful defense against cyber threats and the confidence to make strategic business decisions. Founded in 2011, ThreatConnect (then called CyberSquared) started… https://t.co/6FxrV1pVxY https://t.co/UGhnCJ9JnJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Sr. Administrative Specialist: SAP NS2 Sr. Administrative Specialist – Herndon-20171 Job Close By continuing to use and navigate this website, you are agreeing to the use of cookies. Accept – SAP Careers home – SAP employees – Join our talent… https://t.co/ufSn0whRah https://t.co/mFHFKDZWpA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer / Developer: Job Description Software Engineer / Developer (14775) Introduction: The Johns Hopkins University Applied Physics Laboratory (APL), a national leader in scientific research and development, located midway between Baltimore… https://t.co/2ujiOVClOy https://t.co/fMQaoHXccO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior C++ Financial Developer: Senior C++ Financial Developer McLean, VA Join a team of Financial Engineers responsible for the C++ Library that implements the major market and credit risk models for a trillion-dollar balance sheet of mortgages and… https://t.co/7OlS9YrlEZ https://t.co/ynqq7lxFmN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer Power and Control Circuit Design 4:   Job Description – Engineer Power and Control Circuit Design 4 (18008951) Engineer Power and Control Circuit Design 4 Requisition ID : 18008951 Location : United States-California-Redondo Beach US Citizenship… https://t.co/gvH0jArf9C https://t.co/8PW7Nn6umk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering: COMPUTER/IT Developer for Ariba, Inc (Palo Alto, CA) to develop, maintain, and improve our automated functional test, integration test suite, and performance test suite. Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science, Engineering, Mathematics, or a… https://t.co/8w2cvDyZqu https://t.co/29bvyy2nYV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Project Manager (Energy Efficiency, Emerging Technologies): TRC Energy Services (TRC) creates and implements sophisticated and innovative solutions to the challenges facing America’s energy markets and infrastructure. TRC provides energy… https://t.co/WG0ZU6Ctgo https://t.co/dbtntPILts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Survey Project Manager: Discipline Survey Job Location(s) US-VA-Sterling Type Regular Full-Time Use your browser ‘Back’ button to return to job listings Overview Manage the day to day operations of Rail Survey for the DC area. Responsibilities * VA… https://t.co/RJuKTnbnCx https://t.co/18kNfWvRGT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[STIP Service Desk Lead: STIP Service Desk Lead ====================== Req #: ******Location: Chantilly, VA USJob Category: Information TechnologySecurity Clearance: SecretClearance Status: Must be Obtainable Job Description CACI is currently looking for… https://t.co/mjpc60PVpP https://t.co/QBqeF8kQmc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Data Analyst: The Clinical Analytics &amp; Reporting Team is responsible for designing, developing and overseeing analytical solutions for our clinical and operations executives in support of DaVita s clinical strategy. Our team s mission is to… https://t.co/EgGQMSsq7C https://t.co/F3Fnz0wJq6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer I, IT Process Analyst: Thermo Fisher Scientific – Engineer I, IT Process Analyst Job in Carlsbad, CA – Home – Discover Our Stories – Career Areas – Engineering – Field Service – Finance – General Management – Human Resources – Operations &amp;… https://t.co/PfC8sAjBoD https://t.co/QVqIjeLZAg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Contract: I2TS3 Position Title: Supervisor, Project/Task – Project Manager (L2) Location: Fort Gordon, GA GENERAL SUMMARY: GDIT is seeking candidates to support the US Army Intelligence and Security Command (INSCOM). Under the I2TS 3… https://t.co/g9u3zPUwZ9 https://t.co/KhVowhcifo]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>