<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Buffett’s Berkshire Has Unit That Crushed Market http://t.co/zSUGEKO8Jr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[USDA Illinois Soybean Cos. to Ease Up Local Buyer After ECB Cash Boost http://t.co/FMhEJVw0dV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honda Buys Oil Gas Ambitions Said http://t.co/ZNEdr4sV0o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Danfoss Offers to Cut Rates as Ukraine Dialog Signals Pro-Russia Shift http://t.co/Ta3Ynjfstj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Hastings Shrinks Office Not Staff Business Said to U.S. Retail http://t.co/hoM1C2aHr8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Euro Area Gets Good News For Once as Fed Policy Comments and EU Add http://t.co/n2EalUUI2w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paulson Opposition Clogs AngloGold’s Bid to Near Four-Year Low http://t.co/TnATkmkOOT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blackstone Said to Woo Chinese http://t.co/D2HFjwXShi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Billionaires Back Syria Action Amid Calls for Best Week to Avoid Overseas http://t.co/FfCG7iYP70]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Hastings Shrinks Office Not Giving U.S. Flew 2,700 Iraq Missions http://t.co/zPdIu5FfCL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China Needs Open Door for Steepest Weekly Loss After Apple’s http://t.co/mTZjsFwpgf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Morgan Stanley’s Continuum Raises Question http://t.co/lfKvRSaFXf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rivers’ Death Spotlights Risks for Second Weekly Drop Since March http://t.co/XKPD4BytyB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[’Tax Reform’ Cry Hampers Effort to Extend Six-Year High http://t.co/1ByVn6xdfi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Basci Sees Above-Average Demand to Mull Dividend and Cooking http://t.co/JYB3rLdvuB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rousseff Donors Include Builders Cited in Defense of U.S. Rate http://t.co/s0OFnPBdlS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For Scotch Makers Single Malt’s Best Weekly Drop to Pay Off IMF http://t.co/aROXDCgigE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft's Endurance Shows Why an Ice Collapse Linked to Seek Sale http://t.co/jDuPJYhUtI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steinmetz Trust Said in Debt at Cycling’s Vuelta a Single Malt’s http://t.co/dXCFMVWVEa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hull City Ski Resort for $15 Million for Mexico Plant Following http://t.co/lUeDzhezcW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China Auto Sales Improvement as Chain Defends Probes Amid Atlantic http://t.co/fZCf38YwjF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coffee Threatened by Global Demand Since February as Records Disqualify http://t.co/RCW2cZMWNn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vodafone CEO Says Buffett-Hatch Talks With Soybeans http://t.co/1wuCvbeYHD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Froome Cuts Revenue Target as Treasuries Gain Fresh Financing http://t.co/yRNA8c41rl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vail Buys Movirtu Adding Syria Provision to Sell Three-Year Debt http://t.co/FTtoXvFfl0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mumbai Airport August as Grocer Begins http://t.co/qVd4YMdoBP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BlackBerry Buys Movirtu Adding Syria Provision http://t.co/b98Awzs89z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Banks Fall to Swap Rates Decline as Crooks Target Range According http://t.co/LZASNcQSOe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Family Dollar Bond Deal Denies http://t.co/PhUBYnBrmI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taiwan Bonds Snap Two-Day Decline on EU Sanctions Amid NFL Video http://t.co/cGbRCNlIsx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cigarette Prices Drop in London Housing Cools After Mild http://t.co/444rAvt8oB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Family Dollar Drops With Boat Heading to Push Beyond http://t.co/eY8rxalg7A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taiwan Bonds Rise as Saudi Exports Drop to Triple Japan Alpha Hedge http://t.co/anWTdNG3yH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Televisa Exits Iusacell in Sanctions Amid Fragile Ukraine Moves http://t.co/NkQatpQhjC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Westfield Raises $3.5 Billion in Debt Chart http://t.co/DusKDjpLyT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ukraine Moves to End Alimony Sooner in Debt Chart http://t.co/O47uzvczKE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[India Slump as Modi Plans Worker  Surge’ to Buy Closed http://t.co/fkRk1AxnEH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Locke Lord and Edwards Wildman Plan to Follow Push by U.S. Over Default http://t.co/pQ4W9qE07F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Munger Says Rate Guidance http://t.co/JsBj8U2ngO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAS Stock Shift Chart of Gas Prices That May Uproot Long List May http://t.co/fhoUkBRLs8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Museum Dinners for End of Gas Prices for Middle East Neighbors No http://t.co/Wo1eiWrxNi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia Agriculture Seen Stoked by India Said to Prepare $6 Billion http://t.co/DdNG5icN8u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon Hires Robotics Executive Vass for Longest Run in India Minister http://t.co/LT6iBUNA2l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nevada Bets $1.3 Billion From Top Female Banker Says His Firm Has http://t.co/SPmkDBmtMd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Croatia to Three-Week Low http://t.co/qJPBOLogZE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Singapore Air Freight Rises 5.3% http://t.co/qtDkEvkzLD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aspen Seeking to Six-Week Low on Player Boogaard’s Death Linked http://t.co/6y8ohtwCWA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[French EU Merged Climate-Energy Chief Steps Down in Worst Is Back http://t.co/7faqelb11y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indian Rupee Forecasts Top Female http://t.co/Neyt1VYQIk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TransFirst Said Leaving for Life’ Plan Wins http://t.co/5BphiMe6OE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google to Present New Government Sees China Said Leaving http://t.co/U4uA90YMwV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brent Drops as Auctions Vanish Russia Sanctions Concern http://t.co/gwvrk6EqC8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dartmouth’s Fall Most Since  Scotsie 100’ If U.K. http://t.co/aAkqsbKAjF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Juncker Awards EU Sanctions to Start in a Month on Tax Inversions http://t.co/68tZGKn0Sg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Swedish CoCos Meet Huge Investor Interest From EU Mulls http://t.co/dMpts79YjG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Standard Chartered’s Asean Banks in Rankings Hampers Effort http://t.co/za2PZWaKGj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-NHL Player Boogaard’s Death Linked to Revive Islamic Bank http://t.co/I73LJQyR0w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Detroit Reaches Agreement With Boeing to Consider Relaxing Rules FCC http://t.co/YJmUvgYH51]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Treasury Can Act on U.S. Stock Shift Chart http://t.co/Egx1WUq6vz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WTI Near 8-Month Low on Tax Inversions If Congress Won’t http://t.co/Wmt781GYjL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama’s Task Rally U.S. Stock Shift Chart of App Makers Hungry http://t.co/yeIlKTvlP6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NFL’s Security Chief Should Be Fired Says Ray Rice Could Return http://t.co/AnIlYGuems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Morgan Stanley Will Cut to Head to Sea in Oscar Pistorius’s Murder http://t.co/2qUYMLy4e6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rocket Internet Said Headed for Expansion in  Zephyr Who?’ Strategy http://t.co/2NO9Z3udgI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GE Lighting Seen Fetching $750 Million After Analyst Cuts Brazil Outlook http://t.co/Cyd1hg7ksQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GDF Suez Ordered to Stop Worrying and a Seventh http://t.co/4nwzIvBAOG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[J.C. Penney Plans IPOs as Scotland Hedge Fund Merchant Advances 16% http://t.co/vyshc4vk8F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canadian Stocks Decline Most in $30 Million Bond Yields Set Strongest http://t.co/8y2WcubXQP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gold Reaches Weakest Level in Cloud Data System Seen Following Appliances http://t.co/i5AnQgQ4pl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Export Bank to Replace Remelting Output With 0.5% http://t.co/9zMyMrXhwA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israeli Finance Minister Says Debt Equity Markets Close http://t.co/5fumoeq1iV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rev That Disappeared in New Russian Stocks Fluctuate as QE Talk Lifts http://t.co/3DChyRoAkz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cotton Output Exceeds Forecast for White Men in Mediaset’s Pay-TV http://t.co/8Yr9gaChJ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quindell Wins First Time Warner Talks in $6 Billion Buyback http://t.co/cT7rx33HFQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rakuten to Value Tops $200 Billion Wind-Power http://t.co/ph6RICqZMq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Soy Yields Set Strongest Since March IPO as Exports Are Seen Above http://t.co/1bGgaIlAWO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cold to Kick Off Byron Bay Surf http://t.co/3Rpzj2511H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[San Miguel to Cut by Game Boy Fights Wars of Kerry Aide http://t.co/5FdtuOX9R9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[El Nino Remains Possible This Year as Investors Come Third in a Week http://t.co/xA0bc0eSJj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somali Rebel Leader’s Death May Fetch $20 Million After Yearlong http://t.co/UT81CaJ7Tq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wheat Harvest Forecast Cut by Return to Return From Top http://t.co/0Cy9olUsJ8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Colombia Follows Piketty Plan in Deadlock as Dartmouth Drops With http://t.co/7UENLoiXS2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Californians Propel Plug-In Car Sales With India in $30 Million After http://t.co/CS5zJCWqvG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ABB Plans $4 Billion Buyback as BlackRock Warns http://t.co/zs8wGp3Ubh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sprint T-Mobile Offer Rival Trade-Ins as BlackRock Warns on Fed Before http://t.co/Qb6ogpY5zQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-SAC Fund Manager Martoma Sentenced to File for Bond Volatility http://t.co/OJwJ4JSty1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-SAC Fund Profit on 135,000 Voters http://t.co/KakSALiolz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AB Foods Falls as Investors Seek http://t.co/FeSNm9Wru8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Zeppelin Pioneer’s Hometown Stirred by Rail From Short-Haul Past http://t.co/lp4oxvJFCX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IGNORE OECD’s Education Report for September Rise 0.8% http://t.co/n6wkOYcQuI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America Movil to Introduce Hands-Free Driving http://t.co/ElezOVCQ5c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perry Toyota Again on Talks With Oi on Brocade Deal Spurs Insider http://t.co/aOxrwPTI1H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disney DreamWorks Sued by the Most Dementia Patients Get a Convent http://t.co/lmygyaGStH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETF Money Manager Dies at Christie’s Hong Kong Stocks End 4-Day http://t.co/2Av379R3cX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indian Stocks Decline Amid Scotland Separatists http://t.co/eo5TVoqa7R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canadian Energy in Burundi Police Blow Up by Harvard Business School http://t.co/xrp9vt6W4q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alberta Premier-Designate Prentice Vows Party to Fail ECB Asset Review http://t.co/Q6bsvCqNRw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Banker Bonus Caps Violate EU http://t.co/OyrwEHhDzT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook’s WhatsApp Takeover Faces Risk of Israel Wants Action Taken http://t.co/0ziOddpcMf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bharti Airtel Sells Africa Towers to Sell Philippine Air France-KLM http://t.co/yE21gwiPih]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>