<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Terminal Automation Engineer: Terminal Automation Engineer Honeywell Careers Chinese (Simplified)Czech (Czech Republic)Dutch (The Netherlands)English (US)French (Canada)French (France)German (Germany)Portuguese (Brazil)Spanish (Spain)Create a Profile|Log… https://t.co/U7N54mwRwy https://t.co/3v9kxA9ZX2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Traveling Superintendent – Retail TI: Houston, TX Compensation Unspecified Posted Today We are a commercial general contractor headquartered in Texas, doing business across the country. Our projects are both ground up and renovation and are mostly within… https://t.co/TQtrzNwF7T https://t.co/vMf8MIW6Oy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deep in the Pentagon, a secret AI program to find hidden nuclear missiles: WASHINGTON (Reuters) - The U.S. military is increasing spending on a secret research effort to use artificial intelligence to help anticipate the launch of a nuclear-capable… https://t.co/tvIZ2oNYby https://t.co/lpDgh3hY9b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Analyst: We are seeking a Data Feeds Business Analyst to join our expanding Commercial Technology teams in Houston, TX. This is a client-facing Business Analyst role responsible for working with customers and partners to define… https://t.co/JdKgkOy6d3 https://t.co/R4yCgvIkZA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Full Stack Developer: .Net Full Stack Developer Ref No.: 18-21765 Location: Houston, Texas Position : .Net Full Stack Developer Duration : Full Time Permanent Work Location : Houston, TX Job Description .Net Development background Angular 2 Strong… https://t.co/vmTx3MN33u https://t.co/Uo9U1RlHqQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[German robotics sales growth to slow after record 2017: BERLIN (Reuters) - German sales of robotics and automation equipment, an engine of the country's export-led economy, are expected to shrug off growing tensions over international trade to rise by 9… https://t.co/ZAFyJof34q https://t.co/bk0x1dG3f2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, Quality: Microsemi, Inc. has an early career Quality Systems Engineer opening based in Houston, Texas to be a key contributor in the testing effort of our storage firmware and driver applications. In this role, you will be responsible… https://t.co/ViqlUWazDO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior System Software Engineer: Texas Instruments – Job detailsTI Careers – – – Applicant Login – About TI – Company – Careers – Investor relations – Citizenship – University – Public policy – Careers – Our company – Why TI – Career paths – Search jobs… https://t.co/Uol62niiY8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETC – Web Application Development and Data Analytics Analyst: Salary/Rate N/A Permanent Location Houston, TX Texas, US, United States Posted By Chevron Date Posted 33 minutes ago Expires 22 Jun 2018 Qualifications None ETC – Web Application Development… https://t.co/C7PRt65iWU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Developer (C#/WPF, Houston): Senior Developer (C#/WPF, Houston) Toggle navigation – About Us – Inside Luxoft – Benefits – Automotive – Excelian – Training &amp; Communities – Relocation Program – Social Responsibility – Discover Us – Events – Referral… https://t.co/prdr05gBTD https://t.co/vigoaKNzvS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer: Network Engineer in Houston, TX at Alltran Join Our Talent Network Join Our Talent Network Toggle navigation – Careers home – About Us – Interview prep – All jobs – Our culture – Our events – Our events – Join Our Talent Network Toggle… https://t.co/84pZPuBFXX https://t.co/Qp13SQMbae]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[France does not expect UK to develop own satnav rival to Galileo: PARIS (Reuters) - France does not think Britain will launch a rival to the European Union's Galileo satellite navigation system, minutes from a meeting between a cabinet minister and… https://t.co/JeSQjHfTv7 https://t.co/EfvbsAAquR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Multifamily Superintendent- Top Tier Owner/Builder: Houston, TX Compensation Unspecified Posted 05/15/2018 As a company we hold a strong belief in building successful long term relationships with our clients. We as a company, work with our clients as a… https://t.co/JDhsgARSoq https://t.co/RNm2RZ8hZt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Web Developer (.Net/SharePoint): Sr. Web Developer (.Net, Point) – V3Main ************** – Home – About – Mission, Vision, &amp; Values – Leadership – Government – Cybersecurity – News – Services – IT Managed Services – Agile Software Development –… https://t.co/W5WhRRKEtL https://t.co/UFoS3oDTpB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Software Engineer: Microsemi, Inc. has an early career Quality Systems Engineer opening based in Houston, Texas to be a key contributor in the testing effort of our storage firmware and driver applications. In this role, you will be responsible… https://t.co/6vxGPfx7f4 https://t.co/DgKSWm3Moq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Developer (C#/WPF): Lead Developer (C#/WPF) Toggle navigation – About Us – Inside Luxoft – Benefits – Automotive – Excelian – Training &amp; Communities – Relocation Program – Social Responsibility – Discover Us – Events – Referral Program – Recruitment… https://t.co/cyw4Fo6Kc4 https://t.co/7QzgZTDXY1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sap Abap Apo Developer: SAP ABAP APO Developer Houston, Texas – United States Posted Date – 05/29/18 Primary Skills SAP Netweaver 7.0 EHP3 Overview Role: SAP ABAP APO Developer Location: Houston, TX Duration: 1 year plus potential extensions Environment:… https://t.co/921P2GqCTh https://t.co/zbTX1oFwxZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Network Administrator: * Senior Network Administrator Job Locations US-TX-Houston Job ID 2018-1719 Category Information Technology Overview About Pharm-Olam International: Pharm-Olam International is a mid-size Contract Research Organization (CRO)… https://t.co/QMmOPNPKZz https://t.co/zNTiVKL8NF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TERADATA DBA: TERADATA DBA HOUSTON, Texas – United States Job Start Date – 05/10/18, Posted Date – 05/10/18 Primary SkillsTeradataTax TermsC2COverview Location:- Houston TX Position Type:- Contract Rate:-$45 per hr Who are we looking for? Looking for DBA… https://t.co/TbOFQDAR5D https://t.co/pxn1q2vQBm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Software Engineer New Grad: Microsemi, Inc. has an early career Quality Systems Engineer opening based in Houston, Texas to be a key contributor in the testing effort of our storage firmware and driver applications. In this role, you will be… https://t.co/YSbnNTBt5V https://t.co/jfNEntd4D6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GM settles lawsuit with motorcyclist hit by self-driving car: (Reuters) - General Motors Co agreed to settle a lawsuit filed by a motorcyclist involved in a minor crash with one of its self-driving cars in San Francisco late last year, the U.S. automaker… https://t.co/y6VBLP6rGL https://t.co/aRnuR00Qfj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, Quality: Microsemi, Inc. has an early career Quality Systems Engineer opening based in Houston, Texas to be a key contributor in the testing effort of our storage firmware and driver applications. In this role, you will be responsible… https://t.co/iCBvyFiBJs https://t.co/APhCFLK0Nc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Software Engineer – Masters New Grad: Microsemi, Inc. has an early career Quality Systems Engineer opening based in Houston, Texas to be a key contributor in the testing effort of our storage firmware and driver applications. In this role, you… https://t.co/XXgnoBcTLg https://t.co/3FQureKcHV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Water/Wastewater Project Manager: SNC-Lavalin’s Atkins business is one of the world’s most respected design, engineering and project management consultancies. SNC-Lavalin’s Atkins business has been providing infrastructure planning, engineering,… https://t.co/67BXdity3F https://t.co/LLcVoMYlEo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Superintendent-K-12/Education construction-Ground Up/Renovations: Houston, TX Full-time $65k – $140k Posted Today If you are a Superintendent-K -12/Education construction-Ground Up/TI with experience, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us 90% of… https://t.co/D9QvcjU1Od https://t.co/vELWISik7S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: HigherEducation: DevOps Engineer We Work Remotely See more DevOps &amp; Sysadmin jobs Back to all jobs DevOps Engineer Posted May 28 HigherEducation Headquarters: Houston, TX ******************************* View all HigherEducation jobs… https://t.co/CzTqxVpQpW https://t.co/OYmOszdlZ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Management Office Coordinator: **Project Management Office Coordinator** Locations:Houston, Texas Job Family: Internal Services New Search Apply English (US) **Job Description** **Division:** Power Generation Services **Business Unit:**… https://t.co/46oGNG7SfL https://t.co/9agVL1ccfz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Audit / Auditor: Job Description Hi Jose, We have been engaged by a client of ours in the Central Houston area. They are seeking an Internal Auditor for a Temporary to Hire role.The company is a top flight organization that boasts a great work… https://t.co/cz0364NqvF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager, Engineering – Specialty Chemicals, Full-time: Business unit: AMPE About AkzoNobel Industries worldwide rely on our essential chemistry in the manufacture of everyday products such as paper, plastics, building materials, and personal care… https://t.co/K06yPjKQL0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Operate Landscape Manager – DBA – Houston, TX: Salary/Rate N/A Permanent Location Houston, TX, United States Posted By Shell Date Posted 33 minutes ago Expires 07 Jun 2018 Qualifications None Operate Landscape Manager – DBA – Houston, TX in Houston, TX,… https://t.co/S9SVEyZx3t https://t.co/2BTGfUtKkD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Telegram says Apple has prevented it from updating since April: MOSCOW (Reuters) - Apple has prevented the Telegram messaging service from updating globally ever since Russia ordered Apple to remove the service from its stores, Telegram's CEO and founder… https://t.co/8e3CKjmfPZ https://t.co/wKkbU848us]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anywhere Expert Device Replacement Onboarding Acting Coach (Houston):   Job Description – Anywhere Expert Device Replacement Onboarding Acting Coach (Houston) (PSS29817) Job Description*  Anywhere Expert Device Replacement Onboarding Acting Coach… https://t.co/AcTYcKU8KH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. IT Project Manager: Vaco has a contract opportunity (potential contract to hire) in Houston, TX for a Sr. IT Project Manager. The IT Senior Project Manager (Contract) role is responsible for providing a standardized approach to identify, prioritize,… https://t.co/PXetXC8Dot https://t.co/MtwcGC3Ecr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager-MEP: Careers Center | Project Manager-MEP Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome page Returning… https://t.co/kI24sAgG8K https://t.co/wVXW3kDvgi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETC – Web Application Development and Data Analytics Analyst: Salary/Rate N/A Permanent Location Houston, TX Texas, US, United States Posted By Chevron Date Posted 33 minutes ago Expires 22 Jun 2018 Qualifications None ETC – Web Application Development… https://t.co/AJPIA4Wj7n https://t.co/1psJ9lY1Rx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Implementation Consultant Enterprise Data Management (Energy): Implementation Consultant Enterprise Data Management (Energy) An Implementation Consultant is responsible for providing a range of services to deliver the EDM product suite through… https://t.co/e0fuFHVSif https://t.co/Zk9gkyEVXC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Engineer (Manual, Houston): Project Description One of the world’s largest providers of products and services to the energy industry has a need to develop and support enterprise information system in Oil &amp; Gas domain. Project is related to collection,… https://t.co/NhX5h6l3BG https://t.co/7Lx9mAgPNy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Belgium's Bpost eyes cross-border deliveries boost with DHL partnership: (Reuters) - Belgian postal operator Bpost said on Wednesday it was teaming up with DHL for e-commerce deliveries in the Benelux region, in a move to boost its position in… https://t.co/QtPqQI53om https://t.co/wqqTxLh7Ar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Research Analyst: Principal Research Analyst Candidate will discover price and market information for the North American light olefins/polyolefins and/or aromatics and provide support in sales and marketing initiatives. They will also provide a… https://t.co/Foi0BqUkJQ https://t.co/gaw1lFTkL6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Contract Analyst – Technical Research Prinicipal: Contract Analyst – Technical Research Prinicipal About IHS Markit IHS Markit harnesses deep sources of information, analytics and expertise to forge solutions for the industries and markets that drive… https://t.co/mTV18zplj0 https://t.co/3L8sx6Nu3i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consultant: Consultant The consultant will be required to become proficient in IHS databases, both Enerdeq and Edin, familiar with IHS Connect, and other tools such as Questor, Harmony, Plays and Basins, etc. The consultant will work under a project… https://t.co/VJJtBuXpmW https://t.co/5JBgpiwSAW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Orion Software Integration Deputy Lead: Req ID : 429698BR Job Code/Title : E1075:Software Engineer Sr Stf Job Description : Orion Software Integration Deputy Lead responsible for helping to develop and track the overall software integration plan and… https://t.co/Apq4CjoBEK https://t.co/EvwjOVrABQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla hits parked California police vehicle; driver blames 'Autopilot': WASHINGTON (Reuters) - The driver of a Tesla Inc Model S crashed into an unoccupied, parked police vehicle in Laguna Beach, California, on Tuesday and the driver told investigators… https://t.co/wYHzTZcISA https://t.co/BvyLJQUOx1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[North America Refining Analyst: North America Refining Analyst Principal Research Analyst – Downstream Summary: The Principal Research Analyst functions as a core member of the team to produce quality analysis, reports, consulting deliverables, and… https://t.co/p40Hs7A7Di https://t.co/mmAvNo19dW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anywhere Expert Device Replacement Onboarding Acting Coach (Houston):   Job Description – Anywhere Expert Device Replacement Onboarding Acting Coach (Houston) (PSS29817) Job Description*  Anywhere Expert Device Replacement Onboarding Acting Coach… https://t.co/q0xjOq7ToS https://t.co/qjfZKhcDiD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Audit / Auditor: Job Description Hi Jose, We have been engaged by a client of ours in the Central Houston area. They are seeking an Internal Auditor for a Temporary to Hire role.The company is a top flight organization that boasts a great work… https://t.co/z0p6OYjpNM https://t.co/WEc4pVevef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Architect: Functional Area:IT – Information Technology Estimated Travel Percentage (%): Up to 25% Relocation Provided: No AIG Travel Assist, Inc. The Business Architect, as member of the CTO Team, works closely with business analysts to align… https://t.co/kSz0yXYLdz https://t.co/kfhBF7w8ML]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Administrator, Senior Yeshiva Univ: Network Administrator, Senior – Yeshiva Univ Department Global Services # of Openings per Req 1 Role Description Performs hands on LAN, WAN, Security, Phone system, Server, Storage, Computer Equipment and… https://t.co/XuPRFyPRLB https://t.co/doyxka7ush]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PHP developer: PHP developer Houston, Texas – United States Job Start Date – 05/24/18, Posted Date – 05/24/18 Primary SkillsPHPTax TermsC2COverview Interview Process- 2 skype Rate 55 Location- Houston, TX. Job Description An employer is looking for a… https://t.co/bGLt3rQVq2 https://t.co/uF30YCjqoc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chromascan Project Analyst – Paints Coatings, Full-time: Business unit: Marine &amp; Protective Coatings About AkzoNobel AkzoNobel is a leading global paints and coatings company and a major producer of specialty chemicals, with leading market positions and… https://t.co/XoUjFPE2wi https://t.co/44Rg0rdCy2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber in talks to resume services in Abu Dhabi: transport official: ABU DHABI (Reuters) - U.S. ride-hailing company Uber Technologies is in talks to resume services in Abu Dhabi after a nearly two-year suspension, a transport official said on Tuesday. https://t.co/mOerN3A9My https://t.co/zgPro1RnSi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instructional Designer: Instructional Designer at Endurance International Group (View all jobs) Houston, Texas The Instructional Designer will be responsible for ongoing development and revision of written learning curriculum to ensure engaging… https://t.co/yKty1gQ1Cs https://t.co/fRoSaoSKxa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consulting Associate Director: Consulting Associate Director Associate Director – IHS MARKIT Chemicals Consulting JOB SUMMARY: The Associate Director’s primary responsibility is to convert his or her experience, knowledge, insights and analysis along… https://t.co/JAhisHayCf https://t.co/JRQJ8tJ8TZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst: Shell – Job details ? HomeSearch openingsSearch resultsCurrent pageJob details Job details Tweet Job 1 of 1 to job Send to friend Save to cart Auto req ID76718BR Job TitleBusiness Analyst – Houston, TX Country of Work LocationUnited… https://t.co/EjfgHGRhn7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Consultant: Sr Consultant This position will function as a core member of the Upstream Consulting team which provides consulting services around the key IHS Markit competencies of capital and operating cost estimating, field development planning and… https://t.co/RBzWh0br8H https://t.co/HFGXjtK2dn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP HR ABAP: SAP HR ABAP Ref No.: 18-23293 Location: Houston, Texas At NTT DATA, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The quality, integrity, and commitment of our employees are key factors in our company’s growth, market… https://t.co/My4mO2DdcZ https://t.co/OBrCH7D2TG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Licensing Software Engineer- C++ and Java: For Siemens Licensing Software Engineer- C++ and Java job – Research &amp; Development – Multiple Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard – Toggle navigation – My Dashboard – Our Stories –… https://t.co/rkueMJIo5z https://t.co/dyLQFUgw7T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Network Manager: Position Title Senior Network Manager Auto Req ID 8567BR Relocation Assistance Yes Region/Pole Americas Functional Work Area Information Technology Job Purpose &amp; Responsibilities Essential Functions/Responsibilities: We are… https://t.co/of21e2Aewq https://t.co/7pHZ511a2N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer Ref No.: 18-23351 Location: New York City, New York Role: .Net Developer Location : Charlotte, NC, Houston, TX, New York City, NY, Chicago, IL Duration: Full Time Permanent Job Description Strong Experiance *******, C#,… https://t.co/LgTbb21sUw https://t.co/fiZoaNyx5f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Administrator III: Database Administrator III Database Administrator III ID 16416 Location US-TX-Houston Business Unit SESI Corporate, LLC More information about this job SESI Corporate, LLC, is the employer of the corporate staff of Superior… https://t.co/TNYJg1GAdr https://t.co/U8cH0tJLku]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: 37-year-old Restoration and Renovation Construction Service Company seeks an experienced Project Manager in Houston, TX and surrounding areas. This vital team member will be responsible for overseeing field operations for high-end… https://t.co/srypCpSnS4 https://t.co/EISvqO0xcw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Consulting Engineer- Cisco Contact Cener Enterprise: Senior Consulting Engineer- Cisco Contact Cener Enterprise in Houston, TX – CDW – Home – Teams – Life at CDW – Benefits – Transitioning Military – Join our Talent Network Join the CDW COMMUNITY… https://t.co/zqT7bqr1j1 https://t.co/I52iayXYqM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETC – Web Application Development and Data Analytics Analyst: ETC – Web Application Development and Data Analytics Analyst ============================================================ Date: May 23, 2018 Location: Houston, TX Texas, US Apply now Apply now… https://t.co/rrIauib9lO https://t.co/EWAaX8kRco]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital Oil Field Technical Lead: Digital Oil Field Technical Lead ================================ Date: May 23, 2018 Location: Houston, TX Texas, US Apply now Apply now * Start apply with LinkedIn Start apply with LinkedIn Help * * Start apply with… https://t.co/s7n83UkEyY https://t.co/5pMUf2zRvp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Trading Business Analyst: Salary/Rate N/A Permanent Location Houston, TX Texas, US, United States Posted By Chevron Date Posted 33 minutes ago Expires 22 Jun 2018 Qualifications None IT Trading Business Analyst in Houston, TX Texas, US, United States… https://t.co/Sug13oQtPb https://t.co/BogDtUk70U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Trading Business Analyst: IT Trading Business Analyst =========================== Date: May 23, 2018 Location: Houston, TX Texas, US Apply now Apply now * Start apply with LinkedIn Start apply with LinkedIn Help * * Start apply with Seek Start apply… https://t.co/JG9V78SkEC https://t.co/SFGSXhkQZg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Geological Geophysical Application Developer: Geological &amp; Geophysical Application Developer ============================================== Date: May 23, 2018 Location: Houston, TX Texas, US Apply now Apply now * Start apply with LinkedIn Start apply… https://t.co/Hedny81smU https://t.co/SMP22XAslK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Trading Business Analyst: Chevron is one of the world’s leading energy companies, with approximately 60,000 employees working in countries around the world. We explore, produce and transport crude oil and natural gas; refine, market and distribute… https://t.co/XqulvCr4IB https://t.co/GYVwQ0xcVV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Assurance (QA) Engineer: **************’s mission is to provide easy, accessible and affordable online health care services for everyone. Everything we do focuses on helping our patients become healthier and happier. We have easy-to-use online… https://t.co/svwA9KfY93 https://t.co/2c99rhXAWU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fullstack (Java,Angular) Developer (Houston): Project Description A well known institutional banking client is undergoing a front-office technology overhaul for their commodities and financial markets businesses. One component of this programme is a new… https://t.co/XNFbmhnDXh https://t.co/0frjEi0BLJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer – Front End: Java Developer – Front End Ref No.:18-02534 Location: Houston, Texas Position Type:Contract Job Description: – 10+ Years experience delivering front end technologies on Java based projects – Languages: TypeScript, JavaScript,… https://t.co/LtO38mUmJz https://t.co/ePNIfOqI0l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UX Architect | Houston Sr. Consultant: About the role As a client-facing UX designer, you will deliver primary and secondary research and client interviews to ensure that all projects are driven by user needs and business outcomes. Youll facilitate and… https://t.co/kMQQzNTRm6 https://t.co/2A8Lgo9Q7W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Qlik Sense Developer: Group 1 Automotive is seeking a Qlik Sense Developer at our corporate office in West Houston in the Memorial City area. Group 1 is a Fortune 500 company that owns and operates automotive dealerships and collision centers in the… https://t.co/Rz2N5lrpbP https://t.co/G3JiAdYkBH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Presales Solutions Architect: The Pre-Sales Solutions Architect is responsible for providing technical expertise and developing the technology solutions corresponding to pre-sales opportunities. This role will work in a highly collaborative environment… https://t.co/nXbHIlMYY4 https://t.co/EqtH1JDyOF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GCFIT – Executive IT Support Analyst: GCFIT – Executive IT Support Analyst ==================================== Date: May 21, 2018 Location: Houston, TX Texas, US Apply now Apply now * Start apply with LinkedIn Start apply with LinkedIn Help * * Start… https://t.co/WL1mcIGEgX https://t.co/zBM6PozxfE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – NetIQ Directory and Resource Administrator – Houston, TX: Software Engineer – NetIQ Directory and Resource Administrator – Houston, TX Tracking Code ******* Job Description Discover the new Micro Focus – now the world’s 7th largest… https://t.co/xLbjcjKj2a https://t.co/egkmrhtgbg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Xamarin developers: ******/Xamarin developers Ref No.: 18-18573 Location: Houston, Texas Lead Developer: Masters/bachelor’s degree in computer science/Computer Engineering or other related fields with a minimum of 8 years of experience in Mobile… https://t.co/HtTc9sDCCl https://t.co/wJRAnf2X9W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Administrator (Oracle DBA): Database Administrator (Oracle DBA) =================================== Req #: ******Location: Fort Sam Houston, TX USJob Category: Information TechnologySecurity Clearance: SecretClearance Status: Must be Obtainable… https://t.co/jQLW6ppDqA https://t.co/uHVs5XZQ4i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PHP Developer: We are looking for an experienced PHP Developer to assist in the design and implementation of new software systems and applications. Our ideal candidate for the PHP Developer position is one who can articulate the attributes of full life… https://t.co/juFtkvREKx https://t.co/LzLz8B2KcZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oregon family finds Amazon's Alexa has a mind of her own: (Reuters) - A Portland, Oregon, family has learned what happens when https://t.co/ljXqBSqXgj Inc's popular voice assistant Alexa is lost in translation. https://t.co/GwziIs5Wwh https://t.co/3L1Yb7rKlt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Healthcare IT: EHR Trainer – EPIC: Responsible for the development and evaluation of training materials for Epic applications, end-user training and oversight of training team. Onboard, develop and mentor Credentialed Trainers and Principal Trainers to… https://t.co/AGXa56HoC3 https://t.co/GgilJvaGWD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .NET Developer: Senior .NET Developer – Houston Texas 77024 Skip Navigation Toggle navigation Menu – Search – My Account – Saved Jobs (0) – Sign In Job Details Back to Search Results Senior .NET Developer – Job ID #: 342 – Functional Area: IT –… https://t.co/51jmG9sv2R https://t.co/LSzi3wZGXr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL SERVER: SQL SERVER Ref No.: 18-18387 Location: houston, Texas experience using secure code storage TFS. Strong communication skills (written and verbal). Strong customer service skills. Strong commitment to fostering and promoting teamwork. Ability… https://t.co/R3UVOjE3vc https://t.co/xCUSJImdpd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Headworks International Headworks International is changing the world through water! Every day, Headworks International devotes its considerable resources to meet the worlds demand for our most precious resource: clean water. We have… https://t.co/k8udDaCnH7 https://t.co/rxjuHX4d4F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FracCommand Applications Specialist: PRIMARY FUNCTION: This position contributes to the companys success by acting as the technical specialist supporting * the rollout of new products(involved in all aspects of the whole process from feature requests and… https://t.co/UoS7iyRoue https://t.co/mUmwYw38Tc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Analyst: We are seeking a Data Feeds Business Analyst to join our expanding Commercial Technology teams in Houston, TX. This is a client-facing Business Analyst role responsible for working with customers and partners to define… https://t.co/J0ux5m2NZ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Network Administrator: * Senior Network Administrator Job Locations US-TX-Houston Job ID 2018-1719 Category Information Technology Overview About Pharm-Olam International: Pharm-Olam International is a mid-size Contract Research Organization (CRO)… https://t.co/vHNa7qwyzT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PowerBuilder Developer: Careers Center | PowerBuilder Developer Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome page… https://t.co/99DbCsHjC4 https://t.co/6c8H1DcEuM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Project Logistics (Wind Energy Vertical): Job Description What’s the opportunity? Project Manager – Project Logistics (Wind Energy Vertical; located off of highway 249) is responsible for the overall management and coordination of… https://t.co/wCtrLCBaXt https://t.co/uFaSF3z1ZR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer V: Software Engineer V Ref No.: 18-01209 Location: HOUSTON, Texas Position Type: Contract Start Date / End Date: 06/11/2018 to 12/21/2018 Job ID: UALJP******** Title: *Software Engineer V Duration: 6/11/2018 – 12/21/2018 – 6 month… https://t.co/xI7hnl7MuB https://t.co/pCkirhq9NV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Windows Device Driver Developer: Windows Device Driver Developer Houston, Texas – United States Job Start Date – 05/14/18, Posted Date – 05/14/18 Primary Skillsc++,CTax TermsW-2OverviewJob title: Windows Device Driver Developer Location: Houston, TX… https://t.co/8gdoi5Khhw https://t.co/olEST85OrY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consulting Associate Director: Consulting Associate Director Associate Director – IHS MARKIT Chemicals Consulting JOB SUMMARY: The Associate Director’s primary responsibility is to convert his or her experience, knowledge, insights and analysis along… https://t.co/V47xcqEGTr https://t.co/QddyzIYP9q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon wants to foster small independent delivery fleets: SEATTLE (Reuters) - https://t.co/ljXqBSqXgj Inc on Wednesday said it would offer incentives to entice entrepreneurs to set up their own small package-delivery businesses as part of Amazon's latest… https://t.co/lwhfMPjqLo https://t.co/XcmsQ6ri3u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Developer: I am working with a fantastic client located in the Houston area that is looking for an Application Developer. The client offers an excellent compensation and great benefits package. RESPONSIBILITIES: * Serve as a Project Manager… https://t.co/1jaPQN733Q https://t.co/nMosN2O0e4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All Source Intelligence Analyst: Req ID 98835BR Business Title All Source Intelligence Analyst Group MCIS Location USA TEXAS Ft. Sam Houston Clearance Level Needed None Category Intelligence Job Duties and Responsibilities Become an integral part of a… https://t.co/3Sr28uWaMe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Scheduled Maintenance The SAP SuccessFactors HCM Suite is currently undergoing scheduled maintenance. We apologise for any inconvenience this may cause. Please visit the Support Portal or contact Customer Support if you need further… https://t.co/C1tOzRuztY https://t.co/99flhPGqVu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Environmental Project Manager: Job Description Senior Environmental Project Manager Senior Environmental Project Manager (******) About UsAt HDR, we specialize in engineering, architecture, environmental and construction services. While we are… https://t.co/Z9vy9EmLEh https://t.co/ZH9CxST8Os]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ERP Accounting Analyst: CANDIDATE REQUIREMENTS MUST-HAVES * Degree in Accounting * Heavy IFS implementation and support experience * Project Management experience * Costing Implementation experience NICE-TO-HAVES * SAP experience a plus ROLE DESCRIPTION… https://t.co/hs5KPvbGzc https://t.co/qxXeiZGzee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Network Security Consultant: Sr. Network &amp; Security Consultant Business Group Control Products and Solutions No. of Positions 1 Requisition Number 77490BR Job Category Engineering and Technicians Position Type Full Time Relocation Eligible No… https://t.co/bTpsrmK896 https://t.co/ec45p0G0Yk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager Energy Services: Project Manager – Energy Services Job at Layne Christensen in Houston, TX Share Position:Project Manager – Energy Services Company:Layne Christensen Job Location(s):Houston, TX Start Date:As soon as possible Employment… https://t.co/RPsUtH7bHp https://t.co/Gu3DfHwxoj]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>