<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about the Bay Area city of Danville, California http://t.co/tBI9DeA0ba]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I die, I'm leaving my body to science fiction. - Steven Wright]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame: Capture the Flag  http://t.co/0XkQ4m3hnt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do you judge me as a musician, John? All I'm interested in is making money. Glenn Miller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Let's Play: LOTR Ep 1: Meeting the Hobbits  http://t.co/vh5GwJk1xs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wait a minute, Doc. Ah --  Are you telling me you built a time machine --  out of a DeLorean? - Marty McFly, Back to the Future]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Budweiser  http://t.co/a1bxG8yR7T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My little friend that I only I can see is wanting me to warn you that he thinks you have serious mental problems He He He!!  :&gt;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cinderella is living proof that a pair of shoes can change your life…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Locate Your Garage Space Before Installation Of Cabinets  http://t.co/T8BuOgwanq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Triple Crown Sports Organization  http://t.co/u4rck2RbrF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Few people SUFFER from egotism. With most of them it's a PLEASURE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The less a man knows --  the more he tells it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Heart  http://t.co/l1wYaTMtHh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Using Tumblr for Business  http://t.co/vEcJZ8hxYv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read The History of the Baseball (the actual ball)  http://t.co/T6qMyHoqAZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today fitness equipment is something we take for granted - ever wondered about its history?  Read more --&gt; http://t.co/JpLVrdlX5t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever wonder about the history of the coffin?  http://t.co/MCAwucp082]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pair off in threes. - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Mountain Climbing from Novice to Experts  http://t.co/TRqxTsebSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make Money by Tweeting, Blogging and Photo Sharing with Izea  http://t.co/IEGoAYu41v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leave it to Beaver is an American sitcom classic - read all about its history -  http://t.co/s7lj8t6Lu4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool A Clear Bottomed 2 - Person Kayak - A Unique Way to Enjoy Paddling! http://t.co/H4DnfrJHTm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Ohio Players    http://t.co/8o2YR3mshT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I was president of the good old U.S.A., I'd turn the churches into strip clubs and watch the whole world pray.  Kid Rock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suitor: A guy who thinks he's throwing a girl a line when all the time he's being roped in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Ben E. King - his story and music  http://t.co/wPcKRmQ1Pl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To me, true rock 'n' roll has a lot of bottom in it.  - Little Richard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He ran out of talent about halfway through the corner. - Buddy Baker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Few people SUFFER from egotism. With most of them it's a PLEASURE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Hamstring Rehab  http://t.co/exl8LGgWys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of American Hamburgers  http://t.co/NsGxnoBShP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No change in musical style will survive unless it is accompanied by a change in clothing style. Rock is to dress up to.  - Frank Zappa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of James Gang  http://t.co/ES70kTWCdN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can accept failure, but I can't accept not trying. - Michael Jordan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Parliament  http://t.co/ocpWGkZDjx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Redrum. -  Danny, The Shining]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most beautiful thing in the world is a ballpark filled with people. - Bill Veeck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Mod Showcase: Secret Rooms Mod  http://t.co/MoF7E0qYLK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One person with courage makes a majority. - Andrew Jackson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Girls are like internet domain names, the ones I like are already taken.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of the Inheritance Series Third Volume – Brisingr  http://t.co/kabZb3duSc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buzz: Be sure not to lock it on my way out. On surface, Neil: Isn't that something? Magnificent sight out here. Buzz: Magnificent desolation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of that Odd Olympic Sport – Curling  http://t.co/WXt4DGj3jI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Habit is second nature, or rather, ten times nature. - William James]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sam Cooke was the king of soul - read his history - http://t.co/5tbL7BEtOf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Media are tools.  Real time is mindset.  David Scott - Marketing Strategist - Author of The New Rules of Marketing and PR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To the uneducated, an A is just three sticks. - A. A. Milne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Creedance Clearwater Revival  http://t.co/MdhsaUosh5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've met many thinkers and many cats, but the wisdom of cats is infinitely superior. - Hippolyte Taine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool 14' Iceberg For Your Pool or the Lake! http://t.co/77pufxBsKS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then close your eyes and tap your heels together three times. And think to yourself, "There's no place like home" - The Wizard of Oz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Petula Clark  http://t.co/uyOo843cX9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we can't live together, then we're going to die alone. - Jack Shephard, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of the first book in the Left Behind Series by Tim LaHaye and Jerry Jenkins  http://t.co/wGRNhcoLVk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need to tie some kerosene rags around his ankles so the ants don't eat his candy #$@ - Dale Earnhardt speaking of Mark Martin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Finance Trade Secrets  http://t.co/5HqrZNzodV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One Family’s Adoption Stories  http://t.co/5QAZeaRZSq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome gardening t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the gardening lovers in your life!   http://t.co/0eRwER2Mkj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Fashionable Jackets for Fall &amp; Winter  http://t.co/lUYNGTVYQy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the The Recent History of Beer  http://t.co/IDe7O3ekN8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret of success is constancy to purpose. - Benjamin Disraeli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How to Select the Right Technology for Seniors  http://t.co/kEtQ43h1l6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It will work. I am a marketing genius. - Paris Hilton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You could get rich manufacturing crutches for lame excuses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who dares to teach must never cease to learn. - John Cotton Dana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An expert is a man who has made all the mistakes which can be made, in a narrow field. - Niels Bohr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know money is the root of all evil if you would like to find out more - just send me $10 - DM me ASAP !!  :&gt;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Elvis Presley    http://t.co/MTi39U60nX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who can believe that there is no soul behind those luminous doggie eyes! - Theophile Gautier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ways to Earn a Living with a Creative Writing Degree  http://t.co/Mpqg7gesHA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must either modify your dreams or magnify your skills. - Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By the time a person gets to greener pastures, he can't climb the fence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome climbing t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the climbing lovers in your life!  http://t.co/A2bK7KMvvl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making the Most of Twitter for Your Business  http://t.co/HAYKpdemdJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Natalie Cole  http://t.co/MZBt7Iszmn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never go to a movie in Poland, you'll end up setting behind a Pole.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Increase Space in Your Garage with Suitable Garage Floors  http://t.co/5M2y7ZKsIa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ultimately, the only power to which man should aspire is that which he exercises over himself. - Elie Wiesel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you are thin, don't eat fast. If you are fat, don't eat fast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This episode was BADLY written! - Gwen, Galaxy Quest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love This Nerds Candy Juniors Tunic Tank Dress with Nerd Glasses - Dig It! http://t.co/VJ0L4vCoOv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A shoe without sex appeal is as barren as a tree without leaves. - Rita De Acosta Lydig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Advanced Weight Scales and Body Monitoring – Keeping Track of your Body Weight  http://t.co/PLT65heGzw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would you say I have a plethora of pinatas? - El Guapo, ¡Three Amigos!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of KC and the Sunshine Band  http://t.co/ir8B007zqI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dis Be Da Place]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then close your eyes and tap your heels together three times. And think to yourself, "There's no place like home" - The Wizard of Oz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conversation:  when three women are talking together.  Gossip:  When one of them leaves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instead of giving myself reasons why I can't, I give myself reasons why I can. - Unknown Author]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just got my Google Chromecast HDMI Streaming Media Player - SO COOL - http://t.co/ot7UlMh2yK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Heineken Phone Case --&gt; http://t.co/68ElCwhiFo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After the third flip, I lost control - Don Roberts after crashing in the Jade Grenade at New England Dragway in 1975.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't see pitches down the middle anymore - not even in batting practice. -  Hank Aaron]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am convinced that every boy, in his heart, would rather steal second base than an automobile. - Thomas Campbell Clark]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great History of the Rolling Stones  http://t.co/u5BZYW9ra4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I was president of the good old U.S.A., I'd turn the churches into strip clubs and watch the whole world pray.  Kid Rock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How tall am I? Honey, with hair, heels and attitude I'm through this damned roof! - Rupaul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, I think we're the greatest rock 'n' roll band in the world.  - Joey Ramone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It ain't over 'til it's over - Yogi Berra]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>