<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Still I wonder if the pendulum is the right model for public versus private markets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bank earnings. Bank of America announced earnings this morning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They trade in smaller lots, take smaller positions, and trade out of them within seconds rather than holding them overnight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What kind of symbols of frugality are they?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This opinion is intuitively appealing but wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With the slow death of bond market liquidity worries I'm auditioning other recurring features for this space.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know, that's just a good headline. Follow me on Twitter!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["They’re not able to make a lot of money from exploiting slow investors following macroeconomic news," says one of the authors.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But its laser focus on pleasing the people who don't like or understand Twitter is not a great sign.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matt_levine I mean, BofA's memo doesn't seem to mention money.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the answer is meh, kind of, sometimes, in a rough sense.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All it requires is over-the-top rhetoric and lots of publicity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But the real benefit of the "hedge fund" title is in framing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sears Holdings' rights offering has expired.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[that this argument doesn't run in reverse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[M&amp;A types are not happy about this; one says "The measures were clearly thought up by people living in the last century."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also, what can you conclude about the risk appetites of (1) overpaid overworked bankers versus (2) moderately paid lazy bankers?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Values and governance. What is the purpose of a company?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things happen
. The story of A123 Systems.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An intriguing fact of our political culture is that the idea of "authenticity" is entirely separated from the idea of "truth."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was thinking we could do something like that. That's probably the easiest thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Staples and Office Depot had tried merging only to be blocked by regulators in a 1997 lawsuit," but, man, remember 1997?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the other hand, trading banks struggle to consistently outperform the other two business types.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The statute of limitations for bringing securities fraud cases is five years. Do you see the problem?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't "give false testimony in a long-running lawsuit over the collapse of a bank client's media empire."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lehman Brothers was solvent, FYI. Well, the U.K. bit of it -- Lehman Brothers International (Europe) -- was.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But the whole thing is very much worth reading, a defense of nuance against snap black-and-white moral judgments.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So score a (possibly unrepresentative) point for the good effects of "bad" governance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My typing those words -- which are not strictly true! -- was probably wire fraud.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JPMorgan's earnings beat estimates on improved trading revenue. Wells Fargo's earnings were down a bit quarter-on-quarter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obviously this is not legal advice, but it seems like there would be easier ways.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LJKawa On the other hand, "Junk-Bond ETFs Show Just How Desperate Traders Are for Liquidity."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Insider traders or not, they are certainly impressive traders.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still, receiving a pile of illiquid unicorn stock is not the worst problem to have.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The taxes he avoids could be used to pay for public schools, "this unconscionable tax avoidance scheme must end," etc. One nice (?)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A late night, a flip of her golden hair, a coy glance, and they’d yield, flip-flops and all, to her cool embrace.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This opinion is intuitively appealing but wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the other hand, from Wells Fargo's perspective, if they're not selling unnecessary expensive products all day, what are they doing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So he turned it down, right? No, of course not, it's Apple.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its lease contained certain covenants; in particular, ALC had to maintain a minimum occupancy rate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But Wells Fargo's plan is different! Wells read a book!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It does seem somewhat unusual for prosecutorial fishing expeditions to play out quite so publicly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matt_levine Also inventing iPhones and stuff, don't get me wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matt_levine ("I personally lost $100,000 in one second.")]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programming note: There will be no Money Stuff for the next two weeks, since I'll be on vacation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Allison Nathan: What about asset managers? Given their growth, are they in a better position to step in?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First, Posner and Weyl come to the question from a quasi-Pikettian standpoint.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On its own, it's perhaps fair to call IEX simpler.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Though the index funds aren't complaining.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There really is a part of me that wants to like this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And then the fund has a problem when you go to it and ask for your $1,000 back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(This is the basic deal of a bank account, too.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guess it should just buy back some stock then.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MylesUdland Based on data as of Dec. 31, 2014, 86.44% of large-cap fund managers underperformed the benchmark over a one-year period.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It makes the entire finance industry more fragile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A. Bank's board, which is a nice example of the genre and pretty compelling: I mean, yes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's slightly more than the usual 80 percent! Be careful out there!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there a tech bubble? If there is, I'd be the last person to tell you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's like a subsection of a subsection of a subsection.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You decide whether the above logic applies to the London gold fix, which "may have been manipulated for a decade by the banks setting it."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This column does not necessarily reflect the opinion of Bloomberg View's editorial board or Bloomberg LP, its owners and investors.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not illegal to have more information than the market.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The index funds have the advantage of free-riding, but the disadvantage of being predictable. Stocks should go up when they join an index.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One popular puzzle in financial markets is whether the rise of passive index funds makes active management easier or harder.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These plans should be vetted with senior management and control functions and be reviewed on a regular basis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So he's the guy who actually sent California the excessive prices.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then they bill the limited partners for the management fee net of the rebates.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One takeaway here is that if you ever find a time machine and travel back to 14th-century Europe (why?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But, whatever, he ran a big important hedge fund, it's worth making sure he plays by the rules.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We’re herd animals, and when someone yells “Crack is bad” the whole country jumps on sending people to prison for decades for drug crimes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyway one consultant says "We're back to pre-pre-recession levels," which is just a terrific line.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strange. Camp's bill apparently also would subject publicly traded private equity partnerships to corporate tax.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But it's not particularly easy or pleasant for humans to be human either.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But why is it so important for Twitter that it attract that Macquarie analyst's mother? Why can't she be happy with Facebook?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Investors are fleeing from a business they see as confidence-based, and therefore prone to unravel at speed."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His staff carry themselves with a sense of mission, and Trump makes them all feel important.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Investor relations is a weird business and I would not want to be in it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(The theory was that the brokers, etc., voluntarily consented to the administrative proceedings by registering with the SEC.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oil. Things are bad, if you're in the oil business.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QuickTake Money-Market Funds

 So the prospect of losing money is scary.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There will always be salespeople, whether they're selling stocks or stock derivatives or stock-derivative-trading algorithms.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, you know, good incentives. Presumably Valeant's bankers were not also paid as a percentage of transaction price.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is not strictly "on Wall Street" but you probably drink coffee, and anyway, it's my linkwrap so I'm linking to it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So if Aleynikov was an officer of Goldman, Sachs &amp; Co., then he should be indemnified.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But the thinking here seems to be: I see the logic, but I don't buy it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have no problem with any of this; acid reflux is one of the major problems facing the financial industry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I mean, ISS says "it appears to be on track to repurchase at least $32 billion in shares" and, sure, that is a number.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It specifically wasn't "everyone who cancels a lot of orders is a criminal," though I suppose we could get there one day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I'm giving you a lot more money than you're giving me now, then you will probably end up giving me a lot more money later.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matt_levine Senior Yen Trader: Do you know what I mean? I was thinking we could do something like that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A worm might eat your snails 
before you can
. Would you like to see pictures of a New Guinea flatworm eating a snail?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[-- are a bank's main expenses, it would be sort of weird to pay them a fixed percentage of profits, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone could sue Trump in a court in Argentina.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And what else would you talk about at a birthday dinner but the examination ratings of a mid-size New York bank?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But on the other hand they'll be happy if you give it back, especially at an even higher yield.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was scamming them. It set up the loans to make sure that they'd default, and then immediately dumped the shares to lock in its profit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And then several former Goldman bankers spoke to Twitter about how much they hated getting their hair cut at Salvatore's.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The question is who will pay for that activity, if passive investors can just free-ride off of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Morgan Stanley really five times more popular than Goldman Sachs?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tilton is not the first to object to SEC administrative proceedings, which have been expanded recently.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>