<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[One third of teens &amp; young adults have successfully connected with health peers online, and 91% of them say the experience was helpful. https://t.co/O7nNHAl1Sh #PeerHealthAdvice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Half of app-using teens and young adults say they have used apps on 1-3 different health topics. 14% have tried apps on four or more health topics - @Hopelab + @WellBeingTrust]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[64% of teens and young adults in the U.S. say they have used mobile apps related to health, including for fitness, sleep, meditation, and medication reminders https://t.co/Sz9UHxWXHZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm going to share highlights of the new report here &amp; on my blog, plus @vjrideout and I are ready to take your questions. There's a lot to discuss! https://t.co/Sz9UHxWXHZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are headlines in the @Hopelab + @WellBeingTrust report for all kinds of stakeholders: educators, policymakers, parents, entrepreneurs, investors... plus teens &amp; young adults themselves...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NEW SURVEY DATA: 

Digital health use among teens &amp; young adults in the U.S. by @vjrideout + @SusannahFox (me!), with @Hopelab + @WellBeingTrust 

https://t.co/Sz9UHxWXHZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DurgasToolbox And as a European, you're awake, so here you go! https://t.co/Sz9UHxWXHZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @vjrideout: 4) But some young people say they continue using social media when they are feeling down, even though they realize it makes…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chatbot is like a tenacious Mom who holds people accountable for what they need to do because she wants you to be successful. 

(As a Mom, I endorse this.) https://t.co/AqLtn42laa https://t.co/BvpZWsPSJH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SAWohlfeil: A homeless shelter in Coeur d'Alene is using an AI assistant named SARA to help keep track of clients, and it's working: th…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SAWohlfeil Fan letter: I loved this article! You did a beautiful job telling the story and getting all the details in. Hat tip to @writeo for giving me a copy. Kudos!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaronc @CHP_San_Diego @Honda Glad you’re ok!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laurenecrawford My gasp startled the dog]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protesting family separation every Friday, 4-6pm https://t.co/roWRAfAsXf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @emmaplatoff: New numbers tonight: More than 400 kids still separated from their parents. Reunification deadline was July 26. https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NewsHour: "I am privileged to represent 130 million people with pre-existing conditions today, and I am grateful for the invitation to…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DrSherryPagoto: R U interested in how behavioral science can be leveraged to improve health? The Society of Behavioral Medicine confere…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MightyCasey Ha! Can't wait for my calendar to untangle so I can schedule it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sgschade Thanks! The stars of my show are our community colleagues, the people who share their insights &amp; ideas in the comments. See: https://t.co/CjmaRfyUgj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheMightySite: "I'm literally just trying to protect my life." Thanks @AugustMaturo
for your advocacy. https://t.co/hmGfLFd0j8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ESchattner Wishing you a sweet new year!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drdonsdizon Thank you for sharing this remembrance. I added @AnyaSilverPoet to the Artists of Health Care list: https://t.co/iNOAJIM1co]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @caregiving: Last day to enter! We'd love to showcase your creative side in our Eighth Annual Caregiving Art Show. It's a family affair-…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @drdonsdizon: A new blog for @OncJournal
Met an incredible person filming for @gotoPER
One important lesson for me: patient centered car…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ReginaHolliday: I just finished the painting for the Kansas Hospital Association “Bee the Change.” https://t.co/C42Ceabtcz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MargaretWhittum: #Neuropathy, or #NervePain, is a common occurrence after #Stroke - it's a burning, freezing, numbness, tightness, etc.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @myers3411: “People affected by health conditions bring insights and wisdom to transform healthcare – ‘jewels from the caves of sufferin…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JWeddingPE: Holy. Smokes. 

Can you imagine what would happen if healthcare tech took this approach, and actually helped innovators mak…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ProfAmyE @BlackbirdBH1 Wonderful! I'd love to hear how it's going - and if I can help, let me know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LillyTrials And even more wonderful artists are highlighted in the comments! Thanks for sharing and let's keep building our lists of artists: https://t.co/ycXDChTmAb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to @Init4Health @nickdawson @bacigalupe @Markagilbert and others for making the jump from Twitter to share links &amp; insights in the comments: https://t.co/ycXDChTmAb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @atlasofcare: For actor and producer @ronsimons, caring for his ailing mother become the production of a lifetime. What happens when the…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Health care folks: When have you bent the rules and tried something new, the way an artist or a hacker does? Please share your story in the comments: https://t.co/iNOAJIM1co]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks - everyone! - for all the links to artists who work at the intersection of health and care. I can't keep up with them all &amp; would love it if you posted comments here: https://t.co/iNOAJIM1co]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DrewQJoseph: At 34, he was diagnosed with #glioblastoma. He and his family have been trying to figure out how to live while facing an i…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@writeo Love it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@malscontent “In such an ugly time the true protest is beauty.” - Phil Ochs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EMRAnswers Thanks for sharing it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Amanda_Lenhart: For complimentary data about teens - see my report with my @APNORC colleagues that examined taking breaks from social m…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MonicaRAnders: As Facebook's Sheryl Sandberg addresses the Sental Intel Committee, new @pewresearch data shows that only 14% of Faceboo…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mr_indisingh Wish I were there!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @malscontent: Art inspires. Art disrupts. Art solves. Art heals.  TY @SusannahFox for boosting the signal w/ a great post &amp; sharing an i…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nickdawson If you have time to add all these fabulous names/links as a comment on my post, I'd love it (tweets disappear so quickly) https://t.co/iNOAJIM1co]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ProfAmyE @ReginaHolliday 100% - she is one of the artists featured in my post: https://t.co/iNOAJIM1co]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nickdawson Amazing! Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TherapyComics Thank you! Will approve later tonight - so great to learn about your work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sound alchemist Yoko Sen asks, "What is the last sound you want to hear?" #Medx https://t.co/WVV4HozHWN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today I'm sharing artists who work at the intersection of health + care -- please add if you know of others!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MargaretWhittum: Thrilled to release the first 2 minute teaser video for #TheGreatNowWhat, a feature-length #documentary #film on #stro…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ibddoctor @StanfordMedX @joyclee Joyce is indeed inspiring!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Markagilbert: This short film documenting my work with patients and caregivers was just rebroadcast in NE. Amazing Memories. The Medici…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CBlotner_: 6 years ago today, I had awake brain surgery. Eating ice cream was a critical component of rehabilitating some of my jaw mus…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wilbanks @StanfordMedX I do love it! A habit of creation. Beautiful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Init4Health and approved! You are amazing. Thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Medx Resident Artist, @carbajalphoto on the importance of vulnerability and how it allows him to be a "more abled" photographer https://t.co/eHwQzwcpo3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No #Medx this year, as @StanfordMedX is on hiatus, so I'm renewing my spirit by looking back: https://t.co/iNOAJIM1co]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rzeiger: I love this permission to not only learn from artists but to see that in some way each of us creates and thus has permission t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Init4Health Thank you! Tweets disappear so fast and I'd love to hear more about what you think - please post a comment on my blog if you have time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New post: Artists bend tools until they break and ask, “Why CAN’T I do that?” We need that spirit in health care https://t.co/iNOAJIM1co]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @VentureValkyrie: New VentureValkyrie blog post: What's Next?! A Plan in Progress - on my personal career expedition.   https://t.co/mYg…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["On account of the intense darkness in the mine, the hieroglyphics on the door were not visible until plate was developed." https://t.co/bsF43pcJ3f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Vance, a Trapper Boy, 15 years old. Has trapped for several years in a West Va. Coal mine. $.75 a day for 10 hours work. All he does is to open and shut this door: most of the time he sits here idle, waiting for the cars to come." https://t.co/y9m07LYKGk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Treasure trove: @librarycongress archive of the National Child Labor Committee Collection https://t.co/BMGprOCyLh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reading: The searing photos that helped end child labor in America https://t.co/4sRHpieNYL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ESchattner Agree. Even tho we are just thinking out loud, I couldn't bring myself to tweet a hypothetical protocol using sensitive data that wasn't opt in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CDW_Healthcare Thanks! I'm honored to be in this group - esp since some of my most popular posts are years old and the comments are more useful than what I wrote. See: https://t.co/snTdTnjFBW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ESchattner Thinking out loud, I'd want to find a way to do a large, longitudinal, opt-in study that tracks people's news consumption and medical records (and probably other sources of data).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever cautious, I checked Dr. Alame out, just in case it was clever spam. Nope! He's a real urologist in Paris. Bonus: search led me to this gem of a header pic: https://t.co/yqz13j1hEx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10+ years of blogging and I'm still amazed at connections we make. Today's example: a new comment on a post I wrote in 2010 (!) https://t.co/NHRWy6Lak3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next up: @MightyCasey interviews @wendellpotter about "how money-driven thinking messes up healthcare, science, and our political system" https://t.co/C3mK7QPWDg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunday afternoons, for me, are for cooking and podcasts. Today: pumpkin muffins and @Doctor_V interviews @vmontori about #WhyWeRevolt against industrial medicine https://t.co/JENwWK2cGU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is amazing - I am a longtime fan of @burklowj and this seals it https://t.co/IsiEHdWGTS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ekeeleymoore I don’t think your region is included yet but I have hope for services like @voro_doctors - peer to peer clinician recommendations https://t.co/Bo940xrrcd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OCHWW: Report: Nearly 66% of teens &amp; young adults say they have used #mHealth apps. Continue reading to find more insights on the inter…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m back at HHS to meet with @HHSCTO and love the #iamhhs videos playing in the lobby! https://t.co/mBCwxQGPi5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @asbernstein2185: We all face skepticism about our ideas, but we don't all know how to turn that into a win. Until now @cathyhuyghe http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HHSIDEALab: .@MonaSiddiquiMD will be speaking at the upcoming @health2con, but you can get a preview for her upcoming talk in this arti…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Cambia: “There’s always room for one more.”-  Cambia’s Janet Campbell, featured on PDX Executive Podcast, on why #diversity and #inclus…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VinceKuraitis Thanks, Vince!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JessBeeGood: Wow. @Walmart sells 50% of all the bicycles purchased in the U.S. &amp; 1/5 of all the food sold in America. They have a huge…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm following #HealthFurther18 from afar - thanks to all who are sharing quotes &amp; pics. Agenda: https://t.co/ER9Es2sviG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm binging on the @Politico Pulse Check podcast with @ddiamond on my flights these days. Best so far: https://t.co/lUBYaXqwYu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LyndaGMitchell: Absolutely. Thank you for sharing! I hope he is okay today. Your experience and sharing it will give others the confide…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MargaretWhittum I love your work - thanks for creating and sharing it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@MargaretWhittum makes art to communicate her pain - follow #TheGreatNowWhat https://t.co/pbQyXZBW8b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With the support of other trauma survivors and the healing power of art, @MargaretWhittum learns to reclaim a powerful and unexpected identity. Watch:  https://t.co/2cHdR0GKIT #TheGreatNowWhat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @docmikeevans: One way I explain P2P: if your kid was diagnosed with diabetes, the first and most powerful thing I would do is connect y…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OtsukaUS You make it easy to want to share your tweets - they are both thoughtful &amp; beautifully illustrated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AC_FL_NonExp This is what I adore about Twitter (and social platforms in general) - you have curated a super specific, super geeky, super HELPFUL resource and shared it. Thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Incredible thread! https://t.co/eI7F6rFuJ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheLizArmy I wrote up my thoughts on Blue Button -- and found out that the VA version DOES give people access to clinical notes: https://t.co/S75ePq16Qi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Must read by @Lygeia - A Cross-Party Win: Empowering Consumers Through Digital Health https://t.co/Y07EG6jjxy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to everyone sharing my Blue Button post! Now updated with new info about how the VA's Blue Button DOES give access to clinical notes https://t.co/S75ePq16Qi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#PeerHealthAdvice is happening with or without "official" health care's help. But I say: let's help! https://t.co/Pk2Qel7Qij]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AMEN! #PeerHealthAdvice https://t.co/HjvDcOMdRs https://t.co/peYhTbkAR2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ANOTHER randomized, controlled trial found: Peer health coaching significantly improved diabetes control among low-income primary care patients https://t.co/N2ac076GXZ #PeerHealthAdvice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A randomized, controlled trial found: Peer mentorship improved glucose control in a cohort of African American Veterans with diabetes. https://t.co/Lgok8nkrz8 #PeerHealthAdvice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Let’s make better health contagious, together!” Heck yes, @ashwinpatel https://t.co/HjvDcOMdRs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MeredithGould +1! My recent picks: AN AMERICAN MARRIAGE by @Tayari + THE HIDDEN LIFE OF TREES by @PeterWohlleben + Mary Oliver on the night table]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChiefDigitalStr @VentureValkyrie @margaretlaws Thank you!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>