<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Time-lapse video of a rocket launch seen from space https://t.co/o6KD2GjqL2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lisp Machine Inc. K-machine (2001) https://t.co/Qnt6j2LI15]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing time-lapse video of a rocket launch… seen from space https://t.co/o6KD2GjqL2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flutter: the good, the bad and the ugly https://t.co/Uxrr95Zk0N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Zora, the Robot Caregiver https://t.co/6u1dAFrijG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meet Zora, the Robot Caregiver https://t.co/6u1dAFrijG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new Yahoo? Facebook should heed the lessons of internet history https://t.co/JFFoXD520k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Using carbon nanotubes and rectennas to yield a 90% efficient solar cell https://t.co/f3R6xX9RrT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every 7.8μs your computer’s memory has a hiccup https://t.co/RnCafQTrRA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some notes about HTTP/3 https://t.co/VXddcdyR8E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's Going on in Your Child's Brain When You Read Them a Story? https://t.co/fC0HwsGYFB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An elevator in a Chicago skyscraper fell 84 floors, requiring a dramatic rescue https://t.co/ny8o3pnCjz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How a Mysterious Tech Billionaire Created Two Fortunes – And a Global Sweatshop https://t.co/53GpsRwVWZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mac mini review–a testament to Apple’s stubbornness https://t.co/AjlYLeNUMl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a Real Train System Looks Like (2009) https://t.co/PqDz6pIZWX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China blacklists millions from booking flights as 'social credit' introduced https://t.co/jAVjz4Yldk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Story Behind the IKEA Photo of Amsterdam https://t.co/r5DOFRXNQ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boss as a Service – Hire a boss, get stuff done https://t.co/mZdttxYFpt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You Snooze, You Lose: Insurers Make the Old Adage Literally True https://t.co/BVvtITCODN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clothing Manufacturing May Be Moving Back to West from Asia https://t.co/ffFx3Ag8HD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new Yahoo? Facebook should heed the lessons of internet history https://t.co/JFFoXD520k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn Service Workers inside and Out with a New PWA Mastery Game https://t.co/a3ZAUx63FU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US asks allies to drop Huawei https://t.co/pq22k1PNyp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Washington Asks Allies to Drop Huawei https://t.co/yl52bHnR1Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World first as wind turbine upgraded with high temperature superconductor https://t.co/c5B6l3WUu8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$200 retail whole genome sequencing now available https://t.co/K4cFMa9nOH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ditching the MacBook Pro for a MacBook Air https://t.co/JBlqEijjXH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analyzing My Google Location History https://t.co/r2uIdDmUyq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gitless: A simple version control system built on top of Git https://t.co/9brH1LZPWF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook policy chief admits hiring PR firm to attack George Soros https://t.co/spKyDDMQ1f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World first as wind turbine upgraded with high temperature superconductor https://t.co/c5B6l4evSI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A simple version control system built on top of Git https://t.co/9brH1LZPWF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Killed by Google https://t.co/9oloTtlqH2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4,000-year-old termite mounds found in Brazil are visible from space https://t.co/xrHljnSacr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you to dang and sctb https://t.co/edfjBwlEwn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Open Protocol for Resumable File Uploads https://t.co/7JBYOEVI9Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boss as a Service – Hire a boss, get stuff done https://t.co/mZdttxYFpt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Archiving web sites https://t.co/SRBrpog1xz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Mystery Font That Took Over New York https://t.co/4mR0WxNSl1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Google Cemetery – A list of dead Google products and why they died https://t.co/5hoIRyRIjy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Mystery Font That Took Over New York https://t.co/4mR0WxNSl1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Art of Job Interviewing https://t.co/6m47fQrJMD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hyperscript Tagged Markup: JSX alternative using standard tagged templates https://t.co/GZnIsiZltc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ask HN: How can I learn to read mathematical notation? https://t.co/38s9WwbSK5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fullscreen desktop application resembling a sci-fi computer interface https://t.co/DEM58wcOAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Show HN: PowerPoint slide builder with handwriting https://t.co/rJMcqvPMRa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The link between premarital sex and marriage stability https://t.co/j069RgX5bn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GDPR:Chat platform Knuddels must pay 20.000 Eur for storing plain-text passwords https://t.co/b0i0hA0GdL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Show HN: Power point slide builder with handwriting https://t.co/rJMcqvPMRa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Show HN: The Google Cemetery – A list of dead Google products and why they died https://t.co/5hoIRyRIjy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inside the court of Ashurbanipal, king of the world https://t.co/1cWO7Chqki]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pembrokeshire treasure hunter unearths Celtic chariot https://t.co/9yqt5F70xi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Robert Langlands: The Greatest Mathematician You’ve Never Heard Of? https://t.co/CPjWzhMroA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Video Games in East Germany: The Stasi Played Along https://t.co/pOuaT1f2Gu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Robert Langlands: The Greatest Mathematician You’ve Never Heard Of https://t.co/CPjWzhMroA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Greatest Mathematician You’ve Never Heard Of https://t.co/CPjWzhMroA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Potentially disastrous Rowhammer bitflips can bypass ECC protections https://t.co/KZbGH15qSu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Military Sweetheart Brooches of the First World War https://t.co/7ipsLf2aLb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still in love with Rust https://t.co/5BieUprZr3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amp – A complete text editor for the terminal https://t.co/mbXq3UUvvK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still in love with Rust https://t.co/5BieUpJAPD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon admits it exposed customer email addresses, but refuses to give details https://t.co/gLjdrdNbh0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Silent and Simple Ion Engine Powers a Plane with No Moving Parts https://t.co/4qwRUY4R4U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ask HN: Why not more hiring of junior devs, then on-the-job-training? https://t.co/INs1kwDfqT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thinking About Thinking (1999) https://t.co/jyS5XEcFAP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon Rekognition updates face detection, analysis and recognition capabilities https://t.co/UsLFYOEoR5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Slow Software https://t.co/9VHGsr6GQy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elliot Schrage on Definers https://t.co/ZumnJPrXXQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thinking about thinking https://t.co/jyS5XEcFAP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Aren't There C Conferences? https://t.co/i3wn7HkTLN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Working TRON Legacy UI for Linux / Mac / Windows https://t.co/DEM58wcOAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Popular Dark Web hosting provider hacked, 6,500 sites down https://t.co/VTVyV0bnO8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You and Your Research by Richard Hamming (1995) [video] https://t.co/EeJ4xHgfFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Texas Is About to Create OPEC’s Worst Nightmare https://t.co/9MIIcVI1mB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[American Is Killed by Bow and Arrow on Remote Indian Island https://t.co/wLZ16ny9FW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hackers erase 6,500 sites from the Dark Web in one attack https://t.co/oXEUXfOfRM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Aren't There C Conferences? https://t.co/i3wn7H3iUf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CUDA 10 in Clojure https://t.co/XZ3mhOcLay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon admits it exposed customer email addresses, but refuses to give details https://t.co/gLjdrdNbh0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some Amazon employees bought NYC condos before news of HQ2 location emerged https://t.co/iIi1Y25TMm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Silent and Simple Ion Engine Powers a Plane with No Moving Parts https://t.co/4qwRUY4R4U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CV Compiler is a robot that fixes your resume to make you more competitive https://t.co/hNiSIzQXnS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The World Will Be Our Skinner Box https://t.co/RvqLmuUwcl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When having fun on Twitter went wrong for Brent https://t.co/explzWJoxD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Concurrency Glossary https://t.co/qfpTNhzyLT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An overview of terms used in concurrent computing https://t.co/qfpTNhzyLT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Show HN: A dictionary of concurrent programming terms https://t.co/qfpTNhzyLT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Second Half of Watergate Was Bigger, Worse, and Forgotten by the Public https://t.co/s6ck7rzrRp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why wooden bikes are superior https://t.co/HZPYgZWCIe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[D compilation is too slow and I am forking the compiler https://t.co/CsEIfGFagr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The EU Terrorist Content Regulation – a threat to the ecosystem and user rights https://t.co/SRw3Jwqnsi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This JavaScript can snoop on other browser tabs to work out what you're visiting https://t.co/flBzzpxFRb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A small French privacy ruling could remake adtech https://t.co/UOT2iFVIzK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Autodesk to Acquire PlanGrid (YC W12) to Accelerate Construction Productivity https://t.co/eQI6IWiErL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A list of practical projects that anyone can solve in any programming language https://t.co/A93AVMRsdA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TKE: Modern Tcl/Tk-based text editor https://t.co/qyBL34umx7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ask HN: Have you ever regretted working on a product? https://t.co/IXIhcZjtQ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Superintelligence: The Idea That Eats Smart People (2016) https://t.co/RMFK5Bq0P8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flying for Thanksgiving https://t.co/Gcrqu1NVua]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PG&amp;E-friendly wildfire bill being prepared by lawmakers in wake of lethal fires https://t.co/DmOXZqk5lw]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>