<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Girls...this is for you: http://t.co/jFjamfCbHV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every moment has a little bit of magic. –Rapunzel (Princess Stories)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Barbie: "You have everything." | Ken: "Everything, except someone to share it with." –Toy Story 3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take a chance cause you can and you will see all the possibilities. If you try, you will find. –Disney Fairies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where one thing falls, another grows. Maybe not what was there before, but something new and wonderful all the same. –Bambi's Mother]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smiles can be catching. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't look backwards for very long. Keep moving forward, opening up new doors and doing new things. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go find a new dream. –Flynn Rider (Tangled)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just because you can't understand something, it doesn't mean it's wrong. –Arthur (The Sword in the Stone)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You just need to believe in yourself. –Rex (Toy Story 2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes the things that you're looking for, you can't see with your eyes. You have to see them with your heart. –Peter Pan (Disney Dreams)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We can't change who we are, and the sooner you accept that, the better off your game and your life will be. –Clyde (Wreck-It Ralph)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The harder the battle, the sweeter the victory. –Sebastian (Little Mermaid Series)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't you worry, okay? Things will work out. We started this thing together, and that's how we'll finish it. –Mushu (Mulan)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Say 'please' and 'thank you' even if you're feeling grumpy. –Snow White (Princess Stories)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listen with your heart, you will understand. –Grandmother Willow (Pocahontas)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When life gets you down, you know what you gotta do? Just keep swimming, just keep swimming. –Dory (Finding Nemo)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eat, drink and be merry, and tomorrow we diet. –Goofy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The past can hurt, but the way I see it, you can either run from it, or learn from it. –Rafiki (The Lion King)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I remember all the wonderful times we've had together. They're not things. They're memories. –Ariel (Little Mermaid Series)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Piglet: "How do you spell love?" | Pooh: "You don't spell it. You feel it."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you keep on believing, the dreams that you wish will come true. –Cinderella]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Girls talk too much. –Peter Pan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laughter is timeless, imagination has no age, and dreams are forever. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not easy to find someone to see your best. –Piglet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe it's time to stop following someone else's orders and start following your heart. –Cinderella (Cinderella II)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JAPAN. WHAT. WERE. YOU. THINKING:  http://t.co/oEIs9shu6q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd get over losing anything, but I'll never get over losing you. –Toy Story]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're not supposed to name it. Once you name it, you start getting attached to it. –Mike (Monster, Inc.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow the voice in your heart. Always know that's how to find who you are. –Disney Fairies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lewis: "I don't even know what I'm doing." | Wilbur: "Keep moving forward." –Meet the Robinsons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know, you worry too much. In fact, everybody worries too much. –Jiminy Cricket (Fun and Fancy Free)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can say goodbye and you can say hello, but you'll always find your way back home. –Hannah Montana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You cannot possibly understand. You have no idea what it's like to lose everything. –Beast (Enchanted Christmas)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lilo: "People treat me different." | Nani: "They just don't know what to say." –Lilo and Stitch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's a pie crust promise. Easily made, easily broken. –Mary Poppins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Growing up doesn't happen all at once. It takes its own time. –Kanga (Pooh's Heffalump Movie)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone can fall in love. –Cinderella (Cinderella II)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who says that my dreams have to stay just my dreams? –Ariel (Little Mermaid Series)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doorknob: "Crying won't help." | Alice: "I know, but I just can't help myself." –Alice in Wonderland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be strong, be true, be forever ‘who you are’. –Kala (Tarzan II)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whatever choice you make, let it come from your heart. –Queen Clarisse (Princess Diaries 2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The way to get started is to quit talking and begin doing. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Telling stories and laughing with friends: precious moments you'll never forget. –Brother Bear]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mulan: “They're disgusting.” | Mushu: “No, they're men.” –Mulan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’ve got no strings, so I have fun. I’m not tied up to anyone. –Pinocchio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's nice to be needed, isn't it? –Ursula (Little Mermaid Series)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Without trust, there can be no relationship. –Mushu (Mulan II)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I found true love because I kept a beautiful dream in my heart. –Cinderella (Cinderella 3)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One thing you should know, no matter where I go, we'll always be together forever and ever. –Christopher Robin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You’ll be in my heart from this day on, now, and forever more. –Kala (Tarzan)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is good to have a failure while you’re young because it teaches you so much. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All my troubles and obstacles have strengthened me. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In learning you will teach, and in teaching you will learn. –Tarzan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nobody minds. Nobody cares. –Eeyore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ITS A MYTH! http://t.co/TywNCrayaM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[can i please get this in my backyard? http://t.co/wP14keTTne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People say nothing is impossible, but I do nothing every day. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If nothing changed, there'd be no butterflies. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we stick together, we can see it through ‘cause you've got a friend in me. –Toy Story]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You used to be much more "muchier". You've lost your muchness. –Mad Hatter (Alice in Wonderland)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You and I are a team. Nothing is more important than our friendship. –Mike (Monsters, Inc.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing should ever bring you down, knowing what goes around will come around. –Princess Diaries]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the advantages of being disorganized is that one is always having surprising discoveries. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worrying won’t help anyone. –Mary Poppins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes I feel like I really don’t belong here, like I’m supposed to be some place else. –Hercules]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When opportunity knocks, open the door. –Don Carlton (Monsters University)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All my troubles and obstacles have strengthened me. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're not like anyone else. No doubt about it. You're second to none ‘cause you're the one and only one. –Eeyore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That place between sleep and awake, the place where you can still remember dreaming, that's where I'll always love you. –Peter Pan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MIND BLOWING  http://t.co/YLTgFH19AG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goodbye? Oh, no, please. Can’t we go back to page one and do it all over again? –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Home is love, and love is always home. –Ariel (The Little Mermaid Series)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do a good job. You don't have to worry about the money. It will take care of itself. Just do your best work. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You’ll always be part of my favorite story. –Belle (Enchanted Tales)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't grow up too fast, too soon. Save some time for dreaming. –Kanga (Pooh’s Heffalump Movie)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Be Patient" is very good advice, but the waiting makes me curious. –Alice (Alice in Wonderland)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don’t listen to them. You just need to keep trying. –Mike (Monsters University)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i can't believe they used to sell this at mc donalds http://t.co/4VvebJHmwS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's because I like you, I don't want to be with you. It's a complicated emotion. –Marlin (Finding Nemo)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just follow your heart. Go as far as your dreams. –Cinderella (Cinderella II)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes we only see how people are different from us, but if you look hard enough, you can see how much we're all alike. –Jasmine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One girl is worth more than 20 boys. –Peter Pan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like a shooting star, I will go the distance. I will search the world. I will face its harms. I don't care how far. –Hercules]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live each day as if it’s the first day of your life. –Donald Duck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wouldn't call this normal... http://t.co/vLaFpvjItX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one should marry someone they don't love. –Shang (Mulan II)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I tried all of my best wishes, and none of my wishes came true. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The way to get started is to quit talking and begin doing. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don’t really know someone unless you’ve cried with them. –Art (Monsters University)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s his loss. He can’t hurt you no more. –Lotso (Toy Story 3)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman appreciates a man who can make her laugh. –Genie (Aladdin)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All I need is a chance to do something great. –Chicken Little]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I knew when I met you, an adventure was going to happen. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just change your perspective, your point of view. The magic of your dreams is right inside of you. –Peter Pan (Disney Dreams)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celebrate your friends, today and every day. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If at first you don’t succeed, try, try again. –Bernard (The Rescuers)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A good friend can always brighten a gloomy day. –Eeyore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you got your pals, you got all you need. –Dodger (Oliver &amp; Company)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We may have our differences, but nothing can come between us. –Jasmine (Aladdin Series)]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>