<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Trini Lopez    http://t.co/PzZb6jPtAy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to C.S. Lewis  http://t.co/tAsFV80aIM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He had a forward spring... And an early fall...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Running SUCKS! How to Run for Fast Weight Loss - For Busy Women Who HATE Running --&gt; http://t.co/T4vW9Iik4Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the The Early History of Beer  http://t.co/WV9lDhv5tt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picking Earphones for Fitness Activities  http://t.co/5OGE8XsU58]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pizza in a cone? Yes indeed! Pizza cones are the newest way to prepare fun, personalized pizzas for the family!  http://t.co/Et3cY0t26y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Cascades  http://t.co/a2sjVlgqg5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Understanding Attention Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder (ADHD)  http://t.co/l8PNFcNu46]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's one small step for [a] man; one giant leap for mankind. - Neil A. Armstrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of McDonald's  http://t.co/b76eSisI5m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bird does not sing because it has an answer...  It sings because it has a song. - Chinese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A wife doesn't mind seeing a man make a fool out of himself as long as some other woman isn't helping him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only way to prove that you're a good sport is to lose. - Ernie Banks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a very easy way to return from a casino with a small fortune: go there with a large one. - Jack Yelton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love Minecraft?  Check out the hot new video blogger Crimson Mine - http://t.co/1wgCq3IZ6Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Barbara Acklin – “Love Makes a Woman”  http://t.co/MnYPCVQ67d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Deep Purple  http://t.co/C9XTLc9Sev]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Very Interesting History of Shoe Sizes  http://t.co/pLLgr0WAF7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Building Experts - Get Some Free Tips  http://t.co/2Tt2IwERz3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A baseball game is simply a nervous breakdown divided into nine innings. - Earl Wilson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out Why Technology Is Helpful To Seniors  http://t.co/HNTN0jqHox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Jackson Browne  http://t.co/Xwom9EllHz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A college is a place where pebbles are polished and diamonds dimmed. - Robert Ingersoll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think education is expensive, try ignorance - Derek Bok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Molly Hatchet  http://t.co/Rbkyzmb6AN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things could be worse. Suppose your errors were counted and published everyday, like those of a baseball player. - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I grew up in a world that told girls they couldn't play rock 'n' roll. - Joan Jett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pessimist: A man who thinks that all woman are bad Optimist: A man who hopes so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow the whiskey.  - Kid Rock, who arrived with "Redneck Woman" singer Gretchen Wilson, on his plans after the Country Music Awards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So cool and elegant - what is the history behind Ballet shoes?  http://t.co/vntAN29Zik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Skeeter Davis  http://t.co/ZhUVuslrCK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best thing about animals is that they don't talk much. - Thornton Wilder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Marie Antoinette's Watch  http://t.co/He8DWbSyWS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A New Star Wars Movie Is Coming in 2015!  http://t.co/FDwbPtZfvB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CONSCIENCE: The thing that hurts when everything  else feels good…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One deer to another:  "I wish I had his doe"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spring is when you feel like whistling even with a shoe full of slush. - Doug Larson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Guide to Business to Business Internet Marketing on LinkedIn  http://t.co/4cULNxXjif]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Budweiser  http://t.co/a1bxG8yR7T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You teach best what you most need to learn. - Richard David Bach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He ran out of talent about halfway through the corner. - Buddy Baker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Small Dogs Can Make Great Pets - Picking the Right Breed  http://t.co/tipfbkxMw4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Fitness Alternative Energy Devices  http://t.co/RlNaGFF29b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I didn't grow up thinking, 'Oh, maybe someday I'm going to have a shoe named after me.' -  Sheryl Swoopes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Ramones  http://t.co/zYoEIp1QWg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Successfully Use Other Websites for Link Building  http://t.co/SsIf6gHVxV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sign on a greenhouse: Fresh flowers just out of bed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this very cool bed fan - cools right under the covers! http://t.co/M4Z9ndUglT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Chilled Stones to Keep Your Drink Cool - Milled in Vermont http://t.co/tOLx6asRVI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then close your eyes and tap your heels together three times. And think to yourself, "There's no place like home" - The Wizard of Oz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Design is a constant challenge to balance comfort with luxe, the practical with the desirable. - Donna Karan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the History Of Pac-Man  http://t.co/RZuV7PDEuE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He looks like a girl.  Marlon Brando on Leonardo DiCaprio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I looked and looked but I didn't see God. - Yuri Gagarin, 14 April 1961]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana’s Lyme Journey – Part 17 – More on Supplements  http://t.co/1a6CJcoUrf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Clash  http://t.co/DGqxmhoOyP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best use of life is to spend it for something that outlasts it - William James]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turbochargers are for people who cant build engines. - Keith Duckworth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awe cool - A Lock N' load target alarm clock/Gun alarm clock - shoot the dang thing! http://t.co/Uw7rlZ6rmi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Snooky Lanson  http://t.co/icFILmTPTG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Top 10 fitness gyms  http://t.co/E2web8Ty9i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adversity causes some men to break; others to break records. - William A. Ward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Careers end with a ground ball to shortstop, not with a home run. - Bull Durham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually, I majored in marketing and I have a bachelor of science. - Wanda Sykes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rock is so much fun. That's what it's all about - filling up the chest cavities and empty kneecaps and elbows.  - Jimi Hendrix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Celiac Disease And Gluten Free Foods  http://t.co/8LbKUOwJFr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never look back unless you are planning to go that way. - Henry David Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is what survives when what has been learned has been forgotten. - B. F. Skinner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Guide – Business to Business Internet Marketing Tips  http://t.co/KioPKIEuz2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The Official How I Met Your Mother Premium Grey Silk Suit Jammies http://t.co/McLtpsbMlA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Create your own Ice, Chocolate, Jelly in the shape of Han Solo in Carbonite!!!  http://t.co/ylCZF11rwR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marriage lets you annoy and aggravate one special person for the rest of your life.  What a joy LOL!!  :&gt;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Men I may not know, but shoes, shoes I know. - Carrie Bradshaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't concentrate in flats! - Victoria Beckham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great overview on using Redstone in Minecraft - http://t.co/rHj6sM8sln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Who  http://t.co/IVZyASyfjH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Fort Worth, Texas  http://t.co/A9lNWkm1yN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these top 10 science fiction authors!  http://t.co/3iaBqA1D4R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only thing worse than a Mets game is a Mets double header. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read The History of the Beau Brummels  http://t.co/hrBcGMh4Z2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The lead car is absolutely unique, except for the one behind it which is identical. - F1 commentator Murray Walker.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crack is cheap I make too much $ to ever smoke crack. Lets get that straight. OK? We dont do crack We dont do that Crack is whack - Whtney H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the beginning, God created man, but seeing him so feeble, He gave him the cat - Warren Eckstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many a man doesn't start living until he's married. And then he's finished.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That guitar is okay but you'll never make a living with it - John Lennon's Aunt Mimi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Champions keep playing until they get it right. - Billie Jean King]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One deer to another:  "I wish I had his doe"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Colonize Mars: Can This Dream Become a Reality?  http://t.co/KqKzAvPRRy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have to have a lot of little boy in you to play baseball for a living.  - Roy Campanella]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is what happens to you when you're busy making other plans - John Lennon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automatic rotating laser light that provides hours of fun for your feline and canine friends - Keep the cat happy!  http://t.co/cJPTJ3J7XT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wouldn't feel right wearing clothes covering my body.  Christina Aguilera]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One day your life will flash before your eyes. Make sure it is worth watching - Mooie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Shelley Fabares  http://t.co/e6ai2jC2Nf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Management is nothing more than motivating other people. - Le Iacocca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She's got double D's! You can't cover those suckers up! Jessica Simpson's Dad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the fascinating history of that classic baseball park - Wrigley Field - http://t.co/t0lP0wGcaH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Willie Mays' glove is where triples go to die. - Jim Murray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bring out your dead. - Monty Python and the Holy Grail]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>