<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WorkforceJames: In this video, I interview @CEB_HR's @briankropp from the #ReimagineHR event earlier this month. https://t.co/aMykRAJNO8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HBSAlumni @Maxeme @CEB_News thanks for having me.  Lots of great fun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 sides to every story? amazon vs NYT https://t.co/GTqgWsozPY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joningham thanks for the conversation at #reimaginehr http://t.co/raNTcKCbA3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEB_HR: Thanks to everyone that attended #ReImagineHR! Couldn't attend? Missed anything? Apply for the key takeaways http://t.co/VvczSx…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US government trying to break down silos on talent, #enterprisecontributors across the government? http://t.co/6yPtekOjoO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even in America, Ikea Does Things the Swedish Way https://t.co/zwTLDrI7uw

Beth Kowitt at Fortune talks to Ikea’s … https://t.co/GaFMnH9GLE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does Labor Mobility Depend on the Kindness of Strangers? https://t.co/Zb3joOskcn

Matthew Boesler at Bloomberg fla… https://t.co/wCHBudP9Zu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Volkswagen’s US Chief Steps Down https://t.co/mwc8FUdYwM

Michael Horn, the president and CEO of Volkswagen’s US o… https://t.co/X7pAVA1fge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gig Economy Platforms for Legacy Companies https://t.co/O1xAVaRmjK

PricewaterhouseCoopers recently launched an on… https://t.co/MXOZJ7yoCe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Thousand Employees Benefited From Salesforce’s Equal-Pay Audit https://t.co/epcVHeECZC

Last November, Salesforc… https://t.co/q2YxvjllId]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The CEO Bonus Giveaway: Does it Work? https://t.co/BeeUzThwQ0

As LinkedIn struggles with underwhelming earnings a… https://t.co/c1d7JyL5N7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEB_HR: "A well-written thank you note from a manager has as much of an impact as a cash bonus," via @briankropp https://t.co/rOKy5OG6Ia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More Evidence that Women Leaders Add Value https://t.co/YvdViHFdec

On the occasion of International Women’s Day, … https://t.co/S9f15g1Aag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Dollar Here, a Promotion There: Gender Gaps Are Everywhere https://t.co/7m7PJGxyjm

Today is International Women… https://t.co/K0wDW5MrF2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Case Against Showing Health Data to Shareholders https://t.co/IRNmrRpix8

As more employers begin collecting e… https://t.co/9MRGfovFzi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Investing in Women Leaders https://t.co/SAqGZ62Bey

That’s exactly what State Street Global Advisors plans to do w… https://t.co/mEFqCKan8b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When CEOs Sacrifice Their Bonuses, Employees Don't Usually Stick Around https://t.co/mVZ31smN5e via @business]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To Pay or Not to Pay for Performance: The Skeptics’ Rebuttal https://t.co/gKjYfROhGn

In an interview with Jena Mc… https://t.co/SjuUNKgYhW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Airbnb Gets a Diversity Officer https://t.co/8aZRCfiDFB

Airbnb has become the latest tech company to hire a chief… https://t.co/oGI7rciYWB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Medium Drops Holacracy https://t.co/qmxinKHK8W

In a blog post published on Friday, Medium’s Director of Operation… https://t.co/uYpsTz2kd3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe Colleges Can’t Bridge the Skills Gap https://t.co/xzjCLHbeGG

A new analysis by CareerBuilder and Emsi finds… https://t.co/7k6a8d0umi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[February Jobs Numbers Look Good, But What Happened to Wages? https://t.co/75tUzsS6bk

The US job market outperform… https://t.co/I3awd6gTMo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can All Bosses Be ‘Superbosses’? https://t.co/s8UOSMiGLu

I’ve been doing research and giving presentations on lea… https://t.co/p1uXSHCRqe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEB_HR: Employers are shifting larger share of Healthcare cost to employees #IncreasingDeductibles https://t.co/hks1oFOQw3 https://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More Steps Taken Toward a Fitness-Tracked Workforce https://t.co/C2otVnLl5Y

This week, several health insurance c… https://t.co/DjnJoQp5S7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You Don’t Have to be Cool to Attract Millennial Tech Talent https://t.co/JLGwi37aWY

Late last year, General Elect… https://t.co/7VFjd5qKXz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@workforcenews also interesting to note the perceived pay gap across most companies https://t.co/Wt56vsVMH1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elon Musk Says His Companies Will Audit Pay for Gender Gaps https://t.co/Qc8MK9SAVY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elon Musk Says His Companies Will Audit Pay for Gender Gaps https://t.co/J5US0Pu0qv

Some high-profile companies, … https://t.co/1581RC9qUJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Equal Employment Opportunity Commission Files First LGBT Discrimination Suits https://t.co/5ed93gs1eX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Student-Loan Benefits Pay Off https://t.co/WACGgsrXb0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Equal Employment Opportunity Commission Files First LGBT Discrimination Suits https://t.co/lckW87D612

Ever since … https://t.co/bWBoJSIGQw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Student-Loan Benefits Pay Off https://t.co/hTnu5ltaOM

Student loan assistance for employees is one of the mos… https://t.co/rY7gZvWhSO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Report Shows 90 Percent of Employers Taking Myriad Measures to Control Rising Health Care Costs | Business Wire https://t.co/k8CfVTdoh8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will the 360 Review Go the Way of Stack Ranking? https://t.co/vY0REw49h7 #]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Replacing &lt;i&gt;Him&lt;/i&gt; With &lt;i&gt;Her?&lt;/i&gt; Boards Seldom Do https://t.co/GdADHAXAFy #]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Power Corrupts Collaboration https://t.co/3gSUFa4dFF #]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What makes people so frustrated about their paychecks? The feeling that it's unfair https://t.co/bWIRl4JLqo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your Employees Aren’t as Excited About Change as You Are https://t.co/32JcRgrZu7 #]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The ‘No Qualified Woman’ Fallacy https://t.co/WOEzhLSHwy #]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most Workers Don’t See Gender Pay Gaps, but Wouldn’t Like It If They Did https://t.co/uncvwF3Akr #]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Not to Talk About Poor Performance https://t.co/iEsTZ32ren #]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making the Value of Talent Clear to Investors https://t.co/M8aWUNUfx8 #]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEB_HR: Learn how Millennials have an impact on your Talent Management strategy in our complimentary webinar this Thursday https://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEB_HR: Why performance reviews like Yahoo’s are out of favor #ForcedRankings https://t.co/cOiEMknGdA https://t.co/wa0PgqPz36]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEB_HR: Employees who are most committed perform 20% better and are 87% less likely to leave the organization https://t.co/2OH6BgyKm9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OrganiSolutions: Easier to quit your company &amp; find a new job than find a new job within your own company @briankropp @lydiadepillis ht…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to boost morale and retain talent https://t.co/lP3hS9E4XL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEB_HR: How to boost morale and retain talent, via @BrianKropp #CareerProgression https://t.co/0DK4FsFWMH https://t.co/FQEyQN7q2e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Important to recognize the need for D&amp;I before graduates get to your company  https://t.co/rr5LnlfwAH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 ways to motivate disengaged employees - CGMA Magazine https://t.co/WtQz353Lo7 via sharethis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter Embraces Gender-Neutral Parental Leave https://t.co/MsW7YDeWLr

As of May 1, the social media company will… https://t.co/ODZIkrUD4u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rewards Must be Meaningful to Drive Employee Behaviors https://t.co/ZgKEeFtENn

Meaningfulness is a key theme that… https://t.co/MKw17he2iZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disney’s CEO Succession Just Got More Complicated https://t.co/Y7IZZRI7Il

Thomas Staggs, a longtime executive at … https://t.co/fJ7d48PbIt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[San Francisco Weighs Mandating Parental Leave at Full Pay https://t.co/jaIUwWvHYO

The San Francisco Board of Supe… https://t.co/pScahEsYDW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Matchmaker, Matchmaker, Get Me a Job https://t.co/xj3rjrYwKH

On the first of the month, the online dating service… https://t.co/JrUzCkBNSI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Whitened’ Résumés Fare Better, Even at Diversity-Conscious Employers https://t.co/KAXr5kR1S4

In a recently publi… https://t.co/rm2PQHKUWJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[March Jobs Report: ‘The Boom We’ve Been Looking For’ https://t.co/DFeghwDrzQ

Friday’s jobs report from the US Bur… https://t.co/ly7BqjXU6E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Defense Department Launches Retooled Performance Rating System https://t.co/OWgaaExw43

The Defense Department is … https://t.co/rtE17v5VVw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Employee-Driven Job Market for Q2 https://t.co/SOEeasMD2S

CareerBuilder’s latest job forecast finds that the U… https://t.co/nwZR2pfy6A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Living Wage’ Becomes Law in UK https://t.co/8lgwbHyux1

The UK’s National Living Wage law, which requires employe… https://t.co/AJihgtDLVw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New York to Hike Minimum Wage, Mandate Family Leave https://t.co/VkSc3pRdwP

A budget deal reached in Albany betwe… https://t.co/Fm8TmmED94]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Flubs Gmail April Fools Day Prank, Angering Professionals https://t.co/um5UsVL5MK 

Though we’re abstaining… https://t.co/vLUzlzMdJZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Do Employees Value More: Wages or Health Care? https://t.co/Uu5go0oOMG

A recent analysis of survey data from… https://t.co/QIgut4YLiv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unequal Pay for More Than Equal Play? https://t.co/rD92RBdFiE

Following the recent pay gap controversy inside wom… https://t.co/AQnQJss53U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bank of America Expands Parental Leave https://t.co/g2E9f0SuwT

The financial giant announced on Wednesday that pa… https://t.co/xjxoRY4Zw2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEB_TlntMonitor: "Change-fatigued employees are eager to find a role where they have more stability" - @briankropp https://t.co/DO99NFa…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Profiling the Programmers https://t.co/kTdhO3QSEI

The coding community site Stack Overflow’s annual developer sur… https://t.co/mo29Vvqrnc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Gaps in the Leadership Gap https://t.co/HqNYItjQHs 

American Association of University Women

It’s not news t… https://t.co/VoQJD5Lcrj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SCOTUS Deadlock Keeps Public Employee Union Agency Fees Alive https://t.co/Cb5y69vEdf

The Supreme Court issued no… https://t.co/kFBzVJD3Vo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[California Proposes Universal 401(k) https://t.co/TW9x7v0fuB

Legislators in California aren’t just considering ra… https://t.co/xLHY2WQXPl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Career development is top priority for employers seeking to retain talent https://t.co/o4Yv35sFHD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Designing Equality for Women https://t.co/Gw6rf4ejlC

Harvard professor Iris Bohnet’s new book, What Works: Gender… https://t.co/d6454hEGfP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What’s the Use of a Lazy Worker? https://t.co/HQBV6Kfflf

At NPR, Yuki Noguchi showcases the work of Eisuke Hasega… https://t.co/5pQSz61RWD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What California’s $15 Minimum Wage Deal Means for Employers https://t.co/cYdSncmsNP

California Governor Jerry Bro… https://t.co/25nZU1U5kL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alternative Work is Growing, but the ‘Gig Economy’ Is Just a Part of It https://t.co/VQ7wwdo7Kl

Anna Louie Sussma… https://t.co/hMFhwhkAQR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over 100 Employers Sign on to Boston’s Gender Pay Transparency Compact https://t.co/6zq1lykgqI

Boston Mayor Marti… https://t.co/7gjykgUFGO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deliberately Developmental Organizations https://t.co/k7BcTTyhc7

Harvard professors Robert Kegan and Lisa Lahey’s… https://t.co/zREVqKG93Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perfect Teams? We Just Need Better Ones https://t.co/InUbKiNOg0 

Type “what makes a perfect team?” into Google an… https://t.co/0oKEfILv9m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Inequality Becomes Automated https://t.co/npMHTglGr2

At the Harvard Business Review, economist James Bessen … https://t.co/YgEwILIAq6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SCOTUS: Meatpacking Workers Can Collect Overtime for Donning and Doffing Gear https://t.co/SwIWvrVMpX

On Tuesday,… https://t.co/HVoqKW449p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US Employers Must Reveal Ties With Anti-Union ‘Persuaders’ https://t.co/5xwCF9E0we

This week, the US Labor Depart… https://t.co/NOoBiekgrz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If You Make the Board Walk the Plank… https://t.co/UM4qQPyg3G

…you better make sure you have the right candidates… https://t.co/3sn8vHT1cH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Speedy Hire Clause? https://t.co/dM7agNfvAV 

From Vampire’s Kiss (Giphy/Scream Factory)

Scott Wintrip at ERE… https://t.co/FlJjzB19Cd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Do You Say ‘Flex-Time’ In Gujarati? https://t.co/6IlwV4WwXB

Flexible work arrangements aren’t just a luxury f… https://t.co/I0nIhvRUPz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will the New Overtime Rule Exacerbate Presenteeism? https://t.co/AVZIzgfI2G

Writing at Compensation Café, compens… https://t.co/IetzPvjR5e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Bill Would Grant Equal Leave for Military Moms and Dads https://t.co/OUXJttSuWF

When the Pentagon unveiled it… https://t.co/uCqk7JRPBV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @joshdavisphd: Thanks strategy+business for featuring one of my articles in "Ideas That Work" https://t.co/tC4SK7OEzP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEB_TlntMonitor: Why are Millennials in South Africa willing to gamble their jobs for new opportunities? https://t.co/kKbrIvbsmL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @andydiaz: Is the salient leading indicator that you've gone native in management consulting using the word "around" when you really mea…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Report: Talent pool remains thin as workers opt not to move jobs https://t.co/TioecK6Rb3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEB_HR: Discover eBay's new approach to performance management and their success journey during tmrw's free webinar @ 12p ET https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Samsung Aims for an Extreme Culture Makeover https://t.co/S2G4E8osQh

Responding to a slowdown in the growth of it… https://t.co/4vF5mQ2hpr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon Review Finds No Pay Gap, But Is That the Whole Story? https://t.co/dVMesLGZdx

Less than a week after the S… https://t.co/iIRwLqP1ex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Great and Talentful Oz https://t.co/8PPnvhEP1y

“While the immigration debate in the United States and elsewhe… https://t.co/uiMvxwdZlV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Right to a Messy Desk https://t.co/STqBpMjv9f

At Workplace Insight, consultant Mark Eltringham thinks through… https://t.co/1OYMnOVTaB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teach for America Cuts Diversity Officer in Push to Decentralize https://t.co/a1NOcEQwEc

Teach for America reveal… https://t.co/Slc1DV7PeN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Job Differences Explain Most, but Not All, of the Gender Pay Gap https://t.co/sa3SHVT7AS

A new report from Glassd… https://t.co/k7AeGX37PL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most US Professionals are Professional Learners https://t.co/rjAdme7c6q 

The Pew Research Center released a major… https://t.co/PYOWwIxDBf]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>