<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tribelaw: The Kennedy vacancy brings abortion rights to the fore in the midterms because women can no longer take Roe v. Wade and judic…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ChrisMurphyCT: Let’s call it like it is: the Supreme Court is turning itself into a political arm of the Republican Party. Weakening or…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CNN: Democratic Sen. Dick Durbin has called on the Senate to wait to consider Trump's nominee to replace Justice Kennedy until the new…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @brianklaas: If you’re unhappy with the Supreme Court’s recent decisions, recall:  Democrats narrowly lost the Senate with a few close r…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SenWarren: Mitch McConnell should follow the Mitch McConnell rule. Let the American people have a say when women’s health and equal rig…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tedlieu: My statement on the retirement of Justice Kennedy.

“The American people should have a voice in the selection of their next Su…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So what you're saying is, we're fucked: Supreme Court To Lose Its Swing Voter: Justice Anthony Kennedy To Retire https://t.co/KSJqv6dl7c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @eveewing: Teachers - a meaningful thing you can do right now is ensure that your students know how truly unpopular Dr. King’s actions w…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @theanthonyking: It’s encouraging that Sarah Huckabee Sanders was judged not by the color of her skin but by the content of her characte…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @libshipwreck: The system works, it was meant to maintain white supremacy and that’s exactly what it’s doing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @brhodes: The breakdown in civility and our politics occurred when a sitting President couldn't even get a hearing on a Supreme Court no…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @The_Millions: "I always tell my students they should be writing about their obsessions and the things that are preoccupying them. And s…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jnmedina8989: Lol @ all the white politicians lecturing a 79 year-old black woman on the indecency being denied service at a restaurant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @adriennemaree: things to never be civil about: concentration camps, genocide, white supremacy, misogyny, harm to children, mass trauma,…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @missmayn: If I can’t go to Planned Parenthood for a routine pap smear without being screamed at and harassed by Christian protestors th…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pandamoonpub: "A trippy, unique spin on the vampire mythology that'll satisfy Deadheads and noir purists alike." -- J.L. Delozier, auth…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Kristen_Arnett: how many times a day now do you look at the news and shout "jesus FUCKING christ" because at this point that's maybe my…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @writerscenter: If you've dabbled in flash fiction, but need a spark of inspiration for new stories, this four-week online course is for…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's all celebrate the brilliance of @killianczuba's t-shirt design for @barrelhouse https://t.co/KKVXbfpYUw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not only #WriterCamp and @GlenstoneMuseum this weekend, but also...!!! https://t.co/m0bO6mEQV9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @housleydave: Team picture, @barrelhouse #WriterCamp June 2018! https://t.co/P5tKlQLUyO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheRickyDavila: Alison Ettel aka #PermitPatty: https://t.co/Eoc34o76hk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WriterCamp @barrelhouse https://t.co/aa1uqfUS5e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#writercamp @barrelhouse https://t.co/4rpKXiVl57]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @upperrubberboot: The Female of the Species by @TaraCampbellCom in @lunaquarterly: https://t.co/o8CRwhwcQK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just doin' a little work by the stream. @barrelhouse #WriterCamp https://t.co/kxaStguDYl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @t_mcallister: 7 days left to submit to @barrelhouse open call for work by previously unpublished writers. Still not many essay subs (ab…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ParkerMolloy: https://t.co/tWx9WQ1hpX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @markmobility: Brilliant. https://t.co/w6MFjcbD65]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ComedyCentral: This is just like the time Eleanor Roosevelt wore that "GREAT DEPRESSION? I FEEL FINE" onesie to visit a soup kitchen. h…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @extreameeyes: 'Morally Bankrupt': After Tax Cuts for Richest, House GOP Unveils $5.4 Trillion Attack on Nation's Safety Net https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @brandon_r_horan: If you are offended for not hearing "Merry Christmas" from your Starbucks cashier or get really upset over someone kne…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stay alert, folks. They're always trying to slip something in your drink while you're looking the other way. 

https://t.co/HfvfyGIX9W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @johnpavlovitz: If you purposefully and unapologetically run people over with your car—you don't get points for stopping when lots of pe…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RepJoeKennedy: You might not know this about me, but I'm a white guy. And as a white guy, I would encourage @realDonaldTrump &amp; his fell…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where would we be without an independent media to uncover stuff like this? Thank you, @Ericnpr at @NPR: Investigation Into The VA Reveals A Culture Of Retaliation Against Whistleblowers https://t.co/NULUrsCY0f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ohmygosh so good! Better to Eat You With by Hannah Gordon (aka @_hannahnicole) in @JellyfishReview https://t.co/NZZGuyfZzt via @wordpressdotcom #flashfiction]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @surlybassey: I went to school with the children of upper-middle class ppl while being poor. One of the weird things about that educatio…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With all the crap going on now, let's take a moment to celebrate a talented @AmericanU student getting a chance, and the money, to pursue his dreams: Tiny Creatures Fuel Student's Big Dreams https://t.co/FAhhtLOQaR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @arunindy: About 75 people blockading ICE prison in Portland, OR. DHS keep coming out to ask protesters to let 9 ICE employees to leave.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MrFilmkritik: When a dog died on an airplane, Congress immediately introduced a bill to bar airlines from endangering animals.

Trump a…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CharlesMBlow: Melania felt it was too traumatic to move her son to DC in the middle of the school year so she spent millions of taxpaye…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SamGrittner: I just have two questions about Space Force:
1) When will Flint, Michigan have clean water?
2) When will Puerto Rico have…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LCNM99: The immigrants are stealing our jobs!
What jobs are they stealing?
Well, they are on welfare!
They don't qualify for welfare.
W…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MattPerez18 We already got all that in 2016.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love this story by @jnjoneswriter  in  @pidgeonholes https://t.co/W96k3NuJlZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fabulous @danbrady82 reading @TheInnerLoopLit @ColonyClubDC ! https://t.co/4ySjJBCh71]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@housleydave I so wish I had written this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @housleydave: Like a lot of stories about golden tickets to heaven and aliens and planets made of drugs, this really picks up once they…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ReeAmilcarScott Oh, please just let this whole presidency be performance art by Sun Ra. He'll clue us in any day now, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ziwe: scott pruitt resigning is like someone storming out of a restaurant after they’ve already eaten all the food]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RepBarbaraLee: This is so unacceptable on so many levels. I don’t even know where to start.  
https://t.co/sDI2OTWxee https://t.co/dv0T…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JohnFugelsang: Jim Jordan running for Speaker of the House proves the GOP has evolved from a guy who molested wrestlers to a guy who me…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HGwriter @livesinpages Actually, who needs essays, I'll just compile a list of Fox headlines and send it off to the publisher now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@livesinpages Okay, that's gonna be the name of my first book of essays: "Trash-Ass Opinions"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nike Adjusting Her Sandal, Again https://t.co/6ug7vR3Gmo @WritersResist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BBBCentralOhio: @finnick_Resists @DrSCubed @AviAhvee @MuslimIQ 3/3 We are constantly monitoring and reviewing the actions of businesses…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oof, this guy followed her home to call her despicable names because he thought she cut him off. That's some dangerous behavior right there. I wouldn't want him working in my home. https://t.co/ffLjW8jKin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jekeleme: @NylonMag I would say you should do better but I'm pretty sure the writer and editor are tone deaf and have no real connectio…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kelsiidarling: @NylonMag I have this thing where I don’t click on weed stories featuring white people exercising a privilege that  got…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kenolin1: Time to thank the 11 GOP Congressman who filed articles of impeachment against AG Rosenstein today. Their filing contains num…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah yes, Google set me up with this memory of the pink donkey #piñata, an essential for every good wedding. https://t.co/CbJSHJJCXZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @planet4589: Mars Express, which has been orbiting Mars since late 2003, has found evidence for a large body of liquid water underneath…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VonettaWrites @geekandahalf You won't regret it. I use it several times a week!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PoetsRTN: Jerrod Schwarz's erasure poetry from Donald Trump's letter to Kim Jong-un (first published on our site) was featured in @pale…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @2040Books: We’re sending you high fives when you press that submit button for our #contest! #fiction and #nonfiction #manuscripts from…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nakisnakis: We (@PipelineAngels) have a paid part-time opportunity &amp; would love to encourage Deaf POC to apply!

Details:
-&gt; Administra…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sahilkapur: Sen. Bob Corker characterizes Trump's farm aid proposal: "You have a terrible policy that sends farmers to the poorhouse, a…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheRickyDavila: Anti-trump Protestors Raise $100K to Continue Nightly Demonstrations Outside the White House. Keep it going! #Day9
http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just when I think today's gonna be a reading day instead of a #writing day, my brother sends me an article he knows will piss me off so much I'll have to write something--and it works! Goodbye day, but hello new #poem. #amwriting #pissedoffpoet https://t.co/8UYetSw1Yt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @stonecold2050: Trumps signature looks like a Klan rally https://t.co/2CYZaSkfYd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["More mammals are becoming nocturnal to avoid humans
You’re this close to the most comfortable sleep ever..."

42,000 Matches https://t.co/R179uVohAy via @litbreak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@raimalarter Thanks for sharing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @IjeomaOluo: Imagine how much good Obama could have gotten done if Congress was even half as permissive of his efforts to lead the count…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MoonLitDC: This week - explore ways poets shape anger into poetry at the Femme Fatale DC Pop-Up Store and learn to read tarot in Meridi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JulianCastro: Don’t waste a minute of your time being daunted that @realDonaldTrump has a base of diehard supporters. So did Richard Ni…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There's a vitally important word in the epic tale of Beowulf &amp;...it's been translated incorrectly for a very long time...aglæca/æglæca...is used to describe Beowulf &amp; his three antagonists: Grendel, Grendel's mother, &amp; the dragon." https://t.co/Zu1Qf4iNtZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @thehill: NFL halts policy barring players from protesting during anthem https://t.co/dmk5kdh3Zv https://t.co/X7V7HaRf8I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kimgoodwin: I have had more than one male colleague sincerely ask whether a certain behavior is mansplaining. Since apparently this is…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Y'all, go see this #movie. You'll thank me. It's amazing! #Blindspotting https://t.co/i2sdOFmLPc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KarenKilgariff: every person in this administration is someone you were taught to steer clear of at the lake]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @housleydave: And...duh... here's the link! Two gone already...https://t.co/v6YrFIo6J9 https://t.co/KFwOUnVIJP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @housleydave: Pssst Internet: these shirts are not yet sold out at the @barrelhouse store (but they probably will be soon). https://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BetoORourke: The press is not the enemy of the people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DavidJollyFL: Next up, Melania holds a presser to say she thought her jacket said "I really do care" not "I really don't care".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ideosinkrasee Yeowtch. But we're all there with you. Aaaaalll of us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you, @kathyfish! https://t.co/7cfpyKcCbA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow. Check out this #poem by @RhinoPoetry

...and you don’t want
your daughter learning
to shoot a rifle
with the other kids
who aim at a silhouette
of someone’s son
tied to a haystack...

https://t.co/lZWHmh5dpA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ambernoelle That line has to be the beginning of a story.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @shannonrwatts: On the same day a Russian nationalist and lifetime @NRA member was arrested for “conspiracy to act as an agent of the Ru…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PoliticsProse: Join @Free_KGD, @thedoaksgirl, @deniselow9, and @ChristianTeresi tonight at The Wharf as they discuss poetic responses t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WalkerBragman: Know what a real national embarrassment looks like? 

It looks like the wealthiest nation on Earth arguing over costs in…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grampa: Now Billy, it's time to go to sleep.

Billy: Aw, come on, dedushka, tell it one more time.

Grampa: Okay, Billy, just one more time: Once upon a time the United States of America was its very own, separate country...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MichaelSteele: "My people came to me...they said they think it's Russia. I have President Putin. He just said it's not Russia. I will s…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @scullymike: "I asked Japan if they attacked Pearl Harbor. They said no. What else can I do?" - President Franklin. D. Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We all knew it would come to this:

"Article 1

I am the Lord your #POTUS . Thou shalt have no other gods before Me..."

https://t.co/UHILfSfC07 https://t.co/PJA03FwqoO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@geekandahalf :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @naomi_zeigler: Thinking about how lucky I am that the DC boil water advisory is a temporary inconvenience, not an everyday reality. Fli…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cmclymer: She told us what would happen.

She was mocked as “over prepared” and “shrill” by pundits.

Hillary told us this would happen…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nowthisnews: We’re just going to leave this here today https://t.co/WkFVQ4BzIf]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>