<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Got my sushi paintings all packed up, hanging the show tonight. Come to the Roundhouse Centre tomorrow night to see all 100 on the wall!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HallGallery hey thanks for following!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArtsVancouver me too!! Lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mermaidwhimsy yup I brought it this time!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessicagowling HAHAHAHA gosh no!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jessicagowling thanks buddy! takin a break today :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's all 100 finished sushi paintings for viewing. Come see them in PERSON on wednesday night at the rounhouse! http://t.co/9x9tV9Ow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted 52 photos on Facebook in the album "100 Pieces of Sushi" http://t.co/Eor5tlO3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mermaidwhimsy i will post a pic of it on my site very soon!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mermaidwhimsy self-inflicted. for a one day show this wednesday night. i was on my way to get a celebration brew and forgot my wallet!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArtsVancouver its done! now we can hang soon again!! oy :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finished varnishing 100 paintings. My eyes are sure to be crossed for a couple hours :s http://t.co/5LJLRpSj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Emily_V_Cooper thx buddy -  I'm a bit tired :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eastcoastdandy thx man! Things are def workin out! U still in the theatre, I hope!? Now I just attend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Wednesday you can come see my 100 Pieces of Sushi project on display at the Roundhouse Community Center in... http://t.co/POYQNcxF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These are the last 5 paintings-I've now finished all 100! Time for a beer  http://t.co/FDKiHhlF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted a new photo to Facebook http://t.co/RKynzw99]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out tonight's spread!  http://t.co/CQZmD0TU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@indi_gone that sounds awesommmmme]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mizzledrizzle thx for teh follow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LFolliott oh man me too it's hard to stare at it for this long..haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eastcoastdandy most definitely man, I can't ever stop :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Painting some fish  http://t.co/Zlh9nvJi http://t.co/U4X22gpF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eastcoastdandy heeeeey Ian!! hows the haps these days mate?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gypsyles fantastic!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gypsyles hey how are ya - thanks for the follow! like the camel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NadiaNBaker hey thanks! its a one day show. May 16, this coming wednesday at the roundhouse center in yaletown;reception 7-10, show all day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeteKohut thanks man! i really enjoy makin it so im glad others enjoy too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IanNewbold hey thanks for the follow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here are the 7 pieces to finish tonight http://t.co/jBHHjnaf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a painting of octopus sashimi!
37/100 
http://t.co/WUJMSDcW via @pinterest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[less than a week until the roundhouse show - cant wait to show my 100 sushi paintings! here's number 70: http://t.co/1zVSux1G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeteKohut hey buddy thanks for following!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted 9 photos on Facebook in the album "100 Pieces of Sushi" http://t.co/VqYJI3Xw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Flores_Jessica hello :) thanks for following me :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here are numbers 69-72. Getting closer...! http://t.co/ozUIX58d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I posted 12 photos on Facebook in the album "100 Pieces of Sushi" http://t.co/pJ2GDoxr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@levinpainting hey thanks for the follow!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArtsVancouver takin a break tonight to go to the Van Halen concert though...back at it tomorrow (and every day til Tuesday!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hedleysean wow thanks for that! makes my day for sure!! :) im just doin what i love! haha.  That show was great. Back in July for another!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ive now got 68 of 100 of the sushi paintings done. Show is next wednesday... final stretch!! http://t.co/IxeD417w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnthonyGilesArt thanks for following! thats a good looking stout..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SueHotchkis hey thanks for following!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Art4Alex thanks for the follow! i dig those studio shots]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wesleydharmon hey there thanks for following!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArtMagenta hey thanks for following! sweet illustrations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hedleysean Hey there - thanks for the follow!! I like your background]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[68 paintings done now. Here are a few recent ones  http://t.co/RYKujDFv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here is a pair of edamame paintings http://t.co/wnVAe78r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First of several more finished pieces for the eve - this is #56 of 100 (I think..:) http://t.co/Nkl6Duxd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a painting of some eel sushi! http://t.co/fk0nV5Ml]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sushi No. 21 - Set is coming together! http://t.co/1ZWrJK3S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Juliesviews1 ya thats a good thing haha. thanks! i enjoy makin em ;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Juliesviews1 thanks for following back - those drawings are pretty dope!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessFabian they're my art socks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paintin at the beach after work...doesn't get much better! http://t.co/9JpX3v3t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cybelenegris hey thanks for following :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've crossed 50% completion with these 100 sushi paintings! http://t.co/DElny7Zh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet! This painting raised over $400 at a recent charity auction in Whistler! (Photo cred: Andrew Chin) http://t.co/dXvnJuhE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@filipevsm hey there, thanks for following!!! i make ART!! 

http://t.co/XWFbF0Is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SafeintheSound amazing! i believe they have free food comin too! (wine will be 4 bucks)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SafeintheSound @lutboutique wow thanks! I have a blast just doin it! Got
A cool piece up at the roundhouse on may 16...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My sushi project is nearly 50% complete - it's starting to come together! http://t.co/xL6MbGLB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HelenatUBC thanks buddy! ill be lookin forward to that night! cant wait to see em on a wall, im almost half done]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HelenatUBC its gonna be up at the roundhouse in yaletown for a one day  group show on wed, may 16; 10-10, reception is 7-10pm!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SafeintheSound hey thanks for the follow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArtsyShark hey thx for teh follow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkSchwartz hey thx for the follow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HelenatUBC Thanks buddy! the set's gonna keep growing. 15 days left until its done!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A selection of nine sushi paintings from the weekend:  http://t.co/Onv7xb8m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArtsVancouver haha not even!! Just
Lovin the sush]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmolcanart haha sounds good! Too bad u couldn't come but
I'll stick photos on my blog and link to it afterwards!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mermaidwhimsy ya I think it turned out pretty
Sweet!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sushi sushi paintings! I'm about 1/3 done the full set (of 100) http://t.co/qDkYeFO9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Car Free Day is this weekend. I will be at Heritage Hall (Main and 15th), THIS SUNDAY, 12-5pm working on pieces and selling!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LandmarkProdVan thanks for following - i love theatre..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[check out my t-shirts for sale!

http://t.co/dDzXvyE8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[awesome!! Thanks!! “@jmolcanart: Hung my first art purchase @jonshawpainting http://t.co/hRFqv6MV”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmolcanart hey got your paintings here today :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wanna buy a shirt? Finally got my store up :) Very limited quantities! 

http://t.co/dDzXvyE8 http://t.co/qx4yI368]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the first in a [likely] series of parrot pieces! Stoked to play with all the colour.. http://t.co/XbbRBssF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's the first steps in a new 3x4
Foot painting of a giraffe (s) http://t.co/bFBhxW0a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FloraGordon I went on an art trip to NYC in my last year of undergrad - what an amazing place for art. Vancouver needs a boost!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Doctor_Vigari thanks for teh follow! im gonna have to come check u guys out!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm happy that this happy puffin got sold to a happy couple yesterday :) http://t.co/UPdfgKsC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been hearing lots of good stuff about the Matisse show @VanArtGallery - Hopefully check it out next week #art #vancouver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @birdonawireart: We have our Private View TODAY come by for wine &amp; #art btw 7-9:30 @JonShawPainting &amp; @blue_studio in attenda ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@The_Art_Space thanks for following!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@birdonawireart @jonshawpainting @kstennant @blue_studio No prob, bob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@birdonawireart @kstennant @jonshawpainting @blue_studio yup ill be ther e- i was referencing the date being incorrect originally :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@birdonawireart @jonshawpainting @blue_studio thursday..?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Second stage. Can you see the owl? http://t.co/mvngo1Dn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @VijsRailway: Truck getting a final wash before get transformed to #VijsRailwayExpress. #CurryArtInMotion http://t.co/nwqfeYeQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey everyone - this is an after-hours get together for Robi and my work at the shop. Food and wine! Come on byyyy http://t.co/pPbdnuvB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmolcanart (cuz I'm not with email now)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jmolcanart I just saw! I think one of those is unavailable, but I'll send you all the deets via email tonite or early tomorrow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ImVincentMurphy heeeeeeeeeyo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kstennant hey thanks for the follow! i also use ink and paint together.. :)]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>