<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I have never felt in tune with the whole rock industry.  - Robert Wyatt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is the ability to listen to almost anything without losing your temper or your self-confidence. - Robert Frost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of LA Gear  http://t.co/dz8LZXRP0G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Asked a woman in an art store, "you don't consider this horrible thing art, do you" "No madam" replied the dealer, it's a mirror.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The entrepreneur always searches for change, responds to it, and exploits it as an opportunity. - Peter F. Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tornado Automatic Cocktail Shaker - VERY COOL http://t.co/Psm7UuZz8F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Seniors and Social Networking  http://t.co/fIQQq54WhW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Barbara Mason  http://t.co/VTX88nHAYx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Great Tips from Web Marketing Experts  http://t.co/3jkAnjYuFM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The pessimist sees difficulty in every opportunity. The optimist sees opportunity in every difficulty. - Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool man a Switch Blade Pocket Comb - look tough!  http://t.co/fsxBKLIY8e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Reviews By Children Affect a Product’s Sale  http://t.co/X3OHqxQTf8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you can look in the mirror and smile at what you see, then there's hope for you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make Your Own Ice Cream Cookie Bowls - YUM! http://t.co/ePknCnSTMZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[STAR TREK ENTERPRISE - Brake Light Vinyl Decal - ENGAGE!  --&gt; http://t.co/QjMjVi0Dqv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feed sparingly and defy the physician. - James Howell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exciting History of Baseball  http://t.co/ArJMAyRejs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to that hilarious sit-com Three’s Company - http://t.co/IuZ0Ywc14x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Mott the Hoople  http://t.co/MCsnRsi4pI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True friends are like diamonds - bright, beautiful, valuable, and always in style. --&gt; Nicole Richie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So my degree was in political science, which I think was - the closest I could come to marketing is politics. - Steve Case]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new source of power is not money in the hands of a few, but information in the hands of many. - John Naisbitt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overwhelming underdogs. - Yogi Berra While Referring to the 1969 New York Mets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I read Shakespeare and the Bible, and I can shoot dice. That's what I call a liberal education. - Tallulah Bankhead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's easier to ask forgiveness than it is to get permission - Grace Hopper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like this ship! You know, it's exciting! - Scotty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fall seven times, stand up eight. - Japanese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to look young and thin, hang around old fat people. - Jim Eason]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only those who risk going too far can possibly find out how far one can go. - T.S. Eliot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a rock and roll singer.  -  Adam Ant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome darts t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the darts lovers in your life!   http://t.co/Zvi8wS7iSH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Glowing "Moon In My Room" Wall Decal - Glows! http://t.co/SHSNHa1Hna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the great department store of life, baseball is the toy department. - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dog has lots of friends because he wags his tail and not his tongue. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Play is the only way the highest intelligence of humankind can unfold. - Joseph Chilton Pearce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is the key to unlock the golden door of freedom. - George Washington Carver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...Spinal Tap rocked my world. Its for rock what The Sound of Music was for hills. They really nailed how dumb rock can be. Jack Black]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Tennis – The Sport of Kings  http://t.co/j0c55EkVsE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Tom Petty and the Heartbreakers  http://t.co/rGDQuBCXEq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About How Technology Has Helped Seniors to Make Great Strides in their Lifestyle  http://t.co/suVd1ibNfl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes are the quickest way for women to achieve instant metamorphosis - Manolo Blahnik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The History of Rolex Watches – The Start of Something Great  http://t.co/JQtpVdU277]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was a pretty good coach and working with marketing was like coaching. - Bernard Ebbers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is what we are, and football is what we have become. - Mary McGrory]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love any movie that has a retarded person working at Starbucks.  Chris Kattan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money, if it does not bring you happiness, will at least help you be miserable in comfort. - Helen Gurley Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cooking for Geeks: Real Science, Great Hacks, and Good Food  -&gt; http://t.co/tBh8gVqihA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Try not. Do, or do not. There is no try. - Yoda, The Empire Strikes Back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Small Dogs Can Make Great Pets - Picking the Right Breed  http://t.co/Uv9qMGw82p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Skol Beer  http://t.co/TOP0TrKOkI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ELVIS - The King - One Person's Thoughts  http://t.co/VyV7Pi7RCv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh these are just cool - tiny functional cannons - shoot your co-workers LOL http://t.co/UApkLG38u0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The time for action is now. It's never too late to do something. - Carl Sandburg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Glowing "Moon In My Room" Wall Decal - Glows! http://t.co/SHSNHa1Hna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Guide to Business to Business Internet Marketing on LinkedIn  http://t.co/ynLt1gVlB7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill, strange things are afoot at the Circle K. - Ted, Bill &amp; Ted's Excellent Adventure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Overview of the USSSA Youth Sports Organization  http://t.co/qo3PM62The]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Great Book - The Majestic Tree of Life  http://t.co/S6dW97As3L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A hamburger by any other name costs a lot more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Kiss  http://t.co/vhD0SfBHzx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketing is too important to be left to the marketing department. - David Packard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Linda Ronstadt  http://t.co/lPdJNLzPw6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is nothing so stupid as the educated man if you get him off the thing he was educated in.  - Will Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A twelve-year-old Ben Linus brought me a chicken salad sandwich. How do you think I'm doing? - Sayid Jarrah, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A tax collector has what it takes to take what you got]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Human sacrifice, dogs and cats living together --  mass hysteria! - Dr. Peter Venkman, Ghostbusters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Arthur Lyman -- The Pioneer of "Exotica" Music http://t.co/QfPZ5scRKR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learning Styles - Learn About Teaching so They Can Learn  http://t.co/XBiTHuC4fm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's later than we think and most of us aren't even thinking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hiring Strategy Consulting Firms: The Importance of Competitive Analysis  http://t.co/LmqNVa3GAH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Triple Crown Sports Organization  http://t.co/ccm7ZvhnwW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bird does not sing because it has an answer...  It sings because it has a song. - Chinese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Fun! BANG! Turn it off this Lamp with a gun, and it "plays dead". Then bring it back to life with another shot! http://t.co/9PEGUkF6xw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read an Introduction to Whataburger  http://t.co/fUh3OnnttP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dream house is one that cost twice as much as you ever dreamed it would…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you cease to dream you cease to live - Malcolm Forbes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Life? Cool! Where can I download one of those?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Great Tours of Europe  http://t.co/UPQjsnae5m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Search Engine Optimization (SEO) to Drive Traffic to Your Website  http://t.co/F4P2sbLnBR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do I set a laser printer to stun?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life started getting good when I started making money. Balthazar Getty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft: "You've got questions. We've got dancing paperclips."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My wife is such a terrible cook the police made her register her stove as a deadly weapon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Creative Writing Degree - Why You Should Consider One  http://t.co/NwmSHLKdZ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I led the league in Go get 'em next time." - Bob Uecker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever hear of instant credit? You just add money]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion is what you adopt when you don't know who you are. --&gt; Quentin Crisp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is A SERP exactly?  http://t.co/kMNvDnPwlp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Useful Products to Help Housebreak Your Pet  http://t.co/yI9dx2WIlm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep you can keep your devices charged via solar power - find out here - http://t.co/gDlG2sRHzb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never, never, never, never give up. - Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cross Fit is a growing fitness craze - find out about its history here - http://t.co/uEnBxKVbCv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's behind you doesn't matter. - Enzo Ferrari]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The time has come the Walrus said, To talk of many thing’s Of shoes and ships and sealing-wax of cabbages and kings - Lewis Carroll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then there was the crooked crematory operator who sold the ashes to cannibals as instant people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Youth is when we want to set the world on fire... Middle age is when we hope our children won't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've looked into the eye of this island, and what I saw was beautiful. - John Locke, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one really knows who created Bitcoin - read about the fascinating history of Satoshi Nakamoto... http://t.co/qdhOc8v0mM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I take a dim view of watching my own destruction. - Jack, "Invasion of the Body Snatchers"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Few people SUFFER from egotism. With most of them it's a PLEASURE.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>