<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DebMiller58: Getting ready to welcome 100 #CDNmuni leaders to #ottcity for @FCM_online Board meetings and Advocacy Days!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @UNFCCC: High-Level segment of the @UN Climate Conference #COP22 in Marrakech about to start. Live webcast: https://t.co/Do64K1Vg1O http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ONU_fr: #Marrakech @COP22 Ban Ki-moon: "villes, citoyens, entreprises ont un rôle crucial à jouer pour mobiliser le soutien à l'Accord…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: .@doniveson helps launch the #GlobalCovenantofMayors for Climate &amp; Energy today at #COP22 #CDNmuni]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: FCM delegation en route to @COP22 in Marrakech. Follow their #ClimateChange journey &amp; learn about the #CDNmuni role: https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: FCM scholarships have an impact! Look at these testimonials from past winners and  apply today. https://t.co/5DyY8qyDtp  #C…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JimWatsonOttawa: I'm on-site. No tunnel collapse. Staff are reporting a small construction incident with minor injury to one worker. Gl…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Urban_Adam: "Safe &amp; secure housing provides the foundation for engaging in community." - @MayorMattBrown. #ldnont #cdnmuni. https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: The #GoC is listening to #CDNmuni about investing in quality of life to attract people to Rural Canada- @clarksomerville.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: Our #cdnpse scholarships encourage females in their studies of politics, as well as #CDNmuni involvement. Apply now! https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HillaryClinton: "To all the little girls watching...never doubt that you are valuable and powerful &amp; deserving of every chance &amp; opport…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CBCAlerts: Won't change result, but Hillary Clinton has edged ahead of Donald Trump in popular vote: 59,092,337 votes (47.64%) to 58,96…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CanadianPM: PM Trudeau congratulates Donald J. Trump on his election as the next President of the United States: https://t.co/WpoiRdfhpQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ReseauFCM: L'avenir du logement au Canada | Voyez nos solutions urgentes pour une stratégie nationale sur le logement: https://t.co/Bhj…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @thedailybeast: Van Jones tonight on America's "deeply painful" moment: https://t.co/QO4OE6YpjF #ElectionNight https://t.co/R83JctjRc3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @doniveson: #MoreThanMean tweets video: Great resource on gender to watch in your workplace shared at @womenshelter #BWTG b'fast https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Mayor_Bowman: Today is #AboriginalVeteransDay, a time to pay respect to the courageous Indigenous people who fought on our front lines.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FCM's Women in local gov. scholarships are now open. Apply here https://t.co/qGbgZneWFV #CDNmuni]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: See our toolkit for some of the many ways #CDNmuni leaders are responding to the #TRC’s historic Calls to Action: https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: Get to know some top climate protection leaders in #CDNmuni and contact them to share knowledge. https://t.co/rBmsyCGUQx ht…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: Municipal priorities were front &amp; centre of the fed. fiscal update this week, check out our recap: https://t.co/0GTpmVcKIq…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @doniveson: On the contrary: the City of Edmonton's position is that pollution pricing is key to any robust energy and climate transitio…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: Canada’s Housing Opportunity | See our submission to GoC's consultations toward a Nat'l Housing Strategy. https://t.co/gMXp…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: Interested in working for one of #Ottawa's top employers? For new job postings browse our careers page! https://t.co/FDzmxU…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @carolesaab: Thank you to Ministers @Bill_Morneau and @SohiAmarjeet on a strong plan to grow our economy &amp; improve life for Canadians th…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great news for #CDNmuni https://t.co/p433LZDdkw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ReseauFCM: La FCM est la voix nationale des #munican. Découvrez comment la FCM représente le Canada rural à la table fédérale. https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dal_alderson: .@jyduclos and @colemancountry host indigenous leaders + @FCM_online President @clarksomerville to talk #housing challeng…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: Tomorrow is the last day to apply for our #CDNmuni - #FN Infrastructure Partnership Project on solid waste! Apply: https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: Learn green solutions @CityBrampton uses to retrofit older suburbs in our new article series. https://t.co/d0JqcZ0Fwj #FCM_…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: Phase 2 of federal #infra plan needs safe &amp; affordable housing for all Canadians. https://t.co/6WxA5SUjr1  #CDNmuni https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: Learn why women need a voice in prep. of local econ. development initiatives. Register before Oct 27! https://t.co/IDO6TjQW…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: .@sylvie_goneau second VP of FCM, speaks to finance committee pre-budget consultations on behalf of #CDNmuni. https://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: New PCP Climate Heroes articles profile leaders in climate change. Talk to these heroes to share ideas. https://t.co/8JC2cJ…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LindaJeffrey: #Brampton ready to meet demands of university proposal
https://t.co/q2LwCg0YST]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nicholas_falvo: Brock Carlton: even though 80% of FCM's members have &lt;10K residents, #housing is one of our top priorities. #HoH2016 @b…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @fcm_peigi: A reconciliation reading list: 15 must-read books #cdnmuni https://t.co/M9kAMByzhJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @clarksomerville: Canadian cities push back on plans for infrastructure bank https://t.co/cn5rGrIZEV @FCM_online #cdnmuni]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @carolesaab: Great piece on @FCM_online call for a fix to affordable and social housing crisis. @globeandmail #cdnpoli #cdnmuni  https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ctvwinnipeg: Housing is unaffordable and in need of a $13-billion federal fix: cities: The Federation of Canadian Municipa... https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: Learn why women need a voice in prep. of local econ. development initiatives. Register before Oct 27! https://t.co/IDO6TjQW…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: DYK: Canada's first female mayor  Barbara Hanley was elected today in 1936. https://t.co/vVUFZt4Wlb @sudburydotcom @EqualVo…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: What a historic year for FCM &amp; #CDNmuni! Take a look at some of our many 2016 milestones: https://t.co/B8gtK6xKVz https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SenSanders: There is not a single state where working 40 hours/week at the minimum wage is enough to afford a one-bedroom apartment. Th…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: .@CRTCeng broadband decision: Big win for rural &amp; northern communities. Read our statement: https://t.co/Um2Sbx0BHu #CDNmun…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: Read about once-radical sustainability ideas that are now best practices. https://t.co/Phh5ZSJlDV #FCM_GMF #CDNmuni https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: Canada #150muni network is growing and @melaniejoly invites all #CDNmuni to join. https://t.co/dZOJHsi68j https://t.co/viqE…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @canada150th: Get ready to share what Canada means to you during the @redcouchtour in #2017! #Canada150 https://t.co/z517NexuI6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: Better transit can drive our progress toward truly world-class Canadian cities. @clarksomerville https://t.co/6hk4EsKbI1 #C…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: We’re hiring a Project Manager – Jordan Municipal Support Program (JMSP). Apply by Jan. 2, 2017. https://t.co/TwWnizehYS #C…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FCM_online's how to get started on Brownfield redevelopment webinar is today https://t.co/exwFHeEw4V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: See our toolkit for some of the many ways #CDNmuni leaders are responding to the #TRC’s historic Calls to Action: https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: DYK: 1 in 5 renters spends half their income on housing. https://t.co/6WxA5SCI2r #LetsTalkHousing https://t.co/AjOFktpySW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @luce_lavoie: FCM is proud to be working in partnership with #Canada150 showcasing #CNDmuni and local leaders #muni150 https://t.co/fzqy…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: Looking to upgrade your wastewater plant? See how @cityofcranbrook, BC did it in our new case study: https://t.co/AMUiTPEIc…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @bankofcanada: It’s official! #bankNOTEable Viola Desmond, an icon of Canadian rights and freedoms, will be on new $10 bank note https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_Alex: Join @FCM_online for a free webinar next Wednesday: Getting started with #brownfield redevelopment. @actual_media @FCM_Stepha…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: FCM scholarships have an impact! Look at these testimonials from past winners and  apply today. https://t.co/5DyY8qQeRZ  #C…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: We’re hiring a Manager, Funding (Asset Management Program). Apply by Dec. 12, 2016. Please share! https://t.co/y4Sy3AvyL1 #…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Women_Canada: Does your project play a role in #GenderEquality? Submit your proposal before Dec. 8! Learn more at: https://t.co/9IjhcAt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Dartmouth_Tim: It's an honour to serve as a #canada150 @FCM_online leader especially with @downtownpaul here in HRM @hfxgov https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_Helen: Battleford Agency Tribal Chiefs &amp; City of North Battleford wrap up CEDI workshop - land use, ec-dev &amp; reconciliation https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations Mayor Krantz, such an accomplishment! https://t.co/Bd1477w9Fk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: Join a network of francophone municipal leaders who are revitalizing brownfields Canada-wide: https://t.co/vjVOqxlrwf #FCM_…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CISAL_FCM: "Our objective is to have more women elected to localgovernment, we want 30% representation of women in office" @FCM_online…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CISAL_FCM: Vice President of @FCM_online @JennyGerbasi shares her experience as an elected official with 50 Women Mayors in Colombia @C…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_Brock: Panel starts @SALGA_org Day 3: municipalities and the global agenda. Quote: "Cities (and towns) are an opportunity, not a pr…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: .@clarksomerville to speak at #OGRA2017 on the important role of #CDNmuni. https://t.co/AO7jPboHpf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: Meet PCP member Alain Desjardins, who is turning @Plessisville into a leader in GHG reduction in Quebec. https://t.co/scxgb…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MINJobs: The City of Airdrie is looking for new talents! Check the available positions and apply here: https://t.co/dOnumhLhIt #AB #alb…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#GivingTuesday https://t.co/iDT9Z2rKhP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: Learn how cooperation between #CDNmuni &amp; federal government helps communities weather the effects of #climatechange https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CanadianPM: Canada will provide $112.8M for international aid projects that will benefit several African countries and Haiti: https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: Explore the many innovative ways #CDNmuni are taking the lead to cut greenhouse gas emissions &amp; fight #climatechange https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OttawaCitizen: How Ottawa's newest affordable apartments for the vulnerable only cost $27 a year to heat https://t.co/HSjTubndYO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_Julie: There is nothing normal about violence against women (blog) https://t.co/mVhOwY4aNA via @HPCaImpact]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Urban_Adam: In speaking to the @FCM_online board, @SohiAmarjeet clearly gets it. "Infra enables econ, social and envt prosperity". #ldn…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JennyGerbasi: Infrastructure Minister Sohi speaks to FCM board:  "We are here to build a country" @SohiAmarjeet @FCM_online https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nytimes: Prime Minister Trudeau unexpectedly finds himself dealing with a U.S. president who largely rejects his values https://t.co/zd…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: Big city mayors call for coordinated nation-wide response to opioid crisis. @PnPCBC @nenshi #CDNmuni https://t.co/4MBSBThaXL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @carolesaab: Big-city mayors call on Ottawa, provinces to help tackle opioid crisis- @globeandmail #cdnpoli @FCM_online #CDNmuni  https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MayorGregor: Cities are at a breaking point with #fentanyl opioid crisis. We need Prov/Fed support with health solutions #vanpoli https…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: Opioid crisis: Mayors launch task force, engage federal ministers. https://t.co/iqjOBUxUAa #CDNmuni #cdnpoli https://t.co/u…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CBCPolitics: New Canadians to pledge honour for Indigenous treaties in new citizenship oath https://t.co/lceQ4MHABi #hw #cdnpoli https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @H_Castleden: Thanks @FCM_online for opportunity to join great webinar on promising practice for engaging stakeholders and rights-holder…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: Inclusive communities at home &amp; abroad? Let’s talk about it now more than ever: Register: https://t.co/g0AeXxfiZs @CanadaDe…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NavdeepSBains: As always, a pleasure to meet with @MikeSavageHFX to discuss ways we can work together to grow the economy in #Halifax h…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SohiAmarjeet: Pleased to join @FCM_online to announce 2 new funds to help address climate change and strengthen infra planning https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_Brock: FCM Prez @clarksomerville and Minister @SohiAmarjeet  announce 2 new programs to support #CDNmuni" https://t.co/pbznD9EPe8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great News for #CDNmuni ! https://t.co/AgFeUhFyd3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_Alex: #Cities provide hope and concrete action in the fight against #climatechange. Get inspired here: https://t.co/Ya02h8zNKH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AlexMunter_: “There can be no keener revelation of a society's soul than the way in which it treats its children.” - Nelson Mandela htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @greg_tedesco: #HamOnt's social housing waitlist back up over 6k households. We have a collective obligation to do better. #AffordableHo…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_Ariel: Mayors in the US and Canada are leading the way in creating welcoming communities for immigrants and refugees. This is polit…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: Big-city mayors reach out to newcomers and refugees. https://t.co/QkaXPba7S0 #CDNmuni]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Justin_Ling: These are the six who lost their lives last night. #jesuisquebec https://t.co/JqLMNW3kbQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_Brock: join us for #reducepovery2017 webinar with @doniveson &amp; @FredEisenberger tomorrow. https://t.co/OnhwrusPpx @Tamarack_Inst @V…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RickHansenFdn: Could your city be the most accessible in Canada? Apply for our Accessible Cities Award at https://t.co/MYaZ9edmAV. http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FCM_online: FCM is the national voice of #CDNmuni. Read about how FCM is bringing Canada’s rural voice to the federal table https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JustinTrudeau: #ACanadianIsACanadian https://t.co/6cqitwZJhE]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>