<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator: Req ID : 407091BR Job Code/Title : E1993:Systems Administrator Sr Job Description : This Enterprise Business Services (EBS) position supports the Space Systems Company (SSC) located at the Lockheed Martin Sunnyvale, CA facility.… https://t.co/d1XostXon4 https://t.co/HtAtjdEfIg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineering Manager – Syracuse, NY: Req ID : 437046BR Job Code/Title : L1075:Software Engineering Mgr Job Description : At Lockheed Martin Rotary &amp; Mission Systems, we are driven by innovation and integrity. We believe that by applying the… https://t.co/9wn2oOsg8s https://t.co/TBpr8y9s2w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Engineer: Data Engineer – Capital One Services II LLC in Chicago Metro Area; Multiple positions available: Perform technological design, development, modification, &amp; implementation of software &amp;/or data apps using existing &amp; emerging tech platforms.… https://t.co/GykW8HR0uE https://t.co/D1EXs1kFPr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developers: Software Developers Attune Global Inc. Coppell, TX Attune Global Inc., seeks Software Developers for analysis, design, and development of software applications using various software languages and tools. Job Location: Coppell, TX and… https://t.co/eMrWdvUHdD https://t.co/yw7XCV6PdV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Implementation Business Analyst: Implementation Business Analyst, Willis Towers Watson Job #******M8, South Jordan, UT Menu ToggleMenu Hide – Glassdoor – Linkedin – Twitter – Facebook – English – Espaol – Franais (FR) – Franais (CA) – Join Our Talent… https://t.co/VDAAL3zCW8 https://t.co/04YtNipf9w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior DevOps Engineer: Location San Jose – CA, US Level Bachelor Experience 5-10 Experienced Available since 5/9/2018 Functional area Background Reference req2879 Introduction ASML brings together the most creative minds in science and technology to… https://t.co/9AOkBXKFs8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Security Administrator: SAP Security Administrator for Sacramento Municipal Utility District (SMUD), Sacramento, CA. Configure and support SAP Security applications. Req. B.S. in CS, MIS, or closely related &amp; 3 yrs. exp. incl. SAP Security design,… https://t.co/S5z6SHZOuY https://t.co/TiYd3sTvXB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Web Service Developer: MetroStar Systems Careers ========================= Java Web Service Developer Web Development Suitland, Maryland MetroStar Systems is seeking an Java Web Service Developer who is responsible for the web services design and… https://t.co/hoG7apfuCw https://t.co/bveAF9XqKy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Account Strategist: Account Strategist (Multiple Positions); Mountain View/Palo Alto/ San Bruno, CA; Perform market research and technical analysis in connection with growing Google products and services. #JUN2018MVSBPA -AS Exp Incl: web… https://t.co/erTQK13pSx https://t.co/fHDEaTN0jy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Siri UI Web Developer: DESCRIPTION: Changing the world is all in a day’s work at Apple. If you love innovation, here’s your chance to make a career of it. You’ll work hard. But the job comes with more than a few perks. Are you looking for an exciting… https://t.co/DJ6Af2JpQk https://t.co/iu0IxC5Qss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exercise Project Manager: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Honolulu, HI Job Type: Management Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/1/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management and… https://t.co/G33KLAuw33]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior DevOps Engineer-Data/DBA: Job ID 2018-3652 Location US-CA-San Jose Category Network Operations About the Job Senior Devops Engineer Come join us and be part of our team as a Senior DevOps Engineer – Data/DBA focused on Kubernetes. 88 is in process… https://t.co/wNzw0HrjFK https://t.co/K9ZEH9mSuP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Planning Data Analyst: Under direction of the Director, Planning or designee, perform a wide variety of duties including analysis of volume, operational and business assumptions in identifying and assessing new business opportunities for the System… https://t.co/EuA0xIUMSw https://t.co/geGN7uv9aT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Program/Project Manager Military Health Systems TMIP-J: GDIT has openings for Project Management Professionals for the support and maintenance of the Joint Theatre Medical Information Program (TMIP-J) and the JOMIS (JATS &amp; DHRES) Program Office.… https://t.co/raZtzLDePm https://t.co/stTYG7CsHW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer- Army Software: San Diego California : California Job Summary: General Atomics Aeronautical Systems, Inc. (GA-ASI), an affiliate of General Atomics, is a world leader in proven, reliable remotely piloted aircraft and tactical… https://t.co/hitmiWmORo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consultant: AVIATION The Boeing Company in Seal Beach, CA seeks Authorized Representative to conduct compliance findings against structural repairs on the 777 aircraft fuselage components. Position req MS degree (or foreign equiv) in Engineering, or… https://t.co/iaITRpbdzz https://t.co/MDIQ74cQ0o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Programmer Analyst: Sr. Programmer Analyst Bachelor of Science degree in Computer Science, or Electrical &amp; Communication Engineering &amp; 5 years’ of experience: Plan &amp; coordinate programming, testing &amp; document of statistic, program; Generate tables,… https://t.co/L6iNX68Xff https://t.co/QqroScgH1q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NOC Technician II/III: BlueSky Resource Solutions is seeking a NOC Technician in the Denver, Colorado area for immediate hire. This position requires being able to work multiple shifts. The ideal candidate has: – Experience monitoring, troubleshooting,… https://t.co/Qs38crWKXE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: DevOps Engineer Ref No.: 18-26262 Location: Bentonville, Arkansas Requirements: – Supporting and monitoring a 24/7 high-quality video streaming service in a fast paced startup-like environment. – Participation in oncall rotation,… https://t.co/7jPY4DLB1t https://t.co/GsAUtFTTlc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Management Analyst &amp; OPS Research Job: Date: Apr 5, 2018 Location:Springfield, VA, US Company: SAIC Senior Project Management Analyst &amp; OPS Research (Job Number:427447) Description: JOB DESCRIPTION: – Participate in NGA and NSG studies and… https://t.co/fbIq36SXB2 https://t.co/PIqbAGSTQU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supply Chain Quality Manager: Req ID : 433129BR Job Code/Title : L1584:QA Engineering Asc Mgr Job Description : The Supply Chain Quality (SCQ) Requirements Manager will operate out of the Denver or Sunnyvale campus and will report to the SCQ Engineering… https://t.co/Egs3mKQvQX https://t.co/fzi2gyu2vw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Software Engineer: Java Software Engineer (Austin, TX) Responsible for developing applications in support of the company’s web collaboration networks and video conferencing tools. recblid 7neojfa4i7gx9kgdr3f2se7xr11xoj https://t.co/8ZIwhjZ97A https://t.co/D75SFFzJ7W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Development Loan Officer: Business Development Loan Officer The Economic Development Corporation of Kansas City, MO is seeking a qualified individual for the position of Business Development Loan Officer. Economic Development Corporation manages… https://t.co/rDtKqlPJFl https://t.co/PVFTyCrwlx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer, Applications: SOFTWARE DEVELOPER, APPLICATIONS needed for Garretson Resolution Group, Charlotte, NC. Engage in analysis, design and development of .Net based applications. Will perform services as a full stack developer and engage in… https://t.co/Z7rhHuhOOp https://t.co/Or8CxOcCO6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MTS Software Engineer – GPU Developer Technology Game Engineer: Job Description What you do at AMD changes everything At AMD, we push the boundaries of what is possible. We believe in changing the world for the better by driving innovation in… https://t.co/jvykL5VGRj https://t.co/FAqL9ZTZ5K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Security Principal Systems Administrator – TS/SCI – National Capitol Region: Requisition ID 2018-41767 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Top Secret/SCI with Polygraph Full/Part Time Full Time Job… https://t.co/nhC75iA8vE https://t.co/uPGdr2OmPP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Civil Engineer Sr. Project Manager: Careers Center | Civil Engineer – Sr. Project Manager Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for… https://t.co/zvXsud2Z7C https://t.co/sjXnQwevy5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[E-Learning Technical Developer: Salary: DOE Industry: Footwear &amp; Apparel What Matters Most: – A minimum of 5 years of experience in instructional design, e-learning, and training facilitation on a global system implementation project required –… https://t.co/rqL893a9iV https://t.co/BMzN3RjwFt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embedded Software Engineer: Plano, TX Full-time $130k – $150k Posted Today If you are an Embedded Software Engineer with experience, please read on! Based in beautiful Allen, TX, we are the world’s leading manufacturer of law enforcement video systems,… https://t.co/bZkY3pXzcS https://t.co/RbgYfwqbIO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist (TS/SCI Required): An analytics and data solutions company that delivers customized solutions to clients, is seeking a qualified Data Scientist with TS/SCI clearance to join their growing team. The Data Scientist will be responsible for… https://t.co/NVkFgJ242s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Administrator: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Panama City, FL Job Type: Engineering, Information Technology Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 5/24/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’… https://t.co/7nRl8e506e https://t.co/6Vi8JntWoW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. QA Engineer: Sr. QA Engineer Pasadena, California – United States Job Start Date – 06/25/18, Posted Date – 06/12/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview Complete Description: Senior Quality Assurance Engineer needed for the functional and automation… https://t.co/maMs2ZGc5e https://t.co/2M9avwPAwM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Company profile We like it when our employees have goals. What about you? Are you ready to grow with your challenges? We at MAHLE are a leading international supplier to the automotive industry. With our products for combustion engines… https://t.co/1jKgMfOdUg https://t.co/a9h6XfkaIl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mobile Developer: Assembly is a talent management agency located in the RiNo area of Denver. We’re a team of designers (and developers) ourselves, and we’re able to match you with projects youll be proud to work on and clients youll enjoy working with.… https://t.co/TZ4l1cWkA4 https://t.co/XXG9M3bNhT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, Performance Optimization (Embedded, H/W): As a Performance Optimization Software Engineer, you will be helping to ensure that our platform runs efficiently on a variety of modern hardware platforms. This includes implementing our core… https://t.co/IGdinekf9o https://t.co/cZ2BlwpF1e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator w/Poly: 1. Manages the functionality and efficiency of a group of computers running on one or more operating systems. 2. Maintains the integrity and security of servers and systems. 3. Sets up administrator and service accounts. 4.… https://t.co/BMZWHgBKFl https://t.co/thYLXXZYDH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Geological Geophysical Application Developer: Salary/Rate N/A Permanent Location Houston, TX Texas, US, United States Posted By Chevron Date Posted 33 minutes ago Expires 22 Jun 2018 Qualifications None Geological &amp; Geophysical Application Developer in… https://t.co/JnTdjxl7aU https://t.co/HSgv7ND99D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems/Software Requirements Analyst, Mid: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Rockville, MD Job Type: Strategy – Planning Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 5/29/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’… https://t.co/WRj639ASor https://t.co/w9t3LMLbMB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Web Developer: .NET Web Developer in Washington, DC | CACI International – Small Business | – Suppliers – About Us – | – What We Do – | – Media &amp; Events – | – Investors – | – Careers – | – Contracts – | – Contact Us Join Our Talent Network – About… https://t.co/xoP5rXxFY0 https://t.co/jICfIUGdpT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Enterprise Database Administrator – Federal Clients: Our Cerner Technology Services has an exciting opportunity for a Sr. MYSQL Database Administrator s. Our Sr. Enterprise Database Administrator s install, upgrade, and configure database… https://t.co/zjcvvY8W5o https://t.co/cMJjkBXVUw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Information Systems Security Analyst 2:   Job Description – Cyber Information Systems Security Analyst 2 (18008623) Cyber Information Systems Security Analyst 2 Requisition ID : 18008623 Location : United States-Colorado-Boulder US Citizenship… https://t.co/Q0ijXqL0LM https://t.co/S6H9H5m1ky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embedded System Engineer – PACCAR Embedded Engineering: Embedded System Engineer – PACCAR Embedded Engineering 8543 Job – Why Work For Us – Get to Know PACCAR – A Great Place to Work – Equal Opportunity Employer – Job Opportunities – Engineering Jobs –… https://t.co/kohMdtVgCF https://t.co/jTgmwHukux]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior UI Engineer: Careers GridMaven, Inc. GridMaven, Inc. Leaders in Converged Grid &amp; Network Management – Home – Solutions – Resources – News and Events – About Us – Contact Us Careers To apply for one of the positions listed below, please send your… https://t.co/R6Ae2rHA2g https://t.co/AVbOVc6uXh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales Operations Analyst: SunIRef:Sales:title Sales Operations Analyst Cisco Meraki 8 reviews – San Francisco, CA 94158 Cisco Meraki knows that technology can connect us, empower us, and drive us. By simplifying powerful technology, we can free… https://t.co/pKH2b4WoRt https://t.co/RtDpABrxmG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staff Software Engineer Foster City, CA: Guidewire’s development team is looking for a proactive, and results-oriented Staff Software Engineer to build elegant solutions for the property &amp; casualty insurance industry’s complex business domain and make… https://t.co/jwxxVu1uJl https://t.co/Xuo3EJke2n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Software Engineer: For Johnson &amp; Johnson Full Stack Software Engineer job – Engineering (IT) – Portland, Oregon Skip to Main Content Our Stories – Latest News – Innovation – Caring &amp; Giving – Personal Stories – Health &amp; Wellness – Our Heritage… https://t.co/Om9OEJC8DU https://t.co/DJUfTjRnP6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Systems Engineer – DevOps, OpenStack: Location US-NC-Raleigh Posting date 4 hours ago(6/28/2018 4:44 AM) Job ID 63734 Category Information Technology Company description At Red Hat, we connect an innovative community of customers, partners, and… https://t.co/8CFI29MG4o https://t.co/GEl2RG8P6X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support: Technical Support GENERAL SUMMARY: Provides assistance and support to company personnel in use of computer equipment and software. Responsible for assisting and supporting personnel by troubleshooting system problems (including… https://t.co/LBPSzkB4M3 https://t.co/02yzYfB3TF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big Data Engineer – Scala, Hadoop, Spark: Milwaukee, WI Full-time $130k – $175k Posted Today If you are a Big Data Engineer with Scala, Hadoop and Spark experience, we would like to hear from you! We are an engineering services company working with… https://t.co/9rIGAmdQbi https://t.co/Cj1PvUgfGE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior Database Administrator/Analyst: Requisition ID 2018-42144 # of Openings 0 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level None Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description Junior Database Administrator Analyst We are seeking a highly… https://t.co/yB9CtAAPyC https://t.co/YKiaVuhKp3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Java Developer: Overview ‘US Citizens and all those authorized to work in the US are encouraged to apply’ ‘No third party candidates considered for this position’ Minimum of 8 years of progressive experience in the following A. Java/JEE, Spring MVC,… https://t.co/kjxNYeUZ0O https://t.co/fsdEXO48Y5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer (MuleSoft): Psyncopate, Inc. in Brea CA, is seeking Developer (MuleSoft) to design, develop, and deploy reusable API’s for the MuleSoft Anypoint platform. No trvl or telecomm. Job duties are proj-based @ unanticipated sites w/in U.S. Relo may… https://t.co/swDsC19bkO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Manager, Analytics and Data Insights: Senior Manager, Analytics and Data Insights https://t.co/ZyW6VLvHFR, Inc. seeks Senior Manager, Analytics and Data Insights in Chicago, IL: Analyze data hands on, understand biz. Functions &amp; generate data… https://t.co/9uiid6vvIw https://t.co/VbYf49i0XI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Advisor, Product Management: Data Domain, LLC (a Dell Technologies Company) is seeking a Senior Advisor, Product Management at our Santa Clara, CA facility to provide input into the formulation of strategic business plans for a product or a line… https://t.co/LO6yYInAQD https://t.co/C16H2DfGuA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Customer Support Specialist / Technical Writer: Innovative Systems provides fundraising software products for Universities and NonProfits. We are seeking an experienced Customer Support Specialist / Technical Writer to join the fundraising software team.… https://t.co/nWRxUASLJE https://t.co/exLTPiBMK2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PGIM Fixed Income Operations – Trade Operations Analyst, Derivatives Futures Confirmations: About the position Opportunity Awaits Are you looking to grow your career within operations and deepen your understanding of financial services products under the… https://t.co/cobZnLp81R https://t.co/UDNMgfz7zb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer SSP Data Management System: Job Description BAE Systems is looking for an experienced Software Engineer to support maintenance and development of web-based applications. The candidate must be able to support the software development… https://t.co/CHr61akb9B https://t.co/QLYjA86HGK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Semiconductor Tech Support Engineer, 2nd Line: Location Hillsboro – OR, US Level Bachelor Experience 2-5 Professional Available since 4/26/2018 Functional area Electrical Engineering, Mechanical Engineering, System Engineering Background Mechanics,… https://t.co/0BqXFYASae https://t.co/FXYhOZRiCC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Developer / Engineer: IT Developer / Engineer Location: Herndon, VA Job Code: 3452 # of openings: 1 Description Bay State Computers, Inc. is a professional services firm and a leading provider of Information Technology (IT) services and products to… https://t.co/Xtr0aUtifE https://t.co/iUWBYLPUim]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Developer: Job TitleApplication Developer – ID:32112 Duration12 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsWeb Developing, Silverlight, MVC5 LocationDenver, CO Date Posted07/12/2018 Our client is looking for an Application Developer to join their team… https://t.co/lCnz0rrOwT https://t.co/o1bR050ewg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior Python Developer: Search and apply for jobs at Piper Companies | Careers at Piper Companies Careers Search Jobs Connect With Us Junior Python Developer Job Attributes Job Id: 19428Job Category: Clinical &amp; Life SciencesJob Location: Research… https://t.co/2t6WRQZCpH https://t.co/wItYKMcqXZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering Product Management: Data Domain, LLC (a Dell Technologies Company) is seeking a Senior Advisor, Product Management at our Santa Clara, CA facility to provide input into the formulation of strategic business plans for a product or a line of… https://t.co/V8lzbOU82y https://t.co/wHIJkIEFIa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Software Engineer: Data Domain LLC (a Dell Technologies company) is seeking a Sr Software Engineer Specialist at our Santa Clara, CA facility to provide technical expertise by independently determining and developing approaches for solutions to a wide… https://t.co/XcCDMWOL9s https://t.co/9l5tpQmv9l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Operations Analyst: – Analyzes current and proposed policies, procedures, systems, forms and reports for the department. – Analyzes existing processes and procedures to recommend operational improvement through standardization, simplification,… https://t.co/gHjKgtBgmo https://t.co/lMVBUQ6XcY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test Manager: Test Manager Ref No.: 18-28116 Location: wilton, Connecticut Hope doing well!! Enterprise Solution Inc. is currently looking to fill urgent Full-time permanent job position Test Manager our client based in Wilton, CT location. If you are… https://t.co/OBzdDiTmdL https://t.co/47ideqpCmM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Architect: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Herndon, VA Job Type: Design, Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 7/4/2018 Job Description Job Number: R******* DevOps Architect Key Role: Design, implement, and lead adoption… https://t.co/nx9OPVnHbl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UI Developer, Security Products Group NSX: UI Developer, Security Products Group – NSX job description at VMware Skip Navigation MENU VMware Search Jobs – MENU – Home – Life at VMWare – Careers – Sales – Engineering &amp; Technology – University &amp; Recent… https://t.co/3LtwuW53M3 https://t.co/ePasiBTSBN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[User Experience Designer: Cerner s UX team is looking for a User Experience Designer with strong experience design chops to join them. In this role you ll be responsible for understanding the vision of Cerner domains and using this knowledge to… https://t.co/IOHMA44bXt https://t.co/M7upgsRenA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Principal Scientist: SENIOR PRINCIPAL SCIENTIST (Morrisville, NC) Liquidia has an immediate opening for a Senior Principal Scientist. Ph.D. and exp in polymer chemistry/materials science, precision analytical technology, and development of thin… https://t.co/DWkMDK7xZ4 https://t.co/GoPpejFXJb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Support Analyst: Support Analyst Beverly, MA 6 months CTH Skills Required : * Proficient in Microsoft Desktop Technologies including Windows 7, Windows 8.x, Windows 10, Office 20XX * Experience with desktop/laptop/Citrix/Active Directory environments *… https://t.co/gZFjcdn85p https://t.co/O4wEzBqkKk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager II: As a Project Manager II, you will manage the cost, quality, and schedule of wireless infrastructure projects for new site builds and for modifications to existing facilities. This involves preparing the scope of work, pricing,… https://t.co/2Hfuff9i3K https://t.co/HXPT02dup0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Salesforce Developer: Senior Salesforce Developer in Orlando, Florida, United States | Management Consulting at Deloitte Toggle menu – Deloitte home – About Deloitte – – Location: United States Available in locations and languages – Students –… https://t.co/NiD39BzWz4 https://t.co/QhdXDpZ4wE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Testing: Application Testing Ref No.: 18-29086 Location: Tampa, Florida Key skills required for the job are: Application Testing-L3 (Mandatory) Test Automation-L3 (Alternate)As a Lead, you are responsible for managing a small team of… https://t.co/DMXWastbd8 https://t.co/Zzllhgy9sj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering Manager 2:   Job Description – Engineering Manager 2 (18014321) Engineering Manager 2 Requisition ID : 18014321 Location : United States-Virginia-McLean US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation Assistance: No relocation… https://t.co/uVWieu43dY https://t.co/lHnIkOJsV4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETL Analyst – Clarity Caboodle ETL Developer/Administrator: ETL Analyst – Clarity &amp; Caboodle ETL Developer/Administrator (46871) Job Type: Full Time FTE/Bi-Weekly Hours: 1.0/80 Shift: Days Hours in Shift: 8 Location: Palo Alto, CA Req: 46871 Job… https://t.co/OnNJbHGVHn https://t.co/CBETM0chbd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Requisition ID 2018-42700 # of Openings 1 Job Function Program Management Security Clearance Level None Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description General Dynamics Information Technology (GDIT) has an immediate opportunity for a Project… https://t.co/xgOS91zcZI https://t.co/obZaa7QQhw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OPS Functional Specialist: Requisition ID 2018-42256 # of Openings 1 Job Function Program Management Security Clearance Level Secret Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description Serves as Functional Analyst to the Office of the Deputy Assistant Secretary of… https://t.co/ZsUCyYSX5j https://t.co/7Wrj53LdFh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SENIOR Mainframe Programmer (COBOL / CICS): Job Openings – – Home – About Trigyn – Company Profile – Corporate Governance – Board of Directors – Executive Team – Partnerships &amp; Alliances – News &amp; Events – Quality Policy – Diversity – Performance Ratings… https://t.co/f1NpNmX1U9 https://t.co/rh3rtpyYpz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer Intern (Summer: Software Engineer Intern (Summer 2018) Jobs Description at Cox Enterprises Skip to main content Careers Home Our People Locations Join Our Talent Community Blog Manage Your Profile Cox Enterprises Cox Communications Cox… https://t.co/7YePoC83Me https://t.co/JYHyzfWJIa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Administrator TS/SCI required: 1. Participates in the analysis, administration and maintenance of voice, video, and/or data communications networks. 2. Assists in managing the usage and performance of voice, video and/or data communications… https://t.co/Y4Fb8mbHvj https://t.co/NuZoyAtwMv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering Strategic Design Consultant: Strategic Design Consultant for SAP Labs, LLC (Palo Alto, CA) work in a dedicated project team which supports other multidisciplinary teams in a particular project area that involves analysis &amp; investigation of… https://t.co/lCw0ksX4O0 https://t.co/cBTObsWAuA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer: TECHNOLOGY Interested candidates send resume to: Waymo LLC, PO Box 26184 San Francisco, CA 94126 Attn: V. Murphy. Please reference job # below: Hardware Engineer (Mountain View, CA) Design, develop, &amp;/or test hardware needed for various Waymo… https://t.co/Y1xbEsqcvY https://t.co/jbZqMuLd58]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NC Programmer: NC Programmer Job in US – KY – Wilder for Precision Castparts Corp. | Production – Manufacturing NC Programmer US – KY – Wilder Search Other Jobs search again Job Attributes Job Id 17013 Req. Id 2 Req. Code PCC-US.****** Category… https://t.co/5ynDkC8LCj https://t.co/T0eGMMFsBl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: . Please contact ******************** if you need further instruction on how to do that. Senior Software Engineer Technology | Washington, DC | Full Time Job Description Senior Software Engineer Asurity Technologies Asurity… https://t.co/BfDipPTGjj https://t.co/SznMQDbvko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solutions Architect: Job Description Transforming the future of healthcare isn’t something we take lightly. It takes teams of the best and the brightest, working together to make an impact. As one of the largest healthcare technology companies in the… https://t.co/LEw42wVhgr https://t.co/ARo0zBzfpz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Applications Developer: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Chantilly, VA Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/25/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management and… https://t.co/cuAAPpqxJb https://t.co/Qepqnh5voP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front End .NET Developer: Buffalo Grove, IL Full-time $90k – $110k Posted Today If you are a Front End Developer with experience, please read on! Based in Buffalo Grove, IL we are an ever growing financial company. Our company cares about our employees… https://t.co/k09Aza4YnZ https://t.co/ZMaMHfRh6V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Principal Operations Analyst / Russian Linguist – TS/SCI – Quantico, VA: Requisition ID 2018-42008 # of Openings 1 Job Function Program Management Security Clearance Level Top Secret/SCI Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description Provides military… https://t.co/IazIfFKah3 https://t.co/c4vq1Vwrbl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Infrastructure Operations Analyst – VMware: TECHNOLOGY SERVICES GROUP (TSG) is the central infrastructure services group with a proven track record of innovating to help BNY Mellon and its customers have the most reliable, nimble and… https://t.co/5TRfZsPGYU https://t.co/55jC4gCW1G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Careers Center | Software Developer Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome page Returning… https://t.co/YC60uPeQc8 https://t.co/6RjOFymeKb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Senior Software Engineer Jobs Description at Cox Enterprises Skip to main content Careers Home Our People Locations Join Our Talent Community Blog Manage Your Profile Cox Enterprises Cox Communications Cox Automotive Cox Media… https://t.co/cao7yvaKdS https://t.co/cAjCJ5SsIY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer-Principal: **Software Engineer-Principal** Locations:Cypress, California Job Family: Research &amp; Development New Search Apply English (US) **Job Description** **Division:** Digital Factory **Business Unit:** Product Lifecycle… https://t.co/oRclbOCmh6 https://t.co/aArekKm2gY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embedded Software Engineer II LabVIEW: Applicant Home Job Description – Ball Corporation Job Title: Embedded Software Engineer II – LabVIEW (******) Job ID: ****** Location: CO – Boulder Full/Part Time: Full-Time Regular/Temporary: Regular Return to Page… https://t.co/5J0IW68x7Q https://t.co/SVMfXU4Cam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warehouse Management Business Systems Analyst: Albertsons-Safeway Company is one of the largest food and drug retailers with 2,300+ stores. The Albertsons-Safeway family of brands includes some of the most prominent brands in food retailing, with a… https://t.co/bGZmwDp56Y https://t.co/YmZpSbN02X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C Software Engineer: POSITION OVERVIEW: We are looking for a knowledgeable C Software Developer to write and maintain various interfaces in our clients system. Do you enjoy creating procedures, enhancing applications and have a passion for law… https://t.co/bx5NVtZIdr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Data Analyst: Job Title: Sr Data Analyst – ENG****** Description Merck &amp; Co., Inc. Kenilworth, N.J., U.S.A. known as Merck in the United States and Canada, is a global health care leader with a diversified portfolio of prescription medicines, vaccines… https://t.co/brdniOpK4i https://t.co/m59wwdPgaS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer I: Applicant Home Job Description – Ball Corporation Job Title: Software Engineer I – (******) Job ID: ****** Location: OH – Dayton (Fairborn) Full/Part Time: Full-Time Regular/Temporary: Regular Return to Page Who We Are: Ball… https://t.co/h4d4RE703F https://t.co/eHYV0rjj67]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Software Engineer: Principal Software Engineer Who you are You are a full-stack SOA engineer / generalist. Experience and (just as important) interest in working in a variety of layers and technologies within a SOA is a must for our team. This… https://t.co/HxvX47fI2l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solutions Director – End User Solutions Job: Solutions Director – End User Solutions (Job Number:437353) Description: SAIC is seeking a Solutions Director – End User Solutions. Note: This position allows for 100% telecommute as long as the candidate sits… https://t.co/Z3f5xzDiit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TECHNICAL LEADER SOFTWARE ENGINEERING: Cisco is the worldwide leader in networking that transforms how people connect, communicate, and collaborate. Since 1984, Cisco has led in the innovation of IP-based networking technologies such as routing,… https://t.co/zu46nU8Q8x https://t.co/zJ7qVpxddC]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>