<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Three Styles of BMX Bikes and their Uses  http://t.co/5DGVwtjSSN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Modern Glo Night Light - Night Light Fashion!  http://t.co/YydWQlLMPJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet - very cool mechanical pin clock - very unique - http://t.co/HEevEklBKL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd make a wonderful Lady Macbeth. I'll wear a pair of platform shoes or something - Bette Midler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Power of Solar Power - Get Plugged In!  http://t.co/Xtsy9fecbS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Journey  http://t.co/Ysiver10t2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Julie London  http://t.co/3s9a8BfDa0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can say any foolish thing to a dog, &amp; the dog will give a look that says, My God youre right I never wouldve thought of that! Dave Barry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Building an Effective Company Blog  http://t.co/W581i8vmep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am not a glutton - I am an explorer of food. - Erma Bombeck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greater your capacity to love, the greater your capacity to feel the pain.  Jennifer Aniston]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Use Twitter in Business  http://t.co/Hdsr5kobds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the dressing room, I always put on my right shoe first. Same thing for my right wristband. -  Mary Lou Retton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Miss Toni Fisher  http://t.co/pqTGAqqRuL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new source of power is not money in the hands of a few, but information in the hands of many. - John Naisbitt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You see things; and you say "Why?" But I dream things that never were; and I say "Why not?" - George Bernard Shaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion is what you're offered four times a year by designers. And style is what you choose. - Lauren Hutton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To the uneducated, an A is just three sticks. - A. A. Milne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not a marketing person. I don't ask myself questions. I go by instinct. - Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To confine our attention to terrestrial matters would be to limit the human spirit. - Stephen Hawking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laverne and Shirley is an American sitcom classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/0WJaGaG3Cr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Overview of Major Web Conferencing Services  http://t.co/0jEmCGcvpl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Hiring a Strategy Consulting Firm  http://t.co/2sjdfuq5Z4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Barbara Acklin – “Love Makes a Woman”  http://t.co/9wFYXlHH2y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I started out writing much more science fictiony stuff and writing about science fiction. - Neil Gaiman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Music of Hot Chocolate  http://t.co/pkG4j5OKU4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two sides: One is light, one is dark." -- John Locke, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great History of Johnny Ace: A ‘One of his Kind’ Musical Legend  http://t.co/eUQNb8Zb2s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Janis Joplin  http://t.co/4O3eEBXDeQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fish Hotel Aquarium - Jazz Up Your Office! http://t.co/mA44sVn2e9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Don McLean  http://t.co/mPv6cwIqc8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Robin Trower  http://t.co/kF6AeDz8Qc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding good players is easy. Getting them to play as a team is another story. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You could get rich manufacturing crutches for lame excuses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of White Castle  http://t.co/bW7VhIbOaL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Left Banke  http://t.co/CtReTlwR3Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About DotNetNuke for Corporations  http://t.co/goMU68FTbX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Review of the Book Eragon  http://t.co/YhUI47EEYq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No change in musical style will survive unless it is accompanied by a change in clothing style. Rock is to dress up to.  - Frank Zappa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Interesting History of Dos XX Beer  http://t.co/iO9vB0Y84Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting Overview of Top 10 International Beers  http://t.co/GC2ZSNP18O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You Have Never Seen Knives Like These - They Interlock with in each other - stylish and modern! http://t.co/IKFBKH5fjd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I'm going dancing, then I wear the highest heels with the shortest dress. - Kate Moss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give a girl the correct footwear and she can conquer the world. - Bette Midler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think the rock'n'roll myth of living on the edge is a pile of crap. - Robert Smith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hiring Strategy Consulting Firms: The Importance of Competitive Analysis  http://t.co/z1Cnpd1vB7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome disco t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the disco lovers in your life!   http://t.co/TU3wlKOqPO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Top 10 Burger Chains in the US  http://t.co/itpZ9AWnuK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no room in baseball for discrimination. It is our national pastime and a game for all. - Lou Gehrig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sign on a barber shop window --  Home haircuts repaired  $20.00]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Willie Mays' glove is where triples go to die. - Jim Murray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only way around is through. - Robert Frost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am for conversations.  But you need to have a message.  Rennee Blodgett - President Blodgett Communications]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clarity trumps persuasion.  Dr. Flint McGlaughlin - Director MECLABS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I get to go to a lot of overseas places, like Canada.  Britney Spears]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would give a million bucks to have seen my mother say "cute shoes" to a naked Ashley Judd. --&gt; Brian Fies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ELVIS - The King - One Person's Thoughts  http://t.co/zoJTQo2M9V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[High heels are pride and privilege, the passkey to decadence. - Karen Heller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would give a million bucks to have seen my mother say "cute shoes" to a naked Ashley Judd. --&gt; Brian Fies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Little Richard  http://t.co/gccaewys8D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About GPS Technology and Fitness Watches  http://t.co/KDqZWRIjf2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep your face to the sunshine and you cannot see the shadows. - Helen Keller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spock. This child is about to wipe out every living thing on Earth. Now, what do you suggest we do? spank it? - Dr. McCoy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our greatest weakness lies in giving up. The most certain way to succeed is always to try just one more time. - Thomas A. Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dream house is one that cost twice as much as you ever dreamed it would…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Increasingly, search is our mechanism for how we understand ourselves our world, and our place with in it.  John Battelle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Isley Brothers  http://t.co/5yA6jByGUt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Paul Evans the Classic Rock Artist?  http://t.co/8SXcEbgj45]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm on a 90-day wonder diet. Thus far, I've lost 45 days. - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read How to Use LinkedIn for Your Company   http://t.co/dUybjIg1DB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read The Story of Traffic the Classic Rock Group http://t.co/ar5e4HD27a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hold fast to dreams, for if dreams die, life is a broken winged bird that cannot fly. - Langston Hughes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Cool History of Mustard  http://t.co/C9uwKKXuA0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the The Burning Bridge by John Flanagan  http://t.co/Abd5ksFeLw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating history of Wrigley Field!  http://t.co/KCyfvuFt4p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Remote Control Inflatable Flying Shark! AWESOME! http://t.co/jHgHGnBNgE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome gardening t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the gardening lovers in your life!   http://t.co/Vpbpl8LkfV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is not a rock opera. This is not Tommy. I can write songs that emote, and that's it. - John Mellencamp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Neil Diamond  http://t.co/7oug7WCzx8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Girls are like internet domain names, the ones I like are already taken.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Chuck Berry  http://t.co/qtZcohJEaR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A little smile adds a good deal to a faces value]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow these Steps to Clean Your Credit  http://t.co/jpZ7oLQyXW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great overview on using Redstone in Minecraft - http://t.co/xMzILTiIDx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating History of ESPN  http://t.co/dOuw4ULaYk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do clever men make good husbands? "No, clever men don't become husbands!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NASA Unveils a Very Cool New Space Suit  http://t.co/sdgA8k7MDr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best thing about animals is that they don't talk much. - Thornton Wilder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ELVIS - The King - One Person's Thoughts  http://t.co/zoJTQo2M9V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Molly Hatchet  http://t.co/11HqXM1ydC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every great batter works on the theory that the pitcher is more afraid of him than he is of the pitcher. - Ty Cobb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He who laughs last, didn't get it!!  :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And God took a handful of southernly wind, blew His breath over it and created the horse. - Bedouin Legend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With four pairs of shoes I can travel the world. - Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a meat-eating world, wearing leather for shoes and even clothes, the discussion of fur is childish. --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Adding Solar Power for Heating Pool  http://t.co/h3sdpktlIN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overwhelming underdogs. - Yogi Berra While Referring to the 1969 New York Mets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first one gets the oyster the second gets the shell. - Andrew Carnegie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A pedestrian is someone who thought there were a couple of gallons left in the tank. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahh nothing like beautiful nerd girls and fun nerd stuff!  Check out Nerd Zing!  http://t.co/kVWGWY9mTm]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>