<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software QA Engineer: Do you dream of what cars of the future will look like when you combine them with connectivity, a smartphone, and cloud services? Can you imagine uniting those dreams with a company that has the skills and relationships to… https://t.co/HJpGbWM83U https://t.co/HA6Gj03wGS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst II: Overview Business Analyst II (BA) will be assigned items from our road map and will be tasked with creating requirements/user stories &amp; acceptance criteria by eliciting feedback from internal and external stakeholders.  The BSA works… https://t.co/FHuXQfmAIC https://t.co/47Cx7PXuU3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior UX Architect: Overview Jellyfish, delivers digital marketing solutions across the world for a host of impressive brands from their offices in the US, Europe, and South Africa. The agency’s award-winning combination of technology and talent help it… https://t.co/5hAS7nHHOC https://t.co/ajMXhvsJ8G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master (SR775) Job: Date: Mar 15, 2018 Location: Albuquerque, NM, US Company: SAIC Scrum Master (SR775) (Job Number:434149) Description: SAIC is looking for an experienced Scrum Master. Job Description: You will work in a highly collaborative and… https://t.co/Q1zljyd9cV https://t.co/uiQTekxliz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Level 2: The software engineer is responsible for developing all the code in the enterprise. Applications are written in a variety of languages including Angular/TypeScript/JavaScript/C#/Python/Java, as well as mobile iOS/Android and… https://t.co/gVayRPo1VM https://t.co/gCF1q5S2Qr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ruby On Rails Developer: [Let’s face it, you’re probably more interested in looking at the technology before really considering us right? Take a minute to learn more about our platform Here… https://t.co/0pjpSZZPRJ https://t.co/vixC8vvSiy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Labs Release Manager: Overview The Release Program Manager is responsible to work across departments to set release strategy, methodology, initiatives and act as an escalation point for any release issues. Release Program Manager reports to the Director,… https://t.co/Ni2sGuy3WJ https://t.co/pYitqnmbUA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Project Manager (Agile/Scrum): Job TitleSr. Project Manager (Agile/Scrum) – ID:31354 Duration6 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsFinance/Banking experience , Agile Scrum Mgmt LocationPlano, TX Date Posted03/29/2018 FOR IMMEDIATE DETAILS ABOUT THIS… https://t.co/9w5OVGieaZ https://t.co/MUIKoBXlJE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cassandra DBA: We practice Agile/Scrum methodology and we program in a variety of languages such as Python, C/C++, &amp; Java. We are building a large scale and high-performance cloud based networking service platform that will deliver the next generation of… https://t.co/fucxkkQDic https://t.co/iCFWuQzLiQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Team Lead (Scrum Master) Job: Team Lead (Scrum Master) (Job Number:431672) Description: JOB DESCRIPTION: Team Lead (Scrum Master) – Scrum Master certification from accredited organization, i.e., Scrum Master Certified (CSM), Professional Scrum Master… https://t.co/HwwH9W7K0T https://t.co/xFmlV2m7Bd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrummaster/Project Manager – Cloud transformation: Come work at a place where innovation and teamwork come together to support the most exciting missions in the world! F5 is looking for a talented and high-energy scrummaster/project manager who can help… https://t.co/3dtHIgiDPu https://t.co/I21i5mKVyS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israeli agency investigating Apple over handling of iPhone slowdown: JERUSALEM (Reuters) - Israel's consumer protection bureau said on Tuesday it was investigating Apple over a failure to disclose to consumers that its software could slow performance in… https://t.co/Jfjlwk2Ede https://t.co/L8AQqpuZtQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UI/UX Designer: Aristotle is looking for a UI/UX Designer (with some JS development experience) that believe those companies that champion a design-centric approach to their product interfaces are the ones that rise above the rest. You live and breathe… https://t.co/AXrapE2rml https://t.co/wiGPzcsvmh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Microsoft Dynamics Developer: Senior Microsoft Dynamics Developer San jose, California – United States Job Start Date – 03/12/18, Posted Date – 03/12/18 Primary SkillsUI,SOAP,HTML,REST,XML,.NET Framework,WEB API,C# and Visual Studio IDE,CRM… https://t.co/kGS9hXllQi https://t.co/ZGS9D7Fhkd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: WMC Global is a market intelligence company bringing insight into the in-market customer experience. We combine software-driven data analysis and enterprise management consulting to help service providers support healthy businesses and… https://t.co/pP2GMXt7qs https://t.co/7uHBjemUql]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jr. Software Developer: Job Description Radiance Technologies is an employee-owned company with benefits that are unmatched by most companies in the Dayton, OH area. We offer highly competitive salaries, a relaxed work environment, flexible work… https://t.co/LXFwG5CfPu https://t.co/6Nu5Ey8NwC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TDD – .NET Developer: OUR CLIENT IN ATLANTA IS LOOKING FOR EXCELLENT .NET DEVELOPERS AT ALL LEVELS TO ADD TO THEIR TEAM! WHAT YOU’LL NEED: * Object Oriented Design and TDD * C#, .NET framework and NUnit/xUnit WHAT EXPERIENCE YOU’LL HAVE * Experience… https://t.co/IeymYl0VPV https://t.co/ZVtQeSKrUf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Senior Developer: Careers Center | .NET Senior Developer Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Returning Candidate?… https://t.co/VPql8PVFOj https://t.co/Qj3PW5pLvz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer – Backend Engineering: Share this opportunity! Senior Software Engineer – Backend Engineering (******) S/W Engineering, Regular Full-Time, Travel Required 20% Samsung Electronics America , Mountain View California Mar 5, 2018… https://t.co/1kYDLGgpoS https://t.co/zp8RdakF5a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master/PM: IT Careers – About Us – Our Culture – In the Community – Leadership – Our Services – Enterprise Strategies – IT Planning – Enterprise Portfolio Management – Process Quality Assessment – Managed Solutions – Project Based Services –… https://t.co/vwwE7gjy9Z https://t.co/WyjL5mJIe4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software QA Engineer: Do you dream of what cars of the future will look like when you combine them with connectivity, a smartphone, and cloud services? Can you imagine uniting those dreams with a company that has the skills and relationships to… https://t.co/iYsf9Ct1Ct https://t.co/k7H5weT5nZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Digital Product Manager – Eden Prairie, MN: Great sales are the result of strong purpose, conviction and pride – pride in your ability and your product. UnitedHealth Group offers a portfolio of products that are greatly improving the life of others.… https://t.co/tR9poRrs8s https://t.co/cyZJRlbv5u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer Team Lead – 15503: Software Engineer Team Lead Camber Corporation (a Huntington Ingalls Industries (HII) company)Distributed Common Ground Surface System – Special Operations Forces (DCGS-SOF) Team is seeking highly motivated applicants… https://t.co/s58WbjVLj3 https://t.co/QAZY410a7j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber loses EU court case in fight against French criminal charges: LUXEMBOURG (Reuters) - France is entitled to bring criminal proceedings against local managers of ride-hailing app Uber [UBER.UL] for running an illegal taxi service, the EU top court… https://t.co/wzTgQnPmci https://t.co/3elfCpOV3E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer (Front End): Adaptive Software is one of the fastest growing parts of the DRG family. Broadly, Adaptive sells workflow and business process software tools to health plans and Pharmacy Benefit Managers (PBMs), the organizations that… https://t.co/iaB3ktMibJ https://t.co/X3q4278KkI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Req ID : 423048BR Job Code/Title : E1072:Software Engineer Job Description : This position is for a software engineer to support the Advanced Programs projects. The candidate will work in an agile scrum development environment to… https://t.co/tfHTMSwZjN https://t.co/HVu6oNQ7C2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/n4LyZSfhwG User Support Specialist – West Valley City, UT OR Eden Prairie, MN: Combine two of the fastest-growing fields on the planet with a culture of performance, collaboration and opportunity and this is what you get. Leading edge… https://t.co/AgozpxPYkw https://t.co/4TC6W5Ok6N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Software Engineer: .NET software Engineer EMS Consultants is seeking a .NET software Engineer.  The ideal candidate will be highly self-motivated and be able to work in a very team oriented environment.  This individual will be responsible for all… https://t.co/FoHmLdbCBt https://t.co/dEdvcHjSWu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Networking Software Engineer: Were looking for a dedicated and passionate Sr. Engineer to join our cloud networking team. If you have experience building scalable, cloud based, web applications, are excited about impacting millions of users, look no… https://t.co/S1cEcRXhDg https://t.co/VvikdWLMoV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Project Lead / Manager: 108094BR Software Project Lead / Manager CA – Goleta Job Description:  Candidate will serve as a senior software project lead / manager of software development, software integration, and software testing phases of various… https://t.co/5DgRb9tSMy https://t.co/woOyRCXwHp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master Ref No.: 18-00576 Location: Boston, Massachusetts Position Type: Contract Start Date: 03/27/2018 Qualifications: Candidates should have 5+ year’s experience as a Scrum Master in a large scale professional environment supporting… https://t.co/gkDCB949Lm https://t.co/L4vAOOgaDe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Lead- QA: Technical Lead- QA Indianapolis, Indiana Fulltime position Job Description: * Written Unit tests * Used version control * Database experience with writing, reading stored procedures and complex SQL * Ability and experience… https://t.co/rEg9hkASWJ https://t.co/oN9Oxxvzks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Agile Program Manager: Senior Agile Program Manager Job ID  2018-16582 Primary Location  Nebraska, Omaha Regular/Temp  Regular Additional Locations  Jersey City,New Jersey,United States Full-Time/Part-Time  Full-Time More information about this… https://t.co/szSHyrc6nJ https://t.co/We9FqF1Q64]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MOBILE SCRUM MASTER: MOBILE SCRUM MASTER ADDISON, Texas – United States Job Start Date – 03/20/18, Posted Date – 03/20/18 Primary SkillsScrum masterTax TermsC2COverview Phone – Skype Visa – H1 [Preferred] Only from Trusted Source, EAD is Fine. 5 Year… https://t.co/D6u8ceqYlR https://t.co/AkdgN68HqI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google appeals Indian antitrust watchdog's 'search bias' verdict: sources: NEW DELHI (Reuters) - Online search giant Google has filed an appeal at the National Company Law Appellate Tribunal (NCLAT) against a judgment from India's competition watchdog… https://t.co/dKfcihzWiS https://t.co/f8oVnEC1Az]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Scrum Engineer – Navisite / Spectrum Enterprise: Client Reference Code: 214876 Who We Are:Navisite, Inc., a Charter Communications Company, is a leading worldwide provider of enterprise-class, cloud services, managed applications and managed hosting… https://t.co/I9gmZ45DVj https://t.co/Yowei0zBkG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: Infosys- Retail, CPG &amp; Logistics Technology Lead US – User Interface Lead Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to create and execute strategies for their… https://t.co/eM12WXo3Lq https://t.co/NBbARm1bJJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Business Analyst(Scrum): Business Analyst Alpharetta, GA Full Time Position Job Description: Strong experience in working as a product owner and senior business analyst. Prior Experience in working on projects using Scrum and SAfe framework is a… https://t.co/SNz3UvI8pA https://t.co/y3Q4SLdU5u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer: Were Hearst Autos and we are going to change the way consumers buy automobiles. With a recognized brand Car and Driver and the best editorial team in the automotive industry were cutting a new path! We are looking for… https://t.co/gq6iGYPNaB https://t.co/XGs7ld9qYp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agile Scrum Master: Key Required Skills: Hands on Agile Scrum Master, training, Agile implementation experience using Scrum, Kanban, Lean, etc., customer engagement, communication, project management MUST be US Citizen or green card holder. Prefer local… https://t.co/MWOjcbVUh0 https://t.co/7KrpPiRIyW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital Product Manager – Eden Prairie, MN: Great sales are the result of strong purpose, conviction and pride – pride in your ability and your product. UnitedHealth Group offers a portfolio of products that are greatly improving the life of others.… https://t.co/cLSc6NUkoP https://t.co/qt8e4VNzYf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Job #:180028444: Job #:180028444 Software Engineer Columbus, OH. Duties: Provide quality technology solutions that address line of business needs by contributing to writing Pega applications, developing stored procedures and general… https://t.co/z7fLtSZqYr https://t.co/KzD5iwquO3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst II: Overview Business Analyst II (BA) will be assigned items from our road map and will be tasked with creating requirements/user stories &amp; acceptance criteria by eliciting feedback from internal and external stakeholders.  The BSA works… https://t.co/em6D7VHhgb https://t.co/u79mGoMiNH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[scrum master: scrum master Ref No.: 18-10389 Location: plano, Texas Hi, Hope you are doing great!! Enterprise Solution Inc. is currently looking to fill urgent full-time permanent job positions as Scrum Master with the client based in Columbus ,Ohio //… https://t.co/yi6jwpVRXf https://t.co/lPIKZiqQed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SCRUM Master: SCRUM Master Ref No.: 18-10465 Location: Pittsburg, Pennsylvania Hi, I hope you’re doing well today!!! I, Ghazala(Enterprise Solution Inc.)would like to check your availability for an Urgent job opportunity asScrum Masters basedinPittsburg,… https://t.co/cS7fgss3aH https://t.co/CFblaXzhKd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agile Pipeline: Description: THE COMPANY Fannie Mae provides reliable, large-scale access to affordable mortgage credit in communities across our nation. We are the leading source of funding for housing in America, which means more people can buy or rent… https://t.co/xea7LtoANA https://t.co/bXThaWWCNK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China joins HK-U.S. battle for Chinese tech listings: HONG KONG (Reuters) - When Charles Li, chief executive of the Hong Kong Exchange, last year announced plans to help the next wave of Chinese tech giants go public in the city, bankers celebrated. https://t.co/hjIazxtdIT https://t.co/X4dLiUkp6G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master II, Partner Solutions: Scrum Master II, Partner Solutions at Cox Automotive Skip Navigation – Careers Home – Early Career – Join Our Talent Community – Blog – Manage Your Profile – Cox Enterprises – Cox Communications – Cox Automotive – Cox… https://t.co/xLrYfdXTr0 https://t.co/H6C8ee8Av6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer: Adaptive Software is one of the fastest growing parts of the DRG family. Broadly, Adaptive sells workflow and business process software tools to health plans and Pharmacy Benefit Managers (PBMs), the organizations that… https://t.co/dnOrYfKNQC https://t.co/DNomKTQAwA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrummaster/Project Manager – Cloud transformation: Come work at a place where innovation and teamwork come together to support the most exciting missions in the world! F5 is looking for a talented and high-energy scrummaster/project manager who can help… https://t.co/3aKH7zpR3Y https://t.co/1Wptsm0McB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master – Exton, PA: Do you enjoy working with highly-skilled, self-motivated colleagues? Do you also have a passion for helping customers be successful? Are you passionate about Lean and Agile practices? If so, Guidewire has an opportunity for you.… https://t.co/W89OlOKMtn https://t.co/H2LPxMU6Z7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Engineer III: Description: THE COMPANY Are you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable,… https://t.co/e8ZWCsjv15 https://t.co/YrMjL2HA2A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer II: Description: THE COMPANYAre you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable,… https://t.co/qaBuJO2zGl https://t.co/mpI4uKns9S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master Ref No.: 18-10518 Location: Columbus, Ohio Hi, Hope you are doing well Enterprise Solution Inc. is currently looking to fill urgent full-time permanent job positions as Scrum Master with the client based in Pittsburg, PA //… https://t.co/VtWmE54gu6 https://t.co/tkQSECAT5d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist: About ThreatMetrix ThreatMetrix, The Digital Identity Company, is the market-leading cloud solution for authenticating digital identities and transactions on the Internet. Verifying more than 25 billion annual transactions supporting… https://t.co/iPaPsYchZc https://t.co/pyY4zIb32t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master / Website Development Project Manager: Other agencies may call this job Project Manager or Account Manager, but we don’t like using the M-word. Rather, we do our web design and software development work in 5-person teams, with each member of… https://t.co/caiI10KsKC https://t.co/tqT3uBByHl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Software Developer: Overview Software Developer IV (SDIV) will be part of a team of some of the best and brightest in the industry who are focused on developing scalable web and responsive applications that touch our growing customer base every… https://t.co/QiEHUF7lNm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Systems Engineering: Description: Job Description This position is a Systems Engineer on the Exploitation Services (program), working hand-in-hand with the ACE, Chief Architect (CA), Chief Engineer (CE) and the Program Management Leadership team… https://t.co/rKygThrhI1 https://t.co/HhdRY0wRYJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master Mayfield Heights, OH Full Time Position Job Description: Should have strong experience in C++ As a Sr. Scrum Master, the candidate is expected to be a Practitioner of agile-lean practices and processes at the team level with… https://t.co/mJDuEBK4aF https://t.co/ArzDOCxtSn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republican senator says Facebook scandals may be 'too big' for company to fix alone: WASHINGTON (Reuters) - A Republican U.S. senator warned on Sunday that Facebook Inc may need to be regulated to address concerns about the company's privacy and foreign… https://t.co/pmMu3GUDE4 https://t.co/QQAEJvYg9b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Assurance and Release Specialist: Quality Assurance and Release Specialist / Cincinnati , OH Overview: Join our scrum team with a focus on Quality Assurance and release planning for our Core Product Development Team. This position will work on… https://t.co/4dschxO5M9 https://t.co/aY009wEnpg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle Database Developer: True Source IT is searching for an up and coming/mid-level database developer well versed in PL/SQL Development to join a trusted client in the northwest suburbs of Minneapolis. This is a fantastic, mid sized company with a… https://t.co/V7ugtQLjTa https://t.co/44UYsVEWpd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[# Scrum Master | GA &amp; MN | 6+ months: Title: Sr. Scrum Master Location: Atlanta, GA or Minneapolis, MN Duration: 6+ months Requirements Must have 5+ years of experience as Scrum Master Need a senior Scrum Master whose has very good recent experience in… https://t.co/qoudjU2eSN https://t.co/6mTOaIe31M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web System Analyst: Web System Analyst Smithfield, Rhode Island – United States Job Start Date – 03/26/18, Posted Date – 03/26/18 Primary Skillsfinancial,Web ApplicationTax TermsC2COverview Primary Responsibilities * Identify, analyze and document… https://t.co/RqnBmojRdi https://t.co/2czRHp2dMa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Business Analyst/Scrum Master: Resource 1 is in need of a SR. BUSINESS ANALYST/SCRUM MASTER for a 6-month contract-for-hire in Elkridge, MD. Ideal candidate will have at least 7 years of BA experience in an enterprise IT environment, WORKING ON… https://t.co/nVsx1mmrsx https://t.co/jBx6UYPZ5F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Web Developer: Highlights for Children, a family media brand that has been nurturing children with excellent, wholesome, and innovative products for more than 70 years, reaches over two million children every month throughout the world. Our… https://t.co/O9khfPLkWH https://t.co/imYNS7rSsc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Business Analyst – Eden Prarie, MN, Schaumburg, IL or Irvine, CA: Under general supervision, the Senior Business Analyst is responsible for gathering, documenting and maintaining detailed business requirements as part of the system delivery life… https://t.co/yfnZjWn2dv https://t.co/vGTd0beYAG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Level 4: The software engineer is responsible for developing all the code in the enterprise. Applications are written in a variety of languages including Angular/TypeScript/JavaScript/C#/Python/Java, as well as mobile iOS/Android and… https://t.co/JPrgR4WUoo https://t.co/I97MzTLYd2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project manager (Scrum Master): Project manager (Scrum Master) Ref No.: 18-00610 Location: Mount laurel, New Jersey Start Date / End Date: 04/01/2018 to 04/01/2019 Technical/Functional Skills – Knowledge of agile methodology and frameworks like Scrum,… https://t.co/6IfpA75hAH https://t.co/gB1PvdZM5I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Oracle Application Developer – EBS, OAF, Forms: Are you an Oracle application developer with strong experience in Oracle E-Business Suite (EBS) and Oracle Application Framework (OAF)? Are you proficient in general skills and technologies such as… https://t.co/020aSgQYFk https://t.co/5ThPtR8R0m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ruby On Rails Developer: [Let’s face it, you’re probably more interested in looking at the technology before really considering us right? Take a minute to learn more about our platform Here… https://t.co/z974eQCnSd https://t.co/AFhc8ZkJol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook suspends Canadian firm AggregateIQ over data scandal: (Reuters) - Facebook Inc said on Friday that it had suspended Canadian political consultancy AggregateIQ from its platform after reports that the data firm may have improperly had access to… https://t.co/6OmY2rMD8I https://t.co/xTNXezozkI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SCRUM Master: SCRUM Master Ref No.: 18-10465 Location: Pittsburg, Pennsylvania Hi, I hope you’re doing well today!!! I, Ghazala(Enterprise Solution Inc.)would like to check your availability for an Urgent job opportunity asScrum Masters basedinPittsburg,… https://t.co/vfKQt5C8JR https://t.co/jtmd0ED64V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: OM1 is a leading healthcare technology company focused on providing outcomes measurement and predictive analytics for value-based and personalized healthcare. Leveraging big clinical data, standardized outcomes measures, and… https://t.co/fAfcLsUKuU https://t.co/0DjqvCgKxy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[scrum master: scrum master Ref No.: 18-10389 Location: plano, Texas Hi, Hope you are doing great!! Enterprise Solution Inc. is currently looking to fill urgent full-time permanent job positions as Scrum Master with the client based in Columbus ,Ohio //… https://t.co/GWTJcYAYIn https://t.co/tvh5G4AfUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master We’re Hearst Autos and we are going to change the way consumers buy automobiles. With a recognized brand Car &amp; Driver, and the best editorial team in the automotive industry, we’re cutting a new path! We are looking for… https://t.co/pXxQt42zZx https://t.co/qx08Eri8x3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior UI Designer – contract: Takeoff Tech is a well-funded, 30-person startup enabling retailers to sell groceries online profitably. Takeoff is developing automated aisleless stores coupled with an end-to-end eGrocery technology stack, offering… https://t.co/ctypFPeoQL https://t.co/btOvyyUjPb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Reporting, BI Business Analyst – Eden Prairie, MN: How do you invent the future of health care? It takes the dedication of thousands of people all pulling in the same direction. OptumCare Care Services is seeking a Senior Reporting/BI Business… https://t.co/VqPty7RhQI https://t.co/t89aFEjY0G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/n4LyZSfhwG User Support Specialist – West Valley City, UT OR Eden Prairie, MN: Combine two of the fastest-growing fields on the planet with a culture of performance, collaboration and opportunity and this is what you get. Leading edge… https://t.co/XU1mAItDos https://t.co/sXqNaDPwvO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Agile Coach: Title: Senior Agile Coach Location: Bellevue, WA Duration: 6+ Months Contract There is an opening for a regular agile coach and another one for Senior agile coach. Required: * For both coaches, at least 3 agile related certifications,… https://t.co/qCGho3FGKh https://t.co/XtluUhJ80l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SCRUM Master: CONTRACT SCRUM MASTER MUST BE LOCAL TO ISELIN NJ AND AVAILABLE TO INTERVIEW IN PERSON IMMEDIATELY. Our client is searching for a Scrum Master with Agile Development experience Must have Scrum certification and heavy Agile Development… https://t.co/jYk7Hz3JrV https://t.co/apkB1b5jS4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big Data Architect: Join our Big Data Team and work on dynamic long-term projects. The majority of our team members are long-term employees who enjoy consistent work and a collaborative team approach! KEY ACCOUNTABILITIES: * Provides thought leadership… https://t.co/p2m3kD3Kzx https://t.co/DPl7NT7YCL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Business Analyst: As part of the TPGSI business team, Business Analyst (BA) will elicit and document business and technical requirements in support of TP strategic objective to design a new eligibility and enrollment system. This new system,… https://t.co/EC0O8dqAkS https://t.co/vT6KJu5djd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cryptocurrency traders use old gold in drive to draw Islamic investors: DUBAI/SYDNEY (Reuters) - In Dubai's decades-old Gold Souk, customers from around the world haggle over bangles and necklaces. Elsewhere in the emirate, the region's top center for… https://t.co/cRNW9x17NK https://t.co/rjsGizxlSv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Scrum Master: Senior Scrum Master – Careers Home – About Us – People &amp; Culture – University Recruiting – Total Rewards – Growth &amp; Learning – Featured Locations – Europe, Middle East &amp; Africa Jobs – Asia &amp; South Pacific Jobs – Latin America &amp;… https://t.co/kGjN4rKzvx https://t.co/O08f4MlWnl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master Mayfield Heights, OH Full Time Position Job Description: Should have strong experience in C++ As a Sr. Scrum Master, the candidate is expected to be a Practitioner of agile-lean practices and processes at the team level with… https://t.co/4dMvanspbn https://t.co/7udLRVOwTU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Android Developer: ANDROID DEVELOPER This is a permanent full time role. Looking for experienced Mobile Application Developers that will be responsible for the development, testing, and implementation of innovative customer-facing mobile applications for… https://t.co/O90PQJOCiD https://t.co/aOlGNnfUyn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Scrum Engineer – Spectrum Enterprise: Client Reference Code: 214876 About Spectrum Enterprise Spectrum Enterprise, a part of Charter Communications, is a national provider of scalable, fiber-based technology solutions serving many of America’s… https://t.co/v81u5g5OqE https://t.co/2OJPPJF9TF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master role in Murrysville, PA: SCRUM MASTER ROLE LOCATION: MURRYSVILLE, PA 15668 OVERVIEW: * Serve the role of Scrum Master as defined in the Scrum Guide * Guide the team and organization on how to use Agile/Scrum practices and values * Assess the… https://t.co/D0611HsYI8 https://t.co/5swElj8mG6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master Job: Date: Mar 21, 2018 Location: Albuquerque, NM, US Company: SAIC Scrum Master (Job Number:435242) Description: Scrum Master Job Description SAIC is looking for an experienced Scrum Master. You will work in a highly collaborative and agile… https://t.co/58h1rojsXi https://t.co/ymXjO9dMyn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager: Position Overview: The Sr Project Manager is responsible for managing key projects as it relates to Operations, Vendor Implementations, New Product Development and major software enhancements. Additionally, the Sr. Project Manager… https://t.co/eHjtGrCcKp https://t.co/zGn7rM8kvE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master II: Description: THE COMPANY Are you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable, affordable… https://t.co/I5fOPFpjCt https://t.co/ntJilNUiQE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US IT Technical Development Lead: PwC/LOS Overview PwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about us at… https://t.co/wdPLtsTK50 https://t.co/QFmdQaYv7Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SCRUM Master: CONTRACT SCRUM MASTER MUST BE LOCAL TO ISELIN NJ AND AVAILABLE TO INTERVIEW IN PERSON IMMEDIATELY. Our client is searching for a Scrum Master with Agile Development experience Must have Scrum certification and heavy Agile Development… https://t.co/GmmFZOD21z https://t.co/1v6kVckboX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior UX/UI Designer: As one of the nations leading pediatric health care systems, Nemours is committed to providing all children with their best chance to grow up healthy. We offer integrated, family-centered care to more than 300,000 children each… https://t.co/oo04aot0KP https://t.co/JPgyCh0txE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chinese Uber rival Didi launches in Mexico, recruits drivers: MEXICO CITY/SAN FRANCISCO (Reuters) - Chinese ride-hailing company Didi Chuxing has publicly launched in Mexico with a website advertising its service to drivers and passengers, setting the… https://t.co/r2KcyjsoCL https://t.co/Nz43QhaoDE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum master: LOCATION: PITTSBURGH, PA/MURRYSVILLE, PA REQUIRED SKILLS: * Scrum Master in Agile * Ability to coach and influence Agile concepts to people that are new to the Agile Methodology. * Scrum Master Certification required * Version 1 or JIRA is… https://t.co/qf8UwOcbMl https://t.co/dVt86cwKMY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CW Scrum Master: CW Scrum Master (******) Georgetown, Kentucky – United States Job Start Date – 03/15/18, Posted Date – 03/15/18 Primary SkillsScrumTax TermsC2C,W-2,1099Overview Dear, I am Mohammed Dastagir with Saxon Global Inc wanted to let you know… https://t.co/UWCdbHN1AI https://t.co/BQdO73nQMS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Reporting Analyst – Eden Prairie, MN or Telecommute: We’ll put you in the driver’s seat on vital projects that have strategic importance to our mission of helping people lead healthier lives. Yes, we share a mission that inspires. We need your… https://t.co/fi32rHeHeP https://t.co/0NyS0oIVFi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[# Scrum Master | GA &amp; MN | 6+ months: Title: Sr. Scrum Master Location: Atlanta, GA or Minneapolis, MN Duration: 6+ months Requirements Must have 5+ years of experience as Scrum Master Need a senior Scrum Master whose has very good recent experience in… https://t.co/HtUixCw6wT https://t.co/E1tADxxYSw]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>