<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Wilnerness590 don't always agree with Mike( mostly do though)  but when I want to know what's happening in game, is my go to to follow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FrankConniff: I agree with right wingers - a psycho with an assault weapon is much less dangerous than a transgender person who needs t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JSportsnet @NHLNetwork But, but I'm watching u on #primetimesports right now and then. Damn transporters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@__msHill damnit Hill. You said. " who needs GPS ". ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@__msHill depends. Am I supposed to be in downtown Kapuskasing right now. Cuz you said turn left at the moose]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @billbarnwell: Fully convinced NHL teams play more exciting playoff games when Doc Emrick is on the call.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelFarber3 But the speed. The only difference is the speed. Intense]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MichaelFarber3: In terms of drama and quality, CHI-STL is beginning to resemble the fabulous CHI-LAK conference final of 2014.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@draglikepull that was 6 minutes of fantastic nonstop action. Seems like a natural Western Conference thing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CandaceDBuckner can we call them The Indy 500?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/GTDzISJdoT via @youtube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donlandrymedia ahh Dubennet on the patio.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joerhobby Yes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not Irony, not coincidence. Inevitable  https://t.co/OUu24bMM4t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dalter Viktoria Movers. Good efficient Used them many times]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dowbboy because #lochmess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realFBra @BraddJaffy Politicspeak Translation: So keep those donations coming and get 'em in fast. Deadline approaching]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NEWSTALK1010 if it was UBER they'd know exactly when it was coming]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sunlorrie: Hey SJWs! Usain Bolt thinks this Ellen gag is so racist that he retweeted it. https://t.co/AhHCU1ZvvX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have no idea what's going on in the #Rio2016  #weightlifting by finals but it's fascinating. Go Armenia I think]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@downsdispatch @NBCNews beat me by 3 years]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilary not physically fit? She must have bone spurs @realDonaldTrump @HillaryClinton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder if Ariel Rogers and Sandy Chapin have ever met?  I bet they have. Stan and Harry: so much in common]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dalter Chauncey would be perfect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Serb Olympic Women's coach Wears it so much better than Trump https://t.co/6y0jcT62bs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @InklessPW: Sorry sorry https://t.co/S8uiE84D70]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sunlorrie: Jeff Weaver, Bernie Sanders' campaign manager, says Donald Trump can win if Democrats underestimate him https://t.co/6WswxzL…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@briannemett yes. I would be. This was mine 2 weeks ago tonight Right In the heart of 'er b'ye https://t.co/ntXgt3p7yb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Speech HRC. But why ya'll so surprised by  the concept of balloons? #DemConvention]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ThatEricAlper: John Prine Set To Release For Better, Or Worse, His First Album In 17 Years:  https://t.co/1JLC8YsVGr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Isolation Beach. So many tiny secret spots in Cape Breton. On the edge of the world @ Louisbourg https://t.co/OpPDTHuqav]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Temporary Backyard for a couple of days @ Low Point Lighthouse https://t.co/l4oMVnq4hC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RosieBarton: It was probably my Mom. She's the worst. https://t.co/7WtxkdKYNL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You are the only person that can walk out of your Ali G interview]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@colbycosh @northsidechad explain your basis for that reference Mr. Cash. May take awhile. I have time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sunlorrie ha!  Pouring through my Barney Miller refs to try to 1 up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheCut @acoyne Doubln' Down at the ole casino]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sunlorrie I clicked to see. Then I smirked. Then I loved the reference so I watched. Then I laughed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ianabramson I cried because I had no shoes. Then I saw a man with no feet. So I said Buddy you must have an xtra pair of shoes somewhere]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sunlorrie Decent Brief. What's lacking ( and is consistently lacking across all media views) is: What would prevent him from winning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Alyssa_Milano Here is a great song that expresses your sentiment perfectly Bruised Orange by the great John Prine https://t.co/mVa1tayhEp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Wilnerness590  Roof is open. Humidity is on high. Dickey has pitches slopen'  a win is nigh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marymoments1 I saw this happen in like real time. Say stuff. Often]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dowbboy big gap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And this is how it starts! https://t.co/zMTK5U7RWL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ddale8 quotes one absolute truth today. The situation many Americans find themselves in https://t.co/O7VD0Kjvb6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColinRatchford there's the brilliant germination of what possibly could be the world greatest Country song here. Let's do it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @acoyne: Perhaps now is a good time to point out that Twitter's latest iteration of quoted tweets represents the final victory of the Co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RealDonalDrumpf: I was tired. https://t.co/5aW9KGHdEF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CFLLandry I thought the same thing. #CFL needs that home base. Friday Night might be the perfect time and place for a concentrated push]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CFLLandry: Kinda liked that overlap thing. Was fun flipping back and forth between #CFL games.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheTorontoSun @SueAnnLevy agree]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@normmacdonald still hurts Norm. Thank god its Tuesday and the Blue is good this time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FarAndWide. Ha. Belt has to match the shoes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FarAndWide: @13inklings love the avatar!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FarAndWide FOUND hanging with Chris Christie's deep under the Hudson were the Ny NJ sewers meet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sunlorrie. Agreed Trump incapable of studious analysis or strategy. Most Media covering is proving themselves inadequate as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sunlorrie: Re Donald Trump: Hands up everyone who pays more taxes than they have to &amp; who doesn't claim capital losses! Bueller ... Bue…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MMFlint This is as an accurate strategy assessment there is. If they don't get off the " how can I lose to this guy" they will.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MMFlint: Pro-Hillary gloaters doing end-zone dance again when still on 50-yd line. U MUST get it in your head TRUMP IS GONNA WIN and ac…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @davidakin: Not again. https://t.co/VV2BBwz1Vz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColinRatchford I love you Young Cuz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SueAnnLevy cmon people so posed. Hopefully it's a little joke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ivortossell @wendyp4545 always know the answer B4 asking  " see. Just like I said. We caught them rigging the polls and they had to stop "]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikebendixen Every Long Weekend. No Rhyme Nor Reason. Other than People like fire works I guess.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OllieConnolly this is a good game]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Wilnerness590 @MarkRaymer @JoeyBats19 Good way to ignore the Dog Whistle Mike. I would take him in my line up any day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CastrosLounge  https://t.co/dUHpv8ethZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The band is always great and the setting makes it even better Thelonious Hank at Castros Lounge https://t.co/GZePR3520B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Done things never change. Unless one falls into a Domi Filled penalty box  https://t.co/pmAshTcZ8E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sunlorrie Salient, they could be better : "do as we say, not as we do” when it comes to issues such as “fighting” climate change.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sunlorrie: Here's my Thursday Sun Media column: Trudeau's hypocrisy on climate exposed https://t.co/QTVJ9RCuou #cdnpoli https://t.co/lW…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$6000.00 reputation. That's quite the reputation https://t.co/VKAQpk1Jt7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And on Christmas Day He rested. But really, he went and got really drunk. Even Santa can't handle a Cape Breton wind https://t.co/yAA4LmyhJ8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love the random acts of hilarity that @CP24 Headline scroll offers up. But ya gotta be quick. https://t.co/0G3E3KMMjr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @bruce_arthur: @NickKouvalis I don't think you're as dumb as you tweet, Nick. I think it says a lot about who you think your constituent…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jack_Astors ONE BIG MEATBALL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The team has to make the statement. beware of the statement Price may make if the Caps are allowed to set up shop in front like SJ did https://t.co/sNC6Bizlht]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sunlorrie @towhey @deaninktown And this is how it starts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JIMrichards1010: East Enders please re tweet ... @TheCeiliCottage @TripleAToronto https://t.co/w9C8LqSTa2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@towhey @BenSpurr what action, what next Cancel? We wait longer. Financial Penalty? No time gain. BMBRDR doesn't care, can't deliver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What. Play by Zaitsev. #Leafs fans who are searching for a defensman You have a serious one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This one is moving fast for them Picturing Love by July Talk. #JULYTALK  https://t.co/sBgQfbxMqu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And Kanye and Trump call Legend John Obvious https://t.co/RqKlO8e0HT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Altidore will score the winner because he reminds me of Joe Carter #TFC Head it in Jose You'll never have a better touch in your life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ddale8 have a look back at the subtle subtweeting @reporterdonpeat did during the Ford times. The preach approach put Trump in the WH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ChazEbert @ebertchicago @Suntimes Not Movie related but he did the possibly the first major John Prine review from early Chicago days]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LindaRegber brilliant. That's all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LindaRegber: PDF is now the world's most popular religion. https://t.co/VQ9WJIDL7j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NEWSTALK1010 okay now. Let's get some perspective. A pedestrian striking simultaneous attack? Enlighten O Headline Writers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's called Doing It Right https://t.co/AtlJr4Q7UW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's so often true. It's the desire for a close game. To the Wire https://t.co/3w9jhYRjJp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichaelFarber3 #exactafukamundo this is a good game ruined]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MichaelFarber3: Upon further review, I can't take any more reviews in this Grey Cup game. The CFL has moved from the Mud and Ice Bowls…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#GreyCup is Shaping Up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EmmMacfarlane @eggb432 @acoyne @AaronWherry @lraitt @StephanieCarvin you're too kind. He didn't. He referred to a list of people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @robdelaney: I think people criticizing Trudeau are forgetting how handsome he is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So this is the origin of Stockholm Syndrome https://t.co/cHvNRW9AUW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jen_keesmaat So that's the origins of Stockholm Syndrome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching The Last Waltz for not the last time and perfecting my Winter Drink. This winter will… https://t.co/4wfdi1Uyru]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>