<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ForeignAffairs: Cities and states must acknowledge the need to manage the physical impacts of chronic climate change as well as the nee…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @scotgp: The Greens are #LeadingTheChange for safer streets as @markruskell publishes his Member's Bill to change the default speed limi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@weebod One's a no mark MSP (even then, it was in all Scottish newspapers and BBC Scotland) and the other's the former First Minister of Scotland.  There was no way they were going to be "treated in the same way".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrLauraVivanco That should have said she limits her chocolate intake to only the weekends. I'm not suggesting she spends her weekends just eating chocolate (although she might).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrLauraVivanco She's good.  Still missing smoking but she limits herself to only eating chocolate at the weekend now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@weebod No, I don't. But that's not what my original tweet was about.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@weebod @jegteg No]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DrLauraVivanco 

Think Louise might like this one... https://t.co/qdsdWTbPn6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could be worse. The Scottish government could be testing P1 kids despite most evidence suggesting it's not good for young kids, eh @JohnSwinney https://t.co/mOA0iDT7pO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @STVNews: WATCH: Would you recycle more if you got paid for it?

That's what happens in Sweden and Scottish Government wants to introduc…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @spikedonline: #MeToo is poisoning American politics. If Kavanaugh is brought down by unsubstantiated accusations, it will set a terribl…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@eirebhoy There were about 40 kids in my class.  By the time he'd finished it would be time to go home (which would have suited me!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ian_mcnicholl: More simply must be done to encourage men to come forward.  This case ended in the ultimate tragedy, the most significan…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jegteg It seems to me people are more interested in taking a political scalp rather than hearing the truth. 

Witnesses, inc. SNP staff, gave evidence saying he was innocent but people want to see him in court (where, no doubt, the same witnesses would still say he's innocent).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@valhalla1965 @rapecrisisscot @Eileen43Eileen You do that.  Bye.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@valhalla1965 @rapecrisisscot @Eileen43Eileen Aye, despite those witnesses including staff who work for the SNP, they all lied to protect a Tory MSP.

Do you have any idea how demented that sounds?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vFreeBirdv @valhalla1965 @rapecrisisscot @Eileen43Eileen There may be better ways to deal with it but in this case it seems to me people are more upset because they didn't get a media circus and a political scalp rather than the discovering the truth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's amazing how many people who claim that Alex Salmond is the victim of some political conspiracy regarding sexual misconduct allegations are happy to believe that Miles Briggs is guilty despite the many witnesses who say he's innocent.

Utter crackpots.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@valhalla1965 @rapecrisisscot @Eileen43Eileen He has the right to prove his innocent. And he did. He was cleared of any wrongdoing because witnesses, inc. those of rival political parties, said he did nothing wrong. 

Why is this innocent man having his name sullied by this action?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@valhalla1965 @rapecrisisscot @Eileen43Eileen According to witnesses, including staff working for other parties inc. the SNP, he didn't do anything wrong so what do you want people to do? Pretend he's guilty so you can label him a sexual predator?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rapecrisisscot Even witnesses working for rival parties said he was innocent.  I dislike the Tories as much as any other sane person but this is victimising an innocent man. And it's politicising sexual assault for your own ends.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rapecrisisscot Miles Briggs said: "I was able to supply the party's disciplinary committee with several witness statements from individuals who were with me the entire evening ... I am especially grateful to the SNP parliamentary researchers who were among those who supported my case."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Scotpol1314 @Balr0g https://t.co/2V6WWLkOYD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Scotpol1314 @Balr0g Okay, well you're clearly howling at the moon.  Bye.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Scotpol1314 @Balr0g I think you're allowing your emotions to get the better of you, pal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Scotpol1314 @Balr0g What double standards?  So far, I've seen the Miles Briggs story reported in the Daily Record, the Sun, the Scotsman, the Herald, The National and BBC Scotland.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good.  Leave it there. https://t.co/jwLMDweyXZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KizzieWiz @Jeggit Care to expand on what you mean by 'suspect'?

Is it, as I 'suspect', that they vote for what they stand for rather than towing to the SNP every time?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Scotpol1314 @Balr0g Then you're pretty deluded. You honestly think a no mark MSP whose party isn't even in Government is going to get as much coverage as a former First Minister?  Come on, behave yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @scotgp: Huge thanks to the one &amp; only @MrMarkBeaumont for adding his backing to @markruskell's #SaferStreets bill. Making 20mph the nor…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NicolaSturgeon Is the expression "Plastic Irishmen" still acceptable?

Asking for a well known SNP MP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Scotpol1314 Are you honestly suggesting that a Tory MSP that most of the country hasn't heard of should be getting the same amount of coverage over an 'allegation' as the former First Minister of Scotland?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ChrisGPackham: So @BBCNews @itvnews according to police estimates we put 10K people on the streets of London in a peaceful , colourful…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NicolaSturgeon Good news that you'll be leaving all the oil in the ground and not backing any more airport expansions eh Nicola?

Or is climate change okay as long as it stops at the border?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeremycorbyn @CWUnews "women spend around £5,000 on sanitary products in their lives"

Exactly how many women are we taking about here? If it's just one WOMAN then where the hell are they buying these sanitary products?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @scotgp: We have a wide range of hoodies, tops, t-shirts &amp; accessories available on our online store.  Perfect for those attending next…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @scotgp: Climate Change, Brexit, Independence, Local Democracy.
Join us at #SGPConf as we #LeadTheChange on the big issues. Reserve your…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @scotgp: We are at the #NaeNukes2018 rally in Faslane today, calling for an end to Trident and a nuclear free world.
#BanTheBomb https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @scotgp: It's inspiring to be at the #NaeNukes2018 rally at Faslane today with Greens and peace activists from across the country and th…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @scotgp: "We will continue to resolutely oppose nuclear arms on the Clyde and seek to raise Scotland’s profile as a global peacemaker."…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NeilMackay: I can not fathom the anger directed at the Green Party for voting against national assessments for P1 - and I say that as s…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McBOTtheIndyman @Isthisabot For voting against a policy they don't agree with? A policy they said they were against in their 2016 manifesto?

By all means disagree but having a go at a party for standing by what they believe in is bizarre. It's a pity others, inc. the SNP, don't always do likewise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SamsHusband You just know that's tempting fate!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @allangrogan: So the greens are now tories?Honestly SNP there wont be a need for Better Together next timesome of your supporters are do…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of course, the next time the SNP vote with the Tories in Holyrood, this place is going to be full of angry indy supporters tearing into the SNP and resigning their memberships.

Otherwise, they're a bunch of hypocrites.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AFaulds: SNP Supporters; You can't trust Labour anymore, all those broken promises

Also SNP Supporters; Oh come now Greens, you have t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brucelharper @Stand_Free1980 @PoliticsScot @JohnCoy29071630 @MichelleGr4h4m @patrickharvie @NicolaSturgeon Oh look, another SNP lickspittle.

"Celtic fan in favour of the OBFA".

Tells you all you need to know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realdaydoh @PoliticsScot @MichelleGr4h4m @patrickharvie @NicolaSturgeon You'd have to ask them. It's nothing to do with the Greens. The Greens voted against a policy they disagreed with. People saying the voted with the Tories need to grow up. All parties vote for and against policies, sometimes on their own and sometimes with other parties.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkBarry67 @PoliticsScot @MichelleGr4h4m @patrickharvie @NicolaSturgeon It was in the Tory manifesto. The voted against it today because they were playing politics. It's still a Tory policy that the SNP lifted from their manifesto.  Maybe chew on that for a while.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkBarry67 @PoliticsScot @MichelleGr4h4m @patrickharvie @NicolaSturgeon The Greens voted againast what is effectively a Tory policy being pitched by the SNP.

Perhaps people should direct their anger at the SNP for trying to implement Tory policies rather than the Greens for voting against them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MarkBarry67 @PoliticsScot @MichelleGr4h4m @patrickharvie @NicolaSturgeon My comment was an ironic response to the original post but the replies have certainly cemented my belief that the SNP are full of strange cultists. Also, there's the fact that the SNP are happy to steal Tory policies but we'll just ignore that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fagashlil76 @NewTownSpeed @jikdmmen @MichelleGr4h4m @PoliticsScot @patrickharvie @NicolaSturgeon Also, the SNP have hardly covered themselves in glory. The very policy everyone is arguing over was actually a Tory policy that the SNP lifted from their manifesto. Perhaps some SNPers could take time to reflect upon that. It might expose some truths about the SNP they don't like]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fagashlil76 @NewTownSpeed @jikdmmen @MichelleGr4h4m @PoliticsScot @patrickharvie @NicolaSturgeon I've had 4 years of putting up with bullsh*t from SNPers. Attacks on anyone who disagrees with the SNP on anything. Conspiracy theories. Being called a Yoon because I criticise the SNP from time to time.

It's put me off voting Yes in future. Imagine how it looks to undecideds?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PoliticsScot @MichelleGr4h4m @patrickharvie @NicolaSturgeon Ah, so you agree that it was a Tory policy then? Maybe you should point that out to your fellow Yessers who've spent the night attacking the Greens for voting against a policy they disagree with.

The Greens voted against a Tory policy that the SNP tried to implement.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WullieForIndy And how many times have the SNP voted with the Tories? Will you condemn them the next time they do so? The SNP &amp; Tories have voted together far more times than the Greens have voted with the Tories.

Again, this was originally a Tory policy which the SNP stole. Unpalatable truth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Murdo01 @MichelleGr4h4m @jikdmmen @PoliticsScot @patrickharvie @NicolaSturgeon Loony.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WullieForIndy You are aware that the SNP lifted this policy straight from the Tory manifesto? Maybe the expression Tartan Tories is apt at this time.  Or you can just pretend it's not true (even though it is) and go back to spouting shit about SNPbad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PoliticsScot @MichelleGr4h4m @patrickharvie @NicolaSturgeon You're angry because the Greens voted against a policy which the SNP stole from the Tories?

I wonder how many of the SNPers arguing in favour of the policy would be doing so if it was the Tories who put it to Parliament?  Very few I imagine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jikdmmen @PoliticsScot @MichelleGr4h4m @patrickharvie @NicolaSturgeon Who's David?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lots of SNPers angry tonight because the Greens voted against a policy that the SNP stole from the Tories.

Strange times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PoliticsScot @jikdmmen @MichelleGr4h4m @patrickharvie @NicolaSturgeon Oh, and by the way, the SNP lifted this policy directly from the Tory manifesto. Maybe you should have a think about that before attacking parties for standing by what they believe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PoliticsScot @jikdmmen @MichelleGr4h4m @patrickharvie @NicolaSturgeon They voted against the policy because that's what they said they would do from the very start. You may disagree with that stance but attacking the Greens for standing by their promises is pretty disgraceful and exposes many in the indy movement as little more than SNP cultists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Credo1611 @PoliticsScot @MichelleGr4h4m @patrickharvie @NicolaSturgeon The P1 testing was a Tory policy.  The SNP lifted it from the Tory manifesto.

Make of that what you will.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PoliticsScot @MichelleGr4h4m @patrickharvie @NicolaSturgeon The Greens stood by their manifesto pledge and explained the reasons why. If you can't understand that simple concept then that's your problem. Of course, we all know the real reason is because you're upset they voted against the SNP and you're acting like a big kid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jikdmmen @PoliticsScot @MichelleGr4h4m @patrickharvie @NicolaSturgeon Do you want a list of all the times the SNP and Tories have voted together? It's considerably more times than the Greens have voted with the Tories.

Don't forget, P1 assessment was originally a Tory policy the SNP stole off them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PoliticsScot @MichelleGr4h4m @patrickharvie @NicolaSturgeon You said you're never voting Green again because they voted for a commitment they made in their OWN manifesto. Quite a ridiculous argument really isn't it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PoliticsScot @MichelleGr4h4m @jikdmmen @patrickharvie @NicolaSturgeon I look forward to your comments the next time the SNP and Tories vote together.  Which should be soon.

Of course, you'll denounce the SNP and threaten never to vote for them again.  Otherwise, you're just another hypocrite spouting meaningless shit on Twitter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichelleGr4h4m @PoliticsScot @patrickharvie @NicolaSturgeon You're clearly insane.  You enjoy the rest of your life posting garbage on Twitter (which is about all you ever seem to do to be honest).  74k tweets in five years.  Wow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Murdo01 @MichelleGr4h4m @jikdmmen @PoliticsScot @patrickharvie @NicolaSturgeon Nice to hear from you loony cultist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichelleGr4h4m @NewTownSpeed @jikdmmen @PoliticsScot @patrickharvie @NicolaSturgeon And you're clearly just another rambling, paranoid cultist who sees unionists hiding behind every hedge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PoliticsScot @MichelleGr4h4m @patrickharvie @NicolaSturgeon The SNP, as the Scottish gov't, set the example. But, as someone who said they wont vote Green again because they stood by their own manifesto commitment, I don't expect you to understand. I look forward to reading your comments the next time the SNP vote with the Tories.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichelleGr4h4m @jikdmmen @PoliticsScot @patrickharvie @NicolaSturgeon Aye, okay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NewTownSpeed @jikdmmen @MichelleGr4h4m @PoliticsScot @patrickharvie @NicolaSturgeon Ha ha.  I'll remember that the next time yer average SNPer tells me the only way to independence is to vote SNP!

Or the classic: "Only the SNP stand up for Scotland!"

Been hearing this bullshit for years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jikdmmen @MichelleGr4h4m @PoliticsScot @patrickharvie @NicolaSturgeon Let's just say I've gone off the idea having experienced the SNP and their followers at close quarters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MichelleGr4h4m @PoliticsScot @patrickharvie @NicolaSturgeon I campaigned for Yes (you're welcome to trawl back several years) but the SNP cultists and loonies have put me right off the idea. If attacking anyone with the guts to disagree with the SNP is what an indy Scotland will be like then it's not something to aspire to be a part of.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PoliticsScot @MichelleGr4h4m @patrickharvie Hey SNPers.  The next time you have an independence referendum I wont be voting yes because the SNP and their followers have proved themselves to be the biggest bunch of hypocrites in politics @NicolaSturgeon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This from a man whose ego caused the death of a socialist political party.  And citing perennial Ross Greer-hater Wings over Scotland too - a guy whose anus prolapsed the day Ross was elected to Holyrood. https://t.co/BuUHtmBFgX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SamGBeaton The SNP could propose a policy of kicking kittens in the face and some of them would be on here and Facebook trying to justify it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SNPer: "Anyone who votes with the Tories is anti-Scottish!"

Sane person: "The SNP have voted with the Tories on several occasions. They even voted with them this week in the Scottish Parliament"

SNPer: "Aye, but, it's okay when we do it..."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Ross_Greer: The SNP vote with the Tories more often than the Greens do. Examples include dozens of amendments to the planning bill this…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PoliticsScot @MichelleGr4h4m @patrickharvie @NicolaSturgeon I believe you.  Many wouldn't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @scotgp: Want to protect the environment? Join the only party in Scotland that is serious about animal welfare and protecting the enviro…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @yayitsrob: There’s something strange and inexpressible about seeing climate-change predictions come true. I’ve heard scientists talk ab…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @thehill: UN chief: World has less than 2 years to avoid "runaway climate change" https://t.co/Ab9X96D2Tq https://t.co/Tm2U01Zn9s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ClydeSSB: BREAKING: Steve Clarke and Kilmarnock have been charged by the Scottish FA after comments criticising the disciplinary proces…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @IndyWorld: Woman who wrote 'How To Murder Your Husband' essay charged with murdering husband https://t.co/SogS3zNnK3 https://t.co/ZGyjT…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GerryHassan: Scottish Green Party 'splitters' on Hope over Fear:
"I think our MSPs would rather drop dead that go anywhere near that st…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peter A Bell describing anyone else as "petty and puerile" is peak Peter A Bell. https://t.co/XLlOL1fAT9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jameskirkup: Burn the Witches! If even Caroline Lucas of the Green Party can be branded a Terf by transgender activists, no woman is sa…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BiologistDan: The beach is red with blood. Over 100 White Sided #Dolphins were slaughtered yesterday on the #FaroeIslands in #Denmark.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NorthNapper: 3 years ago 12 people lost their lives over a cartoon, the world came together with the believe nobody should die because…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LCelts: Gutted. Another great ex-Celt falls prey to the lure of Separatism. Thank God for the Celtic Board of Directors: Unionists and…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iainmacwhirter The problem with a lot of these extreme diets is that they are unsustainable. I reversed type 2 diabetes with sensible eating and exercise. There's no need to cut out whole food groups like sugar from your diet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Crazzyintheusa: Giving an honest answer. https://t.co/uUDROMCBB6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AnnaK_4ever: Here's Serena Williams fighting for women's rights in a skit that makes fun of Amelie Mauresmo's appearance. Amelie, of co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AndrewCastle63: Some closing thoughts on the #USOpen #Serena #Novak 
Did you hear that some umpires/line judges may boycott her matches…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @QuilletteM: From the archives: Attack of the Offendotrons: Tyranny of the Flash Mob | @_HelenDale https://t.co/VNx1GuJjAW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BicycleLobby: The small change is that you ditch your car and get a bike instead. https://t.co/yM7LuTzFfP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pmacgiollabhain Just putting things into context you understand. Not trying to put anyone off their dinner (especially if they're eating meat while raging about a goat being shot).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Pmacgiollabhain On the one hand the goat died instantly. On the other hand lambs, cows &amp; pigs get reared, driven to an abattoir and have their throats slit. In industrial slaughterhouses, chickens are killed prior to scalding by being passed through an electrified water-bath while shackled.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>