<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Logitech is reportedly offering $2.2 billion to bring Plantronics headsets into its hardware empire: Logitech, the manufacturer best known for its computing peripherals like keyboards and web cameras, is in talks to buy Plantronics, a maker of… https://t.co/oXgVl9VdN6 https://t.co/etL7TFbyso]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[House Oversight Committee chairman suggests videotaping Comey testimony: House Oversight Committee Chairman Trey Gowdy says videotaping former FBI Director James Comey in a closed-door testimony next month would prevent selective leaking and avoid a… https://t.co/3qCAdjmEbM https://t.co/AD1C9yaRib]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solution Architect: Because you belong at Twilio The Who, What, Why and Where Twilio is growing rapidly and seeking a Solutions Architect to join our team in London. The role of the Twilio Solutions Architect is crucial to the successful execution of our… https://t.co/JRS5W6z4b3 https://t.co/bNPHCtAb8R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Professional Database Administrator: **Job Description:** **Summary** Plans, designs, develops, and implements complex computerized databases, to include data definition, structure, documentation of databases, long-range requirements, operational… https://t.co/PkDTnmCXZL https://t.co/2w3gtcH0dp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inside Sales Account Manager – Channel: Inside Sales Account Manager – Channel Inside Sales Account Manager – Channel Competitive salary Uxbridge People make Dell – so wherever in the world they work, everyone is rewarded for their contribution. Ready to… https://t.co/sZML1kCS2a https://t.co/BEaxs2210C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's at stake on Cyber Monday: It sounds outdated, but Cyber Monday is still a thing. https://t.co/gaGAIivaYd https://t.co/BLRMliLyuP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET senior developer role: Job Type:PermanentDate Posted:30th October 2018Location:Luton, EnglandContact Name:Zarah AhmedTelephone:+ 44 191 230 1883Reference:30/10/2018za5 Salary:Up to £55000 per annum + friendly working environment, flexi-time .NET… https://t.co/dI7vkJkIG4 https://t.co/fdvhSlIUw6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Technology Systems Analyst: SunIRef:it Senior Technology Systems Analyst PK18 – Princeton, NJ – ********** Find Jobs Company Reviews Find Salaries Find Resumes Employers / Post Job Upload your resume Sign in Home whatjob title, keywords, or… https://t.co/RPwvge9j6D https://t.co/LwWbgG8Nfw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infrastructure Engineer: Infrastructure Engineer  Cellmark is UK's largest forensic and DNA testing companies in the world delivering a broad portfolio of services and specialism; with a proven reputation for quality, reliability and technological… https://t.co/sPKDoQrKxa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Millions under blizzard warning as winter storm impacts holiday travel: A winter storm is expected to bring snow, wind and rain to a large swath of the country and affect travelers in the final stretch of the holiday weekend. https://t.co/fzaomBWewZ https://t.co/nxepniSTKM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Director – London – GBP80, 000pa: My client is a British manufacturer and distribution company with significant global presence; they are well known for creating a range of unique products that are unprecedented within their industry. The organisation… https://t.co/PgTaoJ4ssV https://t.co/3Pn9WwNQO5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer // GBP45,000 // Peterborough: Job Type:PermanentDate Posted:2nd November 2018Location:Peterborough, EnglandContact Name:Adam GowlandTelephone:Reference:F54TWH34CM Salary: Web Developer // £45,000 // Peterborough As the year draws closer to… https://t.co/pacdLCRSQf https://t.co/fp96UcYiu2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ernst: 'Would rather' no government shutdown over Trump wall: Iowa GOP Sen. Joni Ernst said with just days remaining until the funding deadline for key agencies that she would prefer no government shutdown over President Donald Trump's wall. https://t.co/xqN3DWwJRn https://t.co/46S8ACAB3P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Accountant: Financial Accountant Financial Accountant Job Locations UK-London ID 2018-3283 Position Type Permanent – Full Time Overview About the position We are seeking a financial accountant to join our UK &amp; Europe regional accounting team.… https://t.co/f8WjIqtkai https://t.co/SG9oLmYb8b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intermodal Coordinator (Rail): CMA CGM, founded by Jacques R. Saad, is a leading worldwide shipping group. Its 504 vessels call more than 420 ports in the world on all 5 continents. In 2017, they carried 18.9 million TEUs (twenty-foot equivalent units).… https://t.co/qlz7LZm1VK https://t.co/VIxfvYyL7c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The measure now goes to the UK Parliament for a vote: All 27 European Union leaders signed off Britain's Brexit deal, at a crucial summit in Brussels on Sunday. https://t.co/dGLNTQxJXB https://t.co/j2CEu0JPBD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET C# DEVELOPER up to GBP45,000: Job Type:PermanentDate Posted:29th October 2018Location:West Midlands, EnglandContact Name:Zarah AhmedTelephone:+ 44 191 230 1883Reference:29/10/2018 Salary:Up to £45000 per annum + pension, 25 days holiday .NET C#… https://t.co/sL0TXXCXQ7 https://t.co/FWzpArJg7b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Front End Developer @ Seattle, WA 3 Years…: SunIRef:it Senior Front End Developer @ Seattle, WA 98109 :::: 3 Years (C2H) – Seattle, WA – ********** Find Jobs Company Reviews Find Salaries Find Resumes Employers / Post Job Upload your resume Sign… https://t.co/FIIbLgFlYA https://t.co/tB5Fu7D4Eu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Computer Programmer (Consultant): SunIRef:it Senior Computer Programmer (Consultant) – Baltimore, MD – ********** Find Jobs Company Reviews Find Salaries Find Resumes Employers / Post Job Upload your resume Sign in Home whatjob title, keywords, or… https://t.co/1B72grMn63 https://t.co/dB9gLlt0K2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer – Hertfordshire – GBP55k – GBP60k – No Travel: SharePoint Developer £55k to £60k plus bonus – No Travel Required + Excellent Career Progression Plan + Training Budget SharePoint Wizard required to join an elite development team for… https://t.co/PlZqjVaDw5 https://t.co/0NZJfdBDBv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Azure DevOps Engineer, Powershell, Azure, ARM, Service Fabric: Azure DevOps Engineer: Powershell, Azure, ARM, Application Service, Service Fabric Location: Milton Keynes Salary: £500 – £600 Per day Start Date: ASAP I’m working with a well-established… https://t.co/a5xGutXPLE https://t.co/DC4ZRHaJkS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[France to return stolen art housed in museum: France will return 26 works of art to Benin, Nigeria, more than a century after it took them from the west African nation. CNN's Lynda Kinkade reports. https://t.co/6ZzMHg23jm https://t.co/6i2nUHcbB0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Support Specialist: Hiring Now | Application Support Specialist We are currently recruiting for a large organisation in the gaming sector, who are based in Watford and looking for a number of talented Application Support Specialists! We're… https://t.co/6CzeAe5D1p https://t.co/REn0FvfNeQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Business Analyst – Manchester £45-50K: Senior Business Analyst – Manchester £45-50K. Our client based in Manchester is currently looking for a skilled Senior Business Analyst. The role will be to work as a Senior Business Analyst within the PMO,… https://t.co/saqLTsFcWA https://t.co/p0SA4kigCK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Official calls mom's request to use campaign funds for child care a 'misplaced priority': A Louisiana mom, running for office for the first time, thought about taking her kindergartner and her 1½-year-old along with her on the campaign trail. But she… https://t.co/JaSlCGZA44 https://t.co/RnNbXEPbpx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C# Engineer: Are you a C# Engineer looking to learn functional programming in F#? Are you a C# Engineer that wants to experiment with the latest tech? Well then, I have the answer – join a global business, working on highly transactional, highly… https://t.co/bz1m5UorJD https://t.co/1IXnw2BA0z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Applications Developer – .Net/C#/SQL: Chase and Holland are working with a bespoke software development company just north of Nottingham for IT Application Developers (.Net/C#/SQL). This is arguably one of the best companies in the area to work for,… https://t.co/O1IL4Hf7wU https://t.co/p0fvrEJSWX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An argument at a Florida Walmart leads to gunfire and a woman is killed: An argument Saturday at a Florida Walmart garden center ended when a woman was fatally shot several times, Ocala Police Department spokeswoman Meghan Shay said. https://t.co/SjWcK8TtSm https://t.co/zFghpPBoDd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Migration/Administration Analyst: Data Migration/Administration Analyst Location – Cheadle Excellent Salary + Benefits An exciting opportunity has become available for an experienced Data Migration/Administration Analyst to join a leading provider… https://t.co/PkTbzwD5GU https://t.co/B9VGHUhdKl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2nd Line IT Support Engineer – Wimborne – £24-26K: 2nd Line IT Support Engineer required by a technology business based in Ferndown. Are you keen to become an integral part of an IT team requiring you to provide IT support to businesses based in Dorset… https://t.co/0qRpBKSkMF https://t.co/9ry94hicqo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Engineer: Technical Support Engineer Reading Permanent Circa £24-28k + benefits Our client are a market leader in the supply and installation of electronic locking systems into the hospitality and allied sectors supplying to both new… https://t.co/0CmzQEpcgG https://t.co/DoQyuoGvuj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More than 100 sea turtles found dead: A total of 173 sea turtles died off Cape Cod, Massachusetts, this week because of the extreme cold, according to Mass Audubon Director Bob Prescott. https://t.co/rDTXP2JZre https://t.co/E26ZNsdWSz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Floorwalker – Windows 10 Project – Swindon – Up to £140 per day: Floorwalker – Windows 10 Project – Swindon – Up to £140 per day 4 month initial contract – End of November start (Floorwalker, Floorwalking, First Line, 1st Line, Second Line, 2nd Line,… https://t.co/I6udggctIw https://t.co/6vcUESDNQI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Assistant Vice President, QA Testing Manager: Job Description Job Title: Assistant Vice President, QA &amp; Testing Manager – {KD9178} Job ID: ******* Location: Cary Full/Part Time: Full-time Regular/Temporary: Permanent Technology Our technology teams are… https://t.co/CM5qpO37SS https://t.co/IB2IAKkNdy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automation Tester – Hampshire – £350 per day: Automation Tester – Hampshire – £350 per day I am currently looking for a Automation tester who has strong experience with selenium and C#. This is initially a 3 month project working for an integration… https://t.co/3evJcMTxbT https://t.co/7eDsVQZTzm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Account Manager – German Speaking: German Speaking Account Manager – FlightGlobal – London At FlightGlobal we are proud. Proud of our heritage, since 1909, and proud of the future business we are building together. Our people are at the centre of… https://t.co/4bW1lewl0g https://t.co/cisibLfSKZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Consultant: DevOps Consultant – AWS, Linux, Docker – Woking Your Role: As an experienced DevOps Consultant you will play a major part in a large project rolling out across the business. About You: You will be an experienced DevOps Consultant,… https://t.co/YQIBeiXGqN https://t.co/HBhkiqj4cQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Graduate Software Developer: Location: Birchwood, WA3 Our client is an international Global organisation, who are currently experiencing phenomenal growth. This is a fantastic time for the right person for someone who is looking to enhance your existing… https://t.co/TruobOl0BO https://t.co/8nk2LCCbPO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Radio host who satirized ISIS shot dead: A Syrian radio host who satirized both President Bashar al-Assad and opposition insurgents including ISIS has been shot dead in the rebel-held Idlib province, the Syrian Observatory for Human Rights (SOHR) said. https://t.co/NlXr8FkzJl https://t.co/QkZH8InoPL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software developer in test, SDET: Do you like variety – exciting clients and optional work from home and therefore can be based anywhere within the UK? Do you like the challenge of building automation frameworks from scratch or evolving and… https://t.co/JovFw4fvrS https://t.co/GDdHPsbGGO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Research Software Engineer, Artificial Intelligence: Title Research Software Engineer, Artificial Intelligence Job Description IBM Research is the innovation engine of IBM. Nearly every game-changing breakthrough in the information technology industry… https://t.co/iuQAukKna6 https://t.co/0H4YiVMKtD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Design Engineer: Are you an experienced Network Designer Engineer, specialising in Cisco and looking for a new contract? If so then please get in touch…. Network Designer / Cisco / Loadbalance / Checkpoint / Fortinet / CLI / Command Line… https://t.co/IMcSSnbdIE https://t.co/t9SBvTdrrx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harry and Meghan to leave Palace grounds: Prince Harry and Megan will move to Windsor early next year as they prepare for the arrival of their first child, Kensington Palace has announced. https://t.co/rsAKQunK6B https://t.co/ANz04Ar6ru]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ICT Data /Technical Project Manager: A Project Manager is needed to join an Information centric programme. The individual will be responsible for delivering projects related to Master Data Management, Business Intelligence and Enterprise Data… https://t.co/J7q4lNV50G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Product – Payment Factory -SAP Innovative Business Solutions,: Product – Payment Factory -SAP Innovative Business Solutions, Job Close By continuing to use and navigate this website, you are agreeing to the use of cookies. Accept – SAP Careers home – SAP… https://t.co/f0hN5fE5XR https://t.co/7Oh3bg7ypA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Support Engineer: Are you looking to join one of the fastest growing companies in the UK that are investing in new technology, providing one on one training, and input into their future IT infrastructure strategy? This is an excellent opportunity for… https://t.co/BTmqXgqy86 https://t.co/fqiVR9qyqx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer, AI Platform: Company Description We believe everyone should be able to participate and thrive in the economy. So were building tools that make commerce easier and more accessible to all. We started with a little white credit… https://t.co/o7z19K3SPS https://t.co/tlgfB8boAS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[x2 Azure DevOps Engineer: I am working on behalf of a well known Award Winning British technology firm who have an immediate requirement in the Azure team. You will be required to be on site in Coventry 5 days a week to start, remote working can be an… https://t.co/Ud0nO7TStW https://t.co/GxGbvP4mNy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Front End Developer: SunIRef:it Software Engineer – Front End Developer – Columbia, SC – ********** Find Jobs Company Reviews Find Salaries Find Resumes Employers / Post Job Upload your resume Sign in Home whatjob title, keywords, or… https://t.co/kqS45D60he https://t.co/63iYDVGkyW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man thought responsible for Alabama mall shooting is at large, not dead, police say: A 21-year-old man killed by an officer at a mall in Alabama on Thanksgiving night "likely did not fire" the shots that wounded two people and sent terrified shoppers… https://t.co/K3tJPf4riG https://t.co/9BDB78sRYS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Change Consultant: Business Change Consultant up to £70000 Consultancy Excellent Benefits*, Flexible work locality We are seeking a Business Change Consultant to join a leading innovative data team in a prestigious organisation. Our client… https://t.co/pOv6Ek4Ko3 https://t.co/Ffmswm1cma]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GIS Manager: SunIRef:it GIS Manager – Oakland, CA 94606 – ********** Find Jobs Company Reviews Find Salaries Find Resumes Employers / Post Job Upload your resume Sign in Home whatjob title, keywords, or company wherecity, state, or zip code Find Jobs… https://t.co/GZ8Tyu6FqK https://t.co/7CJNvoJdMv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: My Client is a leading consulting, technology and innovation firm who are looking for an IT Project Manager to join their team. The role will be targeted at an IT Project Manager who is familiar with a range of methods to deliver… https://t.co/RFQ98Gog3p https://t.co/PHQcXrIN9g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst – SC Clearance Essential: Role: Business Analyst Contracting Authority: Home Office Contract Length: 12 months Location: Croydon IR35: Out of Scope Pay Rate to Candidate: £550 The role is a Business Analyst role with focus on IT Service… https://t.co/PRwyy4lxzo https://t.co/issp1FjogX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listeria outbreak prompts recall of Vietnamese pork rolls: A multistate outbreak of listeria has been traced to a Houston manufacturer's Vietnamese ready-to-eat pork products, the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention announced this week. https://t.co/mec2lTCCSz https://t.co/nI8Ez20Ci8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Net Developer – Up to £40k p/a – Birmingham: Job Title: .Net Developer Job Type: Full Time/Permanent Salary: £30,000 – £40,000 p/a depending on experience We are looking for an experienced web developer to strengthen our growing team. This is an exciting… https://t.co/01SWDo6usI https://t.co/8KJnm9WISU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Onsite Engineer – Leading Microsoft Gold Partner: Onsite Engineer – Leading Microsoft Gold Partner Up to 27k + benefits + fully funded Microsoft certifications About the business: Our client are a Microsoft Gold Partner who provide Enterprise services &amp;… https://t.co/jhobjDVLIM https://t.co/0vn876inf2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior Software Developer: Junior Software Developer – London – £23k – £26k – Suitable for a Recent Graduate Sparta Global is looking for graduates who want to launch a dynamic career in tech. We hire from a wide range of degree subjects in order to… https://t.co/ho5qkUMGGa https://t.co/jTs01ppqur]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Engineer: Technical Support Engineer Milton Keynes £27,000 + Benefits This is an outstanding opportunity for you, an experienced IT Technical Support Engineer / Application Support Engineer to join a leading Software company in Milton… https://t.co/OYd5nCsvsL https://t.co/Ch75vumt1B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2nd Line Support Analyst – Urgent Contract – Immediate Start: 2nd Line Support Analyst – Urgent Contract – Immediate Start IT Support Engineer required to join our client in Fife. This will be on a 1 month rolling contract with a chance of permanency on… https://t.co/ybRb39sNa9 https://t.co/ddoImuTJbW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BI &amp; MI Analyst: Job Title: Business Intelligence &amp; Marketing Insights Analyst Location: Surrey Salary: £50,000 – £55,000 Evolve Recruitment are currently recruiting for a Business Intelligence &amp; Marketing Analyst within the Marketing department to… https://t.co/IqKTRzwAqi https://t.co/w6gQAbkvje]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NET Developer (Contract): Contract .NET Developer Harrogate £250 – £300 p/d I’m working with a client who are currently seeking an experienced developer to join them on a massive greenfield project. This opportunity will give you the chance to work in a… https://t.co/8WuyG5SQYI https://t.co/8h94jwUqfF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nine Democrats vow to oppose Pelosi for speaker unless changes are adopted: As House Democratic leader Nancy Pelosi clears hurdles in her bid to become the next speaker, nine members of her own party circulated a letter on Friday indicating they will not… https://t.co/GDfx60qFAS https://t.co/798UcWQr4V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Qualified Legal Manager Solicitor: Are you a Solicitor or Legal Manager ? Are you an commercial IT solicitor legal executive with in-house or in private practice with a law degree. A glimpse of what you will be doing… • Assisting the Group Legal… https://t.co/inNBfB9CMU https://t.co/MOpxDALjf6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Night shift technical operator: Night shift technical operator. We are currently searching Nightshift Operators with good IT and excellent customer service skills to work with our client, based in the Swindon area. The role for the night shift operator… https://t.co/vKTNzH8eQz https://t.co/6IWQKjgWw5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Business Analyst – IT Change/Team Management: A Lead Business Analyst is required by a leading organisation based in Swindon. The successful individual will be an expert in their field and will manage a team of Analysts to provide support for the… https://t.co/aHduANr5tq https://t.co/BtOIzwLZMI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales Operations Business Intelligence Analyst: SunIRef:it Sales Operations Business Intelligence Analyst – Provo, UT – ********** Find Jobs Company Reviews Find Salaries Find Resumes Employers / Post Job Upload your resume Sign in Home whatjob title,… https://t.co/AlyT8fPVET https://t.co/bR9y9gEL9l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Trump administration report warns that climate change will have dire consequences for the US https://t.co/209DhMUzsv https://t.co/M65dlkBnaG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Development Manager: Business Development Manager Salary up to £40,000 DOE + Commission at 15% for anything over £20,000 per month. Experienced in IT sales? Experienced in working in an SME and Commercial Market? Have a natural flair for… https://t.co/ZpoCne1b8A https://t.co/6hnV6egCrR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer – Ecommerce: Network Engineer – Ecommerce The Network Administrator role is a senior technical position to Administrate maintain and design the SIE Europe network, while ensuring that all aspects of SIEE systems adhere to policy… https://t.co/rIL0XByp0N https://t.co/Op6Mrwnogd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysis: Trump crosses new lines in frenetic Thanksgiving: Donald Trump might have constructed a political career on the idea of building a wall, but he rejects every institutional and behavioral barrier that constrains a President's freedom to do… https://t.co/fpfok6CUGP https://t.co/N0WcelnuwM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT APPRENTICE: JOB ROLE The role of the IT Apprentice is to offer technical support to both internal and occasionally external customers. Dealing with local issues and supporting projects if / where necessary. Responsibilities. The IT Apprentice will be… https://t.co/Qa93L1Farm https://t.co/2QuEsMNXrF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Assistant: THE COMPANY: Brewster Pratap are recruiting in partnership with our client for an IT Assistant to take on a varied and interesting role spanning IT software support across the business as well as some online marketing support. The role… https://t.co/NcRh19BPuf https://t.co/143IcbD54W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scala developers (or Java developers with exposure to Scala): Scala Developer– Manchester City Centre – £425 – £475 PD – 12 month contract. I am currently recruiting for Scala developer (or Java developer with some exposure to Scala) to embark on a… https://t.co/WPX3tLsaEq https://t.co/AMNUVLZ02c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pay no interest on holiday gifts until 2020 https://t.co/P9dEGafakJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: C# Web Developer Permanent Birchwood – Warrington Competitive salary depending on experience, plus rewarding benefits package * Do you wish to develop market leading software? * Do you have experience in the full development… https://t.co/iKrcoVXDwl https://t.co/Os4yaxCuYG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minneapolis Internal Audit and Financial Advisory — IT Audit Experienced Consultant: At Protiviti, we believe that a career is about more than just working, providing deliverables, and being compensated for your efforts. A Protiviti Career is about… https://t.co/mmosczwNVh https://t.co/VY3TK0tPVA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle Database Administrator: Oracle Database Administrator – Brussels – Telecommunications – 6 Month Contract My client, a Telecommunications company based in Brussels, are looking for an Oracle Database Administrator with development experience for a… https://t.co/ORqViJCz5W https://t.co/zlwI1CKQot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior SharePoint Developer – BAH EHRM: initiate-solutions | Point Developer – BAH EHRM – About Us – Capabilities – Success – Careers – News – Contact Us – More Senior Point Developer – BAH EHRM to IGS – Send your Resume and Cover Letter to… https://t.co/71pJ7bPTcd https://t.co/LyaOMv0MCg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer – Python: Python Developer £50,000 – £60,000 Just south of Manchester, past Old Trafford, but not quite as far as Macclesfield, there lives a world class little Business Intelligence firm. And from the quiet confines of an unsuspecting… https://t.co/BFhEJAMOdO https://t.co/ueYfXwZ8Qr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Consulting Engineer- Cisco Network: Senior Consulting Engineer- Cisco Network in Charlotte, NC – CDW – Home – Teams – Search Jobs – Life at CDW – Benefits – Transitioning Military – Join our Talent Network Join the CDW COMMUNITY true Home / Job… https://t.co/yS9Vrg4IPz https://t.co/f8uzvU6V0G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police: 2 wounded in Alabama mall shooting. Gunman killed: A shooting took place at a mall in Hoover, Alabama, on Thursday night, police said. https://t.co/190cR50NLA https://t.co/RxpvLTeBIn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Test Automation Engineer: SoCode are proud to be working alongside a highly successful, innovative printing technology company based the Cambridge area. Due to growth and success, our client has huge expansion plans and there is an opening for a… https://t.co/knpGKWsK46]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Category Manager: SunIRef:it IT Category Manager – Tarrytown, NY – ********** Find Jobs Company Reviews Find Salaries Find Resumes Employers / Post Job Upload your resume Sign in Home whatjob title, keywords, or company wherecity, state, or zip code… https://t.co/PxVRRmmXYf https://t.co/6cwxQMWP8b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Manager Solutions Specialist:   Job Description – Senior Manager Solutions Specialist (28027) Job Description  Senior Manager Solutions Specialist – 28027  Profession : Business Development  Work Location : Europe-United Kingdom-London  Schedule… https://t.co/dwEsW0DS5A https://t.co/hSvy99uMzb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer Software 4:   Job Description – Engineer Software 4 (18018052) Engineer Software 4 Requisition ID : 18018052 Location : United States-California-Redondo Beach US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation Assistance: Relocation… https://t.co/2BQxst2q2Q https://t.co/2DJU71WBMe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every Black Friday deal worth shopping https://t.co/G5ofroZDZ4 https://t.co/ib0bucSBqp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Developer (SQL Server &amp; TSQL): My client a leading technology and software development business based in the heart of Devon are looking for an experienced SQL Server Developer (TSQL &amp; SQL) to join their growing development team. To be considered… https://t.co/XsKcoPP2NF https://t.co/1kW55XJppq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software engineer – Java &amp; JavaScript: ob Position : Software Engineer – Java &amp; JavaScript Contract Type (published) : Permanent Job Category (multi select) : Highways IT &amp; computing Job Profile (published) : The Technology Services (TS) team within Mott… https://t.co/iygR1lPMCN https://t.co/70aQ1hUFl4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Service Manager: IT Service Manager – Service Desk, ITIL, Implementation IT Service Manager looking for a new opportunity to elevate and develop your career? Does this sound like you …..Yes? Keep reading as this maybe the role for you. This… https://t.co/RrKy2l9WLG https://t.co/UUZ1tT918s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Consultant (O365): Quinton Davies has been engaged by a global business to secure a Technical Consultant for a permanent role that will be home based. Our client have undergone an Office 365 implementation and all has gone well from a technical… https://t.co/bFZizbQeUX https://t.co/atnQohMLGc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Support Analyst: Our rapidly expanding biotech organisation is seeking an Application Support Analyst to join their Service Management &amp; Customer Support Team. You would be working as an Application Support Analyst for a cutting-edge… https://t.co/JQGc1ilmK2 https://t.co/PjMzlrXRtO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump: I'm thankful for the difference I've made: On this Thanksgiving, Donald Trump is thankful for his family -- as well as the "tremendous difference" he has made as President. https://t.co/N3rq7NRbUu https://t.co/xXrfSE6O0S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Service Delivery Manager: This is a fantastic opportunity for an experienced Service Delivery Manager to work with an global human services provider who are commited to building strong socities in which citizens can thrive. Overview The RRP IT Service… https://t.co/PQBQQAZHKi https://t.co/1jgQExce01]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Tester – Graduate Programme – January 2019 Start: Enjoy problem solving? Can you spot mistakes? Possess a keen eye for detail? If you are ambitious, analytical and interested in technology and wish to build a successful career with a FTSE 250… https://t.co/HbcNhVCnxR https://t.co/nDs8m48Dt6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PHP developer: PHP developer / upto £45,000 / Central Bristol PHP/Doctrine/Lavarel/Symfony/Jenkins/MS SQL A new opportunity for both junior and senior PHP developers to join our clients team in the heart of Bristol. Our client is looking to further… https://t.co/47GYZA0Sqy https://t.co/ipGptHdaeS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: After his politicized Thanksgiving call, maybe Trump should not visit the troops: President Donald Trump says he will soon be visiting troops in a war zone. It's a pity he's had to be goaded into that. https://t.co/ybIL8HvQQ0 https://t.co/NzcjwrONxm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Program Manager, AWS Recruiting Operations: Job Description Senior Program Manager, AWS Recruiting Operations We are working to be the most customer-centric company on earth. To get there, we need exceptionally talented, bright, and driven people.… https://t.co/KJKMRgiRTV https://t.co/GjZpcP8lxy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Architect – Gent (Belgium) – 12 Months: Full Stack Architect – Gent (Belgium) – 12 Months+ Full Stack Architect required for my client in Brussels on a long-term mission. ROLE: You will be required to work on architectural improvements to an… https://t.co/J83TaUnhdl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Architect: Technical Architect – Burnley – Up to £45k Server Virtualisation, VMware, Root Cause Analyst, Cloud Solutions, Cisco, Citrix This well-established organisation requires a driven and self-motivated Technical Architect to join their… https://t.co/4ggX20deGb]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>