<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about the Bay Area city of San Ramon, California http://t.co/nmfwUvHAWO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I'm going dancing, then I wear the highest heels with the shortest dress. - Kate Moss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of High Heel Shoes  http://t.co/YfKFyywHlK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one is too big to be kind and courteous, but many are too little]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Pink Floyd  http://t.co/iKjdqJu6uV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome ping pong t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the table tennis lovers in your life!   http://t.co/i9vndDgglI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've learned that when things seem to go wrong, stay calm and wait till you see the bigger picture!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't compare me to my father. Our similarities are different. -  Dale Berra about his father Yogi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Guide to Business to Business Internet Marketing on LinkedIn  http://t.co/4cULNxXjif]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man with a lot of money may be a bad egg, but folks seldom take offense until he is broke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calling upon my years of experience, I froze at the controls. - Stirling Moss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Yanjing Beer  http://t.co/TKbuGF4UEH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sign on a greenhouse: Fresh flowers just out of bed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Andy Kim  http://t.co/MNjlBx3Ml3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Jack in the Box  http://t.co/9tELo1T859]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Mars Rover Curiosity  http://t.co/zzQW6DmPHu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the Little House on the Prairie Episode The Nephews  http://t.co/JKJSnMAXSw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Grand Slam in Tennis – what's the big deal?  http://t.co/3c7rU2ywkd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana’s Lyme Journey – Part 17 – More on Supplements  http://t.co/1a6CJcoUrf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's behind you doesn't matter. - Enzo Ferrari]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ELVIS - The King - One Person's Thoughts  http://t.co/uVX2HKypsX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My name is Inigo Montoya. You killed my father. Prepare to die! - Inigo, The Princess Bride]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poets are like baseball pitchers. Both have their moments. The intervals are the tough things. - Robert Frost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Media are tools.  Real time is mindset.  David Scott - Marketing Strategist - Author of The New Rules of Marketing and PR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One family that practices population control:  the mafia!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It may be true that most people can't stand prosperity, but it is also true that most people don't have to!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the star wars lover in your family - Jedi Dressing Gowns - May the force be with you!  http://t.co/hIXzdcsifU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got hit in the head pretty hard. My clock ran backwards for two years. - Buddy Baker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like my money right where I can see it -- hanging in my closet. - Carrie Bradshaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any government big enough to give you everything you want is big enough to take it away from you, too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making the Most of Twitter for Your Business  http://t.co/HAYKpdemdJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ultimately, the only power to which man should aspire is that which he exercises over himself. - Elie Wiesel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A toupee is ear to ear carpeting!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The dog was created especially for children. He is the God of frolic. - Henry Ward Beecher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My software never has bugs. It just develops random features.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't fix stupid - Larry Morgan, NHRA Pro Stock driver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You gotta love the 80s and there was nothing better than the crazy fitness trends - http://t.co/VYLvtzpKhq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes make me happy. - Actress Lauren Conrad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've never heard a Jay-Z song.  Miley Cyrus on Jay-Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the dressing room, I always put on my right shoe first. Same thing for my right wristband. -  Mary Lou Retton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inflation is when you pay fifteen dollars for the ten-dollar haircut you used to get for five dollars when you had hair. - Sam Ewing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About The History of Fitness Equipment  http://t.co/JpLVrdlX5t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The Top 10 European Beers  http://t.co/u4ANiUcETH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome biking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the biking lovers in your life!  http://t.co/gJiGfwifM2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then close your eyes and tap your heels together three times. And think to yourself, "There's no place like home" - The Wizard of Oz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome cooking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the cooking lovers in your life!   http://t.co/cnULaYsPHS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious What Went Wrong T-shirt - Love It!  http://t.co/aygY2FHpne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing worthwhile comes easily. Work, continuous work and hard work, is the only way to accomplish results that last. - Hamilton Holt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excuse me, miss, a little bit of your face is showing around your makeup - you might want to take care of that!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome burgers and beer t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the beer &amp; beer lovers in your life!  http://t.co/5aqyK5ZhvR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Lesley Gore  http://t.co/shl2ROowqH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its better to own the racecourse then the race horse - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the hot new Minecraft video channel Crimson Mine - http://t.co/lrjpngLIlG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really love this Han Solo iPhone case - may the force be with you! http://t.co/FjCkwb6FK6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Barbara Acklin - The Popular Singer  http://t.co/pKwjwPiYcu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Adding Solar Power for Heating Pool  http://t.co/Ikh5QKPisv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've been carbo loading for the last 20 years in the off chance I have to go on a 4000 mile run across the US!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The History of The Six Million Dollar Man  http://t.co/FFlC3RjUrJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The trick is to stop thinking of it as your money - IRS auditor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not let what you cannot do interfere with what you can do. - John Wooden]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Put on your red shoes, and dance the blues. - David Bowie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Seniors and Social Networking  http://t.co/OuMLSy2xmP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blogging Season 1 of Lilyhammer by Netflix   http://t.co/Nu3IbiYNET]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Jimmy Choo  http://t.co/0H9qorISJN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Kool and the Gang  http://t.co/fDXDq5MwIb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Running SUCKS! How to Run for Fast Weight Loss - For Busy Women Who HATE Running --&gt; http://t.co/T4vW9Iik4Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drill sarge to recruit:  "wipe that opinion off your face!”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion changes, but style endures. --&gt; Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wasn't satisfied just to earn a good living. I was looking to make a statement. - Donald Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've been carbo loading for the last 20 years in the off chance I have to go on a 4000 mile run across the US!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is that which discloses to the wise and disguises from the foolish their lack of understanding. - Ambrose Bierce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How to Select Best Climbing Equipment  http://t.co/6l0SA3eDzg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But I'm a rock 'n' roll singer; that's my livelihood, my occupation.  - Little Richard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If having a soul means being able to feel love and loyalty and gratitude, then animals are better off than a lot of humans - James Herriot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the top burger chains in the US!  http://t.co/qS1I30Kk3U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greetings, programs! - Flynn, TRON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sorry. You are right. Those pants don't make you look fat. - Jin-Soo Kwon  The only three things a woman needs to hear! - Sawyer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Importance of Competitive Analysis of Strategy Consulting Firms  http://t.co/CKumoaysWi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celiac Disease Requires Gluten Free Foods - Learn More  http://t.co/kVngFFH3iF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Skol Beer  http://t.co/Z7DxX5GgCT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get a Hunger Games Mockingjay Pin - http://t.co/okgrwWrp9a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Mountain Climbing from Novice to Experts  http://t.co/TRqxTsebSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Wendy's  http://t.co/oR6KSrakIe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Gladys Knight and the Pips  http://t.co/cAWyBLgSC7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making money is not gonna change anything about what I am, except I won't answer the door. Abel Ferrara]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Brady Bunch is an American sitcom classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/qKRGT5gwpi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But I'm a rock 'n' roll singer; that's my livelihood, my occupation.  - Little Richard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Barbara Acklin a Great Singer http://t.co/5wFJ2WfeYC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Careers end with a ground ball to shortstop, not with a home run. - Bull Durham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL - A Runny Nose In Your Shower Dispensing Soap - Love It!  http://t.co/wY7k7MbTWK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guns Don't Kill People, Dads With Pretty Daughters Kill People http://t.co/DfTTvU98H2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 10 - Support Group Meeting  http://t.co/AEfoGkS63y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret of toe cleavage, a very important part of the sexuality of the shoe; you must only show the first two cracks. - Manolo Blahnik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the fascinating history of that classic baseball park - Wrigley Field - http://t.co/t0lP0wGcaH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame Turf Wars: Them Hackers Though  http://t.co/nodtp1LCIg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Grapevine, Texas  http://t.co/rq30TRxO52]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education costs money, but then so does ignorance. - Sir Claus Moser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool A Clear Bottomed 2 - Person Kayak - A Unique Way to Enjoy Paddling! http://t.co/H4DnfrJHTm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yah! I'm on the "Starts tomorrow" diet!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Middle age is when you still have the spark but now it takes more puffing.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>