<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe I hope too much. Maybe I dream too much. But at least I won't give up until I've tried, and I won't regret anything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want him to text me first just to prove I was on his mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never regretted telling you I liked you. The only regret I have is never hearing what you really thought of me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haters don't really hate you, they just envy you and hate themselves because you're a reflection of what they cannot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll wait for you, until I have no reason to wait anymore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a story behind every person, a reason why they are the way they are. So think about that before you judge someone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Letting go is having the courage to accept change and having the strength to keep moving.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every girl needs a good guy who can help her laugh when she thinks she'll never smile again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I pray not because I need something, but because I'm ought to thank God about something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To love someone is to understand each other, to laugh together, to smile with your heart, and to trust one another.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A real relationship: has fights, trust, faith, tears, pain, argument, patience, secrets, jealousy, and LOVE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder why peoples smile when they heart actually cry? Doesn't it make you feel more sad?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[G: So is it gonna be me or her? B: If you love me, you wouldn't make me choose. G: If you love me, there wouldn't even be an option.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every girl wants a boy who will love her from depth of his heart and protect her from everyone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you God for blessing me much more than I deserve.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't ever be afraid to show who you really are, because as long as you are happy with yourself, no one else's opinion matters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jatuh cinta itu memang di luar kontrol kita. Tapi berkomitmen untuk tetap saling mencintai ada di dalam kontrol kita.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman's smile can also mean pain. Sometimes a smile is just a mask while she tries to remain strong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There comes a time when you have to choose between turning the page or just closing the book.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can never teach a guy to love you the way you want to be loved. You have to wait for him to do it his own way at his own time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be close to that person who makes you happy, but be closer to that person who can't be happy without you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God is ALWAYS doing a work in your life. Sometimes He may be behind the scenes, and you may not feel it right away, but He is there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every girl has that guy she will never stop loving and every guy has that one girl he will never stop fighting for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's the guy who makes me believe that true love can be found.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True love is when someone accepts your past, supports your presents, and encourages your future.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My heart is perfect because you're inside it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That moment when you are really sleepy but you don't want to go to sleep because you are talking to that special someone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know what my future holds, but I'm hoping you're in it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are times when I'd stare at the sky at night and wonder why you are my entire universe when I'm not even a little star in yours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know why we fight or argue. It doesn't make me love you less, but it does make me realize how much I truly love you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't predict when love will arrive. Only GOD knows. The only thing you can do is wait, be patient, and trust Him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go for someone who is not only proud to have you, but will also take every risk just to be with you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like you more than you can imagine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter what standards we set for our lover, the fact will always remain that the person we fall in love with will always be an exception.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A girl is happiest when she knows you make her your everything in front of everyone, every time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you love someone, be brave enough to tell them, otherwise, be brave enough to watch them be loved by someone else.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you least expect it, love will come to you. The universe will present someone for you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By chance we met and by choice we loved.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One thing I don't understand about life. We meet thousands of people, then we will meet that one person and our life will change forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes I don't tell you what I'm feeling, because I'm hoping the silence between us would give you a clue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder if you notice just how much you brighten up my days.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't make you love me, want me, or understand me. All I can do is hope that someday you will.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you're sad you must smile; When you're happy you must laugh; When you're weak you must stay strong!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ketika kamu berhenti mengejar apa yang bukan untukmu, maka Tuhan akan mempertemukan kamu dengan apa yang baik untukmu.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always forgive and love yourself, have the courage to live your life the way you wish, and never be afraid to speak the truth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never ever thought I'd like you this much and I never planned to have you on my mind this often.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You may never understand why God does things that cause you heartache, but you can be sure that God is not making any mistakes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes you just have to give up, not to get nothing, but to get something more worthy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There comes a point in your life when God brings someone in, at a very unexpected time, b/c He wants to show u that u deserve a honest love.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When your day is hard, a simple saying like "Thank you, God" will simply make things feel lighter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You idiot... How many times I have to drop a hint until you realize I like you...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope is some extraordinary spiritual grace that God gives us to control our fears.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saying good morning and good night is not just a simple greetings, but it's a way of expressing love.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoy the little things, for one day you may look back and realise they were the big things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one realized just how much I loved you until you left me and they saw the silent tears coming from my heart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God holds my today and tomorrow in the palm of His hands. I know I am secure no matter what comes against me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When he smiles, I melt deep inside.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It hurts when I want to express what I feel, but all I can do is stay quiet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're the reason I smile. You're also the reason why I haven't been smiling much recently.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love can't always be measured by how long you wait. It's about how will you understand why you are waiting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe this isn't our time yet. I let fate decide. If we were meant to be, we'll be together. Maybe not now. Maybe not yet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best thing in life is finding someone who knows all your mistakes and weaknesses and still thinks you're completely amazing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Relationship's like an onion which has many layers of TRUST and CARE. If you try to cut it, you will find nothing except tears in your eyes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes, you need to be alone, not to being lonely, but to enjoy your free time being you and yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to be the girl who makes your bad days better. The girl that makes you say, 'My life has changed since I met her.']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Distance means so little when someone means so much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What most people need to learn in life is how to love people and use things instead of using people and loving things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you really care about someone, their happiness matters more than yours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you are unsure about your future just keep doing what you know is right. What is meant to be will find you. God will make sure of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first person who comes to your mind once you wake up in the morning is usually the one you love the most.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I could see my life as a puzzle, I would realize that you are the piece that is missing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't let the troubles of life push u down. Know that everything has a season and soon the blessings from God will rain on you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Relationships will always have fights, but having fights shows how much you guys care about each other.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't care about your past. I want to know if there is a place for me in your future.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you really love someone, you will always "Make Time" for them. No matter what, no matter how, you will work it out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One day you will meet someone who doesn't care about your past, because they just want to be with you in your future.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are so many people out there who will tell you that you can't, but all you have to do is turn around and say, "Watch me!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heart, hides what we can't say. But eyes, say what we try to hide.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is like a rainbow. You need both the sun and the rain to make its colors appear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't want someone to tell me how much they care and love about me, I want someone to prove things they say to me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we blame God for every tear, why don't we thank Him for every smile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happiness is a choice. Your circumstance can affect it, but you're still the one who decides your happiness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strength isn't about how much you can handle before you break, it's about how much you can handle after you break.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My concern is not whether God is on our side. My greatest concern is to be on God's side, for God is always right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I called you at 2 am because I'm scared and couldn't sleep, but you stayed up with me till I can, that's when I know I love you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can I expect you to understand me, when truth is, I don't even understand myself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is something which can't be expressed in words, but can be felt by anyone in the universe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A smile is a language of agreement. A smile is a language of peace. A smile is a language of good looks. A smile is a good weapon.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All I need is for you to cheer me up when I'm down, love me when I feel alone and be there when I need you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every tear has it's own meaning, just like every smile has it's own pretending.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I see a shooting star, I only have one wish, and that's to forget you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kindness is a language which the deaf can hear and the blind can see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If God knows we're meant to be together, He'll find a way to bring us closer no matter how far apart we are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some things can only be expressed in music, just as how we cannot explain the smell of a rose.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you really do love him, then fight for him, don't just stand back and watch him fall for her instead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know he's something special when no matter what kind of mood you're in, he can always manage to make you smile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My heart is looking forward for tomorrow, but my mind knows that it won't be like I wish..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are not always going to make great decisions, but God sees your heart and will bless you anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As long as we can see the same sky, breathe the same air, step on the same planet, then you and I are not impossible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone says there are many other guys out there beside him. There's one problem: none of them can make me feel the way he does.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>