<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/UHS7PoiRJe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live your present so lively and lovely so that in future you have only memorable past. –Donald Duck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you live to be a hundred, I want to live to be a hundred minus one day, so I never have to live without you. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don’t really know someone unless you’ve cried with them. –Art in "Monsters University,"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All I need is a chance to do something great. –Chicken Little]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is my life. I’ll decide what to do with it. –Alice in "Alice in Wonderland"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love will always find a way. –Sleeping Beauty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't let your heart be filled with sorrow for all you know tomorrow the dream that you wish will come true. –Cinderella]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you. You’re a real friend, not like some. –Eeyore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is not about the people who act true to your face. It’s about the people who remain true behind your back. –Mickey Mouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whatever you do, do it well. Do it well that when people see you do it, they will want to come back and see you do it again. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't lose hope, love. Once you've lost that, you've lost everything. –Mrs.Potts in "Belle's Magical World"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the morning comes and the sun begins to rise, I will lose you because it's just a dream. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We scare because we care. –Monsters University]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you are what you eat, then I only want to eat the good stuff. –Remy in "Ratatouille"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/u6TGiw8vGu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I tell myself that I am not afraid. –Piglet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don’t look backwards for very long. Keep moving forward, opening up new doors and doing new things. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/BVGsBRBimN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/yE6pXmbRaF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/SMR1kQ8EDB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/HDOCGu7u1K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/PIHCzFjW42]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/jj6Mn8Rx40]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/WhUTaaqD0c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/nfoyNlhdbX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/fDOvyJ5mWp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/us8H2hZAOz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/PO5uc9RLY2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/SC2i1vRFSc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beauty and the best http://t.co/tBhnC0yVUj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/pt9AEXTK0d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can stay in here and hope for a miracle, or U can get out there and make a miracle of your own. –Laverne in "Hunchback of Notre Dame II"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/MmvoiLnnb7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You just focused on the bad stuff when all you had to do was, let go of the past and keep moving forward. –Lewis in "Meet the Robinsons"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd rather die tomorrow than live a hundred years without knowing you. –John Smith in "Pocahontas"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The heart is not so easily changed, but the head can be persuaded. –Pabbie in "Frozen"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take a chance ‘cause you can and you will see all the possibilities. If you try, you will find. –Disney Fairies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It won't change anything. You can't change the past. –Simba in "The Lion King"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't run from love. It has a way of tracking you down. –Tug in "Brother Bear 2"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/sXWV0A7GGU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They say that home is where the heart is, so follow your heart and know that you can't go wrong. – Tigger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/W7J4SlfH9q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awww he's so adorable! http://t.co/ZTE6fu1d3o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/swYrsqAGQw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We might find something that we weren't looking for, which might be just what we were looking for, really. – Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/dLmQfx8fyF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Piglet: “We'll be friends forever, won't we, Pooh?” | Pooh: “Even longer.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every beauty needs her #beast http://t.co/ZPnyqaqVk9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you can dream, then you can’t stop. A dream is a wish that you make with your heart. – "Cinderella"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All my troubles and obstacles have strengthened me. – Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m sorry I bit you. And pulled your hair. And punched you in the face. –Lilo in "Lilo and Stitch"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/UdDla9J4iZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't have to live in fear, ‘cause for the first time in forever, I will be right here. –Anna in "Frozen"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What makes you different makes you beautiful. – Princess Diaries]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't be so hard on yourself. Everyone makes mistakes. –Belle in "Belle's Magical World"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friends make every day an adventure. –Snow White "Disney Hallmark"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Mulan http://t.co/Yv6mYQTjWE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live can be playful. http://t.co/6qich7SygY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I were truly to be myself, I would break my family's heart. – Mulan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/OSQnbiIaGw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Miracles are real but they need someone to believe, so they can happen. – Disney Fairies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When life gets you down, you know what you gotta do? Just keep swimming, just keep swimming. –Dory "Finding Nemo"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things have a way of coming together whenever friends are around. – Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter what happens to me, I'll always be with you forever. –John Smith in "Pocahontas"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s the time of your life, so live it well. – A Bug’s Life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once you love someone, they stay in your heart forever. –Nita in "Brother Bear 2"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I won't give in. I'm stronger than they ever knew. –Jasmine in "Aladdin Series"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This one is different. He’s honest and he’s sweet. He would never do anything to hurt me. –Megara in "Hercules"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No words describe a mother's tears. No words can heal a broken heart. – Tarzan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love does things for reasons that reason cannot understand. –Joe in "The Princess Diaries 2"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A laugh can be a very powerful thing. Sometimes in life, it’s the only weapon we've got. – Roger "Who Framed Roger Rabbit"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As you go through life you'll see, there is so much that we don't understand. –Simba in  "The Lion King II"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We don't like what we don't understand. In fact, it scares us. –Villagers in "Beauty and the Beast"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mater: “I know I made a good choice.” 
Mcqueen: “In what?” 
Mater: “My best friend.” – Cars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Extraordinary things happen to extraordinary people. –Reepicheep in "The Chronicles of Narnia"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When other friendships have been forgot, ours will still be hot. – Mickey Mouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't spend your time looking around for something you want that can't be found. –Baloo "The Jungle Book"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/te06xrj6aP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you ever stop to think, and forget to start again? – Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A friend in good and glad and sad times. The heart remembers them. – Christopher Robin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To the pain of the past, we don't have to feel it any more. Love is an open door. –Anna in "Frozen"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once you’ve lived through the worst, you’re never quite as vulnerable afterward. – Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you are what you eat, then I only want to eat the good stuff. –Remy in "Ratatouille"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buzz Lightyear: “Whatever happens, at least we’ll be together.”
Woody: “For infinity and beyond.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He takes me in his arms, and then I wake up. Yes, it’s only in my dreams. –Aurora in "Sleeping Beauty"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fairy tale endings&gt; http://t.co/MyQCbjWOSh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/RlVoL3mjgv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Do you want to build a snow man"? http://t.co/rzmru5tyII]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/Tgop8cdjhl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/KWas1N9Jx0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/9Ybg33nplj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/Cc4cLB9zeV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/Xuz7HXvRLJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/dttWXERNWW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If there ever comes a day when we can't be together, keep me in your heart, I'll stay there forever. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you walk the footsteps of a stranger, you'll learn things you never knew. –Pocahontas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The past is behind us, right? Tomorrow’s gonna be a new day. –Buck in "Chicken Little"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life flows along with a smile and a song. –Snow White]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A mistake is part of life, and not doing the same mistake is a lesson learned from life. –Mickey Mouse]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>