<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer Cloud Transformation: A Software Engineer job in Austin, Texas is currently available through Belcan. In this role, you will be responsible Cloud Transformation – Cloud Transformation role, you will work as a full-stack developer on a… https://t.co/zOL2e1pcvZ https://t.co/EFv2WRcF3Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[User Experience Engineer Advanced – Arlington, TX or Milford, OH: For Siemens User Experience Engineer Advanced – Arlington, TX or Milford, OH job – Research &amp; Development – Multiple Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard –… https://t.co/RPzwygqO5h https://t.co/b2krjHjMdJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[User Experience Research Manager: Job Description Adobe believes in hiring the very best. We are known for our vibrant, dynamic and rewarding workplace where personal and professional fulfillment and company success go hand in hand. We take pride in… https://t.co/yRLcDf1QoX https://t.co/akR6L92G1X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer: Job Ref: ********* Employer: NTT DATA Country: United States County/State: Texas Address: Post Date: 31/07/2018 00:35 Req ID: 23389 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The quality,… https://t.co/FL4j0MxyUW https://t.co/nG1PJEiDc4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Technician: Job Ref: ********* Employer: NTT DATA Country: United States County/State: North Carolina Address: Post Date: 31/07/2018 00:30 Req ID: 22042 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The… https://t.co/LvgmDTH39Z https://t.co/MbCjaRot37]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer Advanced-Volume Meshing: For Siemens Software Engineer Advanced-Volume Meshing job – Research &amp; Development – Austin, Texas Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard – Toggle navigation – My Dashboard – Our… https://t.co/xmAD7YR8dU https://t.co/T7uASYB79b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Magento User Experience Researcher: Job Description Adobe believes in hiring the very best. We are known for our vibrant, dynamic and rewarding workplace where personal and professional fulfillment and company success go hand in hand. We take pride in… https://t.co/TeNHXdunzA https://t.co/RQhejQSgwf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mobility Developer: Job Ref: ********** Employer: NTT DATA Country: Costa Rica Address: Post Date: 31/07/2018 00:35 Req ID: 21233 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The quality, integrity, and… https://t.co/Zoo7hkSPnP https://t.co/yFhlte0Mut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist I: Purpose of JobWe are currently seeking talented Data Scientist I for our San Antonio, TX or Phoenix, AZ facility. Uses advanced techniques that integrate traditional and non-traditional datasets and method to enable analytical… https://t.co/mHrUwHZRk6 https://t.co/OG3G5JcRSR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Management Specialist: Job Ref: ********** Employer: NTT DATA Country: India County/State: Tennessee Address: Post Date: 31/07/2018 00:08 Req ID: 22066 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible.… https://t.co/MFH4RGx8d3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Data Analyst/ Junior Data Scientist: Business Data Analyst/ Junior Data Scientist – HARMAN on Facebook – HARMAN on Twitter – HARMAN on LinkedIn – Careers Home – About Us – Our Divisions – Professional Development – Featured Jobs – Engineering… https://t.co/L0MPEVvKuT https://t.co/Un3I6A6ryt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Civil Estimator Project Manager: Civil Estimator &amp; Project Manager – Houston, TX in Houston, TX at BO-MAC CONTRACTORS LTD. – Careers Home – Benefits – About Heico – Internships – Featured Careers – Professional Services – Engineering – Manufacturing –… https://t.co/xSbmtxzEaT https://t.co/X2YBZPBGxj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist: * [IMAGE] * * Applicant Login * About TI * Company * Careers * Investor relations * Citizenship * University * Public policy * Careers * Our company * Why TI * Career paths * Search jobs ? Completed page Completed page Completed page… https://t.co/br4a4hEB2A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Audit Manager: IT Audit Manager Westlake, TX Job Reference ID: ITAUD03210 Company Description: Functional Responsibilities Responsible for end-to-end IT Audit. Assists in conducting IT-related risk assessment for the development of the IT audit plan… https://t.co/2Jt33sSIdw https://t.co/r5yPjv31e3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Manager: Job Description IT Manager Location: US-TX-Austin Job ID: ****** Company: : ********** Services, Inc. Position Category: Operations, IT, &amp; Support Engineering Job Description We’re a company of pioneers. It’s our job to make bold bets and we… https://t.co/nKaNPG1HxC https://t.co/XbY09VgQ7F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead, IT Quality Assurance: Location: Texas Job type: Permanent Sector: IT &amp; Communications Category: Auditor Jobs Location: AA Headquarters 1 (DFW-HDQ1) Additional Locations: None Requisition ID: 21524 Overview Join us for a career with endless… https://t.co/0VYkjua2dN https://t.co/0C2JJ3o7EQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Sigmetrix is a global provider of comprehensive, easy-to-use software solutions that help users achieve robust designs through tolerance analysis and the correct application of GD &amp; T. With over 25 years of research and development,… https://t.co/SRCjqWOOHc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Communications Project Manager: Job Ref: ******** Employer: NTT DATA Country: United States County/State: North Carolina Address: Post Date: 31/07/2018 00:09 Req ID: 26849 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is… https://t.co/SEIXTmG4sL https://t.co/MGsYHfHW2R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer, Junior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: San Antonio, TX Job Type: Entry Level Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 7/30/2018 Job Description Job Number: R******* Full Stack Developer, Junior Key Role: Work as a… https://t.co/8njLJmn0mg https://t.co/VDpuiPPJrl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager Software Development Delivery: Project Manager – Software Development Delivery at Conduent Skip Navigation Search Keyword CategorySelectAccountingAdministrative SupportAudit &amp; ComplianceBenefitsBillingBrand &amp; Product MarketingBuck… https://t.co/c7KNSCerEv https://t.co/Ni7mQhtMQo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CyberSecurity Incident Response Lead: Job Ref: ********* Employer: NTT DATA Country: United States County/State: Texas Address: Post Date: 31/07/2018 00:12 Req ID: 22918 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is… https://t.co/wMSMKXIo42 https://t.co/MVZlCQHd3q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Job Description What you’ll be doing… You will be part of the Intelligent Edge Network (iEN) Support Team, focused on developing solutions that drive the success of our bleeding-edge networks and platforms. Utilizing your… https://t.co/PVJ2CI9hXp https://t.co/O9e8pIB6wp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manager, AA Credit Union Technology and Innovation Service Desk: Location: Texas Job type: Permanent Sector: IT &amp; Communications Category: Senior Manager Location: AAFCU Headquarters (DFW-AACU) Additional Locations: None Requisition ID: 21023 Overview… https://t.co/wqUlvO0FQr https://t.co/SWjEsCBsHR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Security Architect: Job TitleSAP Security Architect – ID:31969 Duration6 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsSAP FI/CO, SD, MM, PP, PI, and Hana LocationPlano, TX Date Posted07/26/2018 FOR IMMEDIATE DETAILS ABOUT THIS POSITION, contact ANY of us direct,… https://t.co/4DZJgahhOb https://t.co/W1MTqwR4rR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Analyst: Job Ref: ********** Employer: NTT DATA Country: United States County/State: North Carolina Address: Post Date: 11/08/2018 00:38 Req ID: 25580 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The… https://t.co/xRfYhVdHX4 https://t.co/kfjEh6WXuz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SOFTWARE DEVELOPMENT SPECIALIST: Job Ref: ********** Employer: NTT DATA Country: India County/State: Tennessee Address: Post Date: 21/08/2018 00:29 Req ID: 20990 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The… https://t.co/nWVHeBbovU https://t.co/m9QjIPi7SI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps-Chef Software Developer: Date: Aug 21, 2018 Location: Irving, TX, US Company: NTT DATA Services Req ID: 26581 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The quality, integrity, and commitment of our… https://t.co/9Br2kHk5Wl https://t.co/pFt3JYDwBU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP APO Consultant: Job Ref: ********** Employer: NTT DATA Country: United States County/State: Texas Address: Post Date: 22/08/2018 00:09 Req ID: 28747 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The quality,… https://t.co/wrQslqK23v https://t.co/yRUu34cmKf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Performance Test Lead: Job Ref: ********** Employer: NTT DATA Country: United States County/State: Texas Address: Post Date: 31/07/2018 00:30 Req ID: 21955 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The… https://t.co/sTm9mkAssc https://t.co/AM0w1aqfyh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(Remote) Meditech Systems Integration Sr. Specialist: Job Ref: ********** Employer: NTT DATA Country: United States County/State: Texas Address: Post Date: 31/07/2018 00:11 At NTT DATA, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible.… https://t.co/xqaa4gYDrg https://t.co/CKRTN2isKt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer IV – Spectrum Enterprise: Date posted 07/31/2018 Requisition Number: ******BR Location: United States – Texas – Austin Area of Interest: Engineering/Technical Operations, Telecommunications Position Type: Full Time About Spectrum… https://t.co/OnsXGRpUnJ https://t.co/lxX265A0kK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Test Automation Engineer: Job Description What you’ll be doing… The rapid technology evolution across the network, communication, software and hardware industries presents us with the opportunities to transform Verizon’s own networks, products… https://t.co/2bLhtTyQb0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GI Lab Tech FT Rotating Shift Mission Trails Baptist Hospital: Description: Performs high quality Endoscopy procedures, focusing on patient care and education. Supports and helps achieve departmental goals. Completes established competencies for the… https://t.co/9hIoP7Wa8U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Full Stack Engineer: Job ID : ****** Location : Irving, TX US Level : Experienced Professional Job Category : Information TechnologyDescription : Where good people build rewarding careers. Think that working in the insurance field can’t be… https://t.co/CPXU0jQ316]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Operations Analyst I: Purpose of JobUSAA continuously seeks talented personnel for future opportunities. This sourcing requisition is designed for individuals with recent experience as a Business Operations Analyst who are interested in career… https://t.co/kHU7kGf404]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer-Sharepoint: Job ID : ****** Location : Irving, TX US Level : Experienced Professional Job Category : Information TechnologyDescription : Where good people build rewarding careers. Think that working in the insurance field can’t be… https://t.co/kANMoKy6gC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Developer: Company Overview: ADT is a leading provider of security and automation solutions for homes and businesses in the United States and Canada. ADT’s broad and pioneering set of products and services, including ADT Pulse interactive home and… https://t.co/pZGPjXcM3K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Portfolio Architect – SAP: IT Portfolio Architect – SAP Your Role As the SAP Portfolio Architect, you will have global accountability for the strategic development of our enterprise SAP solutions, focusing on scalability, simplicity, and supporting… https://t.co/alqfqmOLT5 https://t.co/LfhcPm611R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Project Manager : 18-02991 Ref No.:18-02991 Location: Austin, Texas Akraya is looking for a Project Manager for one of our clients. If the job description below is a fit, please apply directly or call Varun Bansal at **************. If… https://t.co/cqz19WASrb https://t.co/EaZLldiD9k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: Job Ref: ********** Employer: NTT DATA Country: United States County/State: Texas Address: Post Date: 31/07/2018 00:35 Req ID: 23385 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The… https://t.co/BuYy8qJX2v https://t.co/svWlsrwytP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Security/Telecom Project Manager: Company Overview: A pioneer in groundbreaking scientific and engineering developments since the 1960s, TRC is a national engineering, consulting and construction management firm providing integrated services to the… https://t.co/xo0OYkK5bW https://t.co/UACKsGabet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Pre-sales Engineer: Job Ref: ********** Employer: NTT DATA Country: United States County/State: Texas Address: Post Date: 31/07/2018 00:34 Req ID: 21643 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The… https://t.co/54rErpkAIO https://t.co/lumdtGauAn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federal Cyber Security System Administrator – Fort Hood, TX: Job Description Federal Cyber Security System Administrator – Fort Hood, TX (******) What you will do Are you looking to grow your career in the rapidly growing cyber security industry? Our… https://t.co/438rb5BSvZ https://t.co/U08Ggtj4Yp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Developer: Project Description One of the world’s largest providers of products and services to the energy industry has a need to develop and support enterprise information system in Oil &amp; Gas domain. Project is related to collection, visualization… https://t.co/jNuvkv5nln https://t.co/1u9YkEiYEt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[API/Integration Sr. Developer: Job Ref: ********* Employer: NTT DATA Country: United States County/State: Texas Address: Post Date: 28/07/2018 00:11 Convert existing integrations on BizTalk and other integration platforms to Redhat,JBoss Fuse Define and… https://t.co/rpyVo6XdBn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering Programmer E: Job not found | ********** Skip to Job Description, SearchClose Find JobsCompany ReviewsFind SalariesFind ResumesEmployers / Post Job Upload your resume Sign in : WhatWhere Advanced Job Search job title, keywords or companycity,… https://t.co/kyzmrgMncM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. BPCS Developer – Technical and Functional: Job Ref: ********** Employer: NTT DATA Country: United States County/State: Texas Address: Post Date: 31/07/2018 00:35 Req ID: 23397 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board,… https://t.co/SSLg0UcZGv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manufacturing Execution Systems Designer/Developer: Manufacturing Execution Systems Designer/Developer Site Logo – Markets &amp; Solutions – Agriculture – Automotive – Building &amp; Construction – Consumer – Electronic Materials – Energy &amp; Water – Industrial –… https://t.co/adPu11KAeE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Level 2 Application Support Analyst: Date: Aug 7, 2018 Location: plano, TX, US Company: NTT DATA Services Req ID: 27688 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The quality, integrity, and commitment of our… https://t.co/aICPRGoAJp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer for next-generation EDA software platform: Requisition Number 5879BR External Posting Title Software Engineer for next-generation EDA software platform Time Type Full time Pay Rate Type Salary Work Shift Regular – Salaried Country… https://t.co/rKZRX0cHsY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Engineer- Audio: Job Description Technical Support Engineer- Audio Date: Jul 30, 2018 Location: Richardson, TX, US Company: HARMAN International Requisition Id : ****** Additional Work Location(s) : Position Summary: This position is… https://t.co/zcuDkwq0qO https://t.co/Q5fWl7dVX1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Plant Maintenance: SAP Plant Maintenance Ref No.: 18-31411 Location: Houston, Texas Hello, Hope you are doing well today! I have an urgent requirement for ‘SAP Plant Maintenance with my end client. If you are available for this job please send me… https://t.co/DyiX5IAuli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Career Opportunities with MyTelemedicine – Phone: 1.************ – Partner Login – Member Login – – – – Home – About – About Us – Leadership – In the News – Careers – How it Works – The Service – How it Works – The Problem – When to… https://t.co/ZmvLyVDW19]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Application Developer: Prestigious Fortune 500 Company is currently seeking a Java Application Developer. Candidate will develop application and system code, participate in code reviews and module testing, and support ongoing maintenance. Candidate… https://t.co/1qXvkzek6o https://t.co/aTeIHwNpwl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Application Developer: Why We Work at Dun &amp; Bradstreet Life here at Dun &amp; Bradstreet is changing for the better. With almost two centuries of experience and a new modern vibe, work at D &amp; B has never been more exhilarating. Our purpose is to grow the… https://t.co/MZbczgQkr0 https://t.co/1uc8wWw4YP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer I Manufacturing: Develops software from design to prototype to production, ensuring correctness and compatibility to meet requirements. The Software Engineer I develops simple or moderately complex solutions under the direction of the… https://t.co/swz9if4Upc https://t.co/L5A6OVIrRh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer : 18-02992 Ref No.: 18-02992 Location: Austin, Texas Akraya is looking for a Java Developer for one of our clients. If the job description below is a fit, please apply directly with your update resume or call Monika at… https://t.co/Otlp9l0rJx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist I: Purpose of JobWe are currently seeking talented Data Scientist I for our San Antonio, TX or Phoenix, AZ facility. Uses advanced techniques that integrate traditional and non-traditional datasets and method to enable analytical… https://t.co/D7h03lihXW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Implementation Consulting Principal, WSO Services – Product Specialist: Implementation Consulting Principal, WSO Services – Product Specialist Duties &amp; accountabilities Support WSOServices and/or WSOAgent Services production issues as they relate to WSO… https://t.co/WENjxDUXkl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst: What Business Metrics/Analytics contributes to Cardinal Health Business Metrics/Analytics is responsible for developing, quantifying and evaluating the transformation of internal and external information into business intelligence to… https://t.co/i95oLd5TFE https://t.co/1r7Yacjyq3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Sales Support Prof Real Time Locating Systems Industrial Automation MI-TX-AZ-CO-GA: **Technical Sales Support Prof. – Real Time Locating Systems – Industrial Automation – MI-TX-AZ-CO-GA** Multiple Locations:Troy, Michigan; Littleton, Colorado;… https://t.co/EU8oNZZkZ8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer Revenue Pricing Systems: Company Description Common Purpose, Uncommon Opportunity. Everyone at Visa works with one goal in mind – making sure that Visa is the best way to pay and be paid, for everyone everywhere. This is our global… https://t.co/Q4K6TrjnNe https://t.co/jAx8g8dBCx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Software Developer: Cloud Software Developer at HP Inc. Skip Navigation Careers Search for jobs Working at HP Blog Faqs Sign in &amp; apply Search jobs Keyword CategorySelectAdministrationBusiness PlanningCollege InternCorporate… https://t.co/NeBNDjhKSv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead RPA Automation Developer/Analyst: Job Ref: ********* Employer: NTT DATA Country: United States County/State: Texas Address: Post Date: 01/08/2018 00:23 Req ID: 25312 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is… https://t.co/kNLUUV7IlE https://t.co/n6VDySLRk4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IoT Software Engineer Tech Lead: IoT Software Engineer – Tech Lead – Job ID #: 13411 – Job Category: Applications Engineering – Employment Type: Experienced Professionals – Division: Internet of Things – Department: ISG Solutions Engineering – Primary… https://t.co/zPPDfwj7ti https://t.co/DsHCZcGLWO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solution Manager – ITSM (ServiceNow): Solution Manager – ITSM (ServiceNow) Your Role As the Solution Manager – ITSM, you will have critical responsibility for managing the evaluation and growth of our ServiceNow platform and IT Service Management… https://t.co/HeE7qnOmn5 https://t.co/7dcANJ2Qnh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle Data Structure Programmer: Date: Jul 30, 2018 Location: Albany, NY, US Company: NTT DATA Services Req ID: 27190 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The quality, integrity, and commitment of our… https://t.co/ROAccAKk6H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP APO DP CONSULTANT: Job Ref: ********** Employer: NTT DATA Country: India County/State: Tennessee Address: Post Date: 02/08/2018 00:08 Req ID: 15232 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The quality,… https://t.co/QYI1U4kNUa https://t.co/Hxjl1wagwR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CyberSecurity Incident Response Analyst: Date: Aug 8, 2018 Location: Plano, TX, US Company: NTT DATA Services Req ID: 24372 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The quality, integrity, and commitment of… https://t.co/DaWnjwX9fs https://t.co/d9JMjO6r5r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP BO Developer (Proactive): Job Ref: ********* Employer: NTT DATA Country: India County/State: Tennessee Address: Post Date: 09/08/2018 00:12 Req ID: 26568 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The… https://t.co/9LhoMugbkJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Multi-disciplinary – II: DUTIES * Creates and produces software operating or applications systems. * Provides analysis related to software design and development, and solves problems. * Formulates operating system advancements and… https://t.co/jMCnYrtID4 https://t.co/3cflRb1R9X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Software Support Specialist, Incode Court: Associate Software Support Specialist, Incode Court =================================================== This role provides basic-level software support for Tyler clients in the use, functionality, and… https://t.co/jH7drQ39IV https://t.co/AiUQh0gfRH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Software Support Specialist, Incode Public Safety: Associate Software Support Specialist, Incode Public Safety =========================================================== Incode public safety provides a full offering of integrated suites… https://t.co/p5DofFLtEc https://t.co/uMd7SGZZl7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Intelligence/ETL Engineer Senior Level: Business Intelligence/ETL Engineer Senior Level Purpose of JobWe are currently seeking talented Business Intelligence/ETL Engineers Senior Level for our San Antonio, TX facilities. USAA Business… https://t.co/hWAgRW0NlX https://t.co/5ExL68sbE3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, Incode Public Safety: Software Engineer, Incode Public Safety ======================================= The Software Engineer is responsible for coding, testing, and documenting application programs of basic to moderate size and… https://t.co/Ug4brnKEQE https://t.co/oPwTOhpTLw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. SAP Security Analyst: Sr. SAP Security Analyst Your Role As a Senior SAP Information Security Analyst on our IT Security team, you will fulfill a unique role by supporting Identity and Access Management tools and SAP Application Security. Bridging… https://t.co/GD1vRqoQfr https://t.co/Utigz5efAW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Data Integration and Data Architect: Job Ref: ********** Employer: NTT DATA Country: United States County/State: Texas Address: Post Date: 27/07/2018 00:25 Req ID: 24368 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is… https://t.co/7Q5fFQJ5yK https://t.co/OtUDdDGjV0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior NOC Network Engineer: Senior NOC Network Engineer Purpose of JobWe are currently seeking a talented Senior Level NOC Network Engineer for our San Antonio, TX (Vista Corporate Center) facility. Assembles key participants and guides and facilitates… https://t.co/uyB5pYxrF6 https://t.co/SkxZSdeLST]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spectrum Workforce Management Systems Administrator: Date posted 07/24/2018 Requisition Number: ******BR Location: United States – Texas – Austin Area of Interest: Other, Sales, Telecommunications Position Type: Full Time Spectrum Workforce Management… https://t.co/hwyZPywba6 https://t.co/qnVjP05zKo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Data Scientist – IoT Cloud Services: Senior Data Scientist – IoT Cloud Services – Job ID #: 13785 – Job Category: Research &amp; Development – Employment Type: Experienced Professionals – Division: Research – Department: Research – Primary Country:… https://t.co/lw4dnpwPiw https://t.co/O8szCOHOr2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Applications Developer – OpenGL/Android: Sr. Applications Developer – OpenGL/Android Your Role Fossil Group is on the forefront of impacting the wearable technology industry by creating innovative Connected Accessories that are fashionable and… https://t.co/1uuJVQccAE https://t.co/hcsNbHFvvv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst 3: Overview PROLIM Global Corporation (**************) is currently seeking Business Analyst 3 for location Austin , TX for one of our Top client. Required Skills: Experience in gathering and analyzing business requirements and develop… https://t.co/dn4b73zdQ4 https://t.co/Fgjfv5876I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Middleware Developer: Job Ref: ********** Employer: NTT DATA Country: Costa Rica Address: Post Date: 31/07/2018 00:35 Req ID: 21239 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The quality, integrity, and… https://t.co/458rCMpL1B https://t.co/uxtPLaCCXk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bioinformatics Data Programmer: Job ID : 67319BR Location : US – Texas – Austin : Job Description When you join us at Thermo Fisher Scientific, you’ll be part of a smart, driven team that shares your passion for exploration and discovery. With revenues… https://t.co/MZjI7rxy0x https://t.co/Jg8tc78suP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Distribution Management IT Consultant: Requisition ID 2018-57549 Category Information Technology Employment Type Regular – Full Time (4) Travel Requirements Greater than 60% Position Code 7955 Position Description The Distribution Management IT Solution… https://t.co/0sk1h4UI93 https://t.co/ERHcOGZWyo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Desktop Support Technician: Job Ref: ******** Employer: NTT DATA Country: United States County/State: Texas Address: Post Date: 28/07/2018 00:10 Req ID: 24386 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The… https://t.co/1rLASvMVwB https://t.co/stBDpATa9r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Agile Coach: Location: Texas Job type: Permanent Sector: IT &amp; Communications Category: Engineers The Enterprise Agile Coach is a Senior Project Manager responsible for developing, promoting, and executing an organizational change strategy for… https://t.co/UdwFYJkUL0 https://t.co/ghnD8Ngnz8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager Electrical Field Service: Job Description Senior Project Manager – Electrical Field Service Are you ready to work with a purpose? At ABB, you can be sure you’re helping to create a better world. The business you’ll secure and the… https://t.co/jBiY5M5ACn https://t.co/wHT3u8i1vZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer/Senior Engineer, IT Access Management: Location: Texas Job type: Permanent Sector: IT &amp; Communications Category: Engineers Jobs Location: AA Headquarters 1 (DFW-HDQ1) Additional Locations: None Requisition ID: 20747 Overview Join us for a career… https://t.co/KmiQXqOROy https://t.co/aEijHrewE9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Agile Coach: Location: Texas Job type: Permanent Sector: IT &amp; Communications Category: Engineers Jobs The Enterprise Agile Coach is a Senior Project Manager responsible for developing, promoting, and executing an organizational change strategy… https://t.co/w75MkJl8Mu https://t.co/5IgrA0pcZd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP ABAP Consultant: Job Ref: ********* Employer: NTT DATA Country: United States County/State: Texas Address: Post Date: 28/07/2018 00:09 Req ID: 26744 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The quality,… https://t.co/nEs6AcClah https://t.co/ElBrlKWDSN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Mobile Architect/Developer: Lead Mobile Architect/Developer – V3Main ************** – Home – About – Mission, Vision, &amp; Values – Leadership – Government &gt; – DIR Contracts – Cybersecurity – News – Services – IT Managed Services – Agile Software… https://t.co/IcpmDb5dEe https://t.co/MlO2p7PvOv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer / Systems Engineer I – Mid level: Software Developer / Systems Engineer I – Mid level Purpose of JobWe are seeking a talented Systems Engineer I /Software Developer Mid Level for our San Antonio, TX – Vista Office. Ideal candidate will… https://t.co/5gxRhfzBaM https://t.co/agAHuznuxc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Senior Software Engineer Jobs Description at Cox Enterprises Skip to main content Careers Home Our People Locations Join Our Talent Community Blog Manage Your Profile Cox Enterprises Cox Communications Cox Automotive Cox Media… https://t.co/6rabNVfrwM https://t.co/Pc52ipZznK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director IT Security: **Director IT Security** Locations:Milford, Ohio Job Family: Information Technology New Search English (US) **Job Description** **Division:** Digital Factory **Business Unit:** Product Lifecycle Management-PLM **Requisition… https://t.co/uBgLOfA0XM https://t.co/2tcxaFfkgy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital Workplace Services Technical Architect – Remote U.S.: Job Ref: ********** Employer: NTT DATA Country: United States County/State: Texas Address: Post Date: 28/07/2018 00:20 Req ID: 23618 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on… https://t.co/4lIaQWU52F https://t.co/w1L16iUYkj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spotfire, R Developer: Job Snapshot Employee Type: Contractor Location: Spring, TX Job Type: Information Technology Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 7/31/2018 Job Description Job Summary: This position is within the Upstream Technical Computing… https://t.co/GCRBJEzANy https://t.co/ZNuMngKE8T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mulesoft Developer IV: Responsibilities: – Design, develop, and test data integration processes per business requirements, following the development standards and best practices as well as participate in code peer reviews to ensure our applications… https://t.co/yUcQly4O0u https://t.co/G6Gp9M4VOm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP S/4 HANA Supply Chain Solution Architect: Job Ref: ********** Employer: NTT DATA Country: United States County/State: Texas Address: Post Date: 14/08/2018 00:09 Req ID: 28015 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything… https://t.co/2OiRCWD8M4 https://t.co/q4OjlklhRH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Implementation Consultant, Munis ERP – Travel/Home-Based: Job Description Implementation Consultant, Munis ERP We are adding Implementation Consultants to our National teams. Tyler Technologies is experiencing significant growth and we are hiring… https://t.co/GzXswPpJfU https://t.co/Ct6mF7kzPP]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>