<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Barbara Mason  http://t.co/iGKsgPDhbV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love cats because I enjoy my home; and little by little, they become its visible soul. - Jean Cocteau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awe cool - A Lock N' load target alarm clock/Gun alarm clock - shoot the dang thing! http://t.co/RJnJZS6Tp3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Publishing Management with HootSuite  http://t.co/c2istWpZcB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is not the strongest of the species that survive, nor the most intelligent, but the one most responsive to change. - Charles Darwin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future is always beginning now. - Mark Strand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australian Beers?  Yep - check them out... http://t.co/CYKOto75kY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Example is not the main thing in influencing other people; it's the only thing - Abraham Lincoln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Boz Scaggs  http://t.co/BUUMgHantD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Using Instagram for Web Marketing  http://t.co/y3WFnAmHmq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just got my Google Chromecast HDMI Streaming Media Player - SO COOL - http://t.co/oXdJhPEDZo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes as much energy to wish as it does to plan!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Building Experts - Get Some Free Tips  http://t.co/xVIvo5jB9k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Kansas  http://t.co/NkS89SVymd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only thing worse than a Mets game is a Mets double header. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Foreigner  http://t.co/iQ9x7UKygE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best thing about animals is that they don't talk much. - Thornton Wilder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Paul McCartney and Wings  http://t.co/MkLHoDxEN3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Locate Your Garage Space Before Installation Of Cabinets  http://t.co/nkm0VWB0Ii]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Mac and Katie Kissoon  http://t.co/jnOiNqgf4q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Success is where preparation and opportunity meet. - Bobby Unser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out Crimson Mine’s awesome Tumblr page... http://t.co/PQ80Ws9tIl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the top science fiction books of all time!  http://t.co/vWJR9RDO8p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't accept your dog's admiration as conclusive evidence that you are wonderful. - Ann Landers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Patsy Cline  http://t.co/l7q9by4jQx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sawyer: You versus Sun - hot oil death match - my money's on you, Sheena. Kate: Thanks for your vote of confidence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Don McLean  http://t.co/f5ggFAns21]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We (San Francisco) have football weather during baseball season, and baseball weather during football season. - Herb Caen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opportunity is missed by most people because it is dressed in overalls and looks like work - Thomas Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Battleship Memorial Park – Mobile Alabama – A Great Historical Experience  http://t.co/3D2f0b2u3L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you don't do what's best for your body, you're the one who comes up on the short end. - Julius Erving]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To know when you have enough is to be rich]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to ZZ Top  http://t.co/WV85sM83oB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Rod Stewart  http://t.co/oTCqpV6tEk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About GPS Technology and Fitness Watches  http://t.co/TfBFL0VMhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best thing about animals is that they don't talk much. - Thornton Wilder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is not preparation for life; education is life itself. - John Dewey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL Offensive Business Cards - Everyone Needs a Stack of These! http://t.co/3MwZOqRS0M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Cheryl Lynn  http://t.co/jXNPNTmFFp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Don Henley  http://t.co/KL3JYWLtW0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Future generations will be born free, equal and in debt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One deer to another:  "I wish I had his doe"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One may go wrong in many directions but one may go right in only one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Temptations  http://t.co/RQp3iLn4SX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You may have to fight a battle more than once to win it. - Margaret Thatcher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Institutions that once had to go through media to deliver information are now themselves media - Andrew Nachison - Founder We Media]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got to party and socialize at an Olympic level.  Bode Miller after a terrible Olympics]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My name is Inigo Montoya. You killed my father. Prepare to die! - Inigo, The Princess Bride]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wal-mart --  do they like make walls there?  Paris Hilton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Alice Cooper  http://t.co/tmIZV0Cdrq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is more than a game to me, it's a religion. - Bill Klem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't care how long you've been around, you'll never see it all. - Bob Lemon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dress shabbily and they remember the dress; dress impeccably and they remember the woman. --&gt; Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame Quakecraft: FAILURE IS AN OPTION!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! http://t.co/9FfvLKlfSI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Future generations will be born free, equal and in debt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it time to go home yet? I keep clicking these damn shoes, but nothing happens. - Robin Hecht]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Seniors and Social Networking  http://t.co/ILy5jhydMj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Popular Places and Activities in Europe  http://t.co/eLKdGEHHcA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About The Christian Faith  http://t.co/vWjvYUEQaW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome gardening t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the gardening lovers in your life!   http://t.co/aXDFGYF4Fe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most beautiful makeup of a woman is passion. But cosmetics are easier to buy. --&gt; Yves Saint-Laurent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Domestic Adoption - A Helping Hand To A New Life  http://t.co/7FIyR3XaOz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nobody remembers the guy who finished second but the guy who finished second. - Bobby Unser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read a Short Introduction to ABBA  http://t.co/jHRGefqBtV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Monopoly Money Extra Long Tie - Fun! http://t.co/jlOyXjLatn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Trust Me I'm A Nerd Mens Sweatshirt - Awesome http://t.co/s2S2MCd3mi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Future generations will be born free, equal and in debt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would love to change the world, but they won't give me the source code]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space isn't remote at all. It's only an hour's drive away if your car could go straight upwards. - Sir Fred Hoyle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I play with my cat, who knows whether she is not amusing herself with me more than I with her. - Montaigne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is A Hedge Fund?  http://t.co/aLeaXQNyv6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Mountain Climbing - Best Mountains to Climb in the World!  http://t.co/nZcrrvT4c1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Great Resort in Palm Coast Florida  http://t.co/3cE4LmQJOb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A teacher affects eternity; he can never tell where his influence stops. - Henry Brooks Adams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Trust Me I'm A Nerd Mens Sweatshirt - Awesome http://t.co/s2S2MCd3mi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One thought driven home is better than three left to die on base. . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Clear Lighted Skateboard with green LED Lights  http://t.co/8Gd5uxvqZM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Experience is not what happens to a man. It is what a man does with what happens to him. - Aldous Huxley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Looking Glass  http://t.co/c9iAcG1MZJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Domestic Adoption - A Helping Hand To A New Life  http://t.co/KGC6iGDJVy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Organizing Garage Cabinets and Storage  http://t.co/obdliKry7K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome soccer t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the soccer lovers in your life!   http://t.co/QfH5UhOdoL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All arguments have two sides, but some have no ends.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Video games for fitness is a growing trend - tie together the love of video games and the need to stay fit!  http://t.co/RIGeBnkVsa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If opportunity doesn't knock, build a door. - Milton Berle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd like to compliment you on your work -- When will you start?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome ping pong &amp; table tennis tshirts &amp; gear - get something for the paddle lovers in your life! http://t.co/JZatZG6Ywv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge a man by how much he does when he doesn't need to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does it mean when a person is such a pacifist that they get shot? I can never understand that. - John Lennon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Pink Floyd  http://t.co/yUdmr6q5ww]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A wife doesn't mind seeing a man make a fool out of himself as long as some other woman isn't helping him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Choosing To Use Solar Power  http://t.co/2IAe8tcAKb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greater your capacity to love, the greater your capacity to feel the pain.  Jennifer Aniston]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fantasy is the impossible made probable. Science fiction is the improbable made possible.  - Rod Serling, creator of The Twilight Zone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good introduction to Minecraft Mods - http://t.co/0LyGDJ2kvi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are 10 types of people in the world: those who understand binary, and those who don't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About The Christian Faith  http://t.co/vWjvYUEQaW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cooking for Geeks: Real Science, Great Hacks, and Good Food  -&gt; http://t.co/nPmhyB3aaE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of the animals except for man know that the principle business of life is to enjoy it. - Samuel Butler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketing is too important to be left to the marketing department. - David Packard]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>