<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The Weird Economics Of Ikea (or how they can keep making stuff cheaper) https://t.co/AaasbzZQKw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @b_judah: 1/3 Historians will castigate Facebook and Twitter, which motivated solely by monetised traffic, created systems that megaphon…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice angle on why shops matter to Amazon—fixing their delivery issues https://t.co/MEtjhtRp4h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone Is Learning How to Take Down the Internet... and its probably China https://t.co/Pp1AoyiDgr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jmspool: If you’re trying to hire designers &amp; require a portfolio, you’re not gonna get top talent. 

The best designers don’t have the…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out how Design Testing can be your secret weapon in the UX process https://t.co/CMuqzqvxTt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jbarro: If I were Hillary, I'd cut this Trump interview into an ad and air it on Fox to demoralize Republicans. https://t.co/GTY0q6UFPq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That footage. Nature. Blimey. #planetearth2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those iguanas have the most bad-ass newborns ever. First task in life: escape tens of snakes. Rest of life must be a cruise #planetearth2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @r4isstatic: This is really good, #UX &amp; #Product people should read and consider carefully. https://t.co/zDIn8lzwig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@larrykim Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Fahrenthold: UPDATE: I've now contacted 433 charities, trying to prove @realDonaldTrump gives "tens of millions" to charity, as he says…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @johnharris1969: Fair play to J O B. This is top.  https://t.co/NzA62zkJk9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Glinner: Dumb as a sack of hammers https://t.co/aN0vILEC67]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Law_and_policy: A UK court has decided that the Article 50 decision has to be taken by the UK parliament.

This is what real sovereignt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SunApology: Rod Liddle in today's Sun. The line between The Sun and Britain First being blurred more and more https://t.co/qX7dCJQPEa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @brendanjharkin: In light of the news of insurance companies now checking Facebook activity, I have set up a handy new page for everyone…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Book making progress. First draft written, now being edited and about to start design... https://t.co/eNDSh3SwG3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An ecommerce UX design tip: give your search results distinct titles https://t.co/BqB8GJVa8t https://t.co/yeZ6xUDYjr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@colortheory Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DThevarajah Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually solid advice... 3 Important Life Skills Nobody Ever Taught You https://t.co/YNJRMdmiQ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lodihana Thanks for following! Take a peek at my new book, coming soon https://t.co/115mePAbAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The shift in media’s business model played a critical role in Trump's victory https://t.co/xysSBsv3hR https://t.co/ux6HyXhpr3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ask_Dwayne_Pyle Thanks for following! Take a peek at my new book, coming soon https://t.co/115mePAbAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thoughts on what can be done with an abundance of cameras and machine learning https://t.co/FgztsKQFCC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danrolfejohnson Ha, yeah that's the real inertia to overcome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For better UX in your product, get everyone doing user testing and meeting users. Simple. https://t.co/tAnR8UB9aN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @deray: Denzel. Boom. https://t.co/TIMyJJqoBH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't attack capitalism, take down rent-seeking https://t.co/FppsJOJvU8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joffley I love a carousel me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An ecommerce UX design tip: don’t hide information in landing page carousels https://t.co/bIRRtoclU8 #ux https://t.co/wQ7nT9l4vq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danrolfejohnson You'd think!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope every Southern Rail customer has been claiming refunds for all the delays. Bankrupting them might be the only way to end this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A couple of handy articles on decent quiet cafes to work at in London https://t.co/LbTcn7SmWE &amp; https://t.co/5NuJf3m1Wq https://t.co/v0kGDG0D2k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mgsiegler: All look bad next to Apple's but only the Microsoft one was done with MS Paint. 

Or KidPix. https://t.co/ankdIi4W4O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mrjamesob: Further to this morning's show, this is what happens when the  'self-employed' are working for minimum wage or less on zero…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Pre-marital counseling' is apparently a thing, blimey https://t.co/etKzDdZLhu https://t.co/nCvQDudx9q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Han5Jan Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting stuff on the creative process &gt; How I Wrote Arrival (and What I Learned Doing It) https://t.co/kwyNstIHG4 https://t.co/lJfC0kmkIf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An ecommerce UX design tip: search results should indicate product variations https://t.co/wnyMf9lAWT #ux https://t.co/Drp0MWtjhD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KristinCochell Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@anotherwpguy Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A very sensible idea... I just supported this case https://t.co/yEgh7MKDTi via @CrowdJustice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Could the bottomless money pit of free video be to Amazon what Russia was to Napoleon?" https://t.co/EBnO8jN0ZW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jeez https://t.co/7t1sLdymeq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber keeps on growing to compete with the big 4 &gt; Buys a Mysterious Startup to Make Itself an AI Company https://t.co/NLEIJfhCPf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Every point of the experience matters" 5 Things I Learnt as a Designer at LEGO https://t.co/FkhoNqmGXe https://t.co/xknmlDQnBm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sachinuppal Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @thugclive: Very quickly Britain is adopting these ugly ideas of "liberals", "patriots", "Brexiteers". A guy on Question Time said "Brem…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A very thorough way of dealing with and storing your customer feedback https://t.co/pZpMz2avMi https://t.co/7NZhXgYEks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice approach to doing UX reviews thru the eyes of the user/persona by @mrjoe https://t.co/GkYSUN8DNl https://t.co/oGcY7XbCj5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alushtom yeah they missed off 'make the logo bigger']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solid advice on visual intention: How To Make Your Not-So-Great Visual Design Better https://t.co/TmRwF2B2Nk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Netflix A/B Testing: interesting stuff on changing the film artwork to attract attention https://t.co/3uJ4F82mFF https://t.co/Znb6fNzj3u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Do Genes Sway the Sensitivity or Resilience of a Child? https://t.co/WShv7zggAK https://t.co/YGkXiVgUqf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thought this for ages. If anything it's very generous https://t.co/hK49sKqmMW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks good, and v faithful to the book https://t.co/ih5zpVluWl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coming in 2017 (!) "Interactive button spins, icon rotation, loading bars, notifications and more animations" https://t.co/Ux68SskQJ1 https://t.co/a8t604cpPz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bunch of advice I've put together on gathering user/customer feedback https://t.co/C3Z7oAd5ad https://t.co/d8kwaNoFAi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most of The Launch And Revenue Numbers You See Are Bullshit https://t.co/sjvufqwYfD https://t.co/alpfMMTk5o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VictoriaUXUF Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a powerful step change in retail. Been wanting something like this for ages for restaurants https://t.co/2oj2NAgC9y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intel Disrupted: Why large companies find it difficult to innovate, and what they can do about it https://t.co/duCZC1IO3R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice little visualisation https://t.co/UUeTIJchvw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Impact of Interaction Design on Brand Perception https://t.co/9tszJPQZG6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brexit: a coup by one set of public schoolboys against another https://t.co/JcMhYZKtZs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrisologus Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ZosteraR Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shearersarm Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robtswthrayguns Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Netflix for your career" How https://t.co/Y15cpkjv0c Became the Go-To Resource for Their Area of Expertise https://t.co/RjAaQeqpPJ https://t.co/9vJ9pULz6G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump, leading the way in social media's new return to the oral age https://t.co/YoqVrsyL8i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ligialimos Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IterationGroup Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great vid, capturing the mess of issues that have been attached to Brexit https://t.co/aor2ZlBnxP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sciencebeta Thanks for following! Check out my new online guide https://t.co/sd1qMfHhBr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Users might say that they don't like a feature (especially if it is new) only to be perfectly competent using it" https://t.co/IduIjE08we]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Quickly test out a couple of options and solve arguments if your team can't agree" – Design Testing https://t.co/TIGUBg9Ujl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Evidence-Based UX Design Guide to User (and Customer) Feedback https://t.co/BPyg6Z08rm #ux https://t.co/Sa3liJpKSD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RobertMackey: Trump's share of popular vote continue to fall as more votes are counted; now just 46.4% (to Clinton's 48.2%); did worse…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An ecommerce UX design tip: Results: distinct titles https://t.co/2oYovxs6gq #ux https://t.co/hLWnXocKQY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An ecommerce UX design tip: A clear button to start shopping https://t.co/Dfn8nJYAfr https://t.co/fbpDqMZKIE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anna Soubry: ‘What’s happened to our country? We’ve lost the plot’ https://t.co/gLkauvPL9r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An ecommerce UX design tip: Allow guest checkout https://t.co/oFKq9hzLDe #ux https://t.co/Czsc0W1OSo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AdamBienkov: Douglas Carswell on Nigel Farage becoming US ambassador: “Ambassadors need discretion and diplomacy. I’m not sure Nigel ha…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to ask questions https://t.co/AvrcOp5LuD &lt; Great advice on getting stories out of people https://t.co/2tsODj6JwL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is great on the future of tech &gt; Who Will Command The Robot Armies? https://t.co/pQnzHYUkIr https://t.co/A5tiSBOdzn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WritePlay: AMAZON: Did you buy a watch?!
ME: Yeah, it's-
AMAZON: You might want THIS watch!
ME: No I already-
AMAZON: ONLY WATCHES FOR…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @peterme: Ugh. Actual empirical evidence of relative intelligence and savvy, https://t.co/gyAajVVrQ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An ecommerce UX design tip: Give detail in different forms https://t.co/jF9sYn4pR3 https://t.co/owxvVsbHIb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chrisapplegate: TFW you voted Brexit but then get upset the consequences ruin your game of Football Manager https://t.co/zSol1ICdIj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Design Museum review – temple to design gets the space it deserves at last https://t.co/5XdSgDi84N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great advice on getting well-paid design/marketing work with clients https://t.co/kJyL33kQAI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @keepnhspublic: GPs must demand MPs stay in Westminster from 8 am til 8 pm all week until they get #NHSCrisis sorted RT if you agree htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Phwoffy Thanks for following! Take a peek at my new book, coming soon https://t.co/115mePAbAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Choosing poverty and the benefits of the Quiet Life https://t.co/v9z4uDrS3k https://t.co/VMIU9tUyw3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our Automated Future: "Off-shoring jobs is often just a 'way station' on the road to eliminating them entirely." https://t.co/jHwM2Z8N08 https://t.co/1cpKcVkBfm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @willmill82: Poundworld have a "Price Ascending/Price Descending" sort option. Poundworld. Pound. World. https://t.co/L7FgJ9lh03]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great piece: Why time management is ruining our lives https://t.co/8nuMqF4DiA https://t.co/sbe8IMi3Wu]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>