<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Undocumented immigrants working at #Trump properties will be given bonus marks for applying.

@realDonaldTrump has earned an incredible reputation for how he treats staff so finding outstanding candidate is unlikely. https://t.co/Go2OboMo1X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @iceblueaccent: @StrategicThghts My prayer these days is that I live long enough to see Trump held accountable, and that he does not cau…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wish those of us like #Trump in our seventies could live just a little longer to see how it works out. Sadly today’s children will inherit a world worse than their parents did. #ParisAgreement https://t.co/mWjFyKBb3Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope #Kushner has to testify on his conversations with #MbS offering advice after #KhashoggiMurder https://t.co/DRbUhqTPmQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jimnelson806 @Norm_Farrell @PlecasFire @impishchimp I don’t think #Plecas has done anything wrong, except for going far too far at Dec 6 LAMC. He should have kept his mouth shut rather than arguing with Polak, just say wait for RCMP. #bcpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Norm_Farrell @Jimnelson806 @PlecasFire @impishchimp We can hope the world works as you describe, my comment was based on a far more cynical view formed from a lifetime in positions that dealt with audits. Plecas shouldn’t bet it all on an audit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @washingtonpost: The latest public figure to face backlash from his tweets: Twitter CEO Jack Dorsey https://t.co/oEzxyphoud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jimnelson806 @PlecasFire @Norm_Farrell @impishchimp Speaker Plecas has had moments he’d likely want to redo. Public bodies regularly audited can be told problem is oversight body (board or #bcleg) failed to set clear rules so spending met sloppy rules, not fault of the spender. #bcpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Norm_Farrell: BC Liberal journalist Tom Fletcher slags Speaker Darryl Plecas for interfering with "The Club" at the BC Legislature. Thi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Jimnelson806: @PlecasFire @Norm_Farrell @impishchimp If you think Tom Fletcher is a part of an "independent press", there is not much p…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tweet from @realDonaldTrump is not from the “leader of the free world” as #Trump has relinquished that position making himself a laughing stock even at #UN. 

Fact checkers will enjoy comparing #Trump’s record to date with those who occupied and respected the Office of #POTUS. https://t.co/9xzFS7Cs99]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WoodfordCHNL: After a decade in the House of Commons #NDP #PortMoody #Coquitlam MP @FinDonnelly won’t run again in the 2019 #cdnpoli el…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like #Ayers is no fool. 

#Trump challenged to staff chaotic, possibility sinking ship. https://t.co/5ZRtsyjxm9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Russians interacted with at least 14 #Trump associates during the campaign and transition https://t.co/oyBNlXKxzL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Belgium’s ruling coalition collapses over U.N. pact on migration https://t.co/IIqLguv5tX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ErnieGorrie: #PR4BC more important to voters than municipal government. https://t.co/qqnitUyy1j More than 40% &amp; ballots still coming in…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @thehill: Kushner gave Saudi crown prince advice on how to "weather the storm" after Khashoggi killing: report https://t.co/Qvk3DdcTEU h…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iceblueaccent My reading of that is medical and recreational cannabis are identical (could be same product from same producer) differences are paperwork and price.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iceblueaccent There’s this https://t.co/4jfgDjeAo4 which is interesting state by state, if you find anything else comparing medical vs recreational cannabis please post it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BernadetteNTF Link missed was to https://t.co/4jfgDjeAo4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BLeeLoganberg I have several friends, one with MS, one who died of brain cancer, for whom medical cannabis is/was essential. Just saying there appears to be no difference between products sold as medical vs recreational except for THC/CBD ratios. Hence curious about Shoppers license #bchealth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oops, here’s link I missed: https://t.co/4jfgDjeAo4 #bcpoli #cbc #bchealth https://t.co/RdgFJUZynI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BLeeLoganberg Hope that’s eventually true but there’s very little research today that would allow anyone to offer informed comment on THC/CBD ratios and doses let alone on drug interactions. I think retail pharma has seen a profit centre. #bchealth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If this site is correct difference between medical and recreational cannabis is all about taxes on identical products. #bcpoli #cbc #bchealth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JeffreyGuterman: On this date December 8 in 1980 at 10:50 PM ET, @johnlennon was assassinated. Photo via John Lennon. #BeatlesGuterman…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@apukwa OK, but same products so just a question of document for insurance?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mtsw: Stocks stumble on news that the guy who hosted "The Apprentice" is actually the President and this wasn't all some weird dream we…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What’s the difference between medical cannabis that Shoppers will offer to those with a “valid medical document” vs what anyone can buy on the gov cannabis site? #cbc #bcpoli https://t.co/WZFfgGeYhS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @youth4pr: " No excuses on the legitimacy of 40% " 

What has changed @BillTieleman 's mind so suddenly? Maybe 5 days ago he was feeling…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BowinnMa: For additional context, that's 15 parking spots out of 750+ that will be impacted along a 20 block stretch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @adamgoldmanNYT: This has been lost on a lot of people: Comey in interview on Friday with House says that even if Mueller is fired, this…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SurreyRCMP: Better think twice about being naughty or nice. #CounterAttack road checks are here to help keep impaired drivers off our r…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Ocasio2018: For the GOP crying that this is a “threat” - I don’t have power to subpoena anybody.

Congress as a body, GOP included, has…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Ocasio2018: I have noticed that Junior here has a habit of posting nonsense about me whenever the Mueller investigation heats up.

Plea…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“That #Trump is fundamentally lawless can no longer be seriously disputed. His own prosecutors now say he took part in a crime — and his former secretary of state says Trump had little concern about what was legal.” https://t.co/SKrzt6slOX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Cdnrumpole: @jillreports Just because she’s rich doesn’t put her above the law. Pursuant to the Extradition Act she was arrested. She i…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Siege warfare’: #Republican anxiety spikes as #Trump faces growing legal and political perils https://t.co/MGaNG5Mp0C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kaitlancollins: Comey denies being “best friends” with Mueller, as Trump claimed. “I don't know his phone number, I've never been to hi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Norm_Farrell: @unionwill @Roysahm1 Police ruled out sabotage. Probably unrepaired corrosion. Companies choose higher level of risk and…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prosecutors just warming up for next round on #Trump. https://t.co/FlfOKOdz5P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysis | #Trump can’t deliver as #McConnell resists pressure to move on criminal justice overhaul, angering some Republicans https://t.co/jp5i4Yrg0E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WoodfordCHNL: The cave discovered in Wells Gray Prov. Park just made the NY Times. #Kamloops #Clearwater https://t.co/1ZTgFpNH2m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@primetimecrime That’s within three weeks. https://t.co/wOPuMlaQNL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @abbydphillip: Trump tells reporters on the South Lawn that Chief of Staff John Kelly will be leaving the WH at the end of the year. He…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friday was a very, very bad day for Donald #Trump @CNNPolitics https://t.co/tpUtjRN5mw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @matthewjdowd: Reminder: there is no law that says a President can’t be indicted.  It is a Justice department memorandum advocated over…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jockfinlayson: The multiple forces driving Canada’s sickly currency ever lower #CdnEcon @nationalbank https://t.co/e06pRBWU1M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion | The latest filings show that nobody can save #Trump now https://t.co/ikdn3OgPm5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NewYorker: Donald Trump responded to Rex Tillerson’s comments at a charity event on Thursday by tweeting that Tillerson was “dumb as a…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Trump’s #WhiteHouse apologists will spin nonsense through this Sunday’s political shows. They must know the worse is yet to come for @realDonaldTrump as #Democrats take over as committee chairs and #Mueller reports. https://t.co/fuUPjuIHLY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @washingtonpost: Prosecutors said that Manafort had told numerous lies in five different areas, including about his contacts with Konsta…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @aravosis: The document clearly states that Cohen committed a crime at the direction of Donald Trump. That’s a criminal conspiracy invol…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ananavarro: #Individual1 lacks basic reading comprehension skills. https://t.co/cmUDrV64QO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @washingtonpost: Analysis: The Foxification of the Trump White House, visualized https://t.co/Aty2EVAATn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FoxNews hasn’t explained this to #Trump yet. @realDonaldTrump continues to live in an alternative universe coloured by #FoxAndFriends. https://t.co/ZIN5gVTjKd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @paulkrugman: As I understand it, we call our chief of state "president" because it was a modest designation, one that didn't carry conn…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NBCPolitics: Thread: Manafort filing. https://t.co/A8Xjl1kXdD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Mueller says #Manafort told ‘discernible lies,’ including about contacts with employee alleged to have #Russian intelligence ties https://t.co/mqQnDElKTH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow! #Trump shouldn’t rely on #FoxNews as it is the only news outlet that doesn’t spell out the deep doo-doo @realDonaldTrump is in. https://t.co/ORtVKrPTae]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MeetThePress: WATCH: What do the new Cohen memos tell us about Trump’s ties with the Stormy Daniels payment? #MTPDaily 

@Mimirocah1: “…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MeetThePress: "We all thought that there would be a new Donald Trump who would come into the White House ... Not only was there was not…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MeetThePress: "The government thinks that the president has done something that if he were not the president, if I had done them ... th…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New #Mueller filing says #Trump’s ex-lawyer Michael #Cohen was in touch with a #Russian seeking ‘political synergy’ with campaign https://t.co/CR2T4DivFu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump is likely waiting for #FoxNews to explain this to him since #Tillerson revealed #Trump doesn’t read and can’t take briefings. https://t.co/9L5pbHAfWx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: Former Secretary of State Rex Tillerson says Trump is 'undisciplined' and 'doesn't like to read' https://t.co/ErQdKV4MEu via @…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dsamuelsohn: NEW: Judge Jackson says she will let Mueller file part of his upcoming Manafort filing today under seal. Looks like Muelle…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jaketapper: CNN: Robert Mueller’s team will file its description of how Paul Manafort breached his cooperation agreement largely under…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MeetThePress: .@CevallosLaw says Michael Cohen is an "example of a defendant who has cooperated some but not quite enough to warrant ..…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SharonLNYT: Prosecutors on Cohen: This was not a blind act of loyalty, as Cohen has also suggested. His actions suggest that Cohen reli…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @yashar: 10. Mueller's Office (remember, different from SDNY): 

"He also has gone to significant lengths to assist the investigation. H…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @yashar: 7. SDNY re Cohen: "A Substantial Term of Imprisonment Is Warranted"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @yashar: 6. "Cohen only met with the Office about the participation of others in the campaign finance crimes to which Cohen had already…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @yashar: 5. "Cohen repeatedly declined to provide full information about the scope of any additional criminal conduct in which he may ha…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always modest #Trump #POTUS doesn’t have enough influence with @senatemajldr to get a vote on Criminal Justice. The Twitter Pres can’t govern. https://t.co/vjgqZ6xgrp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MotherJones: Donald Trump, who only hires the best people, says his former secretary of state is as "dumb as a rock" https://t.co/jZqT6…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @froomkin: Wow! New poll: 76% of Americans believe that Mueller's final report should be made public in its entirety. https://t.co/awOXH…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @maggieNYT: And, there it is https://t.co/9I3nBcrBMh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RepMaxineWaters: John Kelly is one of a long list of failed &amp; incompetent Trump appointees that served in a dysfunctional White House.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PaulBegala: The President is nominating William Barr to be Attorney General.  Shocking.  By what standard is Barr qualified to serve Tr…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @davidfrum: President Trump would be the world's worst poker player.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @politicususa: Rex Tillerson Resurfaces And Confirms That Trump Belongs In Jail https://t.co/8ccfb4uyyU via @politicususa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion | The latest round of #Trump chaos: No one but himself to blame https://t.co/u7faBCcGwk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @2closetocall: Late poll from @insights_west mostly confirming my estimates: among people who have voted already, it's close and the NO…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MeetThePress: NBC News: After clashes with first lady and others, Kelly may soon exit White House

https://t.co/laWqPLCf8G https://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Kelly expected to resign soon, no longer on speaking terms with #Trump @CNNPolitics https://t.co/IiNfDzRzEo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rex #Tillerson just exposed Donald #Trump's greatest weakness @CNNPolitics https://t.co/sa7ufJoEst]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Tillerson says #Trump directed him to do things that violate the law https://t.co/Yi0S0IPx8A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @thehill: "41 percent of Americans don’t plan on getting a flu shot — don't be one of them" (via @TheHillOpinion) https://t.co/OpHkcnby2…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That’ll teach #UN to laugh at #Trump. @realDonaldTrump will further diminish US prestige. https://t.co/aVO0fLKBlg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nytopinion: In the eight years since it was decided, Citizens United has unleashed a wave of campaign spending that by any reasonable s…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big win with little effect for @realDonaldTrump. #Trump is so weak he can’t get @senatemajldr to call his crime bill for a vote that would be certain to pass. Small #Republican group in #Senate has more power than #POTUS. https://t.co/QxOR2HNz5N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kaitlancollins: Secretary of State Mike Pompeo has made clear he wants the U.N. ambassador position downgraded from being a Cabinet-lev…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The “blues” for today’s LAMC meeting are posted at https://t.co/SnaJevTPXd #bcpoli #bcndp #bcliberals #bcgreens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those calling for a “forensic audit” should understand that accurately reporting amounts spent is no where close to a “value for money audit”. #bcpoli #bcliberals https://t.co/UZrJHtzbI8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For those interested, Hansard for LAMC can be found here: https://t.co/QwgyIeZRjq #bcpoli #bcndp #bcgreens #bcliberals https://t.co/YeRyxCGpCW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WoodfordCHNL: Today's Inside #bcpoli w/ @WoodfordCHNL @VaughnPalmer @BCTodayOfficial and @richardzussman as we discuss the latest in th…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MeetThePress: WATCH: How can you police Trump violating the emoluments cause?

@BrianFrosh: “The issue is not what his profits are. He’…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BCLegislature: The Legislative Assembly Management Committee meets at 2pm today. Tune in live: https://t.co/iJnAFAS0eI #BCLeg #BCpoli h…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @samstein: NEW: Trump has told aides he doesn’t care about the national debt in part because when it becomes truly untenable he will be…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MyChickenDinner: If Donald Trump wanted Hillary Clinton locked up, he should have hired her to work on his campaign.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>