<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@tarakjpratt It's a scientific fact that fear is faster than the speed of dark.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Saraoxford: @MYSADCAT @cox_tom Ted is full of self loathing after getting a little bit too drunk at the christmas party. https://t.co/M…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MYSADCAT: Kitten advice: when feeding your kitten soup, always choose a soup the same colour as your kitten #kittenadvice https://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MYSADCAT: https://t.co/DAgTJjl61Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: E-4 Streamliners in Chicago circa 1945. https://t.co/aixG3Kw6Mx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FilmHistoryPics: This rare picture was captured on the set of Tod Browning's (whose career never recovered from it) FREAKS (1932). http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson Are you sure that's a '90s comic? Her breasts are only as big as her head.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @playwrightnow: Writing a play recreates The Hero's Journey: Called from your comfort zone, wrestle with demons, plunge into despair, re…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @skipbolden: Great #filmmakers on #filmmaking https://t.co/QDf7VJNMfK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evanjstern I for one am shocked by your statement! There's Canadian film and television?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshRimer And what about the present? It's under the Christmas tree!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wilw I think they make them that size on purpose, to make you buy more than you need. To be satisfied takes about one-and-a-third donuts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StacieBee "Michael Jackson still was black / Those were the days!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: How to kiss a girl, 1911. https://t.co/GnT29dN3cw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson What?! In this province we argue about "gonch" or "ginch". Eternal enmity to your province!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mightyjoanna As long as we don't find ourselves discussing "the late Joanna", things aren't as bad as they could be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: Cow shoes used by moonshiners during Prohibition to disguise their footprints, circa 1922. https://t.co/mBivOGvgTN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Criterion: From PARIS BELONGS TO US (1961), dir. Jacques Rivette. https://t.co/bKKP9cWz1I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattdagley Yeah, I gambled on one of those too. Same recommendation. If they paid me the 25 bucks, it still wouldn't be a good deal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @colebrax: Terrifying transformation scene from 'Pinocchio' (1940). https://t.co/u8vuPkQA9g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StacieBee Must be someone from Saskatchewan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MerkRobert: Roman, Martin and Harvey. Just because.

@LaFamiliaFilm https://t.co/evAdBHQkfv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Kurt_Vonnegut: Somebody gets into trouble, then gets out of it again. People love that story. They never get tired of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KMWeiland: “If you don't write when you don't have time for it, you won't write when you do have time for it.”-Katerina Stoykova Klemer…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JewelStaite: I feel like we've aged really beautifully. @NathanFillion https://t.co/kA4N4Ju1oZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson So not a "Cerebus" fan then?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @playwrightnow: Think of writing a first draft as pulling off a bandaid. It must be done; it's better in all ways if you do it fast. #2a…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshRimer Wait ... where's your right hand?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actress, writer, and director Julie Delpy (key partner in Linklater's "Sunrise" trilogy) talks about making movies: https://t.co/ohuzqvf6Da.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tarakjpratt Pee like the wind! (That's *like* the wind, not *into* the wind. Jeez, I'll never make that mistake again.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@monicahamburg @MissTia777 Fair enough if the householders want to be nude, but why does the contractor have to be nude? That's not safe!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @colebrax: Happy birthday to Raoul Walsh, seen here reading lines w/ Ida Lupino &amp; Bogie on 'High Sierra' (1941). https://t.co/oaCCmBilB2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson There's a lot of those taken at Stanley Park's Lost Lagoon in Vancouver. Turtles are cute.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson Thanks! I've never noticed it here on the West Coast, but I must admit it's not the type of thing I pay attention to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson Huh. Nope, never heard of it. What is it? (Link? My Google Fu is weak here.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MMFlint: "Where To Invade Next" opens tomorrow in Shreveport, Columbia, SC, Beverly Hills, Billings, Grant's Pass, Savannah, Cloverdale…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson "Spoon!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @ItsAdamCanuck, @TrixieCanuck -- have you seen this? "Let It Defy Gravity": https://t.co/8IUqn6ozWk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsAdamCanuck Tell them how she's defying gravity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @john_sayles: Spoke to @leonardmaltin + @barvonblaq for #MaltinOnMovies  Listen here https://t.co/EWmoNedmK1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: Ann-Margret on a Triumph, from the movie 'The Swinger', 1966. https://t.co/SUuUv4eb9R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: Marilyn Monroe photographed by Milton Greene, 1956. https://t.co/ODhpXWAylx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson As high as their stiletto-heeled combat boots!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson True! But I think they hit a high point in the mid-1990s. (Maybe "high point" isn't quite the term I want ...")]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson It's still the same audience, isn't it? The boys who thought "Spawn" was way cool when they were 14 are now 35.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson Boner jokes always get a rise out of people. (Sorry.) Have you seen this? https://t.co/RzfZZplWwf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I find it hard to get excited about the new "Ghostbusters" movie, as the original was total crap. But this seems to be the minority opinion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kristaferanka There are nice people working in comics?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @playwrightnow: "Write what you know" doesn't mean record your life; rather, capture your thoughts, which will be novel or surprisingly …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pourmecoffee: Harrowing.

"'Josie and the Pussycats’ meet Satan, 1973" https://t.co/3Eh0wA99wF https://t.co/1i89HXOHzC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SteveMartinToGo Breaking! "Draft Steve Martin" movement gains steam.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SteveMartinToGo USAnian politics is much more tiring than UK politics. In the UK, candidates stand for election.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JackKirbyMuseum: Jack Kirby
28 August 1917 - 6 February 1994. Beloved Husband, Father, and Grandfather.
An Inspiration To All. https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson There's the thing! Kaluta said he was lucky he'd kept 30-year-old paperwork, or he'd be 'splainin' to lawyers for years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson "Bedside Press"? I'd like to think that if you were a doctor, your estate would be called "Bedside Manor". (Sorry.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JudgeGort There are a lot of Tweets from you this evening that might cause an impartial observer to question your taste in music.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson Did you hear that Marvel's lawyers sent Kaluta a letter telling him to stop using their property? (Coupl'a years ago now.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LaFamiliaFilm: If you love #Kubrick’s ‘Dr. Strangelove,’ this post is the motherlode. 50 BTS pics by Bob Penn. Mind. Blown. https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @colebrax: Fritz Lang at work on his iconic silent film, 'Metropolis' (1927). https://t.co/Q6yr23DKj4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JohnCleese Alas, 140 characters is not sufficient to debate the metaphysics of Twitter and its position on the body / mind dichotomy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BFI: Do you know your Technicolor from your Kodachrome? https://t.co/oqTWFzvoG9 https://t.co/m0aeezF3lx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson Thanks! I had not heard of Abigail Mathilda "Ma" Hunkel before. Catching up on a fascinating piece of lost comics history.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson Red Tornado! I guessed Forbush Woman, but that wasn't pre-Nelvana. Who published this Red Tornado? I know only DC's version.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The Force Awakens’ Reimagined As Calvin and Hobbes": https://t.co/t5XHFSnL3w. (Hey @ItsAdamCanuck ...)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cinemaquanon: City Lights
(1931, Charlie Chaplin) https://t.co/0zeekHdqG9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FraserMcDonald: Buster Keaton on the set of @thenfb's #TheRailrodder, one of his final film roles. 1964 #tbt https://t.co/uLtJK0yoa7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheAVClub: Hope and Crosby’s Road movies paved the way for future wiseacres https://t.co/EsUElVUrli https://t.co/JqMgRO5cwB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@canucksprayoffs @purplehightops Allie Brosh on recovering from depression: https://t.co/TH9XxFVNKe (and read part 1 also).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mistershrewd Or "gouging". You say tomato ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NathanFillion: It’s that time of year again, when we all succumb to our basest instincts and indulge in the evil that is Girl Scout coo…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or a more serious question for #PolkaDotRocket: What gear do you use? Cameras, audio, lighting, editing, props?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Question for #PolkaDotRocket: What would you do if your imaginary friend didn't like you any more?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Local short-movie-making group #PolkaDotRocket" is having a live launch event on the Web at https://t.co/hCEnMZDIHP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheUnNovelist: Pagefright—your allies are levity and bluff. Pretend you're a writer if you don't feel like one. #amwriting #writing htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kanye West is a big doofus. https://t.co/ZOwMZ2pMM3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Do you like pina coladas, and getting songs stuck in your head?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsAdamCanuck Some people have mean parents. You can't blame the child for that. (Signed, the guy with the same name as "The Omen" kid).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @openculture: Paramount Now Streaming 175 Free Movies, Including Westerns, Thrillers &amp; Crime Pictures https://t.co/hiJXrvc5tr https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Criterion: Guillermo del Toro sits down with the Coen brothers to talk about movies and their career: https://t.co/frelx6i9u4 https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheUnNovelist: Marry somebody you love and who thinks you being a #writer is a good idea. Richard Ford #amwriting https://t.co/ysw5oeU5…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@videomaker @ZoomSound Zoom F8 looks good, but is it true the limiters are placed after the analog-to-digital conversion, and if so why?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cox_tom: My cat Ralph and I performing our celebrated duet of ‘Islands In The Stream’ (I do the Dolly parts). https://t.co/X0asuC7SDN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: Marilyn Monroe performing to troops in Korea, 1954. https://t.co/QcnE9UCK5E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: The only existing photo of a Quagga, a plains zebra that is now extinct, London, 1870. Photograph by Frederick York. htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cox_tom: Squirrels actually have more fun than any other animal but it stays a secret due to the fact they rarely bang on about it on s…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JohnFugelsang: The 3 Stooges, out of makeup. https://t.co/Vdeby5NxI8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeremyDyson Yeah, great, thanks! I would use it. I can pick it up from you hopefully at your convenience, if you will let me know when.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeremyDyson Hey, cool! I still have some SD camcorders that I use occasionally. What's the deal?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: Harrison Ford in his high school yearbook. https://t.co/FAvkMKIeIw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson Well, you can buy little clips to stop the fridge air getting in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tragic news from the world of music ... https://t.co/kIKaiGcI8d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Kurt_Vonnegut: Being a Humanist means trying to behave decently without expectation of rewards or punishment after you are dead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @IanBoothby: Bring your parents to work day was a real bummer at Justice League headquarters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: Twiggy, Vogue, 1967. Photograph by Bert Stern. https://t.co/JNh8Jd1YUM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsAdamCanuck @TrixieCanuck And they all star Tuesday Weld!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson The future ain't what it used to be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsAdamCanuck Kanye West is a big doofus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: Stevie Nicks, Fleetwood Mac, 1978. https://t.co/r1o9Pb5xxm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson I've heard that the new translation does a better job with some of the double-entendres and puns, but haven't seen it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson Is this the new translation?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>