<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai True^^  But we aint got no moneey fo' dat #BrokeFilipino]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai You should give me some on monday? Well at least I saved $70 by not buying PPV =P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rios' attitude though.. #YouDaPunchingBag #PacRios]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai In my house.. Were live streaming the fight online in my room with all 5 of us watching &amp; only my mom is screaming.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This kid gloving! http://t.co/NIy8yY8U2N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Photoset: DJin’ and gloving with the brother. http://t.co/MGA6AanpQ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Djin' and gloving http://t.co/2BJlwDl3Dq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Audio: This is my remix submission to Paul Baloche’s contest for Hark The Herald Angels Sing/King of Heaven.... http://t.co/tf9L1IhJRr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Day 3 of trying to fix a phone...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[gg. The iPhone failed on me. Now I need one again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I fixed my brother's old iPhone 3g. So at least I have a temporary phone and iPod for the meantime.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ummmm... Can someone give me a phone? Please?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need a new phone or iPod or something asap... I neeeed my music!! I wish I had the money right now to buy a new one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think im gunna cry.... Good bye iPod...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There's a song that inside of my soul" #OnlyHope http://t.co/BLa35NHWwK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My latest song got 50 plays in about 24 hours. Thats actually pre' impressive! Thanks people!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally uploaded my latest song "A New Beginning", the first track of the year! Here is a short clip… http://t.co/IaEeZEFWeG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you havent checked out my lastest song, here is the link! #edm #ableton #house https://t.co/Qz8GjPzaqA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Audio: Well here is the first song of the new year. I hope everyone had a great and blessed Christmas and... http://t.co/5v92cCquHZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My new sounds: A New Beginning http://t.co/Rq43iHxEL5 on #SoundCloud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Working on my song in emz_n_emz room 'cause why not! #ableton #edm http://t.co/ppswzC6xxS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you bought me some studio monitors, you'd make my day so much better! A pair of KRKs would work.. Just sayin' =D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VincentAraujo @TheManlySamurai OHH YEAAAAH!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VincentAraujo @TheManlySamurai THe white kid misses me ^__^]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Already working on the first song of 2014. #House #EDM #Dance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai still can't go. Sorrys. :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HAAPPY NEEEW YEAR!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only time I read a book is when a movie has a cliffhanger and I MUST know what happens after but the next movie isn't out yet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai Ill ask my parents again later and see if they change their minds...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai Cant go... =(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What I did on the last day of 2013 is sleep half the day.. Great way to end the year, don't ya think?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CapitalKingsUSA: #BeAKing // available at Midnight http://t.co/Qf8h8CyVyN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Catching Fire was amazing!!! #ThumbsUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai Sounds good, Ill go ask my parents tomorrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai Heey @VincentAraujo , read this whole convo and tell us if ur in or not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai sounds good to me. Coquitlam Centre is probs best for me for travel. See what the others say..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai go hit up Jeff, Yuxin, John, and everyone else. What: doesn't matter as long it's not expensive. Where: not far]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai Friday is probs the best day for me. Wednesday might work if my fam doesnt have plans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai Im available on the week days and maybe Saturday but not sure if im allowed tho. You ask the others yet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cant believe that @BlackMedia followed me on Soundcloud!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plans for today: sleep at around 1am, wake up at around noon, eat, watch a movie, watch another movie, sleep. #GoodByeProductiveDay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The plans I had to be productive today was ruined cause I just downloaded two movies....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just noticed its Dec. 30 today.. New years eve tomorrow... Ummm... goodbye 2013?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maah parents are amazing!! I know it's like a few days after Christmas but whaaatevaaaa xD http://t.co/Iq2X0Zo2ht]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai it's all Aaron...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai yup he's trolling you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai can't do it on New Years :/ Pamily dinner! Maybe the days after New Years?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai well tnx for replying -___- at least iMessage works =P Anyways, I dunno ask what the others wanna do. Not sure if I'm free]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai we'll we have just over a week to make it happen. Btw did you get a text that said "Troll"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I haven't even started my plans that I planned for the winter break... #procrastination]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Im talking to Siri... #ForeverAlone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I reached a total of 50 plays yesterday on my Soundcloud!! Thats the most I've gotten since I released "All For The King' bout 7 months ago!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You peeps should FaceTime me.. ;) you know you want taaaa!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pentatonix thooo! Too gooood!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lqianoo Just use gift bags.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lqianoo This might help.. ;) http://t.co/KhS5BHlOBV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@Calvary__Tweets: "Not even the Grinch can steal Jesus from Christmas!""]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need to get myself a @WeAreNovation Launchpad... Too much fun doing live sets #Ableton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai who said I have gooder grammar anyways?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai but in the end you still an A in english]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai Its better than your grammar at least. I could barely read that last tweet =P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai Laughing my boooty off 'cause of my amazing headshot xD #BestMomentOf2013]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Planning to do an all nighter just to work on a last minute Christmas remix....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I opened up one of my old projects and decided to rework it... I now realize how unorganized I was back when I started producing music.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai #CoooolDatWaay Now go and approve my email so I can see the snow video!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shout out to @TheManlySamurai for da chocolate and duuuuh paragraph long christmas card! Yous duuh best teeenks yous! http://t.co/pQetkhYVB0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well I found something to do for the winter break... ANOTHER REMIX CONTST!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fun night at Jazz Cabaret! Another performance done, one more to go then I'm done for the year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great way to end my day. Thanks @krickenn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Video: Here it is! Just finished uploading my ‘Meet Your Maker’ Mix! http://t.co/rYteoteHKd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai Yeaaaaaah!!!! #SantaIsReal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here it is! Just finished uploading my 'Meet Your Maker' Mix!! A mix done from a few songs from @MatthewParker2 http://t.co/KVIN6NJMtx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai fine. But I still expect a paragraph long christmas card.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai I'm expecting a bag full of ferrero roche or toblerone and a paragraph long Christmas card :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So im rendering my video right now and its going to take bout an hour so im probs gunna upload it tomorrow. Not feeling well so night people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Might be able to upload a video to my youtube channel tonight. Its been awhile since i last uploaded.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My dream music studio? Spent the past hour drawing. The artsy side of me :) #dj #keyboard #piano #art… http://t.co/t3qih7yEOh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Photoset: Sunsets of 2014… So faaar…. http://t.co/NonFHLxpRe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Video: A Sunday evening mix! Enjoooy!! TRACKLIST: David Crowder - After All (Holy) [Capital Kings Remix]... http://t.co/FDfbYCo4Vh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A new mix is on youtube now! Was fun doing it, maybe another one next week! https://t.co/YrwPAHnBib]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uploading a new mix to @YouTube right now! 300 minutes remaining!! In the meantime... HOMEWORK!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I noticed that a lot of my plays on @SoundCloud is from one of my DJ mixes... I think I should post up more of that!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone help me stop.... #Flappy #bird #no #life #help #me #i #need #to #stop #high #score http://t.co/8JNgRmGRTY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Filipino athlete is in the Winter Olympic Games!!! #NoWay #Philippines #Represent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone know any good #CEDM remix albums?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having the hardest time deciding my grade 12 courses.... So haaard!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A cold day but a beautiful sunset! #sunset #coquitlam #photography http://t.co/bdi7mG6v6g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its almost 10pm and im in the mood to do some Djing... Hope my bros dont get mad at meeh xD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have the best peer tutors this semesteer!! Theey are soo awesome! #TheyreFilipino #trolls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai haha no worries! I only need it until I get mah own. #LoseIt5MinutesLater]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheManlySamurai YEEEES!! OMMMMG YEEES!!!! PLEEEEASE YEEES!!! YEEEEEEEEEEEEES!!! YEEEEEES!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yooo @TheManlySamurai do you need your graphing calculator this sem?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We shall make a video one daay! @VincentAraujo https://t.co/pknVNXJOve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Im starting to think Metrotown isnt as big as I thought.. But I checked the time, we were walking around for a good 4 hours...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think its time for us to start Skype hangouts! @TheManlySamurai @VincentAraujo #ButTooLazy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was having so much fun playing this game until the file got corrupted.... #SadLIfe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A short clip of a track that I'm working on. Full track will be on my soundcloud... Whenever I finish… http://t.co/diZasfzhMA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you wanna build a snowman?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are so many stars out tonight!! Soooaw beautiful!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gunna miss these guuys!!! We'll see each other again soon ;) @TheManlySamurai @VincentAraujo and dem others. #MyFace http://t.co/nN80ExQoOB]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>