<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Hospital in Arizona has 16 pregnant nurses: There's a baby boom in an Arizona hospital and it's not coming from the maternity ward. https://t.co/KiU8e7SB60 https://t.co/Yk2SqGEyqp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Test Lead: Overview PROLIM Global Corporation (**************) is currently seeking QA Test Lead for location Detroit , MI for one of our Top client. Job Description: Required Skills/Experience At least 5 years of experience in the below Facets… https://t.co/HQ2YJ7SeXE https://t.co/MR5zMaJba4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. IIB Developer: Sr. IIB Developer – TGT – Farmington Hills, MI | ********** Loading…Server error, please try again laterSorry! It looks like you are in private browsing mode, which is not supported. Please switch your browser mode. Sr. IIB Developer… https://t.co/xHvJyV5dkg https://t.co/CHUCm39DRs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paint Coating Applications Project Manager: Job Description Paint &amp; Coating Applications Project Manager ABB Inc., in Auburn Hills, MI is seeking for an Project Manager to join our Robotics and Motion team, the first major global industrial robotics… https://t.co/85oiVrrgpa https://t.co/kPnEk34mco]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Preet Bharara to Maher: Don't call Trump a traitor: Former US attorney Preet Bharara pushes back at late night host Bill Maher after he referred to President Donald Trump as a traitor. https://t.co/UzCciQHOy2 https://t.co/nZhywAqDwG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Assurance / Solutions Architect: Job Description BAE Systems, one of the world’s leading defense contractors and a stable Fortune 500 Company, has created a new position for a Cyber Assurance / Solutions Architect that will help us move to digital… https://t.co/CdOhLnrwqW https://t.co/uf2BHzz6gs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce Developer: Salesforce Developer Ref No.: 18-33469 Location: Troy, Michigan Job Role: Salesforce Developer Contract Role Location: Troy, MI Skills &amp; Responsibilities: Expertise in Integration concepts Knowledge on GIT Bash and JAVA Remove… https://t.co/lGdvlB9fxq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Robotics Automation Engineer: Job Description We are AAM. We have the POWER to move the world. At AAM, we’re looking for associates who push boundaries and drive solutions for the future. Innovators. Thinkers. Dreamers. Doers. No matter the role or… https://t.co/zUEWKZP36m https://t.co/Yb8D9wciLV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager: Careers: Job Openings and Career Development | Perficient, Inc. |Senior Project Manager Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including… https://t.co/AAyEJG7GxT https://t.co/G4TPTCYyzi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Programmer: Overview PROLIM Global Corporation (**************) is currently seeking Java Developer for location Okemos , MI for one of our Top client. Job Description: Work collaboratively in an Agile team to deliver high quality source code to… https://t.co/Vvzz7Aj4zE https://t.co/1azGSsXKXD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Angular Developer: Careers: Job Openings and Career Development | Perficient, Inc. |Full Stack Angular Developer Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site,… https://t.co/4ot6tOeArQ https://t.co/imruMeGSLB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Fuel Exhaust Management: Job Title Project Manager – Fuel Exhaust Management Division Powertrain Job Description Overview: Lead FEM project activities related to the development, launch and sustaining engineering support of North… https://t.co/EX2kveWx0k https://t.co/GTosEbRZYv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The schoolboys were chatting and laughing before airstrike: For a group of boys in northern Yemen, Thursday was supposed to be a celebration -- a much-anticipated field trip marking their graduation from summer school. https://t.co/Dv9JRicz6H https://t.co/2jjHpfI6Hz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Desktop Support – Level II: Job TitleDesktop Support – Level II – ID:32192 Duration6 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsMicrosoft Office 2010, 2016 and 0365 applications, Active Directory, TCP/IP, DNS, DHCP, SCCM LocationSaline, MI Date Posted07/24/2018 FOR… https://t.co/YAk3qL8NuM https://t.co/PgFZDFdJat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer: Job Postings | Reyrey.comReynolds and Reynolds LogoFacebookLinkedInTwitterYouTubeInstagram Skip to main content [RR – Careers] Careers Super Navigation Careers Menu #ReyReyLife Search Jobs Main navigation [RR – Careers] Careers Main… https://t.co/1vedq5uqnk https://t.co/zhgKhthqpz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why pancreatic cancer is so deadly: Pancreatic cancer is the third-leading cause of death from cancer in the United States, after lung and colorectal cancers https://t.co/JMprK4BajQ https://t.co/RBxPaWeZEX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Firmware Engineer – $80-120K + benefits: Ann Arbor, MI Full-time $90k – $120k Posted Today If you are a Firmware Engineer with experience, please read on! Salary: $90-120K DOE Location: Ann Arbor, MI Looking to be a part of a top-notch R&amp;D team? We are a… https://t.co/3rsYhyZ0HP https://t.co/2Tdo0hWWSW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front End Developer: You’re a good fit for our team if you have worked remotely before. We are a Remote Dev Team. You probably understand that while it’s not hard, it is different. There is a different kind of social aspect to working remotely. Sometimes… https://t.co/a7Vv2aIyMm https://t.co/HpQRrgSJWR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Architect Detroit: The product architect technically leads the development of connected navigation systems that the TomTom Custom Systems product unit develops for its business customers. The product architect is involved in both product… https://t.co/zYuwcwEojY https://t.co/aHgggJZUr3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AWS Devops with CI/CD: Job Search Results Home Home Language English Franais Espaol Sign inRegister Email: Password: Forgot your password? Sign in Please enter your registered email address, and we’ll email you a link to reset your password right… https://t.co/zyq6yfbcoN https://t.co/Da6TxAtsni]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Program Manager Automotive, IOT: Senior Program Manager – Automotive, IOT HARMAN International Date: Jul 18, 2018 Location: Novi, MI, US Description: Position Summary: The Customer Program Manager is responsible for the overall program delivery of… https://t.co/xZ5R5WXSIu https://t.co/Is9JSseIho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Engineer, Sales 1 (5974): Requisition Number 5974 – Posted 04/02/2018 – Sales – Professionals – United States (US) – Saline, MI – Machine Tools &amp; Automation Systems – Liebherr Gear Technology, Inc. – full time Position: Application Engineer,… https://t.co/N0cpd76OFE https://t.co/w9imCywcI6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solution Architect (PLM Teamcenter): * Please wait… A career at Amway is a career in opportunity. At Amway you can explore and grow, make a difference, and find success. Established in 1959, Amway is a multi-billion dollar company, and the world’s No. 1… https://t.co/t60yXqpQ2y https://t.co/d8RzY1jc3A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Security Engineer: Job ID : 68751BR Location : US – Michigan – Portage : Job Description Network Security Engineer When you join us at Thermo Fisher Scientific, you’ll be part of a smart, driven team that shares your passion for exploration and… https://t.co/YgUCpHklLX https://t.co/xXcTVnYECD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Desktop Support Technician: Desktop Support Technician HIRING!!!! A Place to Build Your Future! Do you enjoy troubleshooting computer issues? Do you have a Customer Service focus? Dart Container is looking for you to join our team! We have an exciting… https://t.co/THNOQ42HEu https://t.co/bZ4Pd1rX0R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Services Support Specialist, ERP Solution: Technical Services Support Specialist, ERP Solution =================================================== The Technical Services Support Specialist provides systems management technical support and… https://t.co/n9a47JY4Un https://t.co/LI8uuCurFE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Full Stack Developer: Date: Aug 8, 2018 Location: Ann Arbor, MI, US Company: NTT DATA Services Req ID: 27780 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The quality, integrity, and commitment of our… https://t.co/VwO8aAooDO https://t.co/Km1W99H7iR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sfdc developer: sfdc developer Ref No.: 18-35115 Location: Farmington hills, Michigan Production Support – Bug Fixes – New Enhancements to the site – Monthly Releases – Checking Logs – Batch Jobs on CA Scheduler – Data loads using Data Loader – Creating… https://t.co/RkF85hr33K https://t.co/ijExoMngbL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Business One Specialist: * Zeeland, MI, USA * Full Time Email Me Similar Jobs Email Me This Job If you are a dynamic individual with excellent technical abilities and experience in a manufacturing environment then Plascore, Inc. has the perfect… https://t.co/1LHsK4Pf2w https://t.co/FrnJRFfQ0W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tapper: Remember a time when this was inappropriate?: Paul Manafort's attorney Kevin Downing told reporters he appreciates President Donald Trump's support after Trump called the trial "very sad." https://t.co/2TPvnRFmFA https://t.co/7Oe2b3CND6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Specialist: Technical Support Specialist Senior Service America, Inc. is recruiting for an Technical Support Specialist position in the Senior Environmental Employment (SEE) Program (55 years of age or older) at the U.S. Environmental… https://t.co/SjFMljTVnM https://t.co/DcAhpeK5og]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Developer, Collections Applications: Associate Developer, Collections Applications Associate Developer, Collections Applications Why Work For Credit Acceptance? Credit Acceptance is a rapidly-expanding company with extensive growth… https://t.co/JCjDE1Uj3P https://t.co/xMCXc7py0w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop calling them 'Russian troll farms' https://t.co/tA5qK1N7xH https://t.co/fmnAbm0lN2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist (ADAS, HAD, FAD, KERAS, Python, Robotics, AI): Data Scientist (ADAS, HAD, FAD, KERAS, Python, Robotics, AI) – HARMAN on Facebook – HARMAN on Twitter – HARMAN on LinkedIn – Careers Home – About Us – Our Divisions – Professional Development… https://t.co/fWSSE9S7iY https://t.co/eyXq2Q6tPV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Business Analyst: Careers Center | IT Business Analyst Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome page Returning… https://t.co/CfAQykD9nc https://t.co/yGRTspe18i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Low-carb diets shorten your lifespan, study finds: A low-carb or high-carb diet raises your risk of death, a new study suggests, with people eating the food staple in moderation seeing the greatest benefits to their health. https://t.co/c8RDMYkDrY https://t.co/HnHCF9c67z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, Public Safety Solution: Software Engineer, Public Safety Solution ========================================= Tyler Technologies is looking for a talented Software Engineer to join our public safety product development team. The engineer… https://t.co/HmnQOmnzTc https://t.co/O8hZxjUEUX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Precast/Residential/Commercial: Detroit, MI Full-time $80k – $120k Posted Today If you are a Project Manager with experience, please read on… With an office in Detroit, we are an industry-leading construction company that his been in… https://t.co/xIKLdh2BRN https://t.co/8UjX9F0IB3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats are weighing House leadership options: House Minority Leader Nancy Pelosi is facing mounting pressure over her future, with calls from members of her own party to step aside as discussions about potential successors gain more traction -- both… https://t.co/J89LNwEDhw https://t.co/kBEDh7ZlKY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Controls Engineering Manager: Auburn Hills, MI Compensation Unspecified Posted Today Controls Engineering Manager needed for well established fast growing electrical company!! Top Reasons to Work with Us Great pay, excellent benefits and career growth!!… https://t.co/sAGLru6Flw https://t.co/9PKYzcXyQk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Requirements and Test Lead Continental Engineering Services: Job Title Requirements and Test Lead – Continental Engineering Services Division Chassis and Safety Job Description Continental Engineering Services (CES) is seeking an experienced Requirements… https://t.co/SR0Is1gOhG https://t.co/xAGhnd8i2q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior / Principal Software Developer: Senior / Principal Software Developer Job ID 2018-17444 Primary Location Michigan, Ann Arbor Regular/Temp Regular Additional Locations Omaha,Nebraska,United States;Columbia,Maryland,United States Full-Time/Part-Time… https://t.co/A6qFaDf5h6 https://t.co/sumwqI3b29]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Black in the White House: Meet Ja'Ron Smith: In the wake of Omarosa Manigault Newman's departure from the West Wing in December and recent tell-all book rollout replete with accusations of racism, a senior White House official was asked simply: Who is… https://t.co/QUPLmHzeTA https://t.co/ve6omyyqk4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Applications Systems Administrator Intermediate: Recruiter UNIVERSITY OF MICHIGAN Location Ann Arbor, United States Posted 02 Aug 2018 End of advertisement period 29 Aug 2018 Ref ****** Job Type Professional Services, IT Services Contract Type Permanent… https://t.co/3IfPwWC1n1 https://t.co/VCREReqIY7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Madonna joins sexy-celebs-in-their-60s: If anyone could put the "sex" in "sexagenarian" it would be Madonna. https://t.co/3mK2zTwq1Q https://t.co/uXw1jG7mWX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[oracle Hyperion: oracle Hyperion Ref No.: 18-28440 Location: Kalamazoo, Michigan Job Description: General – 6+ relevant work experience working with Hyperion Planning and FDMEE applications, including HFM, Planning, FDMEE, Essbase, ODI, and Smart View).… https://t.co/gWg0fGCuwR https://t.co/pogiEqgNHX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Oracle Apps DBA: Date: Aug 13, 2018 Location: Southfield, MI, US Company: NTT DATA Services Req ID: 27047 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The quality, integrity, and commitment of our employees… https://t.co/mHD6cNk263 https://t.co/H6vM2fgbyN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How a vegan diet can change your body: Veganism, the plant-based diet which shuns meat and dairy, is having its time in the sun. Since 2008, there has been a 350% increase in the number of self-described vegans in the UK alone. Where this motivation… https://t.co/CYwo3Y04He https://t.co/Gqo0hBIVwx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Operations Manager:   Job Description – Operations Manager (101663) Job Description  Operations Manager  Job Number:  101663   Primary Location : United States-Michigan-Dearborn  Description   Live IT Up at Ciber Global At Ciber Global, we believe the… https://t.co/9bDS3vywOv https://t.co/YBKLBQT8BE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sdet: SDET Ref No.:18-13071 Location: Auburn Hills, Michigan Position Type:Full Time/Contract Start Date: 07/24/2018 Required Skills Selenium Automation engineer with Java and SDET JOB DESCRIPTION: Should be able to start/define Test automation process,… https://t.co/OaiG3mp1gq https://t.co/V6VEI27WIm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Programmer: Overview PROLIM Global Corporation (**************) is currently seeking Java Developer for location Okemos , MI for one of our Top client. Job Description: Work collaboratively in an Agile team to deliver high quality source code to… https://t.co/oGQhmzEvOH https://t.co/nwENP9fe44]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Services Support Specialist, ERP Solution: Technical Services Support Specialist, ERP Solution =================================================== The Technical Services Support Specialist provides systems management technical support and… https://t.co/Hvj1YxtLBE https://t.co/mT80HAzAQO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mobile Apps (iOS Developer – Swift): Mobile Apps (iOS Developer – Swift) Ref No.: 18-32838 Location: Kalamazoo, Michigan Mobile Apps (iOS/Swift) Support Analyst 5-7 years – Experienced in iOS with Objective C – Handling messaging queues will be an added… https://t.co/CACk2aE80q https://t.co/Bvap3Fy3Om]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Test Lead: Overview PROLIM Global Corporation (**************) is currently seeking QA Test Lead for location Detroit , MI for one of our Top client. Job Description: Required Skills/Experience At least 5 years of experience in the below Facets… https://t.co/aZj706pghL https://t.co/HGod2BRkhz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Requirements and Test Lead Continental Engineering Services: Job Title Requirements and Test Lead – Continental Engineering Services Division Chassis and Safety Job Description Continental Engineering Services (CES) is seeking an experienced Requirements… https://t.co/TICoRXCkLE https://t.co/E1r6QeH7yR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Job Postings | Reyrey.comReynolds and Reynolds LogoFacebookLinkedInTwitterYouTubeInstagram Skip to main content [RR – Careers] Careers Super Navigation Careers Menu #ReyReyLife Search Jobs Main navigation [RR – Careers] Careers Main… https://t.co/JRAChMNjTl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Resting spot for scores of WWII sailors and stern of ship found: The USS Abner Read, a destroyer with more than 300 men aboard, was sailing near an island of the US territory of Alaska 75 years ago, hunting for Japanese submarines. https://t.co/NeVwfhfu5B https://t.co/GNB03kO3Ai]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anderson Cooper: Is this about payback or not?: CNN's Anderson Cooper looks at prominent intelligence professionals and their criticism of President Trump, after the President announced the revocation of former CIA Director John Brennan's security… https://t.co/TXeMADL1qV https://t.co/L62BjX1T3H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Business Process Analyst: * Please wait… A career at Amway is a career in opportunity. At Amway you can explore and grow, make a difference, and find success. Established in 1959, Amway is a multi-billion dollar company, and the world’s No. 1 direct… https://t.co/SPLhYSx2bm https://t.co/T9J9Q12ymu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Staff Software Engineer: Job opening: Senior Staff Software Engineer | Continental AG – Go to navigation – Go to content – Go to the end of the page By using the following access keys you can jump directly to the respective links: – 0 Navigation –… https://t.co/lKOQdkRaPh https://t.co/wc65YKFDuJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NY Gov. Andrew Cuomo says America 'was never that great': New York Gov. Andrew Cuomo said America "was never that great" during a speech on Wednesday, drawing criticism from the Republican looking to unseat him in November. https://t.co/9PKVuIpGzK https://t.co/aw9UqEXkxd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sfdc developer: sfdc developer Ref No.: 18-35115 Location: Farmington hills, Michigan Production Support – Bug Fixes – New Enhancements to the site – Monthly Releases – Checking Logs – Batch Jobs on CA Scheduler – Data loads using Data Loader – Creating… https://t.co/hZlnPpIv4F https://t.co/D2SOAfrVAF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suspected Russian spy caught in US Embassy: Suspected Russian spy caught in US Embassy https://t.co/TVXhSaaceJ https://t.co/nkSgEHmuJx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla: Should you buy, sell or short? https://t.co/dObs1WrbPa https://t.co/34SbG0r3PA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Desktop Support – Level II: Job TitleDesktop Support – Level II – ID:32192 Duration6 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsMicrosoft Office 2010, 2016 and 0365 applications, Active Directory, TCP/IP, DNS, DHCP, SCCM LocationSaline, MI Date Posted07/24/2018 FOR… https://t.co/hpVlnULfG0 https://t.co/RMu0eNAGrl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Architect Requirements Engineer: Job opening: System Architect &amp; Requirements Engineer | Continental AG – Go to navigation – Go to content – Go to the end of the page By using the following access keys you can jump directly to the respective… https://t.co/NCN7Nyor7Q https://t.co/BRfyskoQUZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automation Software Engineer Senior: For Siemens Automation Software Engineer – Senior job – Research &amp; Development – Multiple Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard – Toggle navigation – My Dashboard – Our Stories – FAQS – –… https://t.co/1wVUzSdV2s https://t.co/szSqE1U2dK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Service Desk Analyst: JOB ID: ****** SERVICE DESK ANALYST TROY, MICHIGAN REGULAR / ROTATING ADDITIONAL JOB INFORMATION TITLE:Service Desk Analyst CITY, STATE: Troy, MI LOCATION: MITROY 800 Tower Dr DEPARTMENT: Ops Service Center CRC ADDITIONAL JOB… https://t.co/xtpSStwpdL https://t.co/DfJB705Oob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Software Developer: Summary:Job Description The Senior Web Developer builds quick concept prototypes, program for capabilities using client side technologies as well as frameworks, offer cross platform compatibility/support. Responsible for components… https://t.co/ukJOQxksvE https://t.co/udVCICtZpj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Business Process Expert: Job Description – Zeeland, MI, USA – Full Time If you are a dynamic individual with excellent technical abilities and experience in a manufacturing environment then Plascore, Inc. has the perfect career opportunity for you!… https://t.co/SJBEwAN81b https://t.co/o2BDiPKSRS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer and SharePoint Consultant: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Troy, MI Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 8/2/2018 Job Description Job Number: R******* Web Developer and SharePoint Consultant Key Role: Design and… https://t.co/UON4tokiKj https://t.co/zveti5klmK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Defense rests in Paul Manafort trial; closing arguments Wednesday: The defense rested its case Tuesday morning in the trial against former Trump campaign chairman Paul Manafort without calling any witnesses, setting the stage for closing arguments… https://t.co/51fibvT1Vf https://t.co/2glQHTWHWj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Full Stack Developer: Job Ref: ********* Employer: NTT DATA Country: United States County/State: Michigan Address: Post Date: 09/08/2018 00:12 Req ID: 27780 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The… https://t.co/xpkKnX4sX4 https://t.co/Y9FxeFp1Nj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See inside SpaceX's new spacecraft: SpaceX will be the first private company to launch people into space. Crew Dragon will be heading to the International space station after being launched from Florida. https://t.co/MQevIjEHNS https://t.co/itWKXG7pyy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Job Postings | Reyrey.comReynolds and Reynolds LogoFacebookLinkedInTwitterYouTubeInstagram Skip to main content [RR – Careers] Careers Super Navigation Careers Menu #ReyReyLife Search Jobs Main navigation [RR – Careers] Careers Main… https://t.co/Qs1p43M1hq https://t.co/L0bDUS6eIp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer – Emerging Technologies: Senior Software Developer – Emerging Technologies Job ID  2017-12991 Primary Location  Michigan, Ann Arbor Regular/Temp  Regular Additional Locations  Jersey City,New Jersey,United States;St.… https://t.co/3i9i4LrWP4 https://t.co/Vi3okMFEfS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embedded Systems Cybersecurity Engineer (RMF/DOD): Embedded Systems Cybersecurity Engineer (RMF/DOD) job in Sterling Heights, Michigan, United States | Engineering &amp; Technology jobs at BAE SystemsJob Details – Home – Explore Careers – – Life At BAE… https://t.co/GzAx25Ynyq https://t.co/epnqufwDi5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Construction Engineering Project Manager: SNC-Lavalin’s Atkins business is one of the world’s most respected design, engineering and project management consultancies. SNC-Lavalin’s Atkins business has been providing infrastructure planning,… https://t.co/LngFovqvJx https://t.co/Si8xzFljMq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Business Specialist: * Zeeland, MI, USA * Full Time Email Me Similar Jobs Email Me This Job If you are a dynamic individual with excellent technical abilities and experience in a manufacturing environment then Plascore, Inc. has the perfect career… https://t.co/vMbrapJmZJ https://t.co/ljuWgqMxI6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Hardware Developer: Job offer: Huf Group 0 Choose language Partner Portal | Data Security | Contact – English – Deutsch – Companies – Profile – Products – Certifications – Career – News Reset You are here: Start Huf Group &gt; Career &gt; Job Vacancies –… https://t.co/Dmv3eVtOAi https://t.co/hGbJNbW8Dm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Database Administrator: Job Details (*Employee Referral Program applies to this job) Job No.: #******* Location: Multiple undetermined worksites throughout the U.S Job Title: Sr. Database Administrator Job Description: Duties for this position will… https://t.co/OzkQIHHsUR https://t.co/Kec4RslEAB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These may be the best tacos in LA: Angeleno Ellen Bennett, co-founder of apron maker Hedley and Bennett, shares her favorite taco truck and other taco joints. https://t.co/OMPoAanRpc https://t.co/4CUFB2fxh7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Program Manager Automotive, IOT: Senior Program Manager – Automotive, IOT HARMAN International Date: Jul 18, 2018 Location: Novi, MI, US Description: Position Summary: The Customer Program Manager is responsible for the overall program delivery of… https://t.co/PhaQkYYeCS https://t.co/7uhNRoLrSF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Ref No.: 18-33280 Location: Troy, Michigan Role : Java Developer Duration : 12 months Location : Troy, MI Job Description : "Java 8/9/10 certified ; J2EE: Spring Boot, Hibernate and JPA Webservices: RESTFUL API development… https://t.co/DzPw3p5ncz https://t.co/SwhcJzMU8H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Superintendent – New Installation: Start apply with LinkedIn Start apply with Facebook Start apply with Xing Apply Now Please wait… Location: Detroit, MI, Michigan, US Requisition ID: 10083 Schindler stands for mobility. Mobility needs experts. Join our… https://t.co/MMxscVBHPE https://t.co/6EYms71Lng]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Historic face transplant gives suicide survivor a 'second chance': As Katie Stubblefield brushed her fingers across her face, she could feel the wound. https://t.co/sYRd3fiSqx https://t.co/K9SmGDPb5V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead AEM Developer: Careers: Job Openings and Career Development | Perficient, Inc. |Lead AEM Developer Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the… https://t.co/ZjTR5RqVkQ https://t.co/32mhxElsAg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Active Safety Data Analyst: Active Safety Data Analyst – ENG******* in Milford, Michigan, US | Engineering at general motorsJob details page – – – – – – Home – About Us About Us – Our Company – Our Employees – How We Hire – Diversity &amp; Inclusion –… https://t.co/8cBMz8auJP https://t.co/dk289a0mHj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 reasons you're not making more money at work https://t.co/hfGS2YIk7N https://t.co/oUEJpdDeLW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Applications Analyst, SAP MM: Company profile We like it when our employees have goals. What about you? Are you ready to grow with your challenges? We at MAHLE are a leading international supplier to the automotive industry. With our products for… https://t.co/AzVJj2aX5v https://t.co/2LkinjS65x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Developer: Job Details (*Employee Referral Program applies to this job) Job ID ******* Position Sr. Developer Description Summary: Job Duties:Under limited supervision, develop, create, and modify complex batch and online computer applications using… https://t.co/48wxG1WQsH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SDET Automation: SDET Automation in Auburn Hills, US-MI, USA | Technology &amp; Engineering at CognizantJob Details | Cognizant – ************* – Industries – – – Services – – – Latest Thinking – – – About Cognizant – – Careers Home – Get To Know Us – Our… https://t.co/DwfhA1MrJI https://t.co/LvH1pSzSZA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Full Stack Developer: Date: Aug 8, 2018 Location: Ann Arbor, MI, US Company: NTT DATA Services Req ID: 27780 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The quality, integrity, and commitment of our… https://t.co/1zMWpfth8T https://t.co/iMvl5S4ZEH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embedded Software Engineer: Job Title Embedded Software Engineer Division Chassis and Safety Job Description Core Responsibilities: Design, implement, and test embedded software based on Continental standards and processes Define, plan, prioritize, and… https://t.co/6PZEFmKScq https://t.co/G9LdfIov7G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prosecutor overrules sheriff, charges Florida man in 'stand your ground' case: Michael Drejka, who fatally shot Markeis McGlockton after McGlockton shoved him in a Clearwater, Florida, convenience store parking lot, has been charged with manslaughter,… https://t.co/ZwG2xXU0uj https://t.co/HWRVIOGE2f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, Public Safety Solution: Software Engineer, Public Safety Solution ========================================= Tyler Technologies is looking for a talented Software Engineer to join our public safety product development team. The engineer… https://t.co/pBJsDiO6qZ https://t.co/7lVRDuGdAz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fox News host appears to rebuke colleague https://t.co/zCawx639uD https://t.co/zWfmhEzTak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Construction Engineering Project Manager: SNC-Lavalin’s Atkins business is one of the world’s most respected design, engineering and project management consultancies. SNC-Lavalin’s Atkins business has been providing infrastructure planning,… https://t.co/c8QCHYOuAu https://t.co/qKecHNjCmW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Assurance Engineer: Quality Assurance Engineer – Jonesville, MI – Martinrea International Inc. Jobs – Home – Jobs Quality Assurance Engineer – Jonesville, MIToggle navigation Quality Assurance Engineer – Jobs – Login – 31-Jul-2018 to 31-Dec-2018… https://t.co/hmqpgds17I https://t.co/4TQuXnT2WN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Applications Developer: Recruiter UNIVERSITY OF MICHIGAN Location Ann Arbor, United States Posted 01 Aug 2018 End of advertisement period 13 Aug 2018 Ref ****** Job Type Professional Services, IT Services Contract Type Permanent Hours Full Time You… https://t.co/tV6Lz9gHJP https://t.co/3ZJvUBPjyh]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>