<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[When you blame others, you give up your power to change. - Dr. Robert Anthony]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The glass is neither half-full nor half-empty: it's twice as big as it needs to be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Jackson Five  http://t.co/mgW7YLFVUJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You only have to do a very few things right in your life so long as you don't do too many things wrong. - Warren Buffett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Electric Light Orchestra  http://t.co/bx9n9kleJ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating Famous and Historical Watches  http://t.co/am0deC8RK0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space is the stature of God. - Joseph Joubert]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spring is when you feel like whistling even with a shoe full of slush. - Doug Larson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most games are lost, not won! - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Amazing Nappy Brown  http://t.co/Wmm0jaXXjm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More die in the United States of too much food than too little. - John Kenneth Galbraith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoever said that money can't buy happiness, simply didn't know where to go shopping --&gt; Bo Derek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Mike Clifford - A One-Hit Wonder  http://t.co/0aAaHc0cq3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Ride - La Vibora at Six Flags Over Texas in Arlington  http://t.co/zHB0oeRXYE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome gardening t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the gardening lovers in your life!   http://t.co/vsgNoHhZId]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Some Young People Need Mentoring  http://t.co/csi2DgFUQ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Bonnie Lou  http://t.co/4MuOiNJMru]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Fun - Bumper Water Boats with Water Cannons! http://t.co/LcqHEsZeJM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Isaac Asimov  http://t.co/T7bdU8dk2q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The quality of a leader is reflected in the standards they set for themselves. - Ray Kroc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome basketball t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the basketball lovers in your life!   http://t.co/0JlMLEc0Bb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If at first you don't succeed; call it version 1.0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Buckinghams  http://t.co/0vbmGjjcXv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Ensure You Have Safe Drinking Water in a Disaster  http://t.co/3OspmNOYok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one really knows who created Bitcoin - read about the fascinating history of Satoshi Nakamoto... http://t.co/9nZwbc2oeV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Driving a car is like playing baseball. The object in both is to get home safely. - Joe Moore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The purity of a person's heart can be quickly measured by how they regard animals - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's later than we think and most of us aren't even thinking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's one small step for [a] man; one giant leap for mankind. - Neil A. Armstrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Youth is when we want to set the world on fire... Middle age is when we hope our children won't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About The Christian Faith  http://t.co/1mvGfbYr7f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Green Acres is an American sitcom classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/iVEnxjWLVc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must accept finite disappointment, but we must never lose infinite hope. - Martin Luther King, Jr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Clarence Carter  http://t.co/EPNTv8VfF0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peter Townshend shows us it's all right to grow up. There is dignity after rock'n'roll. - Sting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What we want is to see the child in pursuit of knowledge, and not knowledge in pursuit of the child. - George Bernard Shaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cooking for Geeks: Real Science, Great Hacks, and Good Food  -&gt; http://t.co/nf42eDV79I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So exactly what is an atomic clock?  http://t.co/yJ1q5wSOum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball has the great advantage over cricket of being sooner ended. - George Bernard Shaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good introduction to Minecraft Mods - http://t.co/da03g9FilF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 7 - No Luck!  http://t.co/a80cjRuS9W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Either write something worth reading or do something worth writing about.  Benjamin Franklin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Highland Village, Texas  http://t.co/9r4f0qCToU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Fats Domino  http://t.co/ed4PjOk5jw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love any movie that has a retarded person working at Starbucks.  Chris Kattan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Music of Hot Chocolate  http://t.co/EaKEigXDri]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Ral Donner  http://t.co/6EtmDi8Rm2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's basically the same, just darker. - Alan Kulwicki, on racing Saturday nights as opposed to Sunday afternoons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only thing worse than a Mets game is a Mets double header. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Google Webmaster Tools  http://t.co/CiZcSG4eyv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can a guy win a game if you don't give him any runs? - Robert Bo Belinsky after Losing 15 - 0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greetings, programs! - Flynn, TRON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Kim Carnes  http://t.co/eBgZydYmfN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About James Taylor - his biography  http://t.co/bG3UFJ6PBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd just as soon kiss a wookiee! - Princess Leia, The Empire Strikes Back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What you don't know won't hurt you but it provides a lot amusement for other people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Until one has loved an animal,  a part of one's soul remains unawakened. - Anatole France]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science fiction writers foresee the inevitable, and although problems and catastrophes may be inevitable, solutions are not. - Isaac Asimov]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It may be true that most people can't stand prosperity, but it is also true that most people don't have to!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Pink Floyd  http://t.co/941tCqDNLT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Chi-Lites  http://t.co/8cBdrPaqn0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Understanding Attention Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder (ADHD)  http://t.co/Girjta0giH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Foreigner  http://t.co/Ujp7fjp8vr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here I Am T-Shirt What Are Your Other Two Wishes http://t.co/KV8ZZLly1k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Frustrated at Cleaning Your Keyboards and Other Electronics?  Check Out Cyber Clean - Fast and Simple! http://t.co/IeNVy6wuMj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Classic Cassette Silicone Case for Your iPhone! http://t.co/IWldf6WGkK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The internet has turned what used to be a controlled, one-way message into a real-time dialogue with millions - Danniel Sacks, Fast Company]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think the rock'n'roll myth of living on the edge is a pile of crap. - Robert Smith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do I set a laser printer to stun?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wal-mart --  do they like make walls there?  Paris Hilton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is only one success - to be able to spend your life in your own way - Christopher Morley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion Note: Little change in men's clothes this year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mr. Bentley - He builds fast trucks. - Ettore Bugatti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Corona Beer  http://t.co/XxWKENgbYK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never argue with the data. - Sheen, Jimmy Neutron]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Foghat  http://t.co/SgAXMA7RiE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nolan Ryan is pitching much better now that he has his curve ball straightened out. - Joe Garagiola]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Middle age is after one night out you need two nights in. . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Kool and the Gang  http://t.co/cTvNU39oIG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Celiac Disease And Gluten Free Foods  http://t.co/VmyLEAvQvu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you are thin, don't eat fast. If you are fat, don't eat fast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The man who is old enough to know better is always looking for a girl who is not quite old.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Different Types of Beer  http://t.co/BTm8z0MC2R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Dave Mason  http://t.co/lUgc3Bygq2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Home is where -- . You hang your head]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Narcotics Detection – Technology's Place in the War on Drugs  http://t.co/jqJvVbPsLv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great overview on using Redstone in Minecraft - http://t.co/DpIOwpoXY0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the Icebound Land by John Flanagan  http://t.co/OJn70UmZaa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Carlos Santana  http://t.co/H8gtHl3vD8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Girls are like internet domain names, the ones I like are already taken.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our greatest weakness lies in giving up. The most certain way to succeed is always to try just one more time. - Thomas A. Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome basketball t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the basketball lovers in your life!   http://t.co/SnV9vcduax]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A philosopher is someone who knows what to do until it happens to him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Far Out and Super Cool Watches  http://t.co/tdfTS84fbM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One thought driven home is better than three left to die on base. . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Domestic Adoption - A Helping Hand To A New Life  http://t.co/CMNfjexCjM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Great Tours of Europe  http://t.co/nYe4EvGAWT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding good players is easy. Getting them to play as a team is another story. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very very cool a complete working model of SpaceX rocket - awesome tech!  http://t.co/a4cbdzbAhm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In order to break the ice --  crack a smile]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>