<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[To live exhilarating in and for the moment is deadly serious work, fun of the most exhausting sort. -Barbara Grizzuti Harrison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A mind once stretched by a new idea never regains its original dimensions. -Oliver Wendell Holmes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opportunities multiply as they are seized; they die when neglected. Life is a long line of opportunities. -John Wicker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those whose work and pleasures are one are fortune's favorite children. -Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adapt or perish, now as ever, is Nature's inexorable imperative. -H.G. Wells]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret of discipline is motivation. When a man is sufficiently motivated, discipline will take care of itself. -Alexander Paterson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be all you can be and live a good life -- have fun with it. -Tina Yothers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man who finds no satisfaction in himself, seeks for it in vain else where. -Francois De La Rochefoucauld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The hardest thing to give away is kindness; it always comes back to you. -English proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The first recipe for happiness is: Avoid too lengthy meditations on the past." -Andre Maurois]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the depth of winter I finally learned that within me there lay an invincible summer. -Albert Camus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That fear of missing out on things makes you miss out on everything. -Etty Hillesum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dost thou love life? Then do not squander time, for that's the stuff life is made of. -Benjamin Franklin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Talent hits a target no one else can hit; genius hits a target no one else can see. -Arthur Schopenhauer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Work at your job and make a living, work on yourself and make a fortune. ~ Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fall seven times and stand up eight. -Japanese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If A equals success, then the formula is A = X+Y and Z, with X being work, Y play, and Z keeping your mouth shut. -Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't dwell on reality; it will only keep you from greatness. -Randall McBride, Jr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't become a wandering generality. Be a meaningful specific. -Zig Ziglar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a world of action, and not for moping and droning in. -Dickens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One way to keep momentum going is to have constantly greater goals.
- Michael Korda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hard work beats all the tonics and vitamins in the world. -Col. Sanders (yes, the KFC guy)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great things are completed by talented people who believe they will accomplish them. -Warren Bennis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have had enough success for two lifetimes. My success is talent put together with hard work… https://t.co/dR12URoG4x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life leaps like a geyser for those who drill through the rock of inertia. -Alexis Carrel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The time is always right to do what is right. -Martin Luther King, Jr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our truest life is when we are in our dreams awake. -Henry David Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enthusiasm is the inspiration of everything great. Without it no man is to be feared, and with it none despised. -John Bovee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It may be that those who do most, dream most." -Stephen Leacock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good reminder! Now really think about it....

Help others achieve their dreams and you will… https://t.co/ojEWOGxtX3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What do we live for, if it is not to make life less difficult for each other?" -George Eliot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People are not lazy. They simply have impotent goals -- that is, goals that do not inspire them.
- Tony Robbins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is no 'brief candle' to me. I want to be thoroughly used up when I die, for the harder I work the more I live. -G.B. Shaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Help others achieve their dreams and you will achieve yours. -Les Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What I emphasize is for people to make choices based not on fear, but on what gives them a sense of fulfillment. -P. Chance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wisdom is the power to put our time and our knowledge to the proper use.
- Thomas J. Watson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who cherish a beautiful vision, a lofty ideal in their hearts, will one day realize it.
-James Allen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The elevator to success is out of order. You'll have to use the stairs... one step at a time. -Joe Girard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If there is 1 secret to success, it lies in the ability to get the other person's point of view &amp; see things from his angle. -Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is for want of application, rather than of means that people fail. - Francois de La Rochefoucauld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not the will to win, but the will to prepare to win that makes the difference. -Bear Bryant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's no use growing older if you only learn new ways of misbehaving yourself. -Hector Hugh Munro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Without ambition one starts nothing. Without work one finishes nothing. The prize will not be sent to you. You have to win it. -Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many ideas are good for a limited time -- not forever. -Robert Townsend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The grass may be greener on the other side of the fence, but you still have to mow it. -Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes no more time to be courteous than to be rude. -Ann Landers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you have knowledge, let others light their candles with it. -Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Defeat should never be a source of discouragement, but rather a fresh stimulus. -Robert South (1634-1716)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He that has energy enough to root out a vice should go further, and try to plant a virtue in its place. -Charles Colton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every day do something that will inch you closer to a better tomorrow. -Doug Firebaugh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Equal opportunity means everyone will have a fair chance at being incompetent." -Dr. Laurence J. Peter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bad habits are like chains that are too light to feel until they are too heavy to carry. -Warren Buffett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The man who can be nothing but serious, or nothing but merry, is but half a man." -Leigh Hunt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man's life is interesting primarily when he has failed; it's a sign that he tried to surpass himself. -Georges Clemenceau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anything you vividly imagine, ardently desire, sincerely believe, and enthusiastically act upon must come to reality. -Paul Meyer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dream is just a dream. A goal is a dream with a plan and a deadline. -Harvey MacKay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Criticism of others is futile. If you indulge in it often, you should be warned that it can be fatal to your career. -D Carnegie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The world belongs to the energetic." -Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What I aspired to be and was not, comforts me.
- Robert Browning]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you don't make things happen then things will happen to you. -Lanes Company]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing will ever be attempted if all possible objections must first be overcome. -Samuel Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Failure is God's own tool for carving some of the finest outlines in the character of his children. -Thomas Hodgkin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our greatest weariness comes from work not done. -Eric Hoffer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Lives of great men all remind us we can make our lives sublime!" -Longfellow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money cannot buy you happiness. But it does bring you a more pleasant form of misery. -Spike Milligan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest good you can do for another is not just to share your riches, but to reveal to him his own. -Benjamin Disraeli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you have got an elephant by the hind legs and he is trying to run away, it's best to let him run. -Abraham Lincoln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We cannot hold a torch to light another's path without brightening our own. -Ben Sweetland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one gossips about other people's secret virtues. -Bertrand Russell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a world of action, and not for moping and droning in.
- Charles Dickens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every time you don't follow your inner guidance, you feel a loss of energy, loss of power, a sense of spiritual deadness. -Shakti Gawain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Achievement is largely the product of steadily raising one's levels of aspiration and expectation. -Jack Nicklaus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opportunity often comes disguised in the form of misfortune, or temporary defeat. -Napoleon Hill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tell everyone what you want to do and someone will want to help you do it. -W. Clement Stone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Progress is not created by contented people." -Frank Tyger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you don't program yourself, life will program you! - Les Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Becoming a star may not be your destiny, but being the best that you can be is a goal that you can set for yourselves. -Bryan Lindsay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a grand thing it is to be clever and have common sense. -Terence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it fails, admit it frankly and try another. But above all, try something. -Franklin D. Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opportunities? They're all around us. There's power lying latent everywhere waiting for the observant eye to discover it. -Orison Marden]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All you have to do is know where you're going. The answers will come to you of their own accord.
- Earl Nightingale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anger: an acid that can do more harm to the vessel in which it is stored than to anything on which it is poured. -Seneca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learning is like rowing upstream: not to advance is to drop back. -Chinese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing is so common as unsuccessful men with talent. They lack only determination. -Charles Swindoll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Don't stumble over something behind you." -Seneca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sorrow is the mere rust of the soul. Activity will cleanse and brighten it. -Samuel Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The foolish man seeks happiness in the distance; the wise grows it under his feet. -James Openheim]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your big opportunity may be right where you are now. -Napoleon Hill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing can withstand the power of the human will if it is willing to stake its very existence to the extent of its purpose. -Disraeli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The path of least resistance makes all rivers, and some men, crooked. -Napoleon Hill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You can't act like a skunk without someone getting wind of it." -Lorene Workman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope is a good breakfast, but it is a bad supper. -Francis Bacon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The goose that lays the golden eggs likes to lay where there are eggs already. -Charles Haddon Spurgeon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is easier to catch flies with honey than with vinegar. -English proverb #proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being an optimist after you've got everything you want doesn't count. -Kin Hubbard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those that are firm in their will mold the world to themselves. -Johann Wolfgang Von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No wind favors him who has no destined port. -Michel Eyquem De Montaigne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your vision will become clear only when you can look into your own heart. Who looks outside, dreams; who looks inside, awakens. -Carl Jung]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Years may wrinkle the skin, but to give up interest wrinkles the soul.
- Douglas MacArthur]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To win you've got to stay in the game. -Claude M. Bristol]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>