<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[My Name Is Mirian https://t.co/OdEHzQ8tmR via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A&amp;W on #Yelp: It's an A&amp;W, it's fast food but its Canadian, they are serving veg patties and are phasing out plasti… https://t.co/zogaTFmkxT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free Personalized Greeting Cards &amp; Invitations  - so great for work events! https://t.co/TkonBhPwH7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Shayndi NEVER should have happened in the first place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @voteprbc: With #ProRep, a party that gets 40% of the votes gets 40% of the seats in the Legislature.

Get what you vote for. It’s that…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BowinnMa Spaces are one thing but we need to be able to provide quality care.  That means more than licensed spaces it means well-educated caregivers who should be compensated appropriately.  I urge the government to use the same model as our public school system.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@littlebrown @MillerMadeline @AndersonsBkshp Just bought Circe at @UBCbookstore yesterday.  SO hard to put down.  I've got to start reading earlier tonight!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BardemAntarctic: REALLY GREAT news from last night! People all over the world asked krill companies to stop fishing in areas that need…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dig into an Incredible Compendium of Objects Excavated from the Bottom of Amsterdam’s Amstel River https://t.co/PYhfFmPG5i via @colossal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Robert Plant on Waldorf Schools... https://t.co/YXCn1FFU9K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheEconomist Does anyone really care if Drump's golf courses fail?  He's destroyed homes and much of the natural environment there and I hope they all close.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CBCEnt @CBCAlerts Sad news.  I highly recommend the Netflix documentary on him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @globeandmail: Concerns mount as death toll appears to be on rise for minke whales in Maritimes https://t.co/e9qKzzdIaO https://t.co/FBS…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @asjadnazir: Ekapol Chanthawong lost his whole family as a kid. He trained as a monk &amp; then devoted his life to helping coach kids. He k…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @voteprbc: What's so difficult to understand about #ProRep?

Get what you voted for.

#pr4bc
#bcpoli https://t.co/FRVjzLydOr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One Year In, Green-NDP Still Co-operating and Government Gets Good Marks  via @TheTyee https://t.co/q3TOAh2Tkd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The cute vaquitas are becoming extinct -- there are only 12 of them left! But it's not just the vaquitas we're losing, click here to join a global plan to stop this extinction crisis: https://t.co/eKW8R3Ooa1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We could put tens of thousands of people back to work cleaning up aging oil and gas wells across Alberta and the country. @MargMcCuaigBoyd @joececiyyc @SPhillipsAB we want a just transition now https://t.co/g64pExY7WB #PolluterPays #abpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@UN_HRC Stop millions losing citizenship in #Assam #India. Sign &amp; RT: https://t.co/nURiCZOaQ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NatriceR @CBCAlerts He’s too fat and would hurt the poor horse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @calypsocoast: Study finds Vancouver-area laundry microplastics are filtering into ocean
https://t.co/DFW5sinCVA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kaitlynherbst16: Vancouver - 4th Ave @ Macdonald blocked because of a fire https://t.co/NAsNsqRQLp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DalaiLama: While many people consider sensory experience as the main source of happiness, really it is peace of mind. What destroys pea…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tomwfootball: The thing I want to know about this Mbappe picture is: how did he manage to get into Ronaldo’s bedroom? https://t.co/I87V…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cbcnewsbc so how's that working for you in the U.S.?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@2010_14_HeatFan @cbcnewsbc I’ve been there - it’s not the type of place you wear a ball cap in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CaptainSuburb @cbcnewsbc yep but kind of makes it a dead one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chfbc: Breaking: Fraserview Housing Co-op will be opening its Presentation Centre tomorrow! We are now accepting applications for 90 br…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cbcnewsbc Doesn't the Tea House have some sort of dress code?  Anyone with any sense of style and manners knows you don't wear a ball cap inside a fine dining restaurant!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @darcynews: 10,443 shares! Let’s keep it going and get these doggos adopted in time for Canada Day.  https://t.co/rZ7IjSkoQu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @krassenstein: President Obama Yesterday revealed what he told Trump about ObamaCare:  

"Just change the name and claim that you made t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CBCAlerts: 223 international scientists urge B.C. to avoid unsustainable logging practices in its intact rainforests. They say these fo…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheEconomist: Plastic-eating caterpillars could save the planet https://t.co/EJWUqwalv9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheEconomist: Humans aside, no species on Earth has a more complex society than that of elephants https://t.co/ovWt2fKZWV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BCGovNews: "Money laundering isn’t a victimless crime. It’s linked to the opioid crisis, and deaths on our streets. It’s linked to skyr…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nathancullen: Mexican drug cartels, Chinese gangs &amp; Middle Eastern crime syndicates - all have been using Vancouver casinos to launder…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RosieBarton: This is scathing. And factual. https://t.co/RV6b6giiNP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RVAwonk: "[T]he real incivilities that plague our moment in history ... are the actions of a man and his enablers who feel no compuncti…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump You're accusing others of "crazy rants"?!  That's rich.  The world is laughing at you.  #shame]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Urgent: Tell Trudeau to scrap Bill C-69 @CouncilofCDNs https://t.co/EKXtTfOACN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @camanpour: A Native American speaking out for new Americans.

“Immigrants helped to build our country as it is today," says @Deb4Congre…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ubcnews: #UBC linguist creates language for Hollywood film Alpha: https://t.co/JEetswJS3c https://t.co/c96VfkXgY8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CharlieAngusNDP His was the first death of a public figure in my lifetime that brought me to tears.  What an incredible human being he was.  Canada misses him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OrlaGuerin: Bloodied schoolbags belonging to children who never came home after an airstrike by the Saudi-led coalition #Yemen.  At lea…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @krassenstein: BREAKING: Randolph County in Georgia is considering closing 7 of 9 voting precincts during the midterms on Nov 6th.

Rand…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There needs to be gender parity on the Supreme Court https://t.co/4biqYwwtY3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CBCAlerts: Speaking before Montreal Pride parade, Justin Trudeau says Canadians should 'stop talking about' tolerance: 'We need to talk…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can there be a female version of The Dude?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In weeks we could get the 5th largest economy of the world to ban new fossil fuel projects. Click to learn more and help make it happen -- then RT: https://t.co/ya3m5IUpQc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don’t Listen to the Fraser Institute. Canadians Are Not Paying More In Taxes Than ‘The Necessities of Life’(https://t.co/qJhE0zO1GU)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CharlieAngusNDP: John Baird’s appearance on Saudi state TV raises huge ethical questions.
He is a paid advisor to Barrick - a company w…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @camanpour: Kofi Annan, one of the best UNSGs ever. And a good and decent man. RIP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #TransMountain pipeline could drive orcas to the brink of extinction as newborn orcas are dying. Tell @JustinTrudeau and @Bill_Morneau to scrap the Trans Mountain pipeline deal. https://t.co/t4z6nnHc8v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cbcnewsbc: Chinese lanterns + dry climate and wildfires = unhappy firefighters | via @jphballard  https://t.co/hOzP0QUXh4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheTweetOfGod: If I didn't love LeBron James I wouldn't have named the King James Bible after him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @keithboykin: In Trump's World:
Obama: Kenyan
LeBron James: dumb
Don Lemon: dumb
Maxine Waters: low IQ
black countries: shitholes
black…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dearsusanbranch The Golden Rule - do unto others as you would have done to you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dearsusanbranch If you can’t say something nice, don’t say anything at all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dearsusanbranch Don’t call each other names]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ubcfoodie: Starting August 1, @ubcfoodie will no longer offer single-use plastic straws and cutlery. Learn more: https://t.co/lSUr5rmW3…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @krassenstein: BREAKING:  U.S. borrowing expected to hit $329 billion in the current quarter.  This would be the largest July-September…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RepJoeKennedy: 25 Russians indicted. 5 guilty pleas. Mr. President, what you call a stain, we call a justice system standing strong for…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sheila_Scott @CTVVancouver Poor little sweetie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@globeandmail @globepolitics Do it!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SethAbramson: CONFIRMED: DONALD TRUMP JR. LIED TO CONGRESS—A CRIME.

Mueller has him, now, whenever he wants him. Pass it on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @VanFireRescue: The @CelebOfLight starts this weekend! In addition to great @VancouverPD advice https://t.co/xSROKFu0xS pls remember the…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MuhammadLila: You know the #TorontoShooting suspect?  He was Muslim.  You know who else was?  

The head of the trauma unit that perfor…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bike share comes to campus https://t.co/xfP1qNaqDb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MikeHudema: Meet “Scarlet” she was born in 2014. 
When she was 7 months she breached 60 times. 

Unfortunately, recent sightings show h…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank-you @donlemon . Just thank-you. #truthteller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunshine Diner on #Yelp: Classic Benny with side of extra hollandaise https://t.co/GU7ouZis2D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PnPCBC @christyclarkbc @CBCKatie Just what this egomaniac needs is more smoke blown up her ass.  @christyclarkbc worked to undermine our education system and childcare subsidies.  She is a crook and no supporter of women.  Boooooo!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CNN: A wave of garbage was filmed rippling off the coast of the Dominican Republic. An environmental group is working with the governme…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CNN: A company in New Zealand tested out four-day work weeks. The experiment was so successful, now it wants to make it permanent https…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CNN: For the second month in a row, Time magazine has put a provocative photo illustration of President Trump on its cover -- this time…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MichaelSkolnik: Just 22 days ago, five members of the media were murdered while working at the Capitol Gazette in Annapolis, Maryland.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @david_w_ashmore: Ooof, look at the bobbing of the Greenland iceberg as it drifts by  Innaarsuit ~7 secs in (video credit seems to be to…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marriott Will Ditch All Plastic Straws by 2019 https://t.co/Qdfk22wzQo via @thepointsguy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheTweetOfGod: No matter what you think of Donald Trump, you have to admit: he's a piece of shit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pepsi’s CEO has one last task before she leaves. Share this to tell @IndraNooyi to fix her palm oil problem, and end @PepsiCo’s business partnership with disgraced palm oil company @Indofood https://t.co/Wmegklw2UM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Send a message to every minister in Ford's cabinet demanding they stand up for our Charter rights #onpoli #cdnpoli https://t.co/ShH2ehwlCx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @eabl81: @realDonaldTrump The next time you attend a memorial for the thousands of lives lost on 9/11, try not to act as if it's a campa…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @wkamaubell: Going to the #Emmys is a privilege. Winning an Emmy is a privilege. Being allowed to stay w/ your kids when you cross the U…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JFKLibrary: Happy 52nd anniversary, Star Trek! Leonard Nimoy wrote to JFK in 1962 asking for a safer planet. #StarTrekDay https://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @billmaher: It's time to get @AlFranken off the bench so he can come back to doing what he does better than any other Democrat: taking d…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@donlemon I'm sorry to say I'm with @ChrisCuomo  - I think you look much much better with some hair on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OrangutansSOS: There are only 14,600 Sumatran orangutans left in the wild, and the forests they depend on are being chopped down. You c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I could happily live in this esthetic forever.
https://t.co/Klu1ocjAiC - Ralph Lauren 50th Anniversary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lagallyc: Study suggests meat and dairy industry on track to surpass oil companies as biggest greenhouse gas emitters https://t.co/dpyl…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm attending CHF BC Annual General Meeting &amp; Education Sessions https://t.co/jAy032lL7k #constantcontact]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Djawadi_Ramin So sad that Vancouver was canceled.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jjhorgan Early Childhood Education needs to be a part of the Provincial School System (funded by tax payors) and educators need the training to reflect that.  Children deserve quality care and society needs to fund it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cbcnewsbc: Grand Forks votes to buy out entire neighborhood after major flood https://t.co/p5jbEf5fkm https://t.co/dhfwuA3pDg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[meanwhile in Vancouver https://t.co/Ou6bDloEDY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @camanpour: I've never seen anything like this. https://t.co/OLNGcQEQMg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dearsusanbranch Vote @BetoORourke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CouncilofCDNs: “The peoples of #FirstNations need and deserve clean #water. Please act now!” says student Mona to @JustinTrudeau. Mona…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ManInTheHoody: zina bash....sitting normal....checks phone...reads something...sitting not normal https://t.co/RdEdIK3QKG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ItsMeCathi: Hey Twitter, 

Trump has a HILARIOUS survey about the media. He doesn't want word to get out to non-supporters because it w…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CNN #FreeLeonardPeltier]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>