<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[More on the importance of the #CleanPowerPlan and its day in court. "The big kahuna." - @ddonigernrdc https://t.co/yoqfgUff8y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Josh is tweeting up a storm--you'd have to, in order to capture the breadth and depth of support for the #CleanPowerPlan https://t.co/laQ6Th3IKV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JoshDorner: The #CleanPowerPlan heads to court today with backing of EPA admins under 4 GOP presidents. https://t.co/FOFroerysd
https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today is a big day for #climate action. What to expect at the courthouse today for the #CleanPowerPlan arguments: https://t.co/oQZ2ZROiZb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC: If global warming trends continue, lobsters will struggle to survive by the year 2100, acc. to new study. https://t.co/iKzOnqlH5X…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump spends final moments of debate criticizing Clinton's "not nice" ads when they are mostly just clips of him talking. And scene.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @politifactlive: Donald Trump says "wrong" when Hillary Clinton says he supported the Iraq War. But he did so publicly, https://t.co/1JH…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Sifill_LDF: Well hearing a presidential candidate name "systemic racism in our criminal justice system" may be historic. #debatenight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Talk about your low, low bars. https://t.co/LSGccC8RmL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I did not say that." What, this? https://t.co/kY7uFxW05A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC_AF: "Some country is going to be the clean energy superpower of the 20th century" -@HillaryClinton #debatenight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Online because of debate nerves? You could spend the energy reading endless spin, or you could sign up to volunteer. https://t.co/m4EZEqtQiO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The debate is supposed to be a serious job interview, not, well, The Apprentice. https://t.co/P4piosK2Ia #debatenight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lester Holt: 100,000+ nationwide want YOU to ask Clinton/Trump how they'll #ActOnClimate at tonight's debate.  https://t.co/QMMN2Cr9qB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC: To protect our oceans, we must stop Big Oil from expanding offshore drilling. Take action: https://t.co/HNU8Uu868t https://t.co/A…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay. What's next? https://t.co/ooHOsaK9y2 https://t.co/sbO42Yj2yi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Powerful words from @POTUS with the move for the new Atlantic protections. https://t.co/M8XSagCcHT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC: WATCH LIVE NOW: @POTUS speaks about the new Northeast Canyons and Seamounts Marine National Monument. https://t.co/rZEX2lVnHd #Ou…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["As King Canute could not hold back the tide, King Coal cannot hold back rising seas--or the clean energy transition." - @ddonigernrdc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First marine monument in the Atlantic - congratulations to all who have worked so long! https://t.co/vIbLb6nrfE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RheaSuh: Excited to be on @MSNBC's  @amjoyshow w/  @JoyAnnReid. We're talking Trump's cabinet and threats to our climate &amp; environment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CoryBooker: Outrageous that Trump is dismissing this. Russians trying to affect outcome of US elections is threat to us all that must b…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chrislhayes: .@seanspicer on Russian hacking of DNC/Podesta: "this wouldn't have happened Hillary Clinton didn't have a secret server"…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need some good news? CA now moving forward the country's 1) first computer efficiency standards 2) biggest ever set of car charging stations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excited to go see new Star Wars film about underdogs facing their newly dominant enemy to stop planet destroying technologies. #ActonClimate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AaronCouch To put it in terms you can understand, that's like saying Romulans and Vulcans seem the same.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC: NRDC’s @bfinamore explores China's leading role in curbing climate change on the season finale of @YEARSofLIVING. https://t.co/TR…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This would be insane, and at this point in absudist nominations news, almost unsurprising. https://t.co/btoLX6U8kS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KamalaHarris: An EPA head that denies climate change is like a NASA Administrator who doesn’t believe in gravity. Dangerous and alarmin…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC: Donald Trump announced today ExxonMobil CEO Rex Tillerson as his pick to become Secretary of State. https://t.co/5jDnrokj1N via @…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's it called again? You know, the critically important government agency I run/want to destroy.  https://t.co/82mFO9m5Z8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 more projects poised to move forward and costs are plummeting. If our health and the environment weren't enough, It's just good business. https://t.co/whJtNrOH6D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheDarkNolan nice, I'd give it an Adam West feature film]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Conathan: Hey, @realDonaldTrump, #Maine lobstermen know that #climatechange is real &amp; putting their jobs at risk. https://t.co/12kFD0w4…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PaulBlu: ExxonMobil has a $300b drilling deal with Russian firm Rosneft in the Arctic. Has been on hold due to sanctions. https://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hard to imagine a worse nominee to lead State than the leader of a climate-wrecking industry and friend of Putin. https://t.co/74mndl278e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @bruneski: Trump can’t wait to sell out his base https://t.co/joDKRKTIpm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A simple visualization of how the Trump administration could impact our targets for the Paris climate agreement: https://t.co/iLjUOye13K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["This is an aggressively bad choice." That about sums it up. https://t.co/7elxFayAwy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RheaSuh: ... That’s the litmus test. By naming Pruitt, President-elect Trump has flunked. https://t.co/bcNzY7ixJi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SenMarkey: .@AGScottPruitt has tried to undermine the #CleanWaterRule &amp; Clean Air Act —the public health of millions of Americans is at…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @brianschatz: Nominating a climate denier to run the Environmental Protection Agency is offensive. I will do everything I can to stop th…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are confusing "stifling legitimate debate" with pointing out blatant, harmful falsehoods and not standing for their use in journalism. https://t.co/8ZoLvWCrXc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @weatherchannel: Note to @BreitbartNews: Earth Is Not Cooling, Climate Change Is Real and Stop Using Our Video to Mislead Americans http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @bkeefee2: If Google can do it, so can other corporations: https://t.co/4c5aalhTGf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations to the indigenous peoples who wouldn't give up and the activists who supported them like @EthanNuss! https://t.co/TIcv3HBycm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RheaSuh: Today, the voices of an indigenous people were heard. #NoDAPL https://t.co/OO7jbvw52B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC: BREAKING: The Obama administration announces it will not open Arctic or Atlantic Ocean to drilling in its 5-year offshore leasing…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's consider whether someone should run the Energy Department they both 1) want to disband and 2) can't remember. https://t.co/v54zcU3xjx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC: Thank you @POTUS for keeping Big Oil companies out of the Arctic and Atlantic for the next five years. Now, please ban them forev…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“No one should doubt the overwhelming majority... who are determined to keep our commitments" says Kerry re: Paris
https://t.co/xP15SQazPn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Trump can recognize a biz opportunity or cares about 2.5M U.S. jobs, he won't back out of the Paris Agreement. https://t.co/Kc3vrdLyDg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We have to tell Donald Trump and everyone else, we are not going silently into the night" @BernieSanders #NoDAPL #riffingonbillpullman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now hearing from Sen. @BernieSanders: "Our job now is to break our dependence on fossil fuels." #NoDAPL https://t.co/g0kLfbpJTH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We are protecting the Sacred" for our children, say leaders from Standing Rock. #NoDAPL https://t.co/V39zGm4NN1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I ran into a few friends walking past the White House. #NODAPL https://t.co/32vSw6COGb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kansans can tell you Kobach would be a disastrous choice for voting rights, racial discrimination and immigration issues. https://t.co/38rZz2byhO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excited to see 10 new cities join my hometown KC and others in the City Energy Project! https://t.co/SAS2qrthIi #ActOnClimate @NRDC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SenWarren: Steve Bannon promoted white nationalism, @realDonaldTrump. He's been praised by KKK supporters &amp; denounced by @splcenter &amp; @…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be at the DC rally tomorrow in solidarity w/ Standing Rock. Who else will be? #NODAPL https://t.co/imtFBvdgcu  https://t.co/dUY8JE6RGG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GeorgeTakei: These are some Breitbart headlines. Their white nationalist CEO is now Trump's top White House strategist. Pay attention.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kate_sheppard: The national gaslighting is well underway. https://t.co/sWHxD4jQqJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Green_Footballs: This video is the real thing, folks. Anti-Trump protest march today in downtown LA. Please circulate! https://t.co/Pnd…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kylegriffin1: Scathing statement from Harry Reid's spox after Kellyanne Conway suggested legal action against Reid for criticizing Trum…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LastWeekTonight: If you don’t believe man-made global warming is a a silly issue, give to the Natural Resources Defense Council (https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you can afford the time or money, support organizations" like @NRDC. https://t.co/YWfiZ1mVCS @LastWeekTonight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you don't believe manmade global warming is "silly" issue, donate to the NRDC." Thanks @iamjohnoliver! https://t.co/RbrEcBV0qV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sierraclub: "Why we need you now more than ever" - @maryannehitt's post-election inspiration: https://t.co/qhkQKOqHVM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SenatorReid: Winning the electoral college does not absolve Trump of the grave sins he committed against millions of Americans.  https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HillaryClinton: "To all the little girls watching...never doubt that you are valuable and powerful &amp; deserving of every chance &amp; opport…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Understandable pessimism if Trump follows rhetoric. But let's get into the important questions about how we make sure he doesn't, or can't. https://t.co/HIFXEDwigF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Sulliview: A call to action for journalists covering President Trump. My (second) column: https://t.co/L6hIC0HBsy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many Americans voted for Trump. But the vast majority of Americans support environmental protections. #actonclimate  https://t.co/jlLIcLjtWT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC_AF: “If Donald Trump thinks he can launch a big polluter assault, we’ll build a wall of opposition to stop him.” —@NRDC_AF Preside…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @THR: CNN Van Jones: "This was a white lash" #ElectionNight https://t.co/XKgMX3Hm2q https://t.co/M1iiYeY0CL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @paulkrugman: Also: the media harping on emails, which was, as Matt Yglesias says, a bullshit issue from the start, may have killed the…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JamesFallows: I am thinking of Comey now, and of the editors who gave him saturation coverage ten days ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeffvandermeer don't go all piano keys on me, please.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aaanastasia @patricey @kansasalps feel better, Anastasia and also America!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @brianschatz: Congratulations to my friend Tammy Duckworth, a person who shows tremendous courage and clarity. She will be a great Senat…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TomSteyer: This election isn't just about the next 4 years. It's about the next hundred. https://t.co/KwRXfTaPbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @adambduffy: #EckingtonDC long lines in the provisional ballot line. Bring Id and some utility bills just in case.  Otherwise get your v…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let them eat cake. https://t.co/sUh333h4ax]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is wonderful: https://t.co/oY5wBa25Pd

And reminds me of this poem from '08. https://t.co/RPlOI889ul https://t.co/wyTK6jWBSn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All kinds of uncertain, but I'm going with 322 for her and a split Senate. https://t.co/MWddVpianX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh hey there America. #imwithher #sheswithher  #earlyvoting @ One Judiciary Square https://t.co/zv5IfgpcCc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jschmidtnrdc: .@CaseyLefkowitz speaking at the #NoKXL &amp; #NoKXL rally in front of the WH https://t.co/06QUBWq4JB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More than 870,000 messages were delivered at today's @EPWDems hearing to reject #pollutingPruitt. Get this fox away from our hen house.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDCTrumpWatch: Trump issues "gag order" silencing federal agencies. No new press releases, social media, blogs, web content etc. https…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting the answers #PollutingPruitt couldn't or wouldn't provide. @JWalkeNRDC testifying before @EPWDems here: https://t.co/c7MbUsNefT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC: BREAKING: President Trump has signed executive orders clearing way for Dakota Access &amp; Keystone XL to move forward. https://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @petealtman13: .@realDonaldTrump @potus, enviros don't appoint polluter apologist science deniers who block air and water pollution stan…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pkcapitol: Trump went almost 2 whole months without mentioning "illegal votes". Then came his 1st congressional l'ship huddle.
https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@washingtonpost @petulad one intention may be to highlight that men can/should be feminist allies, but most of these quotes don't get there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They did edit the headline, but just delete the tweet too. Also, delete the article and write about the women. This is a seriously hot take. https://t.co/NfFU7vDLqW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Variety: White House shuts down phone comment line, tells callers to use non-existent Facebook Messenger account instead https://t.co/6…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right now, the Foreign Relations Committee is deciding whether to hand the State Dept over to recent CEO of Exxon-Mobil Rex Tillerson. https://t.co/ZHEEJPOlhq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Gizmodo: 2016's new temperature record proves climate change is moving disturbingly fast https://t.co/cyrqEp2pCG https://t.co/QzrxxTkqNh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perhaps they're calling back to "a more civilized age."  @AaronCouch #TheLastJedi #EpisodeVIII https://t.co/ncvax8OsIW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Agent350: Here’s Florida under Tillerson’s climate policy. @marcorubio is a sell-out on a planetary scale. #ExxonKnew https://t.co/jeX7…]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>