<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[UK could go it alone on digital services tax: finance minister: Britain will unilaterally implement a digital service tax if there is no international agreement soon on how to tax big internet companies, finance minister Philip Hammond said on Monday,… https://t.co/YpvJ02louR https://t.co/gLswpNhMFo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instagram names Adam Mosseri as new head: Facebook Inc's Instagram on Monday announced that Adam Mosseri, the current vice president of product, will take over as the new head of the photo-sharing app. https://t.co/WeuigQNlNx https://t.co/AzW0g2KvnY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla shares jump on Model 3 numbers, Musk deal: Shares of Tesla Inc jumped 18 percent on Monday as signs it had met targets for quarterly car production added to relief at Chief Executive Elon Musk's settling of a lawsuit with regulators that had… https://t.co/KyuQcc9c2E https://t.co/UfiEkN6EwA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Groupon to pay IBM $57 million to settle U.S. patent dispute: Online marketplace Groupon Inc on Monday said it would pay $57 million to International Business Machines Corp to settle an intellectual property dispute. https://t.co/FdYVWjKiUd https://t.co/slpZAOY2kT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[easyJet founder sues Netflix over 'Easy': Two seasons in, UK budget airline magnate Stelios Haji-Ioannou is suing Netflix over the title of its Chicago-based show "Easy", arguing it infringes on more than a thousand trademarks he has registered using the… https://t.co/L8xAaVITB4 https://t.co/Qm7kXdbVP3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla shares jump on Model 3 numbers, Musk settlement: Shares of Tesla Inc jumped 18 percent on Monday as signs it had met targets for quarterly production numbers added to relief at Chief Executive Elon Musk's settling a lawsuit with regulators that… https://t.co/m0A08t5BXR https://t.co/QzrUf0MEY7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Quality Assurance Engineer: Job ID : 73078BR_2 Location : US – Connecticut – Branford,US – Pennsylvania – Philadelphia, UK – Altrincham : Job Description Job Description Position Summary: The Senior Software Quality Assurance Engineer is… https://t.co/5TPnqfu3j5 https://t.co/HyMFNyZMZm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-Apple engineers show their startup's self-driving car sensor: Two former Apple Inc engineers on Monday gave new details about the sensor system their startup company, Aeva Inc, is making to help self-driving cars see the world around them. https://t.co/qlhDP3SF8k https://t.co/cIwvv48tJM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Netflix to let viewers pick how TV episodes and movies will end: Bloomberg: Streaming giant Netflix Inc will now allow users to choose how a TV episode or movie will end as it pushes further into Interactive TV, Bloomberg reported on Monday. https://t.co/7xcEEoWNOk https://t.co/KnX6FUvHmS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla shares jump after Musk settles with SEC: Shares of Tesla Inc jumped nearly 16 percent on Monday after Chief Executive Elon Musk settled with the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) over charges of misleading investors, heading off moves… https://t.co/QmVrs4OcS5 https://t.co/psYY2rcZoU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electric cars cast growing shadow on profits: Electric cars are poised to arrive en masse in European showrooms after years of hyped concept-car launches and billions in investment by automakers and suppliers. https://t.co/7UnvqZqgvn https://t.co/XcZPsD3t33]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK could go it alone on digital services tax: finance minister says: Britain will unilaterally implement a digital service tax if there is no wider international agreement soon on how to tax the world's biggest Internet companies, finance minister Philip… https://t.co/KyPt4e1ean https://t.co/mqCnZU7b2a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EU regulators receive second Google report on shopping case: Google has provided a second report detailing the effects of its proposal to allow more price comparison rivals to bid for ads on top of its search page, EU antitrust regulators said on Monday. https://t.co/HdfnkwYiPH https://t.co/v3FS1cpHBX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Risk Data Analyst: The Finance division is home to crew and leaders who drive sustainable value across the global enterprise. Our high caliber professionals serve as trusted and influential strategic partners to business leaders across the organization… https://t.co/6TZl3pK89P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fast and serious: Vietnam's first domestic car manufacturer bets big: At a time when auto companies in the developed world are facing a squeeze on their profits from cash-rich tech firms, Vietnam is betting car-making can be a ticket t o a more… https://t.co/SxCyd8ZBMW https://t.co/CFtEThlELH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[German antitrust watchdog eyes steps against Facebook this year: The head of Germany's antitrust watchdog said on Monday he was "very optimistic" that his office would take action against Facebook this year after finding it had abused its market… https://t.co/lx0t1WobC2 https://t.co/CdXQpuGfEM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Germany's Hubject enters cooperation with Star Charge China: Germany's Hubject, which is developing a method to map and pay at electric charging stations, has entered a cooperation agreement with Star Charge China, it said on Monday. https://t.co/Sw77HzB4K1 https://t.co/kSCoTh24El]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Account Manager Technology Health: Requisition ID 2018-61843 Category Information Technology Employment Type Regular – Full Time (4) Travel Requirements 50-60% Position Code 8142 Position Description The IT Account Manager will provide account and… https://t.co/rKA0BLkFlp https://t.co/rQbhZO7CuN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mideast ride-hailing app Careem resumes Oman services: Careem has resumed services in Muscat, Oman after signing an agreement to partner with a local taxi company, the Middle East ride-hailing app company said on Monday. https://t.co/54sjXkVshF https://t.co/JVCVamfCER]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. sues after California governor signs 'net neutrality' law: The U.S. Justice Department said late on Sunday it filed suit after California Governor Jerry Brown signed legislation to restore open internet protections known as net neutrality in the… https://t.co/sXxWVQUsxu https://t.co/JqQ8hxFEFt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump administration plans to sue California over net neutrality law: Washington Post: The Trump administration plans to sue California over the new net neutrality law the state enacted on Sunday, according to an article in the Washington Post. https://t.co/iUafy5Ra2s https://t.co/Di9UQO2SrJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[California governor signs state law to reinstate 'net neutrality': California Governor Jerry Brown late on Sunday signed legislation to restore open internet protections known as net neutrality in the state after the Trump administration repealed the… https://t.co/ULmlngPnpC https://t.co/LuRW5HdJX9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SEC’s focus on U.S. corporate bosses pays off with Musk settlement: A high-profile settlement with Tesla Inc Chief Executive Elon Musk exemplifies a recent push by the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission to go after executives and not just their… https://t.co/3hOe0KGmCg https://t.co/ZxfitnfYFx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla's SEC deal provides ammunition for U.S. probe, investor lawsuits: Tesla Inc's settlement with U.S. regulators will help soothe investors calling for more oversight of Chief Executive Elon Musk, experts said, even as it gives ammunition to… https://t.co/Gzu92SQ67F https://t.co/tnK2Lw2CKG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Analyst: Business Systems Analyst Ref No.: 18-39801 Location: Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania Role: Business Systems Analyst Location: Pittsburgh, PA Duration: 12 Months Contract Face to Face Interview Skills Required Strong exp. with Business… https://t.co/fmQnNXm2pP https://t.co/4FYPfq8rEg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer/Software Engineer: Translates and develops requirements into workable software solutions. Maintains and develops programs for use in business and IT automation. Incorporates various accepted methodologies to design software and… https://t.co/e4l344e3ur]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Security Presales Solutions Architect: Apply on Company Website Cyber Security Presales Solutions Architect Unisys Malvern, PA Apply on Company Website Posted 1 hour ago Cyber Security PreSales Architect – Stealth Location: Baltimore, MD (as needed… https://t.co/YpvMsF4Weh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tencent announces a restructuring as challenges rise: Chinese internet giant Tencent Holdings announced on Sunday its first restructuring in six years, as it faces increased challenges from tighter government regulations. https://t.co/BarDxYATMD https://t.co/3Ss9rQmAjJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project manager: Project manager Ref No.: 18-39684 Location: Philadelphia, Pennsylvania Start Date: 07/16/2018 Job title : Project manager Duration Long term Location Philadelphia PA Job Description: Needs to be Technical PM with 10+ years exp,… https://t.co/0Seqiq84D9 https://t.co/c3ICbepeQx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Network Engineer: Data Network Engineer | Pencor Services, Inc.Skip to main content – Companies – History – News &amp; Events – Search Careers – Contact Data Network Engineer Company: Blue Ridge Communications Department: NOC Location: Palmerton,… https://t.co/BOrapPi6vh https://t.co/Io6J1dapB7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer: General Dynamics Information Technology (GDIT) has an immediate need for a .NET Developer to analyze, evaluate and develop new and existing web/database applications; working under limited supervision; performing additional duties as… https://t.co/qdPZ6mEPvb https://t.co/bkuiSyjS2D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SEC chairman says Tesla settlement in 'best interests' of shareholders: U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission chairman Jay Clayton said in a statement on Saturday that the agency's settlement with carmaker Tesla was in the best interests of the U.S.… https://t.co/a5kyofJMo2 https://t.co/mR6EU0a8RH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Musk to resign as Tesla chairman, remain as CEO in SEC settlement: Tesla and Elon Musk have agreed to pay $20 million each to financial regulators and the billionaire will step down as the company's chairman but remain as chief executive, under a… https://t.co/Il53mxnHuK https://t.co/Llm9vepDlU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Director, Oracle Cloud Migration – IT Business Info Systems – Full Time: Regular/Temporary Regular Guthrie Entity The Guthrie Clinic Shift Day 40 hours a week Pay Grade TGC A21 FLSA Status Exempt Main Function The Guthrie Clinic is an integrated… https://t.co/4Ei5Rh93hV https://t.co/5CA80hWnpx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Engineer in Test Exton, PA: Guidewire’s development team is looking for a smart, proactive, and results-oriented SDET (Software Development Engineer in Test) to test elegant solutions for the property &amp; casualty insurance industry’s… https://t.co/qN8eTPjU7t https://t.co/odq9KRNjya]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/hyVEKumQGu with Azure cloud: ******* with Azure cloud Ref No.:18-16711 Location: Chesterbrook, Pennsylvania Position Type:Contract Start Date: 09/14/2018 Job Title: ******* with Azure cloud Location: Chesterbrook, PA Duration: Longterm… https://t.co/ufWXEmv6M3 https://t.co/PUcFsoRN3T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Software Developer: Financial Software Developer Job no: COG-****** Work type: Full time Location: Philadelphia Group: Corporate Operations Group Division: Technology Recruiter: Andrew Baker As a Financial Software Developer, you will be key in… https://t.co/7C4YzUvtd2 https://t.co/IEHdM0ym8f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Developer JavaScript, Angular, Kafka, SQL: Job Description Principal Java Developer – JavaScript, Angular, Kafka, SQL The Principal Developer position in the AST Performance, Monitoring &amp; Availability Engineering Team will be responsible for… https://t.co/aBiFKjvvzB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South Korea's LG Display to cut jobs through voluntary retirement: South Korea's LG Display Co Ltd, an Apple supplier, will cut jobs through voluntary retirement for the first time since its founding, a spokeswoman confirmed on Saturday. https://t.co/n568FP6rPR https://t.co/og13kDF4d2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guest Service Desk Team Member: Guest Service Desk Team Member Description: As a Guest Service team member, you are the front end and the face of what we stand for. You’ll be motivated by and always look for opportunities to go above and beyond guest… https://t.co/j59NkBbJWx https://t.co/TiBCUKktbG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle's Kurian to step down as president of product development: Business software maker Oracle Corp said on Friday Thomas Kurian, its president of product development would be stepping down, effective immediately. https://t.co/ik0Fm1PC7j https://t.co/Lb3xHSoJ2f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump administration looks to speed 5G networks, ease hurdles: The Trump administration said on Friday it is seeking to remove hurdles to faster deployment of the next generation of wireless communications, known as 5G, which it touted as revolutionary… https://t.co/v3orRHBDNI https://t.co/4oiO5A7dGL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Airbnb says not property agent, French hoteliers say nonsense: Online rental marketplace Airbnb rejected on Friday a contention by a leading French hoteliers' association that it is a real estate agent and should be subjected to property rules in a case… https://t.co/uMRDy5bHKc https://t.co/j1HV62NyzG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK regulator to enquire if Facebook data breach has affected UK citizens: The UK's Information Commissioner's Office said on Friday it will make enquiries with Facebook Inc and other overseas regulators to find out if British citizens were affected by a… https://t.co/AGm8QgcJo8 https://t.co/RbzDm7RJB9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla's Musk could settle SEC suit but ready for fight: sources: Tesla Inc's Elon Musk could settle with U.S. regulators who have sued to remove him from the electric carmaker's leadership, but he is prepared to fight the securities fraud lawsuit against… https://t.co/JLLhpMovRQ https://t.co/Po8Pfj0ebX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla's Musk could settle SEC suit but ready for fight -sources: Tesla Inc's Elon Musk could settle with U.S. regulators who have sued to remove him from the electric carmaker's leadership, but he is prepared to fight the securities fraud lawsuit against… https://t.co/ZlVGBNQ9kP https://t.co/pOPYGc69DD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook discloses security breach affecting 50 million users: Facebook Inc said on Friday that hackers stole digital login codes allowing them to take over up to 50 million user accounts, after what has already been a difficult year for the company's… https://t.co/RQG25WWxbZ https://t.co/uiuzREmpKu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exclusive: In test case, U.S. fails to force Facebook to wiretap Messenger calls - sources: U.S. investigators failed in a recent courtroom effort to force Facebook to wiretap voice calls over its Messenger app in a closely watched test case, according… https://t.co/Z9WvNegHfW https://t.co/jMH9jKj6kN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. trade judge declines to block iPhone imports: A U.S. trade judge on Friday declined to block the importation of Apple Inc iPhones with chips from Intel Corp , handing a major defeat to Qualcomm Inc in its high-stakes legal dispute with the iPhone… https://t.co/2fpwCxC1uo https://t.co/JyPPqJ8HAv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EU regulators want to know if merchants hurt by Amazon copies: EU antitrust regulators are asking retailers and manufacturers whether Amazon's sales of own brand products similar to theirs have harmed their business, a move which could lead to a formal… https://t.co/HCE4mYZZH8 https://t.co/cNDkQutorb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla shares sink on SEC lawsuit; sources say Musk could settle: Shares of Tesla Inc plunged 13 percent on Friday after U.S. securities regulators accused Elon Musk of fraud and sued to have him banned from the leadership of the electric carmaker,… https://t.co/mPccFAFMzD https://t.co/G6NtRv7nnH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple wins reversal in University of Wisconsin patent lawsuit: Apple Inc persuaded a federal appeals court on Friday to throw out a $234 million damages award in favor of the University of Wisconsin-Madison's patent licensing arm for infringing a patent… https://t.co/7jix1nbAkU https://t.co/mikPqkhuqz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intel says has adequate chips to meet targets amid supply crunch: Chipmaker Intel Corp said on Friday it had enough supplies to meet annual revenue targets and was boosting PC chip output, allaying fears that rival Advanced Micro Devices Inc was eating… https://t.co/m4zcoBMiL9 https://t.co/o2vDRnKZDE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cost to insure Tesla debt spikes to record high: The cost to insure debt holdings in electric carmaker Tesla Inc rose to its highest-ever level on Friday as the bond market reflected growing worries about a default, following the news that Chief… https://t.co/Voknhps7sC https://t.co/QpSq7376hm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Systems Analyst: EQT Corp. – Lead Systems Analyst Job in Pittsburgh, PA Toggle navigation – Who We Are – What We Do – Life at EQT – Campus Recruiting – Careers Home – &gt; Lead Systems Analyst Job in Pittsburgh, PA Lead Systems Analyst City: Pittsburgh… https://t.co/3qvOD0GIGe https://t.co/CDA8VkcWVI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook unearths security breach affecting 50 million users: Facebook Inc has discovered a security flaw affecting about 50 million user accounts which could have allowed attackers to take over those accounts, the social networking company said on Friday. https://t.co/lyiSmVUcBy https://t.co/PpJsiSQENv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google CEO will testify before U.S. House on bias accusations: Google Chief Executive Sundar Pichai has agreed to testify before the U.S. House Judiciary Committee later this year over Republican concerns that the company is biased against conservatives,… https://t.co/Je2D90bN6X https://t.co/Dzmamt7Gku]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook unearths security flaw affecting 50 million users: Facebook Inc has discovered a security flaw affecting about 50 million user accounts which could have allowed attackers to take over the accounts, the social networking company said on Friday. https://t.co/As4gVV3Eff https://t.co/AxgJEUdGIf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cost to insure Tesla debt reaches highest price ever: The cost to insure debt holdings in electric carmaker Tesla Inc , whose chief executive has been accused of fraud by federal regulators, rose to its highest-ever level on Friday as the bond market… https://t.co/KfTDqfdWfJ https://t.co/UqPhSh79sh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intel says focusing on PC chips; to meet revenue targets: Intel Corp is prioritizing the production of chips used in personal computers and has enough supplies required to meet its full-year revenue targets, the world's second-biggest chipmaker said on… https://t.co/LpUNQFTuSl https://t.co/8WJiuYLgQp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fears about Musk's future sink Tesla shares: Shares of Tesla Inc plunged up to 13 percent on Friday as investors worried about the future of Chairman and Chief Executive Elon Musk at the electric carmaker after U.S. securities regulators accused him of… https://t.co/FGIH7j9465 https://t.co/mO9D7RbytQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google CEO will testify before U.S. House panel in November: Google Chief Executive Sundar Pichai has agreed to testify before the U.S. House Judiciary Committee in November, a senior Republican said Friday. https://t.co/qgL3r7AKZZ https://t.co/OZ2s1n1aMT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intel says has enough PC chip supply to meet revenue targets: Intel Corp has enough supplies of semiconductors required to meet its full-year revenue targets and is prioritizing the production of chips used in personal computers, the chipmaker said on… https://t.co/gnXivzO5D5 https://t.co/m7chJy6DUC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla five-year credit default swap hits highest price ever: Tesla's 5-year credit default swap hit its highest price ever on Friday, the morning after it was announced that the Securities and Exchange Commission was suing the company's Chief Executive… https://t.co/n1imsZXBst https://t.co/PdGsHlEqOD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spain gives Uber and Cabify drivers four years to secure licenses: Spain on Friday gave drivers of Uber and Cabify four years to comply with new licensing regulations issued by its autonomous regions and cities, defying protests by drivers for the… https://t.co/xW6Pte9WSH https://t.co/0xq6y2XNbp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Volkswagen partners with Microsoft in cloud push: German automaker Volkswagen AG will use Microsoft Corp's Azure cloud platform to provide all future digital services and mobility offerings across its entire fleet, the companies said on Friday. https://t.co/GuopZAbPD8 https://t.co/tCNKhGAZ5E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Musk would not give up chairman role to settle SEC lawsuit: CNBC: Tesla Inc Chief Executive Officer Elon Musk refused to pay a nominal fine and give up the role of chairman for two years as part of a settlement with the U.S. Securities and Exchange… https://t.co/qgUem88Aft https://t.co/uhqVji0sp3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Slack preparing to go public in early 2019: WSJ: Slack Technologies Inc, a provider of chat services for businesses, is preparing for an initial public offering in the first half of 2019, the Wall Street Journal reported on Friday, citing people familiar… https://t.co/BSQvHZwSmg https://t.co/kzQBYVCh7z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Systems Architect: Department Development – US Employment Type Employee Minimum Experience Experienced System Architect IMPORTANT INFORMATION ABOUT THIS POSITION All applicants must be legally authorized to work in the United States. Visa sponsorship… https://t.co/09Bce9E3Wf https://t.co/dRZV98SWkw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cnc Programmer/ Process Engineer: Location: Wilkes-Barre Job type: Permanent Sector: Manufacturing Category: Engineers CNC PROGRAMMER/ PROCESS ENGINEER US – PA – Wilkes-Barre Job Description * Generate CNC programs with quality design standards and… https://t.co/Na2wDIj5M8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SEC lawsuit sends Tesla shares tumbling: Shares of Tesla Inc dived 11 percent in early trading on Friday after U.S. regulators accused Chief Executive Elon Musk of fraud and sought to remove him from his role in charge of the electric car company. https://t.co/i3c9orxX5X https://t.co/sqrtCqj4fL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Workforce Planning Analyst (Specialist Business Process Analyst): TECHNOLOGY SERVICES GROUP (TSG) is the central infrastructure services group with a proven track record of innovating to help BNY Mellon and its customers have most reliable, nimble and… https://t.co/AXs3BV006q https://t.co/tPqA2CCtm4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. to counter Chinese internet bid in Papua New Guinea: diplomat: The United States is working on a counter-offer to stop Chinese telecom giant Huawei Technologies Co Ltd [HWT.UL] from building internet infrastructure in Papua New Guinea (PNG), its top… https://t.co/q0LyDN2lLk https://t.co/04r4Sc29Ta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager IT: MUST HAVE Agile experience required Ability to work in a cross functional project management environment with proven ability to drive large scale projects Ability to manage multiple stakeholders Ability to manage vendors SDLC… https://t.co/SUzLu79FMK https://t.co/DFqxKD48E1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[E.ON targets innovations for smart energy future: Germany's biggest power supplier E.ON wants smart homes to be smart business in a world of decentralized, low-carbon energy markets. https://t.co/DIdcb6zsBC https://t.co/u5ZwWFSdAu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. regulator sues Musk for fraud, seeks to remove him from Tesla: The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission accused Tesla Inc Chief Executive Elon Musk on Thursday of fraud and sought to remove him from his role in charge of the electric car company,… https://t.co/wCOvMmCU22 https://t.co/zT7NxBvjiP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Field Engineer Civil/Rail: Job Ref: ****** Employer: Bechtel Address: Post Date: 28/08/2018 18:01 Requisition ID: Project Overview: The Pennsylvania Chemicals Project is a world scale petrochemicals facility to be constructed in Monaca, Pennsylvania, USA… https://t.co/WMXROZ3UUF https://t.co/kSbQIh4tBJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automation Engineer II/III/IV: EQT Corp. – Automation Engineer II/III/IV Job in Canonsburg, PA Toggle navigation – Who We Are – What We Do – Life at EQT – Campus Recruiting – Careers Home – &gt; Automation Engineer II/III/IV Job in Canonsburg, PA Automation… https://t.co/xw4fMszFuN https://t.co/gtgaFqSrLF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SEC sues Musk for fraud, seek to remove him from Tesla: The top U.S. securities regulator on Thursday accused Tesla Inc Chief Executive Elon Musk of fraud and sought to remove him from his role in charge of the electric car company, saying he made a… https://t.co/pjNcYdEaEU https://t.co/nB9vd8ml23]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SEC sue Musk for fraud, seek to remove him from Tesla: U.S. securities regulators on Thursday accused Tesla Inc Chief Executive Elon Musk of fraud and sought to remove him from his role in charge of the electric car company, saying he made a series of… https://t.co/cwAaHy31CC https://t.co/iOMZlerB0P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Port of San Diego hit by ransomware attack: The Port of San Diego said on Thursday that the FBI and Department of Homeland Security were investigating a ransomware attack that disrupted the port's information technology systems. https://t.co/mlp5vU8zdY https://t.co/YsGZm4JJnK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mainframe Developer: Mainframe Developer – Brandon Consulting Associates Inc – Philadelphia, PA | ********** Loading.Server error, please try again laterSorry! It looks like you are in private browsing mode, which is not supported. Please switch your… https://t.co/mVVKSDQTqk https://t.co/ziL6WlM9iE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook reveals security incident affecting 50 million users: Facebook Inc has discovered a security issue affecting about 50 million user accounts, the company said on Friday. https://t.co/xdV9DYCnSM https://t.co/MBZq5NhLJh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SEC sue Tesla's Musk for fraud, seek to bar him as officer: U.S. securities regulators on Thursday accused Tesla Inc Chief Executive Elon Musk of fraud and sought to ban him as an officer of a public company, saying he made a series of "false and… https://t.co/IpeAXqK4NC https://t.co/ZUndU9iXWa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SEC sue Tesla's Musk for fraud, seek to bar him as director: The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission on Thursday accused Tesla Inc Chief Executive Elon Musk of fraud and sought to ban him as a director of a public company, saying he made a series of… https://t.co/4wcMTiFACK https://t.co/4FeloGgo6W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SEC sues Tesla CEO Musk, alleges fraud over tweets: The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission on Thursday sued Tesla Inc Chief Executive Elon Musk, accusing him of securities fraud for making a series of "false and misleading" tweets about potentially… https://t.co/YTejMMsoRi https://t.co/YN5qZT5Cjy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SEC alleges fraud by Tesla CEO Elon Musk: court records: The U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission filed a lawsuit on Thursday against Tesla Inc Chief Executive Elon Musk, in which it alleges securities fraud, according to online court records. https://t.co/vbyNDTOJ1l https://t.co/Rs5DerniRj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Archer Performance Engineer: Archer Performance Engineer Ref No.: 18-39431 Location: Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania Archer Performance Engineer Pittsburgh, PA Long-term Contract Job Description: Performance Testing, Client Load Runner 12.20, Client Performance… https://t.co/kGyYW4j2b5 https://t.co/APQnfs8LnU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google CEO meeting with lawmakers amid Republican criticism: Google's chief executive officer, Sundar Pichai, is on Capitol Hill this week to face questions from Republican lawmakers who accuse the company of being biased against conservatives and have… https://t.co/Zkb06de797 https://t.co/62NLDKMQHh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Volvo aims to sell electric trucks in North America by 2020: Volvo, the world's second-biggest truck maker, plans to begin selling electric trucks in North America by 2020, it said on Thursday, as it signed a partnership with California that will allow… https://t.co/RzW2sEFWsv https://t.co/bpa4ZCgU8w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Singapore's Grab in talks to sell Thai unit stake to Central Group: sources: Singapore-based ride-hailing firm Grab is in talks to sell "a decent-sized stake" in its Thai business to Thailand's largest retailer, Central Group, people with direct… https://t.co/jojgKdKPMX https://t.co/kRj7Y8j889]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber, Cabify drivers strike in Madrid to protest against planned law changes: Thousands of drivers for ride-hailing services Uber and Cabify, waving flags and chanting slogans such as "we want to work", marched down Madrid's central boulevard on Thursday… https://t.co/sPGwE1NtmG https://t.co/B9sdn73yde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Group Manager, Application Support (ITIL): Global Custody and Cash Services (GCCS) is searching for an experienced technology manager for their Production Services organization.’ The mission of Production Services is to deliver a full IT service… https://t.co/wwXYrD4rj3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TomTom plans fleet-management sale to focus on maps battle with Google: TomTom is considering selling its fleet-management business to concentrate on competing head-to-head with Google in car navigation software, it said on Thursday. https://t.co/mgPKHU0InQ https://t.co/UNg3iXnG9Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Germany's Merkel says subsidies for e-cars cannot go on forever: German Chancellor Angela Merkel said that subsidies for the purchase of electric vehicles had helped boost demand but that they could not go on forever. https://t.co/mE3Jd4e1CX https://t.co/bjhDVDUW2B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Virtual Singapore project could be test bed for planners - and plotters: With the click of a button, Singapore's security forces could soon use a digital version of the city-state to simulate a bomb threat at a sports stadium - and learn how to respond… https://t.co/AMu4EYuTTA https://t.co/0qF3DojBxG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer – Mainframe: Software Developer – Mainframe job description | Excell – blog – NewsRoom – Contact – Login – Investors – INVESTOR DASHBOARD – PRESS RELEASES – STOCK – ONLINE INVESTOR KIT – SEC FILINGS – CORPORATE GOVERNENCE – WEBCAST AND… https://t.co/LuYBZDviZk https://t.co/XVyZXGL33O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keppel, SPH offer to buy remaining stake in M1 for up to $930 million: Keppel Corp Ltd and Singapore Press Holdings Ltd (SPH) have offered to buy the remaining shares in Singaporean telecom operator M1 Ltd that they do not already own, in a deal worth up… https://t.co/XQLPM1G1uv https://t.co/kG0y2jsrRx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China's August industrial profit growth slips to five-month low: Profit growth for China's industrial firms decelerated to a five-month low in August on shrinking revenues and prices, adding to concerns about demand in the world's second-largest economy… https://t.co/vqGmApCRPL https://t.co/yqWd4tIo9K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Specialist Systems Engineer/Programmer: Specialist Systems Engineer/Programmer-&gt;&gt; Designs and develops solutions to complex application problems, system administration issues, or network concerns. Performs systems management and integration functions.… https://t.co/Vfg3uq2Lna https://t.co/LRKUHaUZBK]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>