<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool 14' Iceberg For Your Pool or the Lake! http://t.co/MDodx9OZT9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We broke something, I think it was traction --  - Carl Edwards after getting spun out by Dale Jr. at Michigan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I led the league in Go get 'em next time." - Bob Uecker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give a girl the correct footwear and she can conquer the world. - Bette Midler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winning is everything. The only ones who remember you when you come second are your wife and your dog. - Damon Hill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read a Great Profile of Bo Jackson – An Amazing Athlete  http://t.co/YoKThEOB3V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to know what a man is really like, take notice of how he acts when he loses money.  Simone Weil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If traffic gets any worse you'll need an appointment to make a left-hand turn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where there is an open mind, there will always be a frontier. - Charles F. Kettering]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smoking kills. If you killed, you've lost a very important part of your life. Brooke Shields]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many a man doesn't start living until he's married. And then he's finished.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A patient man is one who likes slow catsup.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Understanding Attention Deficit Hyperactivity Disorder (ADHD)  http://t.co/aDcLGwq62i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One way to get thin is to re-establish a purpose in life. - Cyril Connolly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sky is no longer the limit. - Richard M. Nixon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A horse gallops with his lungs, Perseveres with his heart, And wins with his character. - Tesio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Top 10 Burger Chains in the US  http://t.co/FsCesbko8A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Capture the Flag 2: Montage of Death  http://t.co/qTpyZpV8qk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The King of ‘Rhythm’ and ‘Blues’: Johnny Ace  http://t.co/HODIctqfKR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Moon is the first milestone on the road to the stars. - Arthur C. Clarke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one is too big to be kind and courteous, but many are too little]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be Prepared!  Learn About these Bartering Resources  http://t.co/D4dBmtY64I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Emmylou Harris  http://t.co/Y59B6YKHDP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Girl 1:  I spent my vacation fishing  Girl 2: Then why did you buy a new bathing suit?   Girl 1:  That was my bait]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone who lives within their means suffers from a lack of imagination. - Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Use Twitter in Business  http://t.co/orWjcndkXU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You could get rich manufacturing crutches for lame excuses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I find your lack of faith disturbing. - Darth Vader, Star Wars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caring For Your New Garage Floors  http://t.co/7GW3MAniUD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is more than a game to me, it's a religion. - Bill Klem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Create your own Ice, Chocolate, Jelly in the shape of Han Solo in Carbonite!!!  http://t.co/IVRioFVrMA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going Mountain Climbing? - Equipment Advice  http://t.co/NHigXoQRNP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the top science fiction books of all time!  http://t.co/mjgiijMK2t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am alive and well and unconcerned about the rumors of my death. But if I were dead, I would be the last to know. - Paul McCartney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Johnnie Tayor  http://t.co/aSYMNilkJH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to War  http://t.co/BleEF76t77]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Rolling Stones  http://t.co/SJvikUzNTe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is a progressive discovery of our own ignorance. - Will Durant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not lose courage in considering your own imperfections. -  Saint Francis de Sales]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stevie Wonder  http://t.co/X7I1mzmuqn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I am become Death, the destroyer of worlds - J. Robert Oppenheimer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I die, I'm leaving my body to science fiction. - Steven Wright]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We worked 80 hour weeks for 30 years to keep from having to get a real job. - Tom Lemon's comment on the rigors of being a drag racing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Management is nothing more than motivating other people. - Le Iacocca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The right people to start video blogging are those with a passion to tell a story.  Steve Garfield - Author Get Seen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I look at modeling as something I'm doing for black people in general. Naomi Campbell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fitness - If it came in a bottle, everybody would have a great body. - Cher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LinkedIn for Your Company Proves to be Effective  http://t.co/zv0GBPZ2J6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I was president of the good old U.S.A., I'd turn the churches into strip clubs and watch the whole world pray.  Kid Rock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes are the quickest way for women to achieve instant metamorphosis - Manolo Blahnik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sports do not build character. They reveal it. - Heywood Broun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man's health can be judged by which he takes two at a time - pills or stairs. - Joan Welsh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can never be overdressed or overeducated. --&gt; Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be not afraid of growing slowly, be afraid only of standing still. - Chinese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I went to college for four years. - Kim Kardashian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Tools for Finding Good Keywords  http://t.co/jkf25bneOk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Beverly Hillbillies is an American sitcom classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/T5eck9Ewgg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In youth we learn in age, we understand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome burgers &amp; beer t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the burgers &amp; beer lovers in your life!  http://t.co/coxEilnGDO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The average dog is a nicer person than the average person. - Andrew A. Rooney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would not invest in any shoe that is too trendy. - Rachel Roy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Very Unusual Hamburgers  http://t.co/PreZm8LdK2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wal-mart --  do they like make walls there?  Paris Hilton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Men who talk like big wheels usually are mere spokesmen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 3 - My Visit With Dr. McFadzean  http://t.co/zTLTW3a3GQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Industry is the soul of business and the keystone of prosperity. -Charles Dickens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About BMX Biking Born from Freestyle Motocross  http://t.co/ZPcGnurFkR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Petula Clark  http://t.co/eab3pn0o5t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trying to sneak a pitch past Hank Aaron is like trying to sneak a sunrise past a rooster. - Curt Simmons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting fired is nature's way of telling you that you had the wrong job in the first place. - Hal Lancaster]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A wife doesn't mind seeing a man make a fool out of himself as long as some other woman isn't helping him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science fiction writers foresee the inevitable, and although problems and catastrophes may be inevitable, solutions are not. - Isaac Asimov]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Lynyrd Skynyrd  http://t.co/Zpdbgs9P2V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Shelley Fabares  http://t.co/ks5mAylemg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Choosing To Use Solar Power  http://t.co/9UYHGKJdOz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Big-Dog Pet Fountain - Keeps Fresh and Tasty Water for Your Big Dog! http://t.co/6mJKyZ4iei]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All our dreams can come true -- if we have the courage to pursue them. - Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helpful Hints for Web Building from the Experts  http://t.co/btesEoUsql]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In science fiction, you can also test out your own realities. - Theodore Sturgeon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read about the interesting history of Garland Texas - http://t.co/NfyZ5QMgSR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft: "You've got questions. We've got dancing paperclips."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give a girl the right shoes, and she can conquer the world. - Marilyn Monroe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peter Townshend shows us it's all right to grow up. There is dignity after rock'n'roll. - Sting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did You Know this About Blackbeard in Pirates of the Caribbean 4  http://t.co/OzB1tIiJOU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Top 10 Burger Chains in the US  http://t.co/FsCesbko8A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read The Story of the Dramatics Classic Rock Group http://t.co/HGCRVxuZMs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Cool Pixie Espresso Maker - Compact and Cute! http://t.co/CSLeOojlur]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jin Kwon: Good... to see... you. Sawyer: Well look at that! Somebody's hooked on phonics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of a sudden, you're like the Bin Laden of America. Osama Bin Laden is the only one who knows exactly what I'm going through.  R. Kelly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A horse gallops with his lungs, Perseveres with his heart, And wins with his character. - Tesio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The worst examples of snap judgment are usually found in the old family album]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make Money by Tweeting, Blogging and Photo Sharing with Izea  http://t.co/pSYw8EN2m3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Libby: How'd you get shot, anyway? Sawyer: With a gun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Son, a father told his growing boy, "just remember on thing:  I know a lot more about being young than you do about being old."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So what is Bitcoin and the Bitcoin block chain exactly? http://t.co/J9yy4rigw3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to know how your girl will treat you after you married her,  just listen to her talking to her little brother.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Hire a Strategy Consulting Firm?  http://t.co/s2UrGBKcoW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good-bye, Broadcast.  Hello, Conversation.  Shel Israel - Co-Author Naked Conversations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After the third flip, I lost control - Don Roberts after crashing in the Jade Grenade at New England Dragway in 1975.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Billy Joel  http://t.co/I5yaxFHoau]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>