<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GorgeouslyFlawd: When your friend doin the most cause niggas around but that's your friend so you mind ya business  https://t.co/BKpUeH…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ChampagneMalc: Listen to your shorty. They be knowing. https://t.co/0y8LPQ2ynT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @thisjenlewis: When you're in a fight and they make a good point https://t.co/Lt7QdSrQi5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MikeChosen1: When you got a girl who doesn't play that 😂 https://t.co/XnbbZubwAU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chrissyteigen: John when you tell him he looks like Arthur https://t.co/0NW3NDtAb1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @_SpecialKayyy: #HurtBae: How many times did you cheat on me?
Him: I wasn't counting
His Memory: https://t.co/pNNAzkghwk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DMV_Drummerboyy: "Baseline" LMAOOOO yall im crying way too hard rn https://t.co/1QsYoQr7Ao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MinaLioness: How many times did you cheat on me? 

I wasn't counting? 

 https://t.co/7j5peGgGoa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BrandonEvrs: It's really disturbing how men indiscriminately hurt women, feel zero remorse, and then blame women for their own actions.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DOES ANYONE HAVE HEART SHAPED COOKE CUTTERS THAT I CAN BORROW RN LOL PLEASEEE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @40oz_VAN: Unreachable girls excite me, the ones that don't fuck with just anyone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WORLDSTARVlNE: CHANCE THE RAPPER IS ME AS A PARENT 😂😂 https://t.co/tqOpq7lzMY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are all my friends dead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When everything fits perfectly everywhere except your waist...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @iamBrILLYant: darling,

it's not your job to teach people how to appreciate you. it's not your job to show them how to love you in the…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what I get in my inboxes.. What the actual fuck dawg??!?!??!? https://t.co/tBNlxeJap1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be careful who you play with, everyone ain't playin...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AaronICE2: Never learned about faith in school but that's what gets tested the most.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HornyFacts: She went from a classy lady to "surprise motherfucka" real quick. 😂

 https://t.co/KXF3WqbVxT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People forget that havin someone who genuinely gives a fuck about you is a gift and should not be taken for granted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Miss u dad 😔😢]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taking a break from everything]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of course my fat ass would wake up to eat perogies at this time lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Phil_Lewis_: Meanwhile, in New York City. https://t.co/2OiArRm1HU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @r_nixie: THIS is why we fight for safe, legal abortions. So this never has to happen. https://t.co/9JuR9zqe5E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time is the healer and the killer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop postin pics of your rats for national puppy day.. Aka Pomeranians and chihuahuas.. The demon dogs lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @40oz_VAN: Facts https://t.co/E9UciZNzYR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow Cris said I looked mad so that's why he didn't say hi. Dude, that's naturally how I look lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's weird when couples look related]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every time I listen to Sia I feel empowered]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When girls complain about random people addin them on snap but they're the ones puttin their username in their bio???? Bihh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adam Levine looks so fine when he rocked black slicked hair]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You were like an interesting book that I wanted to keep reading.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WORLDSTAR: https://t.co/dFESpUW9SS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WORLDSTAR: Motivational words of the Ugly God himself https://t.co/LxhP70P41N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The next guy to break my heart can literally square the fuck up lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The amount of money I spend on friends and food could have gotten me 2 full sets of sleeves and a whole leg sleeve :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @queenkimbaby: nothing sexier than a man who expresses their feelings and vents, opens up instead of acting hard and acting like it's ba…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @_beatsbynav: Don't ask anyone but me about me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How tf do ppl workout wit Air Max's? I twisted my fuckin ankles yo LOL wtf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ScanBC: #Langley Ambulance responding to 248 St &amp; 40 Ave for a male with a knife stuck in his stomach. Victim says he was slicing bread…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This guy at work asked me if I blocked him off IG.. Hell yeah I did.. You too old to be followin me, dawg.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CalvinHarris: How I made Slide https://t.co/dwu1NgVwFL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stayin silent and makin moves]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I sound like a 14 year old boy goin thru puberty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really got to stop drinkin when I'm sad lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you're tryna sleep but you keep hearin tinas nose whistling rofl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bippity bop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think it's always gotta be a competition against me, you already lost. Only person I compete wit is myself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RIP Nana Lise 💕 😢]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm gonna put myself first before everyone from now on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where would I be in this world without my wonderful friends? I love you my babies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hopelessly devoted to you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jazzyjenni77: FLINT MI HAS BEEN WITHOUT CLEAN DRINKING WATER SINCE 2014 PLEASE KEEP RETWEETING THIS https://t.co/EjYGBCffpO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is by far the worst cold I've ever gotten in my life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[:(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When a door closes, another one opens.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @VancityBuzz: Win 2 tickets to see @JColeNC in #Vancouver via @VancityBuzz https://t.co/MKFZ9U4LoP RT to enter! https://t.co/Lz4msgUcCx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When a company says they're diverse, but all you see is white people....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WORLDSTAR: Chance The Rapper donated $1 million to the Chicago School Foundation 👌 https://t.co/iGDJbHEwR9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel very blessed to have the few good friends in my life. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @40oz_VAN: Be all in or get all out, there's no halfway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Luv my friends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How is JLo almost 50 but looks like she's 30]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @40oz_VAN: Not perfect but I'm solid.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LeekJack_: When college and the Professors are stressing you out 😒 https://t.co/VmI4cZ1E3E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the weather forecast says it'll snow for a week straight... It's fricken March, dawg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tampons are weird]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @carterjwm: HELP ME PLEASE. A MAN NEEDS HIS NUGGS https://t.co/4SrfHmEMo3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BrennenTaylor: When someone says you look like  someone so you look them up and they're ugly af https://t.co/rnvkF87WyR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I do enjoy watchin mukbangs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A nice bowl of quac and chips would be nice rn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook is so not poppin anymore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vancouver weather got me all the way fucked up! Is you gonna rain or naw fuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I genuinely hate people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thinkin bout that delicious blue Gatorade that I had earlier lol damn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why did I even get a phone if the only person that is gonna text me is my Carrier provider lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes Julie 3 days to type god damn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In between an introvert and an extrovert]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Possums are scary looking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vegans are such assholes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys are so gross lol ugh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If someone ignores your messages at least 3 times, clearly they do not want to talk to you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GordonRamsay: You bought it ! Your box is in the back ground https://t.co/PxUnTpGWdh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jayversace: DONALD TRUMP NOW WHY TF WOULD YOU BOMB SYRIA ? #americaisoverparty https://t.co/R5BQ6MTl7Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_annavo Jughead's dad is a Zaddy too hehehe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Talkin to joan is always a good time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_annavo What about Jughead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is my 10th pair of apple earphones... Ffs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's a good brand of earphones or headphones that won't break on me??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Omg leave me alone you thirsty mf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are a spawn of Satan if you're born in April.. Fuck outta here wit all that rain bihhhh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like bein alone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you go on fb and have 20 notifications so you think you poppin but it's just your bestfriend taggin you in memes and videos lol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am so shy but at the same time I'm not shy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Kaykaysay lowkey was stalkin your ig, and I must say you are one beautiful chocolate goddess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dang this green juice is makin me shit lots]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This dude really slid into my dms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you screenshot shit off snap chat and don't care that it notifies the person 😊😊😊😊😊]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>