<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[NYSE glitch forces Amazon and Alphabet traders elsewhere: NEW YORK (Reuters) - The New York Stock Exchange said on Wednesday that trading was suspended on its exchange in five stocks, including Amazon and Alphabet, for the rest of the day due to a… https://t.co/zh9pfXHh6P https://t.co/ZYgCJe6i3W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer: Garmin Intl seeks Sr. Software Engineer in Olathe, KS to participate in the full lifecycle of development from requirements, analysis, design, implementation, testing and deployment. Must have a MS in Computer Science, Engineering… https://t.co/Psy1EUSB8r https://t.co/yFqAqDSDwW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Software Engineer: Job Summary Creates, modifies and maintains software applications individually or as part of a team. Provides technical leadership on a team, including training and mentoring of other team members. Provides technology and… https://t.co/Kf9NtJ6VzB https://t.co/DPqIXwQLJm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ruby Developer: Prestigious Enterprise Company is currently seeking a Software Developer with strong Ruby experience. Candidate will be responsible the development and support of the dynamic production application platform. QUALIFICATIONS: * 3+ years… https://t.co/lCmArmt00z https://t.co/Qq8m3ygN4I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Database Administrator: TITLE: SQL DATABASE ADMINISTRATOR LOCATION: WARRENDALE, PA DURATION: 9MONTHS + JOB DESCRIPTION: * Experience with SQL 2012 and higher and Windows Operating Systems required, familiarity with VMware preferred. * Extensive… https://t.co/lsguksIZc8 https://t.co/SuaVSPgiQ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior SQL DBA: We are seeking a Senior SQL DBA to join our expanding Commercial Technology team in Lewisville, TX. This will be a production DBA role in a cloud-based environment, supporting a proprietary platform and its affiliated products. What… https://t.co/faLRmlxKLW https://t.co/HVTqCOsntQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Security Engineer 5 – Continuous Monitoring Compliance Analysis and Reporting Team: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented… https://t.co/4aKstP51qL https://t.co/dvrnfT7Trz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETL – SQL Developer: Search and apply for jobs at Piper Companies | Careers at Piper Companies Careers Search Jobs Connect With Us ETL – SQL Developer Job Attributes Job Id: 17950Job Category: Data Analytics &amp; Business IntelligenceJob Location: Cary, NC… https://t.co/9wMVhkhSRM https://t.co/rBn0JcZRmM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ad sales surge at Google parent Alphabet, but so do costs: SAN FRANCISCO (Reuters) - Strong growth in ad sales on Google search and YouTube were not enough to offset a surge in costs at parent Alphabet Inc that shrank the first-quarter operating margin,… https://t.co/ERgJUzGhDE https://t.co/GxCyg8LIzQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Security Engineer 5 – Database Security Engineer: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the… https://t.co/FnJvPE9z6T https://t.co/koukLpWpyG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Software Developer Job Description: International corporation located in Eastern Ohio is looking for a qualified candidate for the position of Software Developer to become part of an in-house development team. The developer will be… https://t.co/uftLGD5hQF https://t.co/IaVuPX1pzs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer II: * Responsibility for the configuration and maintenance of network infrastructure * Ability to follow documented processes * Work with engineers to troubleshoot complex problems * Expert level knowledge of the following technologies:… https://t.co/Z9IggQ40Al]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP, gaining market share, raises outlook: FRANKFURT/LONDON (Reuters) - Germany's SAP announced upbeat results in the seasonally tough first quarter, saying it was gaining ground on its main competitors Salesforce and Oracle in the cloud and that its… https://t.co/Uh2nmdDpJL https://t.co/3erQAUJVX5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C# / .NET / SQL Server Developer (Presentation Layer): C#/.NET Developer (Presentation Layer) In search of a C#/NET Developer with focus on the presentation layer and conversational user interface. In addition to C#/.NET, applicants must have or quickly… https://t.co/wllTbDWxBB https://t.co/DWMt45gE1I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Specialist Java Developer: Senior Specialist Java Developer Asset service technology at BNY Mellon has an immediate need for Senior Java application developer and lead. We are looking for 10 plus years of experience.’ Work involves Java… https://t.co/QWSGxuNar6 https://t.co/qI7QDNksvW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT-Assistant Vice President: IT-Assistant Vice President (Morrisville, NC): Perform system analysis &amp; design &amp; develop IT applications for internal (management information) &amp; external (regulatory) Liquidity Risk reporting in accordance with IT standards… https://t.co/2V640XZHGF https://t.co/388x9s7Pfa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Java Developer | Struts, Spring, JavaScript, SQL, SOAP REST Web Services: Full Stack Java Developer | Struts, Spring, JavaScript, SQL, SOAP &amp; REST Web Services Columbus, OH 03-25-2018 Location: Columbus, OH For more than 18 years, CareWorks… https://t.co/qhkNeJvJDj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Administrator: Network Administrator Roaring Fork Transportation Authority Hiring a full-time Network Administrator to upgrade and support connectivity of RFTA’s network. Must provide technical oversight of WAN, monitor network performance,… https://t.co/kM238mIeUC https://t.co/xUWkvpKln5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer With Strong AWS and MySQL: Are you a software engineer turned DevOps enthusiast? Do you want to work for a lifestyle brand powerhouse that is highly profitable and backed by some serious technology? If that sounds like you then check this… https://t.co/cP8rDMHtks https://t.co/xT8SFoel1d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Lead: Project Lead IBM Corp, San Jose, CA: Define &amp; dvlp UNIX S-TAP release test plan &amp; execution process. Design &amp; implement quality processes &amp; metrics. Anlyze changes &amp; new features based on functional &amp; design reqs. Recommend test strategies.… https://t.co/E35EP72Itf https://t.co/Z4hosajfc2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Database Developer – SQL – Los Angeles, CA – $115k: Irvine Technology Corporation (ITC) is a leading provider of technology and staffing solutions for IT, Security, Engineering, and Interactive Design disciplines servicing startups to enterprise… https://t.co/xKywMCST8M https://t.co/fPDb66Xom2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China fund managers slash ZTE valuation after U.S. sanction: SHANGHAI (Reuters) - Chinese funds have slashed valuations of ZTE Corp after the United States banned American companies from selling components to the telecoms equipment maker for seven years,… https://t.co/vSRDhN60ct https://t.co/pSFcWrZ9vv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Security Engineer 4 – Database Security Engineer 4: Job Description Let’s talk about building a rewarding career You’ve got the passion. You’ve got the skills. Now you just need the right opportunity. At Wells Fargo, you’ll have the chance to join a… https://t.co/C6kVX1KvgV https://t.co/ywsJwXI6l6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Engineer: Washington, DC Full-time $100k – $120k Posted Today If you are a Data Engineer with experience, please read on! What You Need for this Position College experience and knowledge of: – C# – Python – Scala – ETL – Beam – Flume – NoSQL –… https://t.co/OCCNLzMgqa https://t.co/SsCDxKLby9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer [Java and SQL]: ABOUT THE ROLE Our client is the leading independent data-driven software platform built to monetize and manage premium video inventory with the greatest speed, control, and transparency, wherever and however audiences… https://t.co/XY2rYL0pRB https://t.co/yKNYkstCyh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Database Administrator DBA SQL Oracle NoSQL Finance Banking Tradin: SQL Database Administrator (DBA SQL Server Oracle Database Administrator SQL Clustering Always-On Mirroring RAC Finance Banking Trading) required by our trading software client in… https://t.co/C5fQPq6d4q https://t.co/KXVhT8H7c3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jr to mid level SQL/ETL Developer: Job TitleJr to mid level SQL/ETL Developer – ID:28534 Duration6 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsSQL Server 2005/2008 6+ years LocationTacoma, WA Date Posted03/12/2018 SQL Developer The ROPS SQL Developer role is a… https://t.co/hCDDW2mxWT https://t.co/h0BQG9kFJM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: InfosysHCADM Technology Lead – US Java – CT Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to create and execute strategies for their digital transformation. From… https://t.co/8AB07yrCvX https://t.co/mWG0JyJImM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Security Engineer 4: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the center of everything we do. Join… https://t.co/50zcc9zcZI https://t.co/tis5S5whYY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL/SQL Database Developer (Oracle) 16449: Description Huntington Ingalls Industries – Technical Solutions Division, Integrated Mission Solutions Group (Camber Corporation) provides mission-critical engineering and technical service to Information… https://t.co/xIboSe9eYL https://t.co/NR5NapN2Pn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server Database Analyst: If you love data and having your hand in every step of a project, our SQL Server Database Analyst role is for you. This role requires cross-functional work with our analytics, project management, account management and sales… https://t.co/niHVuSqZkd https://t.co/8BjvErTJaW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server DBA: SQL Server DBA Ref No.:18-00144 Category: ************* Location: Washington, District of Columbia Position Type:Contingent Start Date: 04/09/2018 Job Req -Additional Info Shift Work?:No Work Schedule:TBD Clearance Requirement:Secret Job… https://t.co/C3Ui2wSA8S https://t.co/2Kdu8PoJKS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#SQL DBA – Philadelphia, PA: Position Title: SQL DBA Consultant Location: North East Philly, PA Type: Contract Requirements 5+ years of experience in Database Administration and Developer for very large and complex databases in SQL Server. Expertise in… https://t.co/OoelblEiU7 https://t.co/CiOvEwJJAn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Consultant 5: Job Description Enterprise Finance &amp; Information Technology offers technology and services that exceed Wells Fargo customers’ expectations and directly enable them to succeed financially. We interact with customers more… https://t.co/VLa8ol9LZ6 https://t.co/NTrfhJQBTR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL/SQL Developer: Beacon Hill Technologies has a 6+ month contract opportunity for an Oracle PL/SQL Developer. Job Requirements: Experienced PL/SQL Developer whose responsibilities include but not limited to database development/support for existing… https://t.co/FbraNoYqPw https://t.co/W8zGXMvzhH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Healthcare BSA with SSRS and SQL skills: Irvine Technology Corporation (ITC) is a leading provider of technology and staffing solutions for IT, Security, Engineering, and Interactive Design disciplines servicing startups to enterprise clients,… https://t.co/gcW1dZxM1n https://t.co/RDKndKiLMN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Full Stack Software Engineer: Payments (PHP, T-SQL, TDD): AN IDEAL CANDIDATE HAS * 5+ YEARS of professional experience as a FULL STACK, full lifecycle software engineer. * Bachelors / Masters degree in Computer Science or related field * 3-5+… https://t.co/VVVHZDwaFm https://t.co/FpZF7sQrJx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Collaboration Tool Software Developer/Engineer (API, SQL, HTML, CSS, Javascript): Collaboration Tool Software Developer/Engineer (API, SQL, HTML, CSS, Javascript) Technology &amp; Analytics Iselin, New Jersey Apply Your Mission: The a Collaboration Tool… https://t.co/G7d1zaTaKx https://t.co/MM9FKTLCCh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Security Engineer 4: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the center of everything we do. Join… https://t.co/ktcSDUWwTu https://t.co/A2S2ZZhtSb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL/SQL Developer @@ BOSTON, MA: PL/SQL Developer @@ BOSTON, MA – Sriven Systems Inc. – Boston, MA – 04-02-2018 | ******** Toggle navigation – Tech Careers – Job Search – Skills Center – Dice Careers Mobile – Career Explorer – Salary Predictor – Career… https://t.co/Unqn8t8sOL https://t.co/Pyz8sEnTt9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Front End Engineer: New York, NY Full-time $130k – $150k Posted Today If you are a Lead Front End Engineer with a track record of success, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us – Autonomy – Great work environment – Ability to rise within a… https://t.co/Avj7qmVn7E https://t.co/NZNN8K4PoI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MYSQL DBA: MySQL Administration and Maintenance * Plan, design, deploy database systems, including base definition, structure, documentation, requirements gathering, preparing operational guidelines, and securing data. * Develop data models and perform… https://t.co/UpfAicMD2O https://t.co/DCq2UCnyEg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Engineer MySQL DBA: *FOR THE FIRST 6 MONTHS TO 1 YEAR THIS POSITION WILL BE 50% 1ST SHIFT AND 50% 2ND SHIFT. ONCE THE ENVIRONMENT GET’S TO WHERE IT NEEDS TO BE THE ROLE WILL SWITCH TO ONLY 1ST SHIFT/NORMAL BUSINESS HOURS** Chicago, IL Under general… https://t.co/f0bUQbZ2Js https://t.co/pDqiXycvxX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Lead – Cloud Analytics: To provide expert level IT Technical Leadership, including the direction, evaluation, selection, configuration, implementation, and integration of new and existing technologies and tools. This position is in the FAS… https://t.co/vrOczpTxpz https://t.co/UirCLqNQjl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server DBA: SQL SERVER DBA (BOSTON, MA) An exciting opportunity for a SQL Server DBA to join a global leader in secure payment technologies. You will be responsible for configuring, troubleshooting and maintaining the company’s production and… https://t.co/Vnk93qBVA0 https://t.co/I4J4IpblHF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: REQUIRED SKILLS Experience in relational database design, development, and support (MS SQL Server T-SQL preferred) Experience in complex database objects in T-SQL and/or PLSQL Experience with SSIS and/or ETL tools Experience with Visual… https://t.co/3iQa2Ec8Yy https://t.co/liAScSSM6w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Specialist Developer (T-SQL, PL/SQL, Database design, objects, tuning): Sr. Specialist Developer (T-SQL, PL/SQL, Database design, objects, tuning) ‘ Developer, Application Development and Tools:’ Responsible for designing custom applications and… https://t.co/ycATNZzC2v https://t.co/IXilfXDLs1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL DBA: INTERVIEW PROCESS: Hiring manager is in need for a SQL DBA Ability to manage multiple projects at once Provide break/fix as well as proactive system support Strong performance tuning and troubleshooting skills Must have experience in SQL… https://t.co/S0SwU5qZyD https://t.co/4C0leAax76]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MySQL/Oracle DBA: MySQL/Oracle DBA – Xtivia Inc – Colorado Springs, CO – 03-29-2018 | ******** Toggle navigation – Tech Careers – Job Search – Skills Center – Dice Careers Mobile – Career Explorer – Salary Predictor – Career Paths – Career Toolkit… https://t.co/dUTqEaqXfD https://t.co/rp5L0JO4MC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Security Engineer 4: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the center of everything we do. Join… https://t.co/jxUWZeGApD https://t.co/p0HRNxIX8j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Engineer (Strong SQL Required!!): This is NOT a contract or contractor role – PLEASE DO NOT submit your resume if you are not interested in full-time employment (FTE). Will be directly supporting software engineers using our clients… https://t.co/XUaLyM4yvV https://t.co/Z4Ez3aXkHZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[T-SQL Programmer / Developer: T-SQL Programmer / Developer Create new T-SQL reports, update existing reports, migrate/convert legacy data/pages to a more dated format; Update Business Rules and Validation as required. Assist IT and business in… https://t.co/9OwlBk0CHj https://t.co/KBOp28PNHk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer – DHS Public Trust Clearance: Herndon, VA Full-time $100k – $140k Posted Today We are a government IT consulting firm based in Herndon, VA. THsi is a full time permanent opportunity requiring a DHS Public Trust Clearance. What You Need for… https://t.co/YuB4VMenaW https://t.co/OiBQFpto5U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drupal Developer: Baltimore, MD Full-time Compensation Unspecified Posted Today We are one of the fastest growing agencies in the US! Due to growth, we are looking to add mid to senior level Drupal Developer's to our team. If you have 3+ years of Drupal… https://t.co/Ooc61nk9Ej]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server Database Administrator: The SQL Server DBA is challenged to work with application development and IT operations to help achieve a state-of-the-art environment that meets current and future business objectives and support Practice Velocitys… https://t.co/dLN7qaepk2 https://t.co/FvCdbeWnay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior MS SQL SSRS/ETL Developer: Senior MS SQL SSRS/ETL Developer ================================ Req #: ******Location: Washington, DC USJob Category: Information TechnologySecurity Clearance: Public TrustClearance Status: Must be Obtainable Job… https://t.co/K4tODN2RyX https://t.co/GhWjCX7Ymh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior business analyst with SQL experience: Primary point of contact for interface between the business users and IT teams. Formulates and defines systems scope and objectives through research and fact-finding, combined with a basic understanding of… https://t.co/jm8Tnfxbl0 https://t.co/lCoYwGjHXF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Employer Installation Administrator – US Telecommute: Working in Operations at UnitedHealth Group is one of the toughest and most fulfilling ways to help people, including yourself. We offer the latest tools, most intensive training program in the… https://t.co/d3vpBJ00Za]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MS SQL Database Administrator: RELOCATION PACKAGE AVAILABLE; CAN SPONSOR A US CITIZEN FOR A DOD CLEARANCE ISS is seeking an MS SQL Database Administrator to support the operations and maintenance of a large number of database servers for the US Army… https://t.co/f82VwTGsMx https://t.co/e13DE6oxiJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Intelligence Developer (SQL Server): Position Title Business Intelligence Developer (SQL Server) Job Requisition Number 18-0260 Location Fargo (Field Support Office) Description The Business Intelligence Developer II (SQL Server) will play a… https://t.co/n0wjLRr9ih https://t.co/GM0zgVX64J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL SQL Developer: PL SQL Developer Ref No.:18-08870 Location: Bangor, Maine Position Type:Full Time/Contract Start Date: 05/14/2018 Job TitlePL SQL Developer Relevant Experience (in Yrs)6-8 Technical/Functional SkillsPL/SQL Developer Experience… https://t.co/TQFtc7ELej https://t.co/R18K0Ns6QN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server Database Architect/DBA Lead: Our direct client is looking for a SQL Server Architect/Lead to provide leadership, guidance, and coordination for large DBA support teams, including coordination of complex database design, development,… https://t.co/L8lfME47oK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Mysql Dba: One of my client is looking for Lead Sr. / Lead MySQL DBA . If interested then please send me you resume ASAP. Sr. / Lead MySQL DBA Duration: 12+ Months Location: Milpitas, CA Rate:- Open Requirements Ensure performance, security, and… https://t.co/pr1yHmCKja]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server Database Architect/DBA Lead: Our direct client is looking for a SQL Server Architect/Lead to provide leadership, guidance, and coordination for large DBA support teams, including coordination of complex database design, development,… https://t.co/frwTDm06qv https://t.co/6sy3BOFMe1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server Application Development – Advisor: Job Description Job Description As a SQL Server Software Developer, you will be responsible for end to end, full-stack development of both internal and client facing applications for Wellpartner’s Contract… https://t.co/cKwp6L8ItV https://t.co/7m8gYntxHl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C#, https://t.co/ejSGKWK6E6, PL/SQL Developer-16800: HII has an immediate opening for an online application developer with strong C# and https://t.co/ejSGKWK6E6 experience. The right candidate should also have experience with complex PL/SQL stored… https://t.co/npqcBLcyIF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Backend Software Engineer – Java / MySQL / AWS: We are looking for a highly talented Backend Software Engineer for our El Dorado Hills office. As a Backend Java Application Developer youll provide support across all of Keepers products (Consumer, B2B).… https://t.co/lW17YA9JV6 https://t.co/crODd1hp4y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL DBA: SQL DBA Chicago, Illinois – United States Job Start Date – 05/15/18, Posted Date – 05/15/18 Primary SkillsSQLTax TermsC2COverview Phone and skype. Duration- 6months. rate- 50-55. Location- Chicago, Il. Client – CVS. No H1B Candidates MUST have… https://t.co/RsUW2aZSgy https://t.co/6wSBd7UkgZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: SQL Developer Primary Skills SSIS,SQL Developer,SQL Server DBA Overview PROLIM Global Corporation (**************) is currently seeking SQL Developer for location Brookfield, WI (Milwaukee Area) for one of our Top client . Job Description:… https://t.co/gXCkkoQeFX https://t.co/QG9s1ddUd8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior Systems and Data Analyst: Junior Systems and Data Analyst Jobs in Huntsville at Boeing Skip Navigation SearchMenu – News – Investors – Employee/Retiree – Merchandise – Suppliers – Features &amp; Multimedia – Commercial – Defense – Space – Services –… https://t.co/NGC7sWrMe4 https://t.co/lDEkq3LMdY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server Developer: – * Bachelor’s degree or foreign equivalent required from an accredited institution. Will also consider three years of progressive experience in the specialty in lieu of every year of education. – At least 4 years of experience with… https://t.co/bvXyvLxFBy https://t.co/0ersqYY06g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineering Supervisor: If you like to work with people in a family atmosphere, enjoy great benefits and provide unequaled personal service to every customer, consider a career with Bell Bank. The Software Engineering Supervisor is the lead for… https://t.co/2bPQnMClC4 https://t.co/WYU4VxpYAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Database Administrator: Fitness International is a well-established, respected fitness company with over 600 state-of-the-art sports clubs throughout US and Canada. Based in our Irvine headquarters, our IT department is expanding to support new… https://t.co/c5d7pcl8BD https://t.co/EeL6R9ET6u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Software Engineer REST Senior Level: Purpose of JobIMPORTANT: Applicants When filling out your name and other personal information below, DO NOT use any special characters or ALL CAPS. Use only standard letters in the English alphabet. Including… https://t.co/Ytb0cuq2fZ https://t.co/fTmwhUV2m3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MS SQL Database Developer: Company Description Visa operates the world’s largest retail electronic payments network and is one of the most recognized global financial services brands. Visa facilitates global commerce through the transfer of value and… https://t.co/QyjcjIigUT https://t.co/m9T18X3s75]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL/SQL Developer: PL/SQL Developer Columbus, OH 05-14-2018 Location: Columbus, OH For more than 18 years, CareWorks Tech has been delivering technology solutions that drive results. As your advocate, the common thread across our associates is crafting… https://t.co/p0H9r1AJW9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior SQL Database Administrator: Client Reference Code: 218473 DUTIES: Function as a production database administrator role in the SQL Database Team responsible for planning, engineering, implementing, and operating database services using MSSQL within… https://t.co/Ms7V1QlWUS https://t.co/0vbEtM4lgX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: SQL Developer Ref No.: 18-21450 Location: Washington, District of Columbia Title:- SQL Developer (SSIS, SSAS) Location:- Washington DC Contract W2 – Candidate should have more than 8+ years of Total IT experience. – More than 5 years of… https://t.co/rnRtJOQQSp https://t.co/fYXlXfBory]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. SQL Server Developer: Be part of a P2’s engineering team that is adding new features and refactoring an energy market trading application. The team is composed of senior-level software developers making a number of complex enhancements while also… https://t.co/BFqYXJGA99 https://t.co/sDQbklkwqK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Design Engineer – SQL/VB Developer Database Architect: The SQL Developer will be responsible for developing applications and integrations using the Microsoft SQL Server platform. This will include reports, vendor exports, data warehousing tasks… https://t.co/OnkuJigJtL https://t.co/GnqtLxbMPG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETL Developer – SSIS, SQL Server: Have you worked with SQL Server, SSIS, tape, bubblegum and related technologies to enable ETL and replication between disparate environments? Perhaps on-prem to cloud, cloud to on-prem, and so on? Workstate seeks mid to… https://t.co/Nq80sWRkTW https://t.co/dz9qoxhQ0d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Database Administrator – SurePayroll: Title SQL Database Administrator – SurePayroll ========================================= About the Organization Paychex, Inc. (NASDAQ: PAYX) is a leading provider of integrated human capital management solutions… https://t.co/EIiC4KgsBB https://t.co/XNIpkaimyD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer – NoSQL: Job Description What you’ll be doing… The Digital Team at Verizon is looking for a highly technical, NoSQL Developer with Java skills to help us develop our next generation of digital experience. The incumbent is a strong… https://t.co/sRYK6oThU3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Database Administrator: Fitness International is a well-established, respected fitness company with over 600 state-of-the-art sports clubs throughout US and Canada. Based in our Irvine headquarters, our IT department is expanding to support new… https://t.co/3s0mrxEJB2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber researchers, Ukraine warn of possible Russian attack: TORONTO/KIEV (Reuters) - Hackers have infected at least 500,000 routers and storage devices in dozens of countries, some of the world's biggest cyber security firms warned on Wednesday, in a… https://t.co/3Ul6ivzhB6 https://t.co/z8fZcoTvKM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer (JavaScript, C#, .Net, SQL): .Net Developer (JavaScript, C#, .Net, SQL) Ref No.: 18-21691 Location: Redmond, Washington Role .Net Developer (JavaScript, C#, .Net, SQL) Location: Redmond, WA Duration: FTE Mandatory Technical Skills A… https://t.co/d9JksP92co https://t.co/afdVo6XYS7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior SQL DBA: Senior SQL DBA Ref No.: 18-01208 Location: Troy ,MI &amp; Cincinnati, Ohio, Michigan Position Type: Direct Placement Start Date: 05/16/2018 Senior SQL DBA Full time Role Troy ,MI &amp; Cincinnati, Ohio Job description for Senior SQL Server DBA 9+… https://t.co/zJTf2c6mXE https://t.co/07eB6TrWAX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Database Administrator: Why work for this company: Lots of growth in the last few years, and plans for continued growth, through mergers and acquisitions. POSITION TITLE: SQL DBA IDEAL CANDIDATE: 3-5 years of experience * Coordinate database tape… https://t.co/dE2erSEXIt https://t.co/HqkjQwaeCD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Foxconn unit aims to raise $4.3 billion in biggest China IPO since 2015: TAIPEI/SHANGHAI (Reuters) - Foxconn Industrial Internet , a subsidiary of the world's largest contract manufacturer Foxconn , said it plans to raise 27.1 billion yuan ($4.26… https://t.co/4FkhqRajGo https://t.co/H74QhC6bQo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid-Level SQL/BI Database Developer – LTSS: Mid-Level SQL/BI Database Developer – LTSS Ref No.:18-00086 Location: Columbia, Maryland Experience Level: 3 Years Start Date: 05/09/2018 Mid-Level SQL/BI Database Developer – LTSS FEi is a leading IT company… https://t.co/8KI5CxqPBW https://t.co/gSgwB2oqp7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior SQL Server Database Engineer: – Location: Lincolnshire, Illinois, United States – Job ID: ******** – Posted: May 10, 2018 – Position Title:Senior SQL Server Database Engineer – Company Name:AON – Job Function:Information Technology/I.T. About AON… https://t.co/ugtYt8MIZ9 https://t.co/RLsFdOQC4k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook face-off: EU gets little news from Zuckerberg: BRUSSELS (Reuters) - Facebook CEO Mark Zuckerberg sailed through a grilling from EU lawmakers about the social network's data policies as lengthy questions left the 34-year-old American little time… https://t.co/R0z5RnJvTn https://t.co/pFzE9zsEIF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vulnerability Automation Engineer: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Baltimore, MD Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 5/9/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest… https://t.co/WrCB077mrW https://t.co/ro2EJJUGIb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior SQL Developer: Senior SQL Developer – (SSD) This details all the information about the job posting. Job Title Senior SQL Developer Organizational Unit Ashley Furniture Industries , Corporate , Information Technology Location Advance, NC 27006 US… https://t.co/1kjmEgNdMx https://t.co/odRXOuJTlK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MySQL DBA Python Engineer: MySQL DBA/Software Engineer with Python Need a strong MYSQL DBA with good python knowledge to automate tasks. You will need server tuning, strong Bash or Python Scripting skills along with DBA tasks Responsibilities: Performs a… https://t.co/qNoqJJFowg https://t.co/6LdTUqv5UE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle PL/SQL Developer: JOB DESCRIPTION Our client is seeking Oracle PL/SQL Developer based in Atlanta, Georgia. Reporting to the Technical Lead the selected applicant’s responsibilities include working with the defined project team to design develop… https://t.co/GBRSWs2OY3 https://t.co/bBo4ETxRxe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Engineer (Strong SQL Required!!): This is NOT a contract or contractor role – PLEASE DO NOT submit your resume if you are not interested in full-time employment (FTE). Will be directly supporting software engineers using our clients… https://t.co/mbiCx0wjyi https://t.co/9g3j5b2fM4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle PL/SQL Developer: Oracle PL/SQL Developer in monroeville, US-PA, USA | Consulting at CognizantJob Details | Cognizant – ************* – Industries – – – Services – – – Latest Thinking – – – About Cognizant – Careers Home – Get To Know Us – Our… https://t.co/rTlB8PPMDt https://t.co/N2Pp03GdUG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle PL/SQL Developer: Oracle PL/SQL Developer * Duration: Contract * Location: Atlanta, GA * Pay rate: W2 Hourly * Job ID: 53381 About the Job Our Client is seeking qualified candidates for the position of Oracle PL/SQL Developer in Atlanta,GA area… https://t.co/fWmo26XD9g https://t.co/H2E0NDYJLB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server Database Administrator (DBA): RumbleOn is seeking an Senior Level SQL Server DBA to join our team ! This position will facilitate the implementation, configuration, maintenance, and performance of critical SQL Server RDBMS systems, to ensure… https://t.co/tDk73O5dhn https://t.co/kq1ABkUQgn]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>