<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Systems Architect – SolidFire: Network Systems Architect – SolidFire Close By continuing to use and navigate this website, you are agreeing to the use of cookies. Accept – Careers – Featured Jobs – Customer Support Jobs – Engineering Jobs –… https://t.co/iGcXVevEvf https://t.co/GMdkwzqvBf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teamcenter Developer: Teamcenter Developer – Spalding Consulting, Inc. ************** *************** – Home – About – Solutions – Careers – Contracts – Contact – My Account Job Openings &gt;&gt; Teamcenter Developer Teamcenter Developer Summary… https://t.co/dMpBI4Icu0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thomas Markle is being vilified for one reason: The abrupt withdrawal of a key player in a wedding less than a week away would pose a major problem for any couple. For a ceremony that will be watched by hundreds of millions of people worldwide, it is,… https://t.co/kzR9HiBQcx https://t.co/vhHAw57N8v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: The stigma Margot Kidder faced down: Margot Kidder, who died Sunday at age 69, was more than just the actor who played Lois Lane in a series of "Superman" films in the 1970s and '80s. She was a passionate advocate for the environment and for… https://t.co/36B2Jt6eYT https://t.co/S1GYZJ8HZO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Support Engineering Manager: https://t.co/mNWLiF8m83 Services, Inc. seeks candidates for the following positions: Support Engineering Manager, Job Code AZJMSupEngMgr: Responsible for managing the software engineering support team to improve software… https://t.co/dmDoq3FfMt https://t.co/Omup7DgxUC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Best Apple iPad to Buy in 2018: Buying an iPad is more complicated than it needs to be, but we're here to help. https://t.co/zh2uciUQnC https://t.co/7hptH3inuV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Analyst Engineer – Reference: 2018-44033c: Reference: 2018-44033 Staff Analyst/Developer sought by DISH Network, LLC in Denver, CO. Lead a team of developers who build &amp; maintain web-based applications; design &amp; architect UI, UX, &amp; data… https://t.co/bHHHvTowK6 https://t.co/tEY49u2G3y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want an Xbox One X? It's $100 Off Right Now: For a new console like the Xbox One X, this $100 discount is pretty amazing. https://t.co/BszxBCE08I https://t.co/oZY55meiLI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Margot Kidder, who played Lois Lane in 'Superman,' dies: Margot Kidder, who found fame as Lois Lane in the 1978 film "Superman," died Sunday at her home in Montana, her manager confirmed to CNN. https://t.co/Goi4ggnHTN https://t.co/g94SBv5CMJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer – BGOV Data Streaming Data Platform: Senior Software Engineer – BGOV Data Streaming &amp; Data Platform Princeton Posted May 4, 2018 – Requisition No. 66922 Bloomberg Government (BGOV) provides users with a premium,… https://t.co/lCi0KqI07v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Requisition ID 2018-24723 Work Location US-NM-Carlsbad Department / Discipline Project Management Additional Work Location .. Position Type Staff / Permanent Job Description Overview / Responsibilities Wood is currently seeking a Project… https://t.co/Z72jMNhQjd https://t.co/jJIFgDmvPw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Staff Software Engineer: Senior Staff Software Engineer Equinix is the leading global interconnection platform, accelerating business performance by connecting companies to their customers and partners inside the worlds most networked data… https://t.co/NeLIrVp9cZ https://t.co/uPtTtatdIO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a shot! 31 amazing sports photos: Take a look at 31 amazing sports photos from May 7 through May 13. https://t.co/fhoW87bYu8 https://t.co/NryneY7hoa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Media Manager / Digital producer: The Gazette is looking for a highly creative, self-starting individual who can also collaborate well in a team environment and be our Social Media Manager while also handling digital producer duties. Gazette… https://t.co/zb5n4rK7la https://t.co/3UVeMI43aJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Price: Everyone should have health coverage: Former Health and Human Services Secretary Tom Price continues to oppose the Affordable Care Act -- also known as Obamacare -- but he also says he believes everyone should have access to health care. https://t.co/V0nPzpIhuB https://t.co/l2QM2cJEB4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Designer / Developer: DeKalb, IL Company – SVI International, Inc. is seeking a Web Designer / Developer to join our marketing team. As a web designer/developer, you will collaborate with departments to build and maintain company websites. From… https://t.co/CnBH0CuyRP https://t.co/blXjPkGh46]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sheriffs Electronic Communications Technician I/II: Sheriff’s Electronic Communications Technician I/II $4,222 – $6,736/Monthly   Equal Opportunity Employer recblid 2nzgwju4lzni9e0h85l3uhfu2s8zxl https://t.co/McT1YM1e4H https://t.co/Wz88FDLaFX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most experts agree: Walking is good exercise: We humans need to exercise in order to stay healthy. Exercise protects against disease and early death, and keeps us mobile and able to perform daily tasks. https://t.co/sy7Fqkxqfg https://t.co/mQp8VB3FSR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Applications Developer: Description: Position Requires a Top Secret (TS/SCI) Clearance with a Polygraph. ******* OPEN TO ALL SKILL LEVELS******** Sponsor is looking for a multi-level Applications Developer. Positions work under minimal technical guidance… https://t.co/3j9AWCrfdB https://t.co/qtiCfpSk6D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer II: Description We are seeking a highly motivated developer/programmer to join our Global Forwarding System development team. The Global Forwarding System development team is responsible for delivering solutions to our business users to… https://t.co/rr6uKAYNdS https://t.co/gIAyhgrUce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Workflow UX Designer (Contract): One of the hottest gaming studios is looking for a Workflow UI/UX Designer to join our team working on the next, big gaming studios experience. As the Workflow UI Designer, you are central to defining an amazing user… https://t.co/zNiaTD5H3f https://t.co/5hypMEpZQM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Release Engineer: Overview We’re looking for skilled software test engineers and analysts who have what it takes to perform quality assurance testing and manage the release of ArcGIS, one of the world’s most sophisticated GIS software systems. Starting… https://t.co/DvKDPR8yVs https://t.co/RvBEvy4z9b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MDS Coordinator: Crystal Heights Care and Rehabilitation Center in Oskaloosa is looking for a qualified MDS Coordinator to join our team. This is a great opportunity for an RN with long-term care/ skilled nursing experience. This position is full time… https://t.co/Uxxwh1fmw4 https://t.co/va6PS2WSMF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Industrial Service Technicial – Madison: Onsite Service Representative CraneWerks, Inc. is accepting applications for an Onsite Service Representative in the Columbus Indiana area. This is a great opportunity for the right person. The Ideal candidate… https://t.co/mnFP22eNtB https://t.co/7B4ewaLerV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior QA Engineer: Granular is the leading software and analytics company for agriculture. We are revolutionizing one of the world’s largest and most important industries by making farmers lives easier and making them more profitable. Our products help… https://t.co/0dbJNOwOFl https://t.co/EG6MpO1iIu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Software Engineer – .NET: Job Description SummaryLooking for a Sr. .NET Software Engineer with 8+ years of experience. Candidate should have senior or lead level development experience experience in .NET, C#, https://t.co/D13bpPiLbd,… https://t.co/pxr1uf8nye https://t.co/PGSYu40vUT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. DevOps Engineer: Do you work best when surrounded by intelligent, ambitious, and humble people? Do you want to help build and manage big data systems that power analytics for one of the fastest growing mobile advertising platforms? Do you have a… https://t.co/EggFR3097V https://t.co/k9B90vuCLu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Neighbor explains why she called 911 on black Airbnb guests: Rialto, California authorities release audio from the woman who called police on three black Airbnb guests. The three guests and one of their attorney's spoke to CNN's Victor Blackwell. https://t.co/Qprd5sxxep https://t.co/XiG2K2WS9l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Model Based Systems Engineer 4:   Job Description – Model Based Systems Engineer 4 (18001079) Model Based Systems Engineer 4 Requisition ID : 18001079 Location : United States-Colorado-Aurora US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation… https://t.co/b0HQS9IfQy https://t.co/0pI2L8Mnq3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Senior Engineer – Platforms: About Avaya Avaya enables the mission critical, real-time communication applications of the world’s most important operations. As a global leader in delivering superior communications experiences, Avaya offers a… https://t.co/Q9k95fdvnx https://t.co/kRL1nAPE7M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aerospace Senior Engineering Project Scheduler: This opening is for a Senior Engineering Project Scheduler on an Aerospace New Product Development Program. The day-to-day duties will include: * Developing new schedules based on aerospace project… https://t.co/AOe6EUv9Hx https://t.co/MS4fLQHjfr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer – Customer Data Services: About GoDaddy GoDaddy powers the world’s largest cloud platform dedicated to small, independent ventures. With nearly 17 million customers worldwide and over 73 million domain names under management,… https://t.co/YmBc4T9xXa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CBRN Technician: Description:Leidos currently has a CBRN Technician opening that will support the Security Engineering Program (SEP) program in Alexandria, Va.   ***Must have current Secret clearance*** ***Hours are 2pm to 10pm, Monday – Friday***    … https://t.co/QvDhSEmVjR https://t.co/oey1XyEDla]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Engineer: Description:Job Description:   The Advanced Solutions Group (ASG) at Leidos currently has an opening for a System Engineer to work at our San Antonio, Texas location. This is an exciting opportunity to use your experience supporting an… https://t.co/mMlro6WFzB https://t.co/KhIxZTwjQC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rep. Waters scolds Kelly: Don't tell me about discrimination: Rep. Maxine Waters (D-CA) and Rep. Mike Kelly (R-PA) clashed on the House floor over race and discrimination ahead of a vote to repeal Obama-era legislation protecting consumers from… https://t.co/B1k8no1swB https://t.co/EbaFi2Ywxp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embedded Systems Software Engineer: Description:The Advanced Solutions Group (ASG) at Leidos currently has an opening for an Embedded Systems Software Engineer to work in Washington, DC.  This is an exciting opportunity to use your experience to support… https://t.co/ajMf760WWD https://t.co/DDzwYEMIhv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Security Analyst: Description:Global Information Grid (GIG) Service Management-Operations (GSM-O), a Defense and Intelligence Group of Leidos has an opening for a Cyber Security Analyst at the JFHQ DODIN Operations Center on Ft. Meade, MD. Job… https://t.co/TmU2Cg7MSR https://t.co/GTSYuCJepE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer: Description:Leidos ranks in the top 40 on LinkedIn’s 2017 "Top Companies" list. We offer challenging and meaningful problems, a collaborative culture, and support for your career goals and growth.   The Mission Systems… https://t.co/FZoAqBhi3A https://t.co/NSwDysSMkL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bourdain helps Anderson Cooper say Newfoundland: Anthony Bourdain and Anderson Cooper sit down to discuss cod culture in Newfoundland, and Bourdain's shocking discovery on his recent trip to the Canadian province. Watch Parts Unknown Sundays at 9PM ET/PT… https://t.co/wlmWfBOPF9 https://t.co/C7hYuyibBh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staff Software Engineer (Platform): We’re LendingHome. We’re on a mission to revolutionize the world of mortgages and put the power, and the keys, where they belong—in your hands. The Role We are seeking a Staff Software Engineer who will lead by… https://t.co/xMSTLwb6Rc https://t.co/xv2tPITf5l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Security T3: Description: The Origin program is seeking a Cyber Security Engineer with the technical expertise to perform a broad range of information assurance engineering tasks in a complex customer environment. Tasks may include but are not… https://t.co/Kh0eZOcF2a https://t.co/rBVAjXlVOl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Linux Systems Administrator: Description:The Defense and Intelligence group at Leidos currently has an immediate opening for a Senior Linux Systems Administrator at San Antonio, Texas.   This position is dedicated to the support of the Defense… https://t.co/NVupQ7ReJZ https://t.co/RudJBmQtKb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JRSS Operational Engineering Manager: Description:Global Information Grid (GIG) Service Management-Operations (GSM-O), a Defense and Intelligence Group of Leidos has an opening for a JRSS Operational Engineering Manager. Our customer is the Defense… https://t.co/cBmyhM0zZY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekend Tech Deals: Google Home Mini, Dell, Raspberry Pi, Anker: Google’s adorable, affordable home assistant device is now (almost) two for the price of one. https://t.co/6t3caTtqvA https://t.co/kNvfYvYzGy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump declares major disaster in Hawaii: President Donald Trump declared a major disaster in Hawaii after days of volcanic activity that sent molten lava and toxic fumes spewing into residential neighborhoods. https://t.co/Zv2KtUlfyY https://t.co/RggYlDPInn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Commercial Superintendent: Jacksonville, FL Full-time $90k – $130k Posted Today If you are a Superintendent with experience, please read on. What You Will Be Doing Responsible for the day-to-day execution of large commercial / industrial construction… https://t.co/unbK1sn2CB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Content Developer – JavaScript, CMS, Contentful, PHP!: Glendale, CA Full-time $100k – $130k Posted Today Based in Glendale, CA we are a TOP ranked technology company developing state of the art 3D Printing technologies. With over 15 years of… https://t.co/h90iwYVNnh https://t.co/zcMLRl1LT0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Assurance Innovation &amp; Technology – Director, Software Engineering: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify… https://t.co/uEglaRGylm https://t.co/FcEhmV3hTO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SalesForce Director- Advisory Financial Services: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more… https://t.co/BeQF3KG0J3 https://t.co/gw2s0PnyYN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gadget Lab Podcast: Why Google’s Duplex Demo Didn’t Have Everyone at Hello: This week on the Gadget Lab podcast, we discuss Google's mind-blowing demo of artificial intelligence at its annual developers conference. https://t.co/91Fb8nBor3 https://t.co/n85plcc0yF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Crimes Unit Technology Manager: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about us at… https://t.co/hhKKNHzd5f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps/Azure Architect, Senior Associate: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about us at… https://t.co/17G6xkIUlx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agile Transformation Manager- Financial Services: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more… https://t.co/PA9Om5tTrt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Amazon Prime Still Worth It?: Amazon Prime's price increase kicks in today—but it's still a bargain for most people. https://t.co/SJb1mNwIt3 https://t.co/5XyGs9OCAX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Cloud Architect (AWS CSA Professional) Job: Date: Mar 21, 2018 Location:Aberdeen, MD, US Company: SAIC Sr. Cloud Architect (AWS CSA Professional) (Job Number:429542) Description: JOB DESCRIPTION: – Provides enterprise architecture expertise to… https://t.co/KJo6mKGIpC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Specialist: IT Specialist Location: Pearl Harbor, HI Job Code: 2207 # of openings: 1 Description Bay State Computers, Inc. is a professional services firm and a leading provider of Information Technology (IT) services and products to the U.S. Federal… https://t.co/PhlEYCC6l9 https://t.co/XDsv6nuL3r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Location: San Jose, California, US Area of Interest Project or Program Management Job Type Professional Technology Interest *None Job Id 1216550 New What You'll Do Global Tactical Systems and Tools (GTST) needs a Project Manager who can… https://t.co/oR4okYhRQH https://t.co/Bd987fFgrp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Estimator- 100M+ High Rise/Stadiums/Hotels (150-200k+): Los Angeles, CA Full-time $0k – $0k Posted Today From developments to high-rise structures to luxury residential destinations, our teams of experts work in partnership with owners, design… https://t.co/4Yi2BmaYrq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer Software 3:   Job Description – Engineer Software 3 (18006320) Engineer Software 3 Requisition ID : 18006320 Location : United States-Colorado-Aurora US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation Assistance: Relocation assistance may… https://t.co/gtu5L20POf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this island the next Iceland? https://t.co/0XtatUk7YU https://t.co/18gRgbpAn0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Network Communications Technician: Senior Network Communications Technician   Position Title Senior Network Communications Technician Announcement Summary Fayetteville Technical Community College is seeking qualified applicants for this critical… https://t.co/Hd5V0MxwGZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Quality Assurance Engineer / SQA Engineer: The SQA Engineer will be responsible for the quality assurance testing of Scribes products which are built on Microsofts .Net platform and utilizing agile development processes &amp; methodologies. This… https://t.co/Z7li1Ykbct https://t.co/pj7oA52ode]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toobin calls Giuliani claim 'corrupt': CNN's Jeffrey Toobin gives his analysis on Rudy Giuliani suggesting that President Trump could issue pardons after Mueller's investigation is complete. https://t.co/9Cfv7ivxRp https://t.co/oSdVkmEeQN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manafort arrived in jail to await trial https://t.co/IQxxsO5EVf https://t.co/iyoDqvNs0z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Integrator: Introduction ASML brings together the most creative minds in science and technology to develop lithography machines that are key to producing faster, cheaper, more energy-efficient microchips. We design, develop, integrate, market and… https://t.co/CWB8CZFbZH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ERP Data Business Process Consultant: Job Title: ERP Data Business Process Consultant Location: Hopkins, MN, Mid-West United States, USA Company: Cargill, Inc Industry Sector:Agribusiness Industry Type: Crop Production Career Type:IT/Software Development… https://t.co/P9TVoOOYJS https://t.co/qbL642uozU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer/ Architect: We are currently seeking a motivated, career and customer oriented Senior Software Engineer/Architect to join our team in Reston, VA to begin an exciting and challenging career with Unisys Federal Systems. In this… https://t.co/KYxlDAfIFY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer Level II: Oasis Systems -Software Engineer Level II Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome page… https://t.co/32bL5MUUNW https://t.co/zTzWvNDJGF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IOS Engineer: Santa Monica, CA Full-time $100k – $150k Posted Today Are you an IOS Engineer who craves to be a part of a bigger mission? If so, read on… We are a revolutionizing the way we finance and shop by offering unprecedented freedom, flexibility… https://t.co/lu5E22fUzu https://t.co/BsQaV7olrW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ronaldo rescues Portugal vs. Spain https://t.co/Irn8H1DzBC https://t.co/5KMvKPUJrj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gadget Lab Podcast: Why Apple, Google, Microsoft Are Stirring the Software Pot: This week’s podcast is all about the software that points to the future of our how we'll use our gadgets – even if they infuriate us in the interim. https://t.co/SzHgkkHjvK https://t.co/o8delbTSiC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will Tiger and Rory make the cut? https://t.co/KxeJgSJiTz https://t.co/jcGh2A8Rok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huawei MediaPad M5 Review: 8.4-inch, 10.8-inch, and M5 Pro: All three of Huawei's M5 Android tablets are worth your time, but which is best for you? https://t.co/gI9DUavmvd https://t.co/29WNaRCNIg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Investigator / Stratford, CT: Req ID : 435203BR Job Code/Title : E5214:Investigator Stf Job Description : At Lockheed Martin Rotary and Mission Systems (RMS), we are driven by innovation and integrity. We believe that by applying the highest standards of… https://t.co/eh3ziHeJwB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: Job ID: ********-11836-TL Company Name: Xactware Description: Senior Java Developer ClaimXperience is searching for a dynamic and creative Senior Java Developer who has the knowledge and experience to help shape our industry… https://t.co/XYOnMQWO4U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The return of pre-existing condition surcharges: The Affordable Care Act is back in court again. In February, 20 Republican states, led by Texas, filed a lawsuit claiming that when Congress reduced the tax penalty (which most people must pay if they fail… https://t.co/CMMJoJqffm https://t.co/VxlCBIVmqk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Lead: DevOps Lead Ref No.: 18-25255 Location: Seattle, Washington Position : DevOps Lead Location: Seattle, WA Duration: Fulltime Architect – 12-15 years exp Architect experienced in architecting or technical designing of Java and Javascript,based… https://t.co/3bgoeFjnV2 https://t.co/LIciLto6ff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chrissy Teigen's message to Trump: Celebrity couple John Legend and Chrissy Teigen have donated $72,000 to the ACLU in honor of President Trump's 72nd birthday, to bring attention to the crisis at the border. HLN's Michaela Pereira reports. https://t.co/FkDMRsJA0r https://t.co/lAR7fRiUJw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Product Management Director: PRODUCT MANAGEMENT DIRECTOR VMware, Inc. seeks a Product Management Director (up to 25% domestic &amp; international travel req’d) to define, prioritize, plan and drive the execution of the vision for VMware’s… https://t.co/3BkgwbLRQU https://t.co/SIVF1ZZFqI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are windowless planes the future of travel?: Could you drop off to sleep in a windowless plane? https://t.co/5KnfZZrrEy https://t.co/voQvtXhNMI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full-stack Software Developer: Tresata has an immediate full time opening for a full-stack software developer position in the Charlotte office to assist in development of our game changing predictive analytics platform. We are looking for someone who… https://t.co/YmryoYFPCg https://t.co/y3PeTqXk1j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Strategy (media/healthcare) – Manager/ Director – (Top Management Consulting): Manager and Director level: * 8 – 10+ years of relevant consulting or industry experience, recent consulting experience is "highly desired. * Delivering IT Strategies… https://t.co/MxsxXb7omp https://t.co/fslOEm6lGV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Backend Software Engineer: Principal Backend Software Engineer (Santa Monica, CA) – Home – Products – Industries – Clients – Company Create a Profile|Log In Yes No Show Details At least one job must be selected in order to apply. Refer Job: – –… https://t.co/LLbcv1x9B3 https://t.co/Mu4nGyrFJD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Security Solutions Architect: Job Description What you’ll be doing… The Principal Architects serve as the technical design authority and architectural expert for sales opportunities across multiple vertical and geographic regions, in support of the… https://t.co/DbqsoCm9gY https://t.co/mPcWUu1vJC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UI Developer: UI Developer Ref No.: 18-24061 Location: Secaucus, New Jersey UI Developer Secaucus , NJ 9-12,Months Digital : Cloud Architecture, Digital : AngularJS, Digital : HTML5-CSS3, Foundation : Advanced Java Concepts Advanced Java/J2EE, Angular… https://t.co/ptLJ2414Pg https://t.co/zKBpEPllYB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CMM Programmer: CMM Programmer (Plymouth) – Job Listing – Loc Performance Jobs Search Jobs | Submit an Application | Home CMM Programmer (Plymouth) Salary Range:Negotiable Exempt/Non-Exempt:Non-Exempt Benefits:Medical, Dental, Life and Disability… https://t.co/vBiglFGre9 https://t.co/YWi154FFbt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Service Desk Technician: The Kennedy Center is the nation’s busiest performing arts center, offering over 2000 performances and welcoming over two million visitors a year.  The IT Department provides, supports and maintains all the technology systems… https://t.co/81tbcJTRdG https://t.co/GT7g8quM9n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The real reason Kamau Bell took a DNA test: W. Kamau Bell didn't need a DNA test to confirm his identity. https://t.co/S2OsYJRiAO https://t.co/u79kQNGeh0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inside Amazon's Painstaking Pursuit to Teach Alexa French: Amazon tries to translate its homegrown voice assistant into a global success. https://t.co/cQqXgp5X7z https://t.co/D0JvtdYpiw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stormy Daniels files new lawsuit against Cohen and old attorney: Adult film actress Stormy Daniels on Wednesday launched a new lawsuit against her former attorney, Keith Davidson, as well as President Donald Trump's personal lawyer, Michael Cohen, saying… https://t.co/LWzR1RntPp https://t.co/CrqtFiQW3n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A New Era of Frankensoftware Is Upon Us: But that's not necessarily a bad thing. https://t.co/Mh3U2xdQz3 https://t.co/T3n86MJdRM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smartphone Mobility Systems Engineer: 30179BR Smartphone Mobility Systems Engineer Washington District Of Columbia United States Support our Mobility on-site customer delivery team by providing senior systems administration support. This is an important… https://t.co/kIXPx9fNNs https://t.co/tjEQQQzVdb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Platform Engineer: Culver City, CA Full-time $120k – $175k Posted Today If you are a Senior Back-End Developer / Platform Engineer with experience of using production tools, features and technology to increase scaling and performance in a JAVA… https://t.co/FMow2DEJKX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Development Manager: job detailsJob Number:1200709Job Title:Business Development ManagerJob Type:Full-timeLocation:San Francisco, CAHours:Post Date:Jun 6 2017Salary:DOEDetailed Job Description: Large Communications Firm is looking for a business… https://t.co/QktzsbFTlt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CDM Phase II Operations Analyst – CyberArk: Req ID 98414BR Business Title CDM Phase II Operations Analyst – CyberArk Group MCIS Location USA VIRGINIA Reston Clearance Level Needed None Category Cyber Job Duties and Responsibilities Become an integral… https://t.co/DaQj93iiwi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Security Solutions Engineer/Architect: OVERVIEW: phia LLC is seeking a highly skilled Enterprise Security Architectto join our team of qualified, diverse individuals. This position will be located in Morrisville/Raleigh, NC. DUTIES: Provide… https://t.co/EVNd6aJLWL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Puerto Rico releases records of deaths since Maria: The Puerto Rican government on Tuesday released to CNN and another news organization a database of information on all deaths that occurred after Hurricane Maria, which pummeled this US commonwealth on… https://t.co/QppsNLWGDx https://t.co/hvzetWVOwq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering Senior Developer: Senior Developer for SAP Labs, LLC (Palo Alto, CA) resp for dev focusing on dsgn, cdng, qlty assrnc of cmplx prdct features in a dev team. Bach dgr in Comp Sci, Engg, Math, or rltd &amp; 6 yrs exp req’d. Will also acpt Master’s… https://t.co/YvQxwM6KFi https://t.co/mweaEdICLl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer Analyst: ENGINEERING: GlobalLogic has mult. openings in San Jose, CA: *SW Engineers (GLSW)-Dsgn &amp; define new feat for sw apps. *Programmer Analysts (GLPA)-Create, write &amp; test programs. *Lead SW Engineer (GLLSW)-Dvlp mobile app sltns. *Sr.… https://t.co/ZBsEygK6eJ https://t.co/VEWcaoqeXs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eevee has two and a half flippers. Here's where she learned to swim: As cries to save our polluted oceans reach a global crescendo, a young sea turtle in the Maldives named Eevee could very well be considered the ultimate symbol of the challenges that… https://t.co/QGIrzku1pr https://t.co/V3RRXy9ssI]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>