<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Engineer III: https://t.co/mNWLiF8m83 Services, Inc. – Austin, TX. Software Development Engineer III – Deliver investigation plans &amp; reports, architectural documents, design specifications, software &amp; firmware source code &amp; build… https://t.co/zZj0CBcrth https://t.co/sxQBtdYtjr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[E3 Game Deals: PS4, Xbox One, Nintendo Switch (2018): While Sony, Microsoft, and Nintendo debut new games at E3, they're rolling out deep discounts on the old ones. https://t.co/5zYdg6kEzQ https://t.co/qgGJLjxj3G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Support Engineer/ Helpdesk Print Room- Big Name Video Game Manufacturing Company- San Mateo: GPL Technologies has the immediate need for self starting and assertive IT Support Engineer to work in the Creative, Design, Events, and Video group of a… https://t.co/NLgsI2j2MX https://t.co/5Ux7oDu7zy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Engineering Manager: 15929BR Systems Engineering Manager General Atomics San Diego California General Atomics (GA), and its affiliated companies, is one of the world’s leading resources for high-technology systems development ranging from the… https://t.co/tehCTfNX0u https://t.co/MF71eMz8JK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Litigation Real Estate Attorney: San Francisco, CA Full-time $85k – $150k Posted Today If you are a Litigation Real Estate Attorney with experience, please read on! What You Will Be Doing (THIS POSITION REPORTS TO LA AND REQUIRES RELOCATION, RELOCATION… https://t.co/P3YqRlvNCl https://t.co/G9S7SBp7rk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CDM ISSO Principal: Req ID 95567BR Business Title CDM ISSO Principal Group MCIS Location USA VIRGINIA Reston Clearance Level Needed None Category Cyber Job Duties and Responsibilities Become an integral part of a diverse team that leads the world in… https://t.co/jSjIpTNtu5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chordiant JSF UI Development: Chordiant JSF UI Development Ref No.: 18-23684 Location: San Jose, California Build UI screens and interactionHTML5, CSS3, Ajax, Javascript – MustAngularJS (nice to have), Ajax : Must be Aware (clientside libs like angular –… https://t.co/MfxW6IhV27]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GOP congressional candidate: Diversity is 'a bunch of crap and un-American': A Republican running for New Jersey's 2nd Congressional District thinks diversity is "a bunch of crap and un-American," according to comments he made in a video posted to… https://t.co/MrvMTNCqb8 https://t.co/z379Hbf0aJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sally Yates: When darkness falls -- my dad's battle with depression: It was May 6, 1986, and I was just days away from graduating from law school. Late in the afternoon, my mother called the Law Review office looking for me. I had just left to grab a… https://t.co/dYEOnqFU61 https://t.co/GqXmPoIM2j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Specialist: Drive Technical Support At Periscope Data: Periscope Data’s mission is to provide the fastest data visualization product on the market. As a Technical Support Specialist, you will be responsible for empowering the Periscope… https://t.co/AxAQLsERLB https://t.co/YtGDqjZeaQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why the 2018 midterm elections matter: Beyond the balance of power in Congress, the 2018 midterm elections' impact will be felt at every level of government for at least the next decade. Learn what the effects might be. https://t.co/ku4zHgRi7h https://t.co/QC63gjmu5s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Senior Software Engineer in Broomfield, CO. Minimum Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science or closely related, plus 2 years experience as Software Engineer are required. recblid r9bk1jxwvomsjuljsr1yl5k5z43h46 https://t.co/amOogATdHg https://t.co/oS3HmxplrR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Consultant – Applications #18071: The Northern Trust Company is seeking a Senior Consultant, Applications in Chicago, IL with the following requirements: BS degree in Mathematics and/or Science, Management Information Systems, or related field or… https://t.co/ILjnJEm3mW https://t.co/ENdFrxPYly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Billions in cryptocurrency wealth wiped out after hack https://t.co/UjYQFOj3y0 https://t.co/67Lq52RTdE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C/C++ Software Engineer for Software Defined Radio: Req ID : 417820BR Job Code/Title : E1073:Software Engineer Sr Job Description : Lockheed Martin invites you to step up to one of today’s most daunting challenges: the use of advanced electronics to… https://t.co/UsUG2q03Bl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Operations Analyst: Full Job Description can be obtained from the link "************************************************************************************ The description below may contain some unreadable words or sentences, so you are advised… https://t.co/foEh44L0nZ https://t.co/qKqEmK6RZ5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager Electronics Development: Location Wilton – CT, US Level Bachelor Experience &gt;10 Senior Available since 4/20/2018 Functional area Project Management Background Electronics Reference req1807 Introduction ASML US, LP brings together the most… https://t.co/6gsK5VudTy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US trade adviser: 'There's a special place in hell' for Trudeau: Peter Navarro, a trade adviser to President Donald Trump, escalated the White House's rebuke of Canadian Prime Minister Justin Trudeau, calling him weak and dishonest on Sunday. https://t.co/9ZD9vQsQWH https://t.co/klcMQifRFv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manager IT Services Provider ACL Labs: Job Description Job ID ****** Specialty / Department Wi It Technical Services Full / Part Time Full-Time Hours / Bi-weekly Pay Period 80 2018-05-10 Location – Aurora West Allis Med Ctr8901 W Lincoln Ave West Allis,… https://t.co/m6ndU9nWTn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Who we are: Conversable is a funded software startup working on a SaaS platform for building enterprise-class chat/voice bots. Our founding team has started and sold several companies, have worked at companies like Zynga, Yahoo, Demand… https://t.co/yRXgCC6u7A https://t.co/mqqmQgon3f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Full-Stack Developer: The Company and Opportunity Axius provides smart home management – think of us like your personal IT Help Desk. By creating a fully inclusive service layer for the home, Axius adds remote support, network security and… https://t.co/HZYRt0fsDk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ServiceNOW Business month contract: Recruiter Pomeroy Location Cherry Hill Cherry Hill United States Salary Competitive Posted 19 May 2018 Closes 16 Jun 2018 Job role Accountant Sector Financial services and consulting Contract type Permanent Hours Full… https://t.co/cA0L5J3jt4 https://t.co/6R3q184EH7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front End Web Developer: Interested in working for a growing, fast-paced company with diverse projects and technologies? COLAB is looking for talented team members to help shape the companys future. At COLAB, we have a close-knit team with no office… https://t.co/gJqRVmKAIF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer, Android: As an Android-focused software engineer at Grio youll be focused on building Android applications using the latest SDKs and industry best practices. You will be able to work on a variety of projects and experience new… https://t.co/1ip1PCSSMU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tapper slams Trump's 'egregious intrusion': Jake Tapper discusses the Trump administration's crackdown on James Wolfe, a US Senate staffer who was arrested and charged with lying to federal agents as part of an investigation related to the unauthorized… https://t.co/VTRZFFOCAf https://t.co/3wIjHw3IPZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[User Experience Designer: Haven Life is an insuretech innovator at MassMutual that offers a new way to get life insurance online that’s actually simple. We combine the culture of a startup with the stability and backing of a Fortune 500 company to create… https://t.co/FyQjlWzeuJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Platform Debug Engineer- C++: Platform Debug Engineer- C++ Hillsboro OR Full Time Position Job Description Validate hardware and platform features and track the enabling status of those features in silicon, low-level firmware/software, OS (e.g. Windows… https://t.co/8KkEtOv2wJ https://t.co/mJPrzZtpiy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Festival of the Impossible, Artists Augment Reality to Tell Fresh Stories: Getting trippy with storytelling at Festival of the Impossible, an AR and VR showcase currently showing in San Francisco. https://t.co/hi5SZsQHCM https://t.co/eDgR3tWowm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple warns suppliers that iPhone demand is falling https://t.co/MHFnP71a15 https://t.co/tQPRANA6Fi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Solution/Application Architect Manager – Consumer Mark: Employer/LOS Overview Employer is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify… https://t.co/VvF9oR8psn https://t.co/NjUKPL2ATK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Automation Test Engineer: Centaurus Technology Partners, LLC Irving, TX Centaurus Technology Partners, LLC. has multiple openings for the following positions to work in Irving, TX and/or various client sites throughout the U.S. Must be… https://t.co/WJQzjTA3oK https://t.co/tpZgaNYx6M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gadget Lab Podcast: Apple's WWDC Was About Using iPhone Less, and Also More: If you went into Apple's annual developers conference thinking it would be about performance, stability, and Animoji—and not new MacBook Pros—you were totally right. https://t.co/MGycagCsEv https://t.co/o2T309v4Fn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Security Engineer: Responsibilities include: Carrier-grade network and security architecture and design. Experienced in Implementation and ongoing operations of both network, security, and application delivery technologies. Customer Support in… https://t.co/lt87Eo5AyV https://t.co/JVCAunU7BU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C#/C++ WPF Developer: Irvine Technology Corporation (ITC) is a leading provider of technology and staffing solutions for IT, Security, Engineering, and Interactive Design disciplines servicing startups to enterprise clients, nationally. We pride… https://t.co/Nk84Rxm629]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Watch the 2018 FIFA World Cup: Streaming services, match schedules, and more for the 2018 FIFA World Cup. https://t.co/WtDFILS1X8 https://t.co/CZhDrkzk6B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Chips From AMD, Intel, and Qualcomm Make PCs Exciting Again: All-day battery. Universal connectivity. A 32-core monster CPU. PCs are about to transform, and it's about time. https://t.co/MK2jsHkJA5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump administration won't back key parts of Affordable Care Act: The Trump administration won't defend central provisions of the Affordable Care Act, saying in a legal filing Thursday night that key provisions of the Affordable Care Act should be… https://t.co/GljGJBFi4l https://t.co/G3jyJndXD9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jr level .NET Developer: Jr level .NET Developer in Norfolk, VA | CACI International – Small Business | – Suppliers – About Us – | – What We Do – | – Media &amp; Events – | – Investors – | – Careers – | – Contracts – | – Contact Us Join Our Talent Network –… https://t.co/1hlMATIv1y https://t.co/rbMRc1EpJ5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java-Developer: Java Developer Populus Group seeks a Java Developer in Columbus, OH to design, develop, test, and maintain enterprise software applications for the financial industry utilizing object oriented design, Java, GitHub, Maven, Jenkins, JSON,… https://t.co/2MqTTcRst1 https://t.co/XtRjY3LFph]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump is dressed as a king on the new Time magazine cover https://t.co/rRxJrZXKLX https://t.co/fxzXXWAIAz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump: Kim summit more than 'photo-op': President Donald Trump said Thursday his upcoming talks with North Korean leader Kim Jong Un will amount to more than just a good picture. https://t.co/ch59DOFCPb https://t.co/oQxff8UM0u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon Fire TV Cube: Details, Price, Release Date: Alexa knows: it's hip to be square. https://t.co/DhTN90vlTZ https://t.co/LYfpu5tHoG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer in Test: Department Development – US Employment Type Employee Minimum Experience Mid-level Software Developer in Test About us INVIDI Technologies Corporation develops products and services for addressable television advertising. Our… https://t.co/UGgegQ3xL1 https://t.co/HzG4JspTre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yuba Electric Boda Boda Review: An E-Bike for Parents: It's as easy and convenient to ride the electric Yuba Boda Boda as it is to drive a car. https://t.co/df1kSr5SJu https://t.co/OVGF1TEBPK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Android Software Developer: ANDROID SOFTWARE ENGINEER Stafford, Springfield, Centreville, VA *US Citizenship required due to federal government requirement* Join Employer as an embedded software developer specializing in emergent Android technologies… https://t.co/kjKb0jrpHe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Program Manager PMP SAP: Prestigious Professional Services Firm is currently seeking a Program Manager that preferably has experience leading SAP/ERP implementation programs. Candidate will lead highly complex projects and programs delivering to the… https://t.co/COhzelEDjc https://t.co/zxVmIXWfP7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cleveland: 'It's not that bad, have a beer!': Walk into most Cleveland sports bars and you'll see shirts boasting "We're not Detroit!" and "Cleveland: It's not that bad, have a beer!" https://t.co/Y2C0AcB8Cu https://t.co/wNq2mmEQdY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sonos Beam Soundbar: Price, Details, Release Date: The latest smart speaker from Sonos plays music and works as a soundbar for your TV. It also lets you control your smart home with your voice. https://t.co/bMyANP51QT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Johnson deserves a second chance, White House says https://t.co/5kEUf54I9o https://t.co/7KTpScmJ6S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Build and Release Engineer (DevOps)Bethesda MD: * Support Continuous Integration (CI) / Continuous Deployment (CD) and DevOps transformation initiatives under the guidance of the configuration manager/architect. * Contribute in developing best practices… https://t.co/9gTFeZ1JT0 https://t.co/0sm8i7BZ3p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Motorola Moto Z3 Play: Price, Specs, Release Date, Mods: Motorola's modular dreams are alive and well with the latest Z series phone. https://t.co/hlUbEMraTI https://t.co/28TIvyIkZw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Operations Support Analyst – MSP: Location: Minneapolis, Minnesota Job type: Permanent Sector: Quality Control &amp; Assurance Category: Analyst Jobs Job Purpose The Technical Operations Support (TOPS) Analyst is responsible to the Manager of… https://t.co/IubCejKYiw https://t.co/4Qoj2omCEa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[External Manufacturing IT Business Analyst: Requisition Number 4332BR External Posting Title External Manufacturing IT Business Analyst Time Type Full time Pay Rate Type Salary Non-Exempt Work Shift Regular – Salaried Country United States Locations San… https://t.co/BoaFvEmU7o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It may take days before all the votes are tallied in some races, but Gavin Newsom and John Cox will face off in California's governor's race in November: Polls are now closed in all eight states holding primary elections Tuesday, and all eyes are on… https://t.co/7ygn59mBvE https://t.co/mO1aOgNFpJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator – Virtual and Remote Access Services – TS/SCI with Polygraph: – Maintains network security and ensures compliance with security policies and procedures – Evaluates hardware and software, including peripheral, output, and related… https://t.co/klN1UjxBtc https://t.co/taDwjtGA2F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Manager, Financial Planning &amp; Analysis: Senior Manager, Financial Planning &amp; Analysis at Endurance International Group (View all jobs) Burlington, MA About Us Our firm, a leading provider of online solutions to small and medium-sized businesses,… https://t.co/Y04Bc6Eiv5 https://t.co/iUccLRbGFa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embedded Systems Engineer, Mid: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Herndon, VA Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 5/27/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management… https://t.co/Fglzz1ZZX7 https://t.co/PO0JRBOztR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software DevOps Solutions Engineer: Careers Center | Software &amp; DevOps Solutions Engineer Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for… https://t.co/Gmj2qiXT2U https://t.co/Z73ogVmHyS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sarah Sanders: I'm an honest person: White House press secretary Sarah Sanders refused to correct her August statement that President Donald Trump wasn't involved in drafting a misleading statement about his son's meeting with a Russian lawyer at Trump… https://t.co/pVc2sXoATI https://t.co/CjiUz73XrL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP TECHNICAL ARCHITECT: KMG Chemicals, Inc. seeks SAP Technical Architect in Fort Worth, Tx. to develop database architectures and designs for the delivery and support of global ERP systems. 10% domestic travel to other company locations required. Mail… https://t.co/FWyqprk9Wu https://t.co/Fw6n6SFAuu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer: SOFTWARE Rootstock Software in San Ramon, CA seeks Senior Software Developer. Define &amp; present proj plans, schedules &amp; deliverables to relevant parties, including mgmt &amp; proj teams. Reqs incl MS and frgn equiv in Comp Apps,… https://t.co/ViXHQ9UpPe https://t.co/clCZO6MhzZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Company Description MRO Built is a leader in the development, manufacturing and installation of high-quality store fixtures and millwork. Founded in 1976 MRO Built has been a trusted partner for many of the nations best retailers and… https://t.co/MLlJcrNLkM https://t.co/NiHPcH6BQ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WWDC 2018: Apple's Software Chief Details How iOS Apps Will Run on Macs: In an exclusive interview, Apple's Craig Federighi explains how developers will be able to get their iOS apps working on Macs. https://t.co/D7cNvITn8l https://t.co/4lOI8wCmzY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer V: Software Engineer V, Web Development The candidate will be instrumental in designing and implementing a web application to interface with an existing server, working directly with the Product Owner to produce required features and… https://t.co/524QmSYt7h https://t.co/YXExkU3TAb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boosted Mini S Review: Pure Joy: It won't replace your car, but Boosted's entry-level board might be what you've been waiting for. https://t.co/P1Ns11Xr40 https://t.co/pTvbWEBjfh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Functional Analyst, SAP FICO: Job Summary The SAP FICO Analyst is responsible to develop solutions, support production applications and review new applications. This position will leverage SAP to support best practices with proven understanding of… https://t.co/l56xmWcA6L https://t.co/yAdHzxRzyi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, Sr: Software Engineer, Sr Skip Navigation Fiserv Menu – Solutions – Industries – About – Careers – Where you fit in – Technology – Accounting &amp; Finance – Contact Center – U.S. Locations – Alpharetta – Brookfield – Dallas/Ft. Worth –… https://t.co/bkAEsE0Bwk https://t.co/csgH0ie7ot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9 times Sarah Sanders said Trump 'hasn't done anything wrong' https://t.co/ZQ8wxNfylb https://t.co/yOUg0ozEDL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer: Engineer: MaxLinear, Inc., a leader in highly integrated RF analog and mixed-signal semiconductor solutions, has the following degreed/experienced position available in Irvine, CA: Systems Applications Engineer. To apply, mail resume to:… https://t.co/u9g2Ns89O7 https://t.co/cr9k2F05yE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Compliance Operations Analyst: VMware, Inc. has multiple openings at various professional levels in Austin, TX. The following software engineering positions develop and/or execute software, testing and validation procedures, programming and… https://t.co/UwPQmUnDqI https://t.co/Y9XXkZO84y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[North Korea shakes up military leadership: North Korea's top three military officials have been replaced ahead of an historic summit between leader Kim Jong Un and US President Donald Trump, according to multiple reports. https://t.co/gpo7hcjaNb https://t.co/LG3X7NvrCL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Netsuite Implementor: Netsuite Implementor Base $110,000 to $125 Base plus Bonus Total 8 plus years of experience in Cloud-based accounting solution implementations. * Must have consultant experience and knowledge of end to end NetSuite implementations,… https://t.co/dl1LBdVfCP https://t.co/3Ehv2GSffN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, Tools and Infrastructure: At Periscope Data, engineers work the whole stack – from shipping UI to optimizing the billions of rows in the data cache.  As a Software Engineer, Tools and Infrastructure, you will build and enhance internal… https://t.co/c6cWA4ip7X https://t.co/H5GQ1TkZko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Five deaths, 197 illnesses in ongoing E. coli outbreak: An additional 25 people have become ill from eating lettuce contaminated with E. coli, the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention reported Friday. https://t.co/az3z9fcxof https://t.co/mEZHU8CKiX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WWDC 2018 Liveblog: News and Updates From Apple's Keynote: Join us for live coverage of Apple's WWDC 2018 keynote at 9 am PDT on Monday, June 4. https://t.co/t44XILEnhs https://t.co/mHRpsuIdFp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer Mid Career C#, C++, or Java TS/SCI in Herndon, VA: Req ID : 423810BR Job Code/Title : E1073:Software Engineer Sr Job Description : Looking for a career with purpose? One that challenges your mind, grows your skills and contributes to… https://t.co/2mXK2t02Eh https://t.co/eE30ydHkvk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: SharePoint Developer ==================== Req #: ******Location: Alexandria, VA USJob Category: Information TechnologySecurity Clearance: SecretClearance Status: Must Be Current Job Description Responsibilities: * Helps to develop… https://t.co/cEPlhBxP5h https://t.co/yenTHVuGGQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Systems Engineer/Programmer: Principal Systems Engineer/Programmer-&gt;&gt; Serves as subject matter expert in leading the design and development of the most complex application problems, system administration issues, or network concerns. Performs… https://t.co/EuBLeqMGQI https://t.co/ctaj7Vgdn3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP ABAP SD LEAD: SAP ABAP SD LEAD Ref No.: 18-01326 Location: Chicago, Illinois Position Type: Direct Placement Start Date: 05/25/2018 Hi, Hope you are doing great!!! Our records show that you are an IT professional with experience in the required… https://t.co/PF8cQhPO3J https://t.co/hiB1MDIwTT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Full Stack Software Engineer: Senior Full Stack Software Engineer-16460 Position Description The Johns Hopkins University Applied Physics Laboratory (APL), a national leader in scientific research and development, is located midway between… https://t.co/6b2EYZum1A https://t.co/MWOmIIr7Ra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WWDC 2018: How to Watch Apple's Keynote on Monday, June 4: On Monday, Apple will lift the lid on its Worldwide Developers Conference. Here's how to tune in. https://t.co/MsPNXEg8Vg https://t.co/mLeVWT19Dn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Manager, Data Science: Description Hi. We’re TiVo. At our core, we’re innovators who continuously seek to fuel the ultimate entertainment experience. We touch the lives of binge-watching, music-loving, entertainment fanatics every day by inventing… https://t.co/kKJLJ5yyOL https://t.co/0s8y8jLncz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Informatica Developer: Informatica Developer Ref No.: 18-21261 Location: Mt Laurel,, New Jersey Position: Informatica Developer Location: Mt Laurel, NJ Duration: 12 Months 1) 6 + years of core experience working in informatica ETL tool. 2) Ability for… https://t.co/yqHH6dtqD8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instructional Developer: Instructional Developer Create a Profile|Log In Yes No Show Details At least one job must be selected in order to apply. Terms of use Add to Saved Jobs Back Position Details Req ID: req4917 Position Title: Instructional Developer… https://t.co/N1siZUZoza https://t.co/CPhEbSXb2D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Big Bang' star on Roseanne: Why? How?: In a candid interview, CNN's Van Jones asks "Big Bang Theory" star Jim Parsons if Roseanne Barr went too far with her tweets. https://t.co/9BYiKOVyDX https://t.co/UA8vqNeo7h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager II: Project Manager II Tracking Code 4696-244 Job Description At Gilbane we’re building more than buildings, we’re helping create schools, hospitals, laboratories and other facilities across the United States and throughout the world that… https://t.co/sHDXJzRgN3 https://t.co/VoSrEMhxvS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Islands to take your breath away: Captain Tho Pham first went out to sea when he was 14 years old. Now, he's been a junk skipper in Halong Bay for more than a decade. https://t.co/mPN5xq7MIL https://t.co/suikGjKIlh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trudeau: Retaliation against US a must: Canadian Prime Minister Justin Trudeau said Canada regrets that retaliatory action is necessary against the US for President Trump's tariff decision against the EU, Mexico and Canada. https://t.co/prouZ1SV29 https://t.co/4FkGraFI5g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior Software Engineer: Junior Software Engineer at Teachers’ Curriculum Institute (TCI) Teachers’ Curriculum Institute (TCI) Junior Software Engineer Mountain View, California, United States Full-time Our Product: We deliver innovative content to more… https://t.co/FnAyOGx1Dk https://t.co/slWXHsSozH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Management Specialist: Xator is hiring! The Database Management Specialist is responsible for maintaining and updating repositories of documentation generated by multiple participants in complex, multi-project acquisition programs. Design,… https://t.co/n57HCsbBFz https://t.co/ElB3UIS2jz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Pose' spotlights LGBT talent: With a cast that features an unprecedented number of transgender performers, "Pose" makes a bold statement about inclusion. But this latest FX drama from producer Ryan Murphy finds familiar themes within its look back at… https://t.co/vFdnKpUjtc https://t.co/s633JD4wA1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior .NET Developer Intern: Job/Internship Description Junior .NET Developer Intern ABB is a pioneering technology leader that works closely with utility, industry, transportation and infrastructure customers to write the future of industrial… https://t.co/nACwmNJNAL https://t.co/gp5Tc4PLg9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[# ColdFusion developer w Java Cherry Hill, NJ: TITILE: Senior ColdFusion Developer Type: Contract Duration: 6+ Months Location: Cherry Hill, NJ Key Skills: ColdFusion with Java backend Requirements * BS in Computer Science or related field of study. * 6… https://t.co/hkvsX4evYH https://t.co/W2uBr1Rr0m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chief Information Security Officer: Grand County Information Systems Chief Information Security Officer Full time, full benefits position. Minimum rate $83,633. This company is an equal opportunity employer to all, regardless of age, ancestry, color,… https://t.co/OEl3Em7Z49 https://t.co/ibOqwebrgW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2018's Best CD's https://t.co/rOcItfALIT https://t.co/fNep4i8O06]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer II – Reference: 2018-44026: Reference: 2018-44026 Engineer II-Software Test sought by DISH Network, LLC in Englewood, CO. Design, implement &amp; manage the manual, automated &amp; performance software tests; contribute to the manual functional testing… https://t.co/wsbgxBH9jT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Samsonite CEO quits after doctorate drama https://t.co/LDiM4Z7SF1 https://t.co/XLxOs33az1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front-End Developer (React): At Expero, we build complex, reactive web applications for expert users: scientists, traders, engineers. If you enjoy lighting up a screen with an intricate 3D geologic scene, a carefully constructed portfolio of trades, or a… https://t.co/Be1R9wF6vI https://t.co/XJGXzIgtLW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Engineer Hardware Architect: Req ID : 422275BR Job Code/Title : E1464:Systems Engineer Stf Job Description : This position support the SBIRS program System Engineering team with an emphasis on hardware system architecture. The ideal candidate… https://t.co/IDSb21il9W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist, Junior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Lexington Park, MD Job Type: Entry Level, Science Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 5/8/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest… https://t.co/DRzXGurIpS https://t.co/qGBxQXIyE3]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>