<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is a dream that comes alive when we meet ~Unknown via @ZnaTrainer #love #life #friends #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If people #believe in themselves, it's amazing what they can accomplish." - Sam Walton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The brave man is not he who does not feel afraid, but he who  #conquers that fear. ~ Nelson Mandela]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take an opportunity to run in new locations. We can all be explorers #runningtip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not all runs require a garmin and music. Sometimes it needs to be you and the ground #runningtip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest danger for most of us is not that we aim too high & miss it, but we aim too low & reach it. ~Michelangelo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Respect the #distance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Never give up on your #dreams. Remember that sometimes, you may need to put those dreams on hold, but never give up!” via @CrusePhoto]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In the first half of the race, don't be an idiot. In the second half, don't be a wimp." via @runnersworld  #truth #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Some people care too much, I think it's called love." - Winnie the Pooh #quote - via @bccf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After climbing a great hill, one only finds that there are many more #hills to climb. ~ Nelson Mandela]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It always seems impossible until it's done" Nelson Mandela #marathon #run #ironman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The only place where your dream becomes impossible is in your own thinking." ~ Robert H. Schuller #love #run via @nuggetsoflove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["U can either advance boldly in the direction of UR dreams, or retreat fearfully in2 the safety of the habitual" ~ Cortes via @nuggetsoflove]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time isn't always on your side, #love now, love often; don't let love pass you by. via @DrAndyBaldwin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people sit back and let others act and do. It just gives us doers an opportunity to really #live]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Running is a balance of physical exertion, enhanced mental awareness and spiritual peace via @JeffGalloway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Dead last finish is greater than did not finish which greatly trumps did not start" - Running shirt at #SBMarathon via @LJ3000]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The best way to gain self-confidence is to do what you are afraid to do." ~Unknown via @RickRunNRide]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't believe people are looking for the meaning of  #life as much as they are looking for the experience of being alive. ~Joseph Campbell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A hero is someone who has given his or her life to something bigger than oneself. ~Joseph Campbell #charity #runners]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Passion is the genesis of genius." Tony Robbins  #run #live]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#run #friends #support #laughs #nature #freedom #awesome]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Eventually you learn that the competition is against the little voice inside you that wants you to quit." Sheehan #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Run with passion, live with passion, and feel with passion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#It's very hard in the beginning to understand that the whole idea is not to beat the other #runners." Sheehan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Listen to your body. Do not be a blind and deaf tenant." - Dr. George Sheehan #running]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I'm always doing things I can't do. That's how I get to do them." ~Pablo Picasso #run #distance #challenge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The man who can drive himself further once the effort gets painful is the man who will win. ~Roger Bannister #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people follow their #dreams, others hunt them down & beat them mercilessly into submission~ Kendall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Running should be a relationship status. #RunNerds via @runaddicted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Life (and #running) is not all about time but about our experiences along the way."-Jen Rhines]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hated every minute of training, but I said 'don’t quit, suffer now & live the rest of ur life as a champion.' Muhammad Ali (via @thequote)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To enhance your well being expand your network of #happy friends via @deepakchopra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Friends don't let friends think negatively." via @AffirmationSpot  #truth #friends #support #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I plan 2run that race so hard I won't want 2think about racing for at least 48 hours."-L. Thorvilson on 2012 Marathon Trials via @RunToWin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our truest life is when we are in dreams awake. ~Thoreau #dreams #life #chances]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In #dreams and in #love there are no impossibilities."
- Janos Arany]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There is no reason your challenging pace of the present cannot be your comfortable pace of the future." -@Run2SaveLives]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The #heart has it's reasons that reason does not know."
- Pascal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What's meant to be will always find a way."- Trisha Yearwood #dream #don't #give #up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing will ever be attempted if all  #possible objections must first be overcome. ~Samuel Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["This 26.2 is for all the girls picked last in gym class" #Marathon Shirt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #positive thinker sees the invisible, feels the intangible, and achieves the impossible. - Unknown via @AffirmationSpot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Never settle for the #dream you think you can reach. Settle on the dream you want.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Positive thinking is a decision, it's a momentum, it's a vibration. via @AffirmationSpot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When we do the #impossible we realize we are special people." via @kcancer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Don't settle for mediocrity when you can have #greatness" unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thrive off of this workload. I simply adore the exhaustion that comes with training hard. -- Deena Kastor via @runtowin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And those who were seen dancing were thought to be insane by those who could not hear the #music - Nietzsche via @TheTrailJogger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The best #runs sometimes come on days when you didn't feel like running." ~anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If one could #run without getting tired, I don't think one would often want to do anything else." C.S. Lewis via @FitChickNYC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Passion is pushing myself when there is no one else around, just me & the road. -Ryan Shay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You must risk to achieve. So, I risk. I choose not to sit on the sideline." - Dr. Lisa Kelly 9/8/11 @TriLisaKay via @LJ3000]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There are people who #live their whole lives on the default settings, never realizing you can customize." R. Brault via @CharityIdeas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Life has got to be #lived. That's all there is to it." - Eleanor Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We all have #ability. The difference is how we use it." -Stevie Wonder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I believe that one of life's greatest risks is never daring to #risk. ~ Oprah Winfrey via @iheartquotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Find your love, your talents, your  #passions and embrace it. Don't hide behind happiness. Experience it!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Challenges are #gifts that force us 2 search 4 a new center of gravity. Don’t fight them. Find a different way 2 stand ~@Oprah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#run, gather your friends, and make a difference together #runners #giveback]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Relish the bad  #training runs. Without them it's difficult to recognize, much less appreciate, the good ones."~Pat Teske]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surround yourself with #positive via @Kcancer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's more to a #race than being faster than last time.” via @nuuutymel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No extra points for #running fast on easy days! Save energy for hard workouts. via @runnersworld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Limits are most often all in your head." - Gary Allen #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["But then you find your inner strength, and realize you're capable of so much more than you thought." -Arthur Blank #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Your present circumstances don't determine where you can go; they merely determine where you start." Nido Qubein via @paulrak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A #race time is just the final page of a book. It means very little without knowing the story leading up to it. #running via @runwicked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Friends who believe in you when others do not, friends who tell you can do it when you fear otherwise, friends are a gift" #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Mental toughness is to #physical as four is to one."~Bobby Knight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a powerful driving force inside every human being that once unleashed, can make any #vision, dream or desire a reality~Tony Robbins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Life is meant to be lived. Take risks. Feel passion. Discover love. Run free.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Doubters can suck it" (saw this at mile 23 -- definitely  #inspired me!!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Somebody who's got nothing to lose can be very, very dangerous." via @Maccanow #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hold fast to #dreams, for if dreams die, life is a broken winged bird that cannot fly - Langston Hughes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You don't stop #running b/c you get old. You get old b/c you stop running." -Jack Kirk, the Dipsea Demon #BornToRun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life has so many roads, why do you limit yourself to just one” via @poetjanetdawson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There are many wonderful things that will never be done if you do not do them." ~ Charles D. Gill via @AffirmationSpot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The biggest adventure you can ever take is to live the #life of your dreams." - Oprah Winfrey #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Don't let your victories go to your head, or your failures go to your #heart." -Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Who runs for #pleasure never gets tired" Dean Karnazes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Passion cannot be instilled; it is either there or it is not" Joan Benoit Samuelson via @LJ3000]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When u're breaking down w/ur insides coming out, that's when u find out what ur heart's made of -Switchfoot (via @Tiffanywilliam)  #marathon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The biggest temptation is to settle for far too little - Thomas Merton #life #love #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["May you live every day of your #life." - Jonathan Swift]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forgive, run, love, run, laugh, run, impossible, run, imaginable, run, unimaginable, #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Life is short, surround yourself with #people who care” via @Lotay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You have to balance reason with passion; reason keeps you open, passion keeps your adrenaline going.” -Unknown (via @MizzSocial)  #running]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There R those days when it's hard 2put 1foot in front of the other,but those R the days when champions R created" McNally]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever tried. Ever failed. No matter. Try again. Fail again. Fail better - Samuel Beckett via @CharityIdeas #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lack of dreaming, a lack of the possibilities, a lack of passion. And I didn't want to live without passion - H. Hefner #live #dream]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our passions are the winds that propel our vessel. – Proverbs #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Passion is the element in which we live; without it, we hardly vegetate.  – Lord Bryron]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One person with #passion is better than forty people merely interested. 
— E. M. Forster]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In #dreams and in #love there are no impossibilities."  Janos Arnay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The tragedy of #life is not that it ends so soon, but that we wait so long to begin it - Anon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anything's #possible if you've got enough nerve. via @Kcancer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never stop appreciating the gifts you are given. Nothing, no friend ever taken for granted #thankful #friends #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There lives in each of us a hero awaiting the call to action. - H. Jackson Brown Jr. #charity #runners]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>