<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Today the world lost a comic genius. An entertainer extraordinaire. So tragic &amp; too soon. You will be greatly missed! RIP @robinwilliams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So sad to hear of the sudden &amp; tragic death of @robinwilliams today. It was an honor to meet you &amp; be in your presence. RIP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I win a #BPPizzaParty I’d want an adult size bouncy castle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2014 #FIFA #worldcup and wild salmon donburi lunch while waiting for clients http://t.co/D59X5lPbCT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FairmontVan it's not bad so far. Lets hope the rain stays away! And you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#bmw #i8 #hybrid #supercar @ the #fairmont #pacrim in #Vancouver http://t.co/Y8CTFAnEGj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Canada Day! http://t.co/rnbTNv8qWG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coorslightca thanks! Do I keep the box? Haha http://t.co/th75csdz8m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coorslightca found one! Code: CF97MY #searchandrescue http://t.co/eOWQJtquQP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coorslightca really? You keep tweeting it starts at 12am July 1st. Oh well, should have tweeted it when I found it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@coorslightca when does the mission start on the west coast PST?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[everywhere, is anywhere, is anything, is everything - Douglas Coupland 2014 #VAG #Vancouver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gumhead - Douglas Coupland exhibit 2014 #Vancouver #VAG http://t.co/fXhyyUGGbW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey boo boo! Caught this guy sleeping in the woods #grizzlybear #vancouver #mybackyard http://t.co/QRAoVeTV7Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's road trip: Vancouver, BC - Portland, OR - Vancouver, BC #supercharging the #Tesla #ModelS in… http://t.co/GPpRUMnOQS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back at the gym after almost a month off. Feels good both physically &amp; mentally. No more procrastination. I need this #onwards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't believe that anybody feels the way I do, about u now. Because maybe ur gonna be the one that saves me &amp; after all, ur my wonderwall.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A great day for another afternoon ride around #StanleyPark #vancouver http://t.co/dslST5rW6I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Driving this bad boy today #TeslaS #electric calemazoo website on the main screen #itsabouttime #whistler http://t.co/9MW0fqtWyL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Square #watermelons made in #Taiwan sold in #Canada for only $79.99 😳! http://t.co/hd8c2vMCZt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The positive thinker sees the invisible, feels the intangible and achieves the impossible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BC Glaciers melting at a rate of 22Bil cubic metres (8.8MM #Olympic size swimming pools of water) /year #climatechange]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My favorite pulled pork sandwich @eathubbub shop on Hornby is opening soon #hubbubrobson #yummy #good http://t.co/2JVnKXSJpM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's not what you are that holds you back, it's what you think you are not."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All men die, but not all men live]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ran 10km after work yesterday and feeling it today. #feelingold #hurting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JimmysTaphouse #beer store may offer cold beer but it's the biggest #ripoff in #VANCity #Vancouver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can choose what you want to be but not who you are. Stay true to yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @funnyortruth: http://t.co/i3QP0cwUH8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Calemazoo: "The first 20 years of the web were won by those that built the best infrastructure. Now it's won by those that build the be…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lilly Wood &amp; The Prick and Robin Schulz - Prayer In C (Robin Schulz Remi...: http://t.co/xZ6UmAPgWh via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I say give away, I mean form a foundation and quietly do some good for those less fortunate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#RIPCorporalNathanCirillo #RIP #seargentatarms Kevin Vickers is a #HERO and the gunman, a coward, a… http://t.co/i8rFZm0IHR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Calemazoo: Calemazoo will connect the world for a more efficient and greater good #nextbigthing #socialmedia #Vancouver #iOS #android #…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Losing love is like a window in your heart. Everybody sees you're blown apart. Everybody sees the wind blow." - Paul Simon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I commit to give away 90% of the first $1B I make.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Confirmed over thinker.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need a vacation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I give thanks for my family and loved ones, safe travels, health, opportunities, water, food and fresh air. Happy Thanksgiving!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This one is around 24inches across or 2ft (60cm) giant sunflower in Chilliwack BC http://t.co/P5VBbuY0I2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Giant sunflowers! ~8ft tall like young trees, these flowers are about 16 inches diameter #chilliwack #bc http://t.co/cd6fH1d6Rs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Missing my beloved dearly!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just back from @HarvestHaus feeling comfortably numb.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["He who believes he can and he who believes he cannot are both correct." - Henry Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We must dare to be great; and we must realize that greatness is the fruit of toil, sacrifice and high courage..." Teddy Rooselvelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel so close to you right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 days and 1 night to put that application together. Fingers crossed we are chosen! #whynofingerscrossedemoji]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great song @NappyRoots ! We are gonna have a good day. http://t.co/jPVYq0F5f3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Held the new #apple #iPhone6 and #6plus today #gladididit #thingofbeauty. Plus feels too big. 6 is #perfection]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feelings are fleeting &amp; on the surface. Emotions are primal &amp; cut to ones core. Hurt my feelings but don't play with my emotions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Vancouver #sunset #peaceful #tranquil #inspirational #myhome #beautifulBC http://t.co/CiTFgh0zeN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another gorgeous #Vancouver sunset #bestplaceonearth #myhome #sunset #endlesssummer http://t.co/CS9fYifTPZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Batton down the hatches, stay dry and hold on my #Philippines #friends. My prayers are with you! #safetravels #typhoon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What the mind thinks the body follows" - Keith, #ANTM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I lay with you, I could stay there, close my eyes, feel you here forever.  You and me together, nothing gets better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DalaiLama: Affection, a sense of community and a sense of concern for others are not some kind of luxury. They’re about the survival of…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sick and tired]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who are certain about an outcome can afford to wait]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Do or do not. There is no try" - Master Yoda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay I'll stop now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever wondered how tall you would be if you were 800 years old? Look up, way up! #cathedralgrove #bc… http://t.co/qLPMBrjOtX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Earlier at @vanchristmas market with this guy #2gluhwein2pilsnerslater #walkinghome #christmas #cheer… http://t.co/O1MP8unbz5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @VanChristmas: @2ChrisSimpson thanks for wonderful support!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VANEATSca if you haven't already you must check out @VanChristmas market! Enjoy a cold beer, hot gluehwein &amp; traditional German foods!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love @VanChristmas! Such a wonderful uplifting experience to see families &amp; diverse nationalities enjoying the market #MerryChristmas #YVR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @StephaneMouttet: Please go to a local book store and purchase a brand new book for a kid who needs one @agoodbookdrive http://t.co/1jPl…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@VanChristmas got my season pass. I'll be back! A yvr holiday tradition @VanObserver @CTVVancouver @VancityBuzz @StephaneMouttet @TeamVBC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @GreyCupFestival this is a no brainer! #Beer and #German #bratwurst @VanChristmas @calstampeders @Ticats http://t.co/WiHGkS4AZg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So happy to see @VanChristmas market is back! If you haven't already, its a must visit this holiday season.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BCFerries fair enough. Thanks for the reassurance. Safe travels and all the best over the holidays!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BCFerries I expect &amp; trust you do however rust is everywhere &amp; painting over it is not fixing it. Built in '76 it's a matter of time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[High winds &amp; a rocky journey, Nanaimo to Horseshoe bay @BCFerries Queen of Rust (Cowichan) doesn't look or feel safe http://t.co/t2iu3NTXOR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just enjoyed an outstanding chèvre salad w wild salmon &amp; a late night sleeve of @TofinoBrewCo @foodwineshelter Thanks ladies!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gonna make you beg for it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last minute trip to Tofino. What a treacherous drive! Pitch black, heavy rain and fog. Thank God for safe travels.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 out of 3 elevators down, ~400 residents, 27th flr, it looks like no gym, no groceries, a bootstrapped dinner and homework tonight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just in time, as they say.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One potato, two potato]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd forgotten how dark it gets so early]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back home to miserable weather]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goodbye #Canmore #Alberta thanks for being so beautiful in nature! You have certainly grown up since we last met.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stay strong &amp; remember why it didn't work out 1st time. Stay true to yourself &amp; don't settle for less than what makes you happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DalaiLama: If you make others happy, you’ll be happy. If you make others unhappy, you’ll be miserable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time is short for those who need it but for those who love it has no limits]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Work hard in silence and let success be your noise!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OfficialJACKEL congrats! All the best for the future. Stay passionate, be persistent, have patience and you will succeed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The life of an entrepreneur. Thank goodness for good friends and family.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Real friends seem few and far between]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I barely interact with people other than for work, supplies and family.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love it when a plan comes together!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #1 #Top100DJs and a future Prime Minister of #Canada in the same day. Nice!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only in #Canada eh? Criminal uses a canoe to try to escape #Halifax #police. http://t.co/BpIQnYJyJz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JustinTrudeau: 841,000 Canadians needed food banks last year to feed themselves and their families. As a country, we can and must do mo…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Calemazoo: Canada Remembers #remembranceday #canada #freedom #veterans http://t.co/IMnXLpN7yR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#VeteransDay gives thanks only to survivors? #RemembranceDay gives thanks to the #veterans plus all the fallen #soldiers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go Hardwell or Go Home #Vancouver #IAmHardwell http://t.co/f139pFANKH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@flyawaywords likewise thank you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When u look up at the night sky, know that u are part of the universe, u are in the universe and most important the universe is in u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Swift, Silent, Deadly.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>