<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Home Party Shows http://tinyurl.com/ckcybv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've just published "DIY- Make a Candle!..." on #bukisa http://cli.gs/U8Q7hz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Handicraft Center: Kpg Ensebang http://dayaknation.com/blog/?p=191]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful Russian handicraft http://tinyurl.com/cww3vp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting Norcastle Round End Table http://tinyurl.com/c2jmpn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing Handicraft And Handloom of India http://tinyurl.com/deffug]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting...... How is a Wax Sculpture Made in Home? http://tinyurl.com/cfmtst]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've just published "Top 5 Eco-Friendly Ways to Wrap Gifts..." on #bukisa http://cli.gs/hWGHEp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exclusive: Devo’s Jerry Casale on Dome Hats and McDonald http://tinyurl.com/dmohon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hats on Stock Certificates http://tinyurl.com/ctbatw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back to The Future II Hats are Available http://tinyurl.com/chhwfu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Swanki Hats GUEST GIVEAWAY!!!! http://tinyurl.com/caa2ts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whats and Hows of Scrapbooking? http://www.craftcentral.com/articles/2009/04/whats-and-hows-of-scrapbooking.html]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've just published "How to Choose the Right Necktie?..." on #bukisa http://cli.gs/4gL57W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Antique Lamps – Treen, Fine, Dark and Handsome http://buyandsellinspain.com/blog/?p=79]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unique Outdoor Antique Lighting Fixtures http://www.beautifulhomeguide.info/lighting/unique-outdoor-antique-lighting-fixtures/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Antique Lighting Collection http://about-antiques.org/antique-lighting-collection.html]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want To Decorate Your Kitchen In Country Style http://hintsandtips4.me/?p=309]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is Blacksmithing http://tinyurl.com/dn44g7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2009 Top Trends for Playing Toys http://tinyurl.com/dls6bk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Soccer Keychains http://tinyurl.com/d34rh3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Retro NES game cartridge keychains http://tinyurl.com/dhgwab]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keychain for my HP http://tinyurl.com/cjqy27]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marvel Keychains and Magnets! http://tinyurl.com/dfs8ob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've just published "Handmade Paper - Do It Yourself..." on #bukisa http://cli.gs/0HQYSH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've just published "Top Tips for Trade Show Booth Display..." on #bukisa http://cli.gs/gmEJDe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Collection of Faucets http://tinyurl.com/cwxyyb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow.... Collection of Whirlpool Bathtubs  http://tinyurl.com/d87fb3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crazy Dinosaur Card Making Ideas http://tinyurl.com/ckpd3w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Make Your Custom Greeting Cards Extra Special http://tinyurl.com/c8b2kk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Creating Printable Photo Greeting Cards http://tinyurl.com/dypmok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wise Up Greeting Cards http://tinyurl.com/dk5c8f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Printable Easter Greeting Cards  http://tinyurl.com/dcj5h7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Student Air Travel Tips: If you happen to be under 26, or are booking and paying for flights for someone in this.. http://tinyurl.com/cuvzyd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Health Care Industry Moves Slowly Onto the Internet: The health care industry, a well-known laggard in informati.. http://tinyurl.com/cozx5e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EU: Earth Warming Faster: Global warming is likely to overshoot a 2 degrees Celsius (3.6 F) rise seen by the Eur.. http://tinyurl.com/cgjd85]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Port of Oakland Approves Pollution Reduction Plan: Oakland Port commissioners approved a master plan for reducin.. http://tinyurl.com/c4lgc8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AmericanAirlines Arena Wins Environmental Award: Miami&#8217;s AmericanAirlines Arena is one of two U.S. sports .. http://tinyurl.com/d4y4ro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EarthTalk: Truth Behind Global Warming?: Question: I keep meeting people who say that human- induced global warm.. http://tinyurl.com/d2mjtk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Iraq War Battle Is Remade As A Video Game  http://tinyurl.com/dhxtb3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hall of Fame and Signs of Better Things http://tinyurl.com/czefnn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally, A Video Game That Lets You Use Steroids http://tinyurl.com/cg5cp3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iraq War Video Game: Appropriate? http://tinyurl.com/dylcce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fallujah Video Game Makes Me Conflicted http://tinyurl.com/ckdnar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ecoTools: Earth Friendly Beauty http://www.theshadesofu.com/2009/04/ecotools-earth-friendly-beauty.html]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Most Trusted Summer Beauty Tool http://www.splendicity.com/articles/my-most-trusted-summer-beauty-tool/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fabulous Earth-Friendly Beauty Tools http://tinyurl.com/cmca54]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our Favorite Beauty Tools http://tinyurl.com/dj7wec]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[wow today is sunny day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Origami – Facts a Paper Sculptor Should Know http://www.craftcentral.com/articles/2009/04/acts-a-paper-sculptor.html]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've just published "My Top 5 Essential Bar Accessories..." on #Bukisa http://cli.gs/9dnbs0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aamir Khan To Make Awareness Of Global Warming: Keen to do your bit to save the mother Earth from threats of glo.. http://tinyurl.com/cuzvxr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Select Kitchen Furniture? http://tinyurl.com/d4p9ap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Freight Forwarding Becomes an Environmental Issue: The environmental debate is hitting the global freight forwar.. http://tinyurl.com/n7mtl4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Environmental Issue: Wood Burning Fireplaces: If you plan to move to a new home or to build a home, you may draw.. http://tinyurl.com/mwzr6y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Environmental Issues in India: The environmental issues in India become more serious every day and she is tu.. http://tinyurl.com/loxerk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Overview of the Environmental Issue Petition Process: If you have an environmental issue that you feel needs .. http://tinyurl.com/mhhq7h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Green Earth - No Longer a Dream: &#8220;Kiss of the sun for pardon. Song of the birds for mirth. You&#8217;re cl.. http://tinyurl.com/km2u2u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christmas Decorations and Environmental Issues: Do you have environmental concerns about Christmas tress and con.. http://tinyurl.com/klbelj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cashing in on an Environmental Issue: You&#8217;ve heard the adage that water and oil don&#8217;t mix. But don&#.. http://tinyurl.com/lmcqh8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Environmental Issue: California Wild Fire Goes Up in History: As the Las Padres National Forest in California bu.. http://tinyurl.com/losskh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Easy Way to Recycle Your Computer For Environmental Issue: The IT production industry has a Large Carbon footpri.. http://tinyurl.com/mzd7xe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is The Sky The Limit For Wind Power? High-flying Kites Could Light Up New York: In the future, will wind power t.. http://tinyurl.com/lldrf9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deforestation Causes &#8216;Boom-and-bust&#8217; Development In The Amazon: Clearing the Amazon rainforest incre.. http://tinyurl.com/krtg2c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sediment Yields Climate Record For Past Half-million Years: Researchers here have used sediment from the deep oc.. http://tinyurl.com/kuzxnf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Illegal Trade In Vietnam&#8217;s Marine Turtles Continues Despite National Ban: Marine turtles are vanishing fro.. http://tinyurl.com/mg8v5o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Individuals Who Apply Pesticides Are Found To Have Double The Risk Of Blood Disorder: A study involving 678 indi.. http://tinyurl.com/nfwhns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wildlife Photography Competition 2009: The CIC organised at its recent General Assembly an international competi.. http://tinyurl.com/nyuzyy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Save Wildlife: CIC Took Position in Paris: At the 56th General Assembly of the International Council for Game an.. http://tinyurl.com/kmm95s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hunters for Peace in Central and South Eastern Europe: The International Council for Game and Wildlife Conservat.. http://tinyurl.com/nh7mt8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now Eco Friendly Shrouds Introduced to Reduce Cremation Emissions: Council crematoria have banned families from .. http://tinyurl.com/ly92a7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anemia Associated With Greater Risk Of Death In Heart Disease Patients: A new study appearing in Congestive Hear.. http://tinyurl.com/mlsnvl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gene Responsible For Rare Form Of Congenital Anemia Discovered: The latest electronic edition of the journal Nat.. http://tinyurl.com/lrf6mn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drugs To Combat Anemia In Cancer Patients Increase Risk Of Death, Study Suggests: The use of drugs to encourage .. http://tinyurl.com/lpmrul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anemia Treatment Improves Heart Structure And Quality Of Life In Kidney Disease Patients: In chronic kidney dise.. http://tinyurl.com/lf2nc9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vast Majority Won’t Have Access To Antivirals In Pandemic, But Generic Drugs Could Help Prevent Deaths: Almost 9.. http://tinyurl.com/la77hk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Strategy Proposed For Designing Antibody-based HIV Vaccine: Most vaccines that protect against viruses gener.. http://tinyurl.com/maqu8z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Newborn Weights Affected By Environmental Contaminants: Recent epidemiological studies have revealed an increase.. http://tinyurl.com/lb3ane]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free Download Report of IPCC Expert Meeting: Supporting material consists of published reports and proceedings f.. http://tinyurl.com/klusrk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free Download Report of IPCC Scoping Meeting: Supporting material consists of published reports and proceedings .. http://tinyurl.com/nokcx3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free Download Report of IPCC Analysis of Emissions: Supporting material consists of published reports and procee.. http://tinyurl.com/kmrynl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free Download Report of IPCC New Emission Scenario: Supporting material consists of published reports and procee.. http://tinyurl.com/n8y9x9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free Download Report of IPCC Expert Meeting: Supporting material consists of published reports and proceedings f.. http://tinyurl.com/nmz8te]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Student Air Travel Tips http://ping.fm/K1RPX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Summer Vacation Fun Tips for Kids http://ping.fm/QVFwe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Las Vegas Vacation-tips, Tricks And Cautions http://ping.fm/Jj7RD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting the Right Limousine Service: Tips and Tricks  http://ping.fm/GAgGi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[11 Tips and Tricks for Greening your Hotel Stay  http://ping.fm/8fPwI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[12 Tips and Tricks of Green Business Travel  http://ping.fm/MThA6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hawaii Travel Packages: Tips And Tricks  http://ping.fm/BWaWD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips and Tricks For Planning The Kind Of Trip You Want http://ping.fm/aKX4l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips and Tricks For Planning The Kind Of Trip You Want: So you want to go on a trip, but  need some help plannin.. http://tinyurl.com/mbe8wb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hawaii Travel Packages: Tips And Tricks: If you are thinking about Hawaii travel packages, it is likely that war.. http://tinyurl.com/na7agw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[12 Tips and Tricks of Green Business Travel: Before we quit our jobs to travel to Argentina, I traveled several .. http://tinyurl.com/nbz2rh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[11 Tips and Tricks for Greening your Hotel Stay: Let’s face it, as much as we love camping, hostels, and eco-lod.. http://tinyurl.com/n8xcad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting the Right Limousine Service: Tips and Tricks: Renting a limousine can be tricky. Like other forms of ser.. http://tinyurl.com/m4p285]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Earth Under Fire: How Global Warming is Changing the World: Environmental photojournalist Gary Braasch is interv.. http://tinyurl.com/laloac]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Air Quality Standards to be Reviewed: The Government is to review air standards to see if they are realistic.
Bu.. http://tinyurl.com/nn6qso]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deadly Soil: Horace Cetoude has been living on Allen Street for 22 years and eating vegetables that he has been .. http://tinyurl.com/nb8twr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pollution Ruling Lets Local Cities Save $1M: Five communities along the Stillwater River will get a regulatory r.. http://tinyurl.com/msbn59]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>