<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Developer, Collections Applications: Associate Developer, Collections Applications Associate Developer, Collections Applications Why Work For Credit Acceptance? Credit Acceptance is a rapidly-expanding company with extensive growth… https://t.co/KMNNOsWFMx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales Implementation Specialist: Job ID : 76191BR Location : US – Michigan – Detroit|US – Michigan – Grand Rapids|US – Michigan – Kalamazoo|US – Michigan – Lansing|US – Michigan – Remote / Field : Job Description When you join us at Thermo Fisher… https://t.co/Z2gKUokkRh https://t.co/P8zKYSoaUw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tech Leader / Technical Project Manager, Automotive: Project Description Luxoft is searching Product Owner to join innovative project in Automotive domain. Currently Luxoft is gathering a new team, which will create new generation of virtualized testing… https://t.co/WbnnVnX8OF https://t.co/mfQg7OGJS8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manager, HEDIS Performance Measurement:   Job Description – Manager, HEDIS Performance Measurement (1803404) Job Description  Manager, HEDIS Performance Measurement – (1803404) Primary Location : US-MI-Troy-TROY Job : Quality Organization : Corporate Job… https://t.co/mYJvdw0PlE https://t.co/gh9j2Fx4E1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kellyanne Conway's husband pushes back on Trump's attacks on Sessions: George Conway, the husband of White House counselor Kellyanne Conway, criticized President Donald Trump for failing to understand his job enforcing the law in the wake of Trump's… https://t.co/52VoCWTDlm https://t.co/HTHlWsqeqR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysis: Sessions a lot closer to being fired: For the last year, Republican senators have been adamant about one thing: President Donald Trump cannot and should not fire Attorney General Jeff Sessions. https://t.co/oC8pa320TE https://t.co/mRzbSw3Xmv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automotive System Architect: Company Description Would you like to transform your ideas into meaningful, exciting, and profitable technologies? Whether in the area of Mobility Solutions, Consumer Goods, Industrial Technology or Energy and Building… https://t.co/cvTFHPV6yQ https://t.co/xuZ3AQNxmg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Util Systems Specialist Grand Rapids, MI MRE: Job Description Util Systems Specialist – Grand Rapids, MI MRE #31161 Date: Jun 27, 2018 Location: Grand Rapids, MI, 50123 Company: The Davey Tree Expert Company Requisition Number: 31161 Company Name: DRG… https://t.co/eEmOXfW6Ao https://t.co/emSSEcW6fx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See Chris Cuomo's full one-on-one with Kellyanne Conway: CNN's Chris Cuomo presses White House counselor Kellyanne Conway on President Trump's untrue statements regarding payments made to adult film actress Stormy Daniels. https://t.co/Qi8QpIVM9p https://t.co/apmBVaYhWo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer Chassis Controls: Company Description Do you want beneficial technologies being shaped by your ideas? Whether in the areas of mobility solutions, consumer goods, industrial technology or energy and building technology with us, you will… https://t.co/F64krZ13qr https://t.co/Wk2Na5lpev]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test-Lead: Test Lead Populus Group seeks a Test Lead at various unanticipated work locations throughout the US to provide software quality assurance and participate in the full Software Test Life Cycle and Bug Life Cycle. Gather business requirements and… https://t.co/J50sVSySqL https://t.co/8jCoDGDs6J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what the storm looked like from space: Nobody wants to be under the whirling clouds of a hurricane, but above them? That's a different story. https://t.co/yXX0rGugO4 https://t.co/ITP78jde4i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. IIB Developer: Sr. IIB Developer – TGT – Farmington Hills, MI | ********** Loading…Server error, please try again laterSorry! It looks like you are in private browsing mode, which is not supported. Please switch your browser mode. Sr. IIB Developer… https://t.co/v3d3dNnIiY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inside the battle for the South China Sea https://t.co/NvVcs523Zw https://t.co/Vv6fOuTjXb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP WM Consultant: Trustek, Inc is a highly recognized provider of professional IT Consulting services in the US. We are actively seeking SAP WM Consultant for a client in Southfield, MI. This is a long term contract position. If you may not be looking… https://t.co/FEgKuIyZ6V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Support Engineer – PLM Software – East Lansing, MI: For Siemens Application Support Engineer – Advanced – East Lansing, MI job – Engineering – East Lansing, Michigan Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard – Toggle… https://t.co/4npy5wJ0N6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network-Engineer: Network Engineer Populus Group seeks a Network Engineer at various unanticipated work locations throughout the US to engineer, install, implement, and maintain network hardware, software, and applications, utilizing Ubuntu, Solarwinds… https://t.co/75iGeHHoDX https://t.co/QfTJxgsTZ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist: Data Scientist (ADAS, HAD, FAD, KERAS, Python, Robotics, AI) – HARMAN on Facebook – HARMAN on Twitter – HARMAN on LinkedIn – Careers Home – About Us – Our Divisions – Professional Development – Featured Jobs – Engineering Jobs –… https://t.co/66FbdalSTf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hardware Engineer, Automotive: Project Description Luxoft is searching experienced Embedded Software Developer for fast growing team in Detroit area. Team develops innovating testing development environment for one of the Luxoft customers. Project… https://t.co/ROhlNbsEdX https://t.co/DSAj1SFtig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Project Manager Ref No.: 18-36591 Location: Troy, Michigan Greetings, I amSatyam Jaiswal, Sr. Technical RecruiterfromEnterprise Solutions Inc. I was keen to know if you are open to explore a new career opportunity. If the job opportunity… https://t.co/YV8nv0jB9a https://t.co/N2BZrdqtCB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Deployment Specialist: Job Description Position Description Deque is seeking a full-time Software Deployment Specialist to join our Support Team. This position will perform the installation and upgrade of new customer implementations of Deque… https://t.co/2Xq5M23Zos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Ref No.: 18-33280 Location: Troy, Michigan Role : Java Developer Duration : 12 months Location : Troy, MI Job Description : ‘Java 8/9/10 certified ; J2EE: Spring Boot, Hibernate and JPA Webservices: RESTFUL API development… https://t.co/i4L5VJUE5b https://t.co/nT91U8nOsw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gretchen Wilson arrested: Country music star Gretchen Wilson was arrested Tuesday night. https://t.co/MyMNvcigVr https://t.co/OFgx1By645]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Manager: Technical Manager Primary Responsibilities: Participate in internal and external stakeholder meetings to assess business needs. Collaborate with Product Management, Operations, Production and other cross-functional groups to define,… https://t.co/iFAIgU3QQZ https://t.co/bLYlf3isRl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kyrie Irving named 'Little Mountain' in Standing Rock Sioux Tribe Ceremony https://t.co/xaAU6Fv1D0 https://t.co/hHZ08devVr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SYSTEMS ANALYST: Job Details (*Employee Referral Program applies to this job) Job No.: #******* Location: Dearborn, Michigan. Relocation may be necessary. Job Title: SYSTEMS ANALYST Job Description: Duties for this position will generally include the… https://t.co/2FNwpfAunO https://t.co/h6o88L0AET]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peoplesoft Project Manager: Overview PROLIM Global Corporation (**************) is currently seeking Peoplesoft Project Manager for location Livonia, MI for one of our Top client. Job Description: Strong ERP and Peoplesoft PM experience. Strong project… https://t.co/YRFFsEfZzk https://t.co/rRiY0Fde0X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Account Executive- Detroit: Description The Role:  PlaceIQ's Detroit Account Executive will be responsible for growing revenue from new and existing media agencies, as well as advertisers based in Michigan, Ohio and Pittsburgh. PlaceIQ is specifically… https://t.co/oWtrNBwdQ7 https://t.co/ayNE58DXO8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big Data Engineer – Scala, Hadoop, Spark: Ann Arbor, MI Full-time $130k – $175k Posted Today If you are a Big Data Engineer with Scala, Hadoop and Spark experience, we would like to hear from you! We are an engineering services company working with… https://t.co/m7izFvpe8x https://t.co/nmApOJdkiy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why American-made fascism puts democracy at risk: Earlier this month, I attended the Unite the Right 2 rally in Washington, DC -- a gathering of white nationalists to mark the anniversary of last year's horrific violence in Charlottesville. Afterward, as… https://t.co/n4UabmQmYv https://t.co/jUj9wqGioQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer IILearning A-Z EngineeringAnn Arbor, MI Tucson, AZ: &lt; Back to Career listingsRequisition ID: vl-******** Simply email resume to *************************** Software Engineer II ==================== Location: Ann Arbor, MI / Tucson, AZ… https://t.co/wUDHjT2Gbv https://t.co/XbHN62wJWr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, ERP Solution: Software Engineer, ERP Solution =============================== The Software Engineer is responsible for coding, testing, and documenting application programs of basic to moderate size and complexity, working with… https://t.co/0Bv4KDkMbd https://t.co/bokKMwwJ25]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facts behind coconut oil is 'pure poison' claim: Cyanide is a poison. Rattlesnake venom is a poison. Certain household products can be a poison. But coconut oil? One professor seems to think so, colliding head-on with consumers who believe it's good for… https://t.co/ku0uF80LdU https://t.co/cu2nAk6XDS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Oracle Apps DBA: Job Ref: ********* Employer: NTT DATA Country: United States County/State: Michigan Address: Post Date: 14/08/2018 00:08 Req ID: 27047 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The… https://t.co/I3xzmr7qHW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sears is closing another 46 stores. Here's where https://t.co/YTxEZcbIs9 https://t.co/SbXwf4WtR4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infrastructure-Solution-Architect AMANDA Lansing MI-: We are looking to hire Infrastructure Solution Architect who is proficient at the formulation of architectures, including requirements discovery and analysis, formulation of solution context, solution… https://t.co/NfnY0Vmbt1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Overview PROLIM Global Corporation (**************) is currently seeking Java Developer for location Farmington Hills , MI for one of our Top client. Required Skills: J2EE development with recent experience in Core Java, System… https://t.co/QyJBgz9N01 https://t.co/JmPGmNd51y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How crazy rich are Asia's wealthiest families? https://t.co/SH75L6kl8m https://t.co/ZeqmdmjPMp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Business Process Expert: * Zeeland, MI, USA * Full Time Email Me Similar Jobs Email Me This Job If you are a dynamic individual with excellent technical abilities and experience in a manufacturing environment then Plascore, Inc. has the perfect… https://t.co/eEF3uFpljS https://t.co/XdXIYqW0Z7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer/SharePoint Consultant, Junior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Troy, MI Job Type: Entry Level Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 8/14/2018 About Us About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our… https://t.co/ChIAa70Lzt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#MeToo founder: 'There is no model survivor': The woman who created the #MeToo movement is calling on her fellow activists to press forward in light of news that one of the group's most prominent voices, Asia Argento, allegedly paid off an accuser of her… https://t.co/0UrSGWEPtn https://t.co/JzosmYcBjh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Technical Analyst – Information Technology: IT Technical Analyst – Information Technology Req ID #: 38389 Location: Mattawan, MI, US, 49071 For 70 years, Charles River employees have worked together to assist in the discovery, development and safe… https://t.co/Y1ifi0MUzI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Powerbuilder-Programmer-with-C—VB-and-ASP—Lansing–MI: We are hiring a Powerbuilder Programmer with strong PowerBuilder coding expertise along with a subset of .NET (MVC/C#/VB/ASP), and web languages (HTML/CSS/JS) experience. Location: Lansing, MI… https://t.co/hY5H9c24zM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pink sees fan's sign, stops concert: In the middle of her concert, Pink walked into the crowd to comfort a grieving teen. The girl had been holding up a sign, hoping to catch the singer's attention. With the crowd's help, she succeeded. https://t.co/rMwKCF7mAS https://t.co/2750vgRNQR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Service Desk Associate: Service Desk Associate Business Stores – Kmart Hourly Job Description Provides ‘World Class’ Member Service by surprising and delighting our members every day. Performs daily responsibilities including, but not limited to:… https://t.co/PfdfCiLigF https://t.co/p3SCOExboB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Process Analyst: * Please wait… A career at Amway is a career in opportunity. At Amway you can explore and grow, make a difference, and find success. Established in 1959, Amway is a multi-billion dollar company, and the world’s No. 1 direct… https://t.co/GphOGZpSS5 https://t.co/BCXnIuDy1n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['LazyTown' actor dies at 43: Icelandic actor Stefan Karl Stefansson, best known for playing villain Robbie Rotten in the popular children's TV show "LazyTown," has died at age 43 from cancer, according to his wife. https://t.co/SuvPtYhLg6 https://t.co/hNL6Onfrkq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infotainment Development Quality Assurance Engineer: Infotainment Development Quality Assurance Engineer – ENG******* in Detroit, Michigan, US | Engineering at general motorsJob details page – – – – – – Home – About Us About Us – Our Company – Our… https://t.co/eaGWP3T7vw https://t.co/F6NsSBODrL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager, Public Safety Solution: Project Manager, Public Safety Solution ======================================= The Project Manager successfully manages the implementation of Tyler software for new and existing accounts, from the contract… https://t.co/eWeXnwpsKg https://t.co/c4vPVxtrpZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Business Process Expert: * Zeeland, MI, USA * Full Time Email Me Similar Jobs Email Me This Job If you are a dynamic individual with excellent technical abilities and experience in a manufacturing environment then Plascore, Inc. has the perfect… https://t.co/IDlLjLUIFT https://t.co/dVg5yym1aV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alisyn Camerota calls out Trump supporter's 'rhetorical footwork': CNN's Alisyn Camerota clashes with American Conservative Union Chairman Matt Schlapp over President Trump's former lawyer Michael Cohen's guilty plea. https://t.co/yqXdvmGgu1 https://t.co/0ejLs4lW1F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GOP leaders mostly silent on Cohen, Manafort: CNN analysts John Avlon and Mark Preston discuss why congressional GOP leaders have mostly remained silent following the convictions of former Trump associates Michael Cohen and Paul Manafort. https://t.co/tlBPr0SVcA https://t.co/tVrIvNrdSw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Implementation Specialist: Overview Public Consulting Group, Inc. (PCG) provides management consulting and technology services to help public sector education, health, human services, and other government clients achieve their performance goals and… https://t.co/fFHngIDL4K https://t.co/OnqyI99RDp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Developer: Job Details (*Employee Referral Program applies to this job) Job ID ******* Position Sr. Developer Description Summary: Job Duties:Under limited supervision, develop, create, and modify complex batch and online computer applications using… https://t.co/ZHxkdCUD4U https://t.co/MNb2ZoUIsl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What you need to know about vitamin D: You may have seen supplements containing vitamin D at your local convenience stores or been tested for deficiency by your doctor. But what is vitamin D, and why do we need it? https://t.co/PRwffj5IAz https://t.co/z7lJlRJjvH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CAE Application Support Engineer Advanced East Lansing, MI: For Siemens CAE Application Support Engineer Advanced – East Lansing, MI job – Engineering – East Lansing, Michigan Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard – Toggle… https://t.co/Sik86pHzhh https://t.co/jvcvwp2xRA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Powerbuilder-Programmer-with-C VB-and-ASP Lansing MI: We are hiring a Powerbuilder Programmer with strong PowerBuilder coding expertise along with a subset of .NET (MVC/C#/VB/ASP), and web languages (HTML/CSS/JS) experience. Location: Lansing, MI… https://t.co/TNgrq1982I https://t.co/ElVUkpQ3SW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The day the news came like a flash flood https://t.co/8eLSXrLxcB https://t.co/rAFWjmvgJu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FMVSS Performance Engineer: FMVSS 201U Performance Engineer, Warren, MI, General Motors. Develop, improve &amp; assure that psgr vehicles meet &amp; /or exceed FMVSS 201U Occupant Protection in Interior Impact – Upper Portion standards, incldg reqmts for vehicle… https://t.co/9LHU7RE7qg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager, Public Safety Solution: Project Manager, Public Safety Solution ======================================= The Project Manager successfully manages the implementation of Tyler software for new and existing accounts, from the contract… https://t.co/FZP7129Ck7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales Director (Professional Services): Sales Director (Professional Services) HARMAN International Date: Aug 9, 2018 Location: Novi, MI, US Description: Requisition Id : ****** Additional Work Location(s) : Primary Responsibilities: – Selling into OEM’s… https://t.co/2EhKheMxIK https://t.co/Z6aziwiTlc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager: Job ID : 74265BR Location : US – Michigan – Kalamazoo : Job Description When you join us at Thermo Fisher Scientific, you’ll be part of a smart, driven team that shares your passion for exploration and discovery. With revenues of… https://t.co/tTPaKrNNXt https://t.co/Bk6bNtQoMY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Giuliani: 'No allegation of any wrongdoing against the President' https://t.co/RjPzEOfO03 https://t.co/1AulZNdQrs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer/SharePoint Consultant, Junior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Troy, MI Job Type: Entry Level Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 8/14/2018 About Us About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our… https://t.co/36c41w3EtD https://t.co/j11wawsRqG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supporters plead to Trump for help (2017): If two coal-fired power plants near Manchester, OH, close, residents say it could become a ghost town. They're asking for help from their President. https://t.co/L4RqCsOlIR https://t.co/Btm85RJwki]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager / Project Engineer: * Zeeland, MI, USA * Full Time Email Me Similar Jobs Email Me This Job Plascore Incorporated, is seeking a technical professional to join our team as a Project Manager / Project Engineer servicing our Cleanroom… https://t.co/EFX5abLZwb https://t.co/k6nwN90VaM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Service Support Specialist – Building Automation – Plymouth, MI: **Service Support Specialist – Building Automation – Plymouth, MI** Locations:Plymouth, Michigan Job Family: Customer Services New Search Apply English (US) **Job Description**… https://t.co/EV6at4cDmj https://t.co/8fVSGmqQa9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Research Analyst I: Sr Research Analyst I Sr Research Analyst I – Powertrain Planning , Powertrain and Compliance , Automotive As a key member of the Cost to Compliance organization which is part of IHS Markit Powertrain and CO2 compliance team, the… https://t.co/X6s6siTfUB https://t.co/qR4Mc96Adx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solution Architect: * Please wait. A career at Amway is a career in opportunity. At Amway you can explore and grow, make a difference, and find success. Established in 1959, Amway is a multi-billion dollar company, and the world’s No. 1 direct selling… https://t.co/OmPkKdWyYt https://t.co/Naw6SI8rsi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Substation Project Manager / Team Lead: Job Description Substation Project Manager / Team Lead Substation Project Manager / Team Lead (******) About Us At HDR, we specialize in engineering, architecture, environmental and construction services. While we… https://t.co/Is0L4CcwfT https://t.co/euj3XuLTrx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Analyst 3: Overview PROLIM Global Corporation (**************) is currently seeking System Analyst 3 for location Lansing , MI for one of our Top client. Responsible for creating intuitive user interface designs for mobile applications, web… https://t.co/spKCJPsdtU https://t.co/GZtKoisgfM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paint Coating Applications Project Manager: Job Description Paint &amp; Coating Applications Project Manager ABB Inc., in Auburn Hills, MI is seeking for an Project Manager to join our Robotics and Motion team, the first major global industrial robotics… https://t.co/qIsXU5DELm https://t.co/jQ7SGF4a6i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Architect Requirements Engineer: Job opening: System Architect &amp; Requirements Engineer | Continental AG – Go to navigation – Go to content – Go to the end of the page By using the following access keys you can jump directly to the respective… https://t.co/S594r8ncHL https://t.co/Oro7S0A2DL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Service Desk Associate: Service Desk Associate Business Stores – Kmart Hourly Job Description Provides ‘World Class’ Member Service by surprising and delighting our members every day. Performs daily responsibilities including, but not limited to:… https://t.co/nrZiECzJ03 https://t.co/GJX477uMzS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winona Ryder says she and Keanu Reeves got married: But are they registered anywhere? https://t.co/1Ql7UeayCc https://t.co/VPejn0WGYH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Developer: Job Details (*Employee Referral Program applies to this job) Job No.: ******* Location: Multiple undetermined work-sites throughout the U.S. Job Title: Sr. Developer Job Description: Duties for this position will generally include the… https://t.co/Y7QNZgqBCo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ITS-Traffic Project Manager I: Job Description – ITS-Traffic Project Manager I Job LocationUS-MI-East Lansing | US-MI-DetroitJob ID0718-18953 HNTB Job TitleProject Manager I – Engineering Position TypeRegular Full-Time CategoryEngineering-Traffic Why… https://t.co/Cpvog9Dbuf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: It's time to fight the ballot bullies in court: In rural Randolph County, Georgia, the local board of elections (all two members -- a third recently stepped down, according to the Washington Post) has proposed closing seven of the county's nine… https://t.co/dsgCKeN9CM https://t.co/irxgXVrA3x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frustrated Knicks fan auctioning off fanhood https://t.co/mvKV0kMnWJ https://t.co/MkWjnAKSUE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Harrison charter Township, MI Job Type: Strategy – Planning Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 8/16/2018 About Us About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’… https://t.co/IrBDg2NDlU https://t.co/DzeUkeRpQT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ITS-Traffic Project Manager I: Job Description – ITS-Traffic Project Manager I Job LocationUS-MI-East Lansing | US-MI-DetroitJob ID0718-18953 HNTB Job TitleProject Manager I – Engineering Position TypeRegular Full-Time CategoryEngineering-Traffic Why… https://t.co/L9ge52EF1c https://t.co/hRDXaPzjXs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Test Lead: Overview PROLIM Global Corporation (**************) is currently seeking QA Test Lead for location Detroit , MI for one of our Top client. Job Description: Required Skills/Experience At least 5 years of experience in the below Facets… https://t.co/PHQHqNjbrz https://t.co/96Bp5EZw09]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CAE Application Support Engineer Advanced – East Lansing, MI: For Siemens CAE Application Support Engineer Advanced – East Lansing, MI job – Engineering – East Lansing, Michigan Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard – Toggle… https://t.co/0RNAEM6dFp https://t.co/uIVm3MVp8X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vatican releases a letter in the wake of a Pennsylvania grand jury report detailing sexual abuses and cover-ups: Pope Francis has acknowledged "with shame and repentance" the Catholic Church's failure to act over sexual abuse by clerics against minors… https://t.co/hE9HEZxBxM https://t.co/VNYpW02UGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Logistics Solutions: Job Description Project Manager – Logistics Solutions ABB Inc., is seeking a Project Manager – Logistics Solution to join our Robotics and Motion team, the first major global industrial robotics manufacturer to… https://t.co/8XPxNC9cEe https://t.co/owKsx7hBi2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A photographic treatment for people with dementia: One of the first dementia patients Laurence Aëgerter met was in the later stages of the illness. She visited the man at a care facility in Switzerland to note his reactions to photographs she had brought… https://t.co/vKeeQf3K1I https://t.co/bVwHrpXNKa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Cloud Infrastructure Automation Lead: 3046693 Senior Cloud Infrastructure Automation Lead Oil &amp; Gas Headquarters GE Oil &amp; Gas United States Provide IT leadership on multiple automation build projects. Help prioritize and drive results for the… https://t.co/w94VDM5Hk9 https://t.co/wAZ8QhTd89]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Service Desk Analyst: JOB ID: ****** SERVICE DESK ANALYST TROY, MICHIGAN REGULAR / ROTATING ADDITIONAL JOB INFORMATION TITLE:Service Desk Analyst CITY, STATE: Troy, MI LOCATION: MITROY 800 Tower Dr DEPARTMENT: Ops Service Center CRC ADDITIONAL JOB… https://t.co/sR1F8sRwib https://t.co/dNlt4wjR3U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Study: Children in Ancient Rome had Vitamin D deficiency: A new analysis of skeletons from ancient Roman cemeteries across Europe has revealed that vitamin D deficiency was a problem for children 2,000 years ago https://t.co/eJ6D78PUiG https://t.co/irnwSD1DjY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Service Desk Analyst: JOB ID: ****** SERVICE DESK ANALYST TROY, MICHIGAN REGULAR / ROTATING ADDITIONAL JOB INFORMATION TITLE:Service Desk Analyst CITY, STATE: Troy, MI LOCATION: MITROY 800 Tower Dr DEPARTMENT: Ops Service Center CRC ADDITIONAL JOB… https://t.co/wJxFssEnK2 https://t.co/rHfqvukkL3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Engineer: Technical Support Engineer The Technical Support Engineer is a critical role withing the TGW Lifetime Services (LTS) team, providing highly technical customer service and support, focusing on the TGW Software solutions. This… https://t.co/vbh6tHz7tH https://t.co/WngjE3oxwv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Architect Detroit: The product architect technically leads the development of connected navigation systems that the TomTom Custom Systems product unit develops for its business customers. The product architect is involved in both product… https://t.co/mSpSNNyvrV https://t.co/CAEdxhjo0P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Giuliani: Truth isn't truth: Rudy Giuliani, President Donald Trump's attorney, said Sunday that "truth isn't truth" when explaining that he won't let special counsel Robert Mueller rush Trump into testifying because he doesn't want investigators to trap… https://t.co/mxnnUGdAPV https://t.co/ooDPwCHogq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Support Engineer – PLM Software – East Lansing, MI: For Siemens Application Support Engineer – Advanced – East Lansing, MI job – Engineering – East Lansing, Michigan Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard – Toggle… https://t.co/WolHyVJx8Y https://t.co/wpYonjWBAG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java UI Developer: Job Search Results Home Home Language English Franais Espaol Sign inRegister Email: Password: Forgot your password? Sign in Please enter your registered email address, and we’ll email you a link to reset your password right away.Your… https://t.co/F20EHlttPQ https://t.co/o1hU5geLHu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Process Support Manager Care Chemicals, Wyandotte, MI: Job Title: Process Support Manager Care Chemicals, Wyandotte, MI Location: Wyandotte, MI, Mid-West United States, USA Company: BASF – We Create Chemistry Industry Sector:Agribusiness Industry Type:… https://t.co/MCPTcYSC6I https://t.co/VzIv2WnDTw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Ref No.: 18-33231 Location: Detroit, Michigan Position: Java Developer Location: Detroit, MI Duration: 12 Months Undergraduate Degree or Technical Certificate. – 5-7 years relevant experience. – Hands on experience in J2EE… https://t.co/NQ5yBHt3cB https://t.co/twREgiE6Xz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Systems Analyst: Job Details (*Employee Referral Program applies to this job) Job No.: #******* Location: Multiple undetermined worksites throughout the U.S Job Title: Sr. Systems Analyst Job Description: Job Duties: Under limited supervision,… https://t.co/lOscfRYOVh https://t.co/QO6zzzytZg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Applications Analyst, SAP MM: Company profile We like it when our employees have goals. What about you? Are you ready to grow with your challenges? MAHLE is a leading international development partner and supplier to the automotive industry as well as a… https://t.co/f1iuYredd9 https://t.co/ezNhFt8Mlu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Software Developer – Virtual Reality: IT Software Developer – Virtual Reality – INF******* in Warren (Tech Ctr), Michigan, US | Information Technology at general motorsJob details page – – – – – – Home – About Us About Us – Our Company – Our Employees… https://t.co/wnibmuyjpX https://t.co/flBmAlIHEo]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>