<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[We must accept finite disappointment, but we must never lose infinite hope. - Martin Luther King, Jr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Are the Major Kinds of Insurance?  http://t.co/nOf3spTLPf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Until one has loved an animal,  a part of one's soul remains unawakened. - Anatole France]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never dance in a puddle when there's a hole in your shoe (it's always best to take your shoes off first). --&gt; John D. Rhodes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One thought driven home is better than three left to die on base. . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Simple Way to Bond with Kids? Use Cooking!  http://t.co/4jLtj8091G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People who enjoy what they are doing invariably do it well. - Joe Gibbs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rock is so much fun. That's what it's all about - filling up the chest cavities and empty kneecaps and elbows.  - Jimi Hendrix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See you in another life, brother. - Desmond Hume, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The noblest search is the search for excellence - Lyndon B. Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your Business Guide for Small Business Internet Marketing  http://t.co/BadT4ea4PS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[STAR TREK ENTERPRISE - Brake Light Vinyl Decal - ENGAGE!  --&gt; http://t.co/QjMjVi0Dqv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome marriage t-shirts &amp; gear - give the gift of marriage!  http://t.co/gcQU8V9Tqp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of McDonald's  http://t.co/Prm6HZpne7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Budget: A domestic quarrel!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The designated hitter rule is like letting someone else take Wilt Chamberlain's free throws. - Rick Wise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Star Wars  http://t.co/pKwyUU9hbg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hiring Strategy Consulting Firms: The Importance of Competitive Analysis  http://t.co/LmqNVa3GAH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame Champions: Confused Much?  http://t.co/DJIR70Mj1L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Musings of a Homeschooling Dad (sort of)  http://t.co/RC6ZpIHWbY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn the Keys to Using LinkedIn for Your Company  http://t.co/VAfu7dSJfs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've looked into the eye of this island, and what I saw was beautiful. - John Locke, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I learned law so well, the day I graduated I sued the college, won the case, and got my tuition back. - Fred Allen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Ankle Watches – Is This the New Place to Wear a Watch?  http://t.co/HqAE3GwK3D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome football t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the football lovers in your life!  http://t.co/XLZSSLYfTL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most games are lost, not won! - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smartphones are reinventing the connection between companies and their customers.  Rich Miner - Partner Google Ventures]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Average White Band  http://t.co/KdAAemZ5lx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is Renter's Insurance?  http://t.co/ZJuyA9uR1y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Little Richard  http://t.co/xQ3f53DPOd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most beautiful thing in the world is a ballpark filled with people. - Bill Veeck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are 10 types of people in the world: those who understand binary, and those who don't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is but one game and that game is baseball.  - John McGraw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It costs a lot of money to look this cheap --&gt; Dolly Parton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He got brains but the're in cold storage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rule your mind or it will rule you. - Horace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like flying jet fighters in a gymnasium - Dick Trickle was asked what racing at Winchester Speedway was like.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn The Importance of a Good Pitching Repertoire for Young Pitchers  http://t.co/jePnsMD1sl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these lovely Dos XX Most Interesting Main the World Commercials!  http://t.co/EBudkmtLPJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To confine our attention to terrestrial matters would be to limit the human spirit. - Stephen Hawking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The kindness planned for tomorrow doesn't count for today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Coors Beer  http://t.co/8VYHwfJ0Un]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because the human history is the history of shoes. The history of places where we ever tread and stand.  - Stebby Julionatan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Management is nothing more than motivating other people. - Le Iacocca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't read other science fiction. I don't read any at all. - Jack Vance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your body is the baggage you must carry through life. The more excess the baggage, the shorter the trip. - Arnold H. Glasgow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome running t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the Running lovers in your life!  http://t.co/mriJeKhTql]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Colonize Mars: Can This Dream Become a Reality?  http://t.co/BYHQx5LNzt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Bruce Springsteen  http://t.co/YRCmxglPw8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman who doesn't wear perfume has no future. Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Style is knowing who you are, what you want to say, and not giving a damn --&gt; Orson Welles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Danger Will Robinson! Danger! - Robbie the Robot, Lost in Space]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most beautiful thing in the world is a ballpark filled with people. - Bill Veeck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Find Gluten Free Recipes  http://t.co/R5wKrxkN6p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future's got a million roads for you to choose, But you'll walk a little taller in some high heel shoes - Hairspray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His timing is perfect, so is his two-timing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Andy Kim  http://t.co/B3vfhym85v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of LA Gear  http://t.co/dz8LZXRP0G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotta Love It - 12 Nerd Rubber Duckies!  Makes Bath Time Fun!  http://t.co/JX55uMHfQ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Great Music of Bill Justis  http://t.co/AwDF2EevDS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The eternal silence of these infinite spaces fills me with dread. - Blaise Pascal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Ankle Watches – Is This the New Place to Wear a Watch?  http://t.co/HqAE3GwK3D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have ways of making money that you know nothing of.   John D. Rockefeller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Lettermen  http://t.co/0R7YD0hpI4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to WordTracker SEO Tools http://t.co/8JYpPnvUg9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Bruce Springsteen  http://t.co/YRCmxglPw8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The worst examples of snap judgment are usually found in the old family album]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I raced a car last it was at a time when sex was safe and racing was dangerous. Now, it's the other way round. - Hans Stuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Narcotics Detection – Technology's Place in the War on Drugs  http://t.co/zB0tC06F91]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Emerson, Lake and Palmer  http://t.co/6uC4pKPPMc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Frustrations of Youth Pitching  http://t.co/Q4TxQJzXIO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never go in against a Sicilian when death is on the line! - Vizzini, The Princess Bride]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Lobo the Classic Rock Group?  http://t.co/8RdJTLHHZ4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Arthur Alexander - The Unknown Legend  http://t.co/7G8xpGtHU4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Major Watch Retailers and Brands  http://t.co/o090iA1grh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The way you can understand all of the social media is as the creation of a new kind of public space - Dana Boyd, Social Media Research MSFT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating history of Baseball Cards!  http://t.co/OF9rAadD73]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Blue Oyster Cult   http://t.co/IFBbkXJm7U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Bonnie Lou  http://t.co/ymg65bmQvY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sky is no longer the limit. - Richard M. Nixon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A New Star Wars Movie Is Coming in 2015!  http://t.co/exsaarWa4b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I'm not back in five minutes, just wait longer. - Ace Ventura, Ace ventura, Pet Detective]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Paul Davis  http://t.co/SkkOGH5Z6O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dog is the only thing on earth that will love you more than you love yourself. - Josh Billings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last word of the Emperor Montezuma, "Someone tell those Marines to stop singing in the halls."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Fashionable Jackets for Fall &amp; Winter  http://t.co/VwhtZfZBba]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make Your House More Attractive With Fall Flowers  http://t.co/0hvx1WMB6Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to Douglas Adams  http://t.co/ksUZcBwVXn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool A Clear Bottomed 2 - Person Kayak - A Unique Way to Enjoy Paddling! http://t.co/9jBRDeHSVC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your Business Guide for Small Business Internet Marketing  http://t.co/BadT4ea4PS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Grapevine, Texas  http://t.co/ACkolKGgaM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Top 10 Asian Beers  http://t.co/slHszczI6c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a rock 'n' roll thing to have one-night stands. - Rick Springfield]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I'm hungry, I eat. When I'm thirsty, I drink. When I feel like saying something, I say it. Madonna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What is Chronic Lyme Disease?  http://t.co/CpnXHpoDNC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just got my Google Chromecast HDMI Streaming Media Player - SO COOL - http://t.co/XUjNSbMIfo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is nothing permanent except change. - Heraclitus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Help with Autism  http://t.co/BcAlWXhZlV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Best Camping Destinations  http://t.co/5NzvCVIlFf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To confine our attention to terrestrial matters would be to limit the human spirit. - Stephen Hawking]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>