<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Where next for baby food? Is it online? In the refrigerated section? Jars? Pouches? Bowls?! https://t.co/fpPWcNo2ls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Healthy cake? Two brands launch #protein packed options: https://t.co/ahg4AFCXhc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is industry's obsession with #snacks misplaced? https://t.co/vD6Uhk5uqb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is the word 'diet' in Diet Coke and Diet Pepsi misleading? https://t.co/PSuLavpT2M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To what extent will Brazilians pay a premium for healthier food and beverage options? https://t.co/BH7F93Xuo8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How will big CPG cos respond to price pressures from discount grocers? https://t.co/b1FUQYglVR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cross-contamination of #gluten could be in FDA's crosshairs https://t.co/GXaZepaekc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["People don't want to go and plant food anymore," says school admin. So what is the solution? https://t.co/A41bSstpct]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To what extent can big companies behave like small, agile ones? @PepsiCo will weigh in at Food Vision USA next month https://t.co/aR0rcCqUuP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do you convince mainstream consumers used to paying $1 for yogurt to pay $2 for a premium option? https://t.co/0Hc5AkaQY2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales of #plantbased meat alternatives are up 6.1% in the year ending in Aug. https://t.co/C4KE2xm06v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Chocolate covered #cheese? @YooliFoods hopes consumers will say yes, please! https://t.co/LlME8ULdJk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every three minutes in the US someone goes to the ER for a food allergy. Find out how manufacturers are responding: https://t.co/NdtCmtjLZN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can savory yogurt in the US be saved, or was it a bridge too far? https://t.co/AqNLvRVtXC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything will be faster for @RXBAR now that it has teamed with @KelloggCompany, exec says: https://t.co/jpdsFOCJW0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@sugarlogix offers a #sugar solution that could actually be healthy: https://t.co/bX55rFS8px]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Launches of #protein drinks are up 35% https://t.co/qjyaWFtDgN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only 20% of Americans eat #protein for snacks, but @Nielsen says research could change that. Find out @ FREE webinar https://t.co/6IAedmJZmG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parents who turn noses up at baby food pouches bc kids can't see the food they eat, now have another option: bowls https://t.co/fpPWcNo2ls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Discover new #protein #snacks https://t.co/ahg4AFllSC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TV dinners are out and meal kits are in, according to new research on #millennials https://t.co/vD6Uhk5uqb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do people who buy diet soda think it will help them lose weight? https://t.co/PSuLavHurm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brazil's struggle with obesity could  create opportunity for better-for-you products https://t.co/BH7F93Xuo8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big CPGs cos are seeing small declines in YOY growth. Find out why: https://t.co/b1FUQYglVR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out how one high school in Chicago is inspiring students to be future farmers of America: https://t.co/A41bSstpct]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FDA sees strong compliance with #glutenfree labeling standard https://t.co/GXaZeoSCVC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#plantbased #yogurt @COYOUSA is ready to make the leap from natural to conventional channel w a price cut https://t.co/0Hc5AkaQY2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@BeyondMeat scores more star power with investment from Leonardo DiCaprio: https://t.co/C4KE2x4oHV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What exactly is farmer's cheese? @YooliFoods is introducing the high #protein #snack to America: https://t.co/LlME8ULdJk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@PepsiCo wants something to replace glycerin ... find out what it is looking for:https://t.co/aR0rcCIvmn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out what the top food and beverage sellers are on Amazon Fresh: https://t.co/gAe3tf0Dbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Insurance claims for ER visits related to food allergies are up 377% Find out what this means for free-from category https://t.co/NdtCmt2aBd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why are major producers of savory yogurt quietly pulling back? https://t.co/AqNLvRVtXC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not all #sugar is bad -- some might actually boost your health, according to @sugarlogix https://t.co/bX55rFS8px]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consumers may love #protein, but they don't love the taste. @firmenich has new flavor solutions https://t.co/qjyaWFtDgN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1/2 of Americans are looking for more #protein. Find out how #snack makers are responding at our FREE webinar Oct 25 https://t.co/6IAedmJZmG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@PlumOrganics goes back to basics, kind of, with new baby food bowls aimed at parents who prefer jars to pouches https://t.co/fpPWcNFDd0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is next for @RXBAR now that it has teamed with @KelloggCompany?
 Find out: https://t.co/jpdsFOCJW0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Brazilians are eating is changing. Find out how: https://t.co/BH7F93Xuo8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How will the rise of Aldi, Lidl and Amazon impact CPG prices?

https://t.co/b1FUQYxXkr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forget canned goods. The future could mean growing fresh legumes in you cupboard: https://t.co/A41bSstpct]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@CSPI considers glycerin safe in food ... but do consumers? https://t.co/aR0rcCqUuP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A 93% sales surge in Amazon US groceries illustrates its potential for brands to sell direct to consumer https://t.co/gAe3tf0Dbh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The free-from category is set to double by 2020. Find out what is behind its explosion in this #podcast: https://t.co/NdtCmt2aBd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is savory yogurt in the US a flop? Or just ahead of its time? https://t.co/AqNLvRVtXC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out why @RXBAR selected @KelloggCompany as a strategic partner for ongoing growth: https://t.co/jpdsFOl94s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out why @RXBAR selected @KelloggCompany as a strategic partner for ongoing growth:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big food? Small food? Smarter food? What do consumers actually want? Find out from @CampbellSoupCo at #foodvision https://t.co/pUepKb2HHc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[36% of parents worry about the sugar content in their children's breakfast: https://t.co/BZscAQywd1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beyond peanut butter: @abbysbetter uses pecans, cashews &amp; almonds to make better for you nut butters https://t.co/uu64p8OFCZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is 100% juice the next best thing to fruits and veggies? The answer from @HarvestSoul may surprise you: https://t.co/jOqxrNG1xZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How a beverage is made -- not just what is in it -- is increasingly important to consumers https://t.co/G1VB6WTke0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Generation Z's focus on convenience makes them more open to ecommerce: https://t.co/9UZURRewpV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does @Albertsons acquisition of @plated mean for the meal kit space long term? Find out: https://t.co/90faB0lsY6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As more Americans plan to cut back on animal #protein the potential for #legumes, #pulses and #beans rises https://t.co/JhRVTAbk90]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How is online grocery shopping impacting sales of #organic food? https://t.co/W5XsWPyX1S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@RippleFoods wants to do for #plantbased cheese, yogurt &amp; ice cream what is happening in plant based 'milk' space https://t.co/pZUoxjI4ou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@DouxMatok is ready to scale up its #sugar reduction technology and is looking for partners: https://t.co/CPKLHETFKp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @abrowdy: Industrial marketers listen in: Soup-To-Nuts Podcast: How brands can defend against private label - https://t.co/hCDwdvQ4Md #G…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How does MyoTechnology's fermented mushroom ingredient stack up against other alternative plant based #proteins: https://t.co/TcEapAnHiT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who says cereal is out of style? @BarbarasBakery found 95% of kids eat cereal before school: https://t.co/BZscAQywd1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An open mind and willingness to ask for guidance helped @abbysbetter' healthier nut butters take off https://t.co/uu64p8OFCZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quorn may be meat-free, but it isn't exactly #plantbased either ... find out what it is and where it is sold https://t.co/eNU0VnMszZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uncertainty around provisions of new Nutrition Facts labeling lingers https://t.co/hZwQqghqNf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[State inspections for #FSMA compliance around agricultural water safety delayed: https://t.co/Z0ZoHnZTOA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New app aims to make it easier for consumers to discover #healthy, #organic brands https://t.co/npwmDBGIp4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How has NAFTA impacted sales of fruits and veggies? https://t.co/iOAtsLXKUH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for a safe way to introduce nuts to your child? @BEFOREBrands has one option https://t.co/kzK1T43mus #allergies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What will it take for Americans to think about yogurt beyond breakfast? @chaatco has a few ideas https://t.co/gwJb9G7b2E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoodBytes: Paul Beiboer, CEO Rabobank North America, on @RabobankGroup's new $1B worldwide initiative together with @UNEP to tackle #so…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmatic digital buying (think banner #ads) is "garbage" bc no one clicks banners just like no one watches commercials says @GaryVaynerchuck at @RaboWholesale conference]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best hand for ROI on advertising today is Facebook says @GaryVaynerchuck at @RaboWholesale conference]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your #brand is yr only protection against becoming a #Commodity. You must connect emotionally to succeed longterm says @GaryVaynerchuck at @RaboWholesale conference]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On succeeding as an #Entrepreneur @GaryVaynerchuck says at @RaboWholesale conf that he isn't in luck business he is in marathon business.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there a market for savory yogurt in the US, @EWatsonWrites asks @Chobani https://t.co/PyCkd3cLVr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Food allergies are terrifying. But @BEFOREBrands is making it a little easier for parents to introduce nuts to children https://t.co/kzK1T3LL5S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out how the resilient #startup @chaatco is reinventing itself and the American #snack market https://t.co/gwJb9GoLUc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Chobani pulled its oats and meze dips lines -- but promises they'll be back 'in some form.' Get the full scoop from @EWatsonWrites https://t.co/PyCkd3unk1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do consumers mean when they say they want 'less processed' food? https://t.co/L8GL2Q71sz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To successfully sell groceries online, retailers must offer more than added convenience of home delivery https://t.co/Z1c9vjwHiW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Jackfruit and #cauliflower will take center stage in 2018 https://t.co/6I1rlXKoGL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does the #sugar lawsuit against @MDLZ signal for the rest of the better-for-you category? https://t.co/mnUygV1gRh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best way to #market a brand has shifted dramatically. Get tips and tricks from @LindaEFood https://t.co/v67fpiO5HY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is #protein an 'overrated fad?' @MiyokoSchinner says yes at #FoodVision https://t.co/whLogVJYjs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New draft guidance from FDA on GRAS submissions will have a significant impact: https://t.co/it6GRniqVW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is #coconutoil healthy? https://t.co/3X1iD43JB7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anti-inflammatory power of macadamia nuts gives @Milkadamia added benefit https://t.co/z4KVV2Fwym]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Political upheaval, uncertain economics have consumers turning to food for comfort in 2018 https://t.co/6I1rlXKoGL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Four in five customers distrust 'natural' on food and beverage products says @HartmanGroup expert at #FoodVision https://t.co/Z1c9vjf5Um]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to overcome three major challenges holding back grocery sales online: https://t.co/Z1c9vjwHiW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is #sugar the next big target for class action suits? https://t.co/mnUygV1gRh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You may want to put your best food forward in marketing, but looking perfect is actually a turn off for consumers https://t.co/v67fpj5Gzw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advice from @Chobani on how to grow a business from #FoodVision USA in Chicago last week: https://t.co/jDSWiD2Fg5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Discover how to provide GRAS panels w the info they need, while still protecting IP from public &amp; competitors https://t.co/it6GRniqVW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does acerola have the answer to stopping unappealing browning for fruits and veggies in juice? https://t.co/FsRmMpuYwM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do Americans actively want saturated fat snacks? https://t.co/3X1iD4lksF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Milkadamia's 'moo is moot' logo resonates w consumers who see cows as irrelevant for food production https://t.co/z4KVV2Fwym]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Early predictions about what to expect at restaurants -- and eventually in packaged food -- for 2018: https://t.co/6I1rlXsNib]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consumers think the phrase clean on packaging to describe food is a bit neurotic, and they distrust it @HartmanGroup expert says https://t.co/Z1c9vjwHiW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does it take for food and beverage to win at #ecommerce? @PeapodDelivers exec has some advice from #FoodVision https://t.co/Z1c9vjwHiW]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>