<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Women need food, water, and compliments.  That's right.  And an occasional pair of shoes. Chris Rock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Writing Company Blogs that are Effective  http://t.co/9jEynBesrx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still love her. But she's retarded, too. Guy Ritchie on Madonna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making the Most of Twitter for Your Business  http://t.co/x1KvXMhM9L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A tax collector has what it takes to take what you got]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatness of a nation and its moral progress can be judged by the way its animals are treated.- Mahatma Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You want to fall in love with a shoe go ahead. A shoe can't love you back, a shoe can't hurt you too deeply either. - Allan Sherman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Frustrations of Youth Pitching  http://t.co/V9d2ZlTsVg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Do Parents Pick Favorite Things for their Kids?  http://t.co/I5qgY6py0p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Bangles  http://t.co/NRdacZR5Hz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I led the league in Go get 'em next time." - Bob Uecker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The universe, as far as we can observe it, is a wonderful and immense engine. - George Santayana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before you take somebody's head off be sure you've used yours]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strikeouts are boring - besides that, they're fascist. Throw some ground balls. More democratic. - Bull Durham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NASA Unveils a Very Cool New Space Suit  http://t.co/hiPPpTHA63]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these lovely Dos XX Most Interesting Main the World Commercials!  http://t.co/aZVHzhuoGL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best augury of a man's success in his profession is that he thinks it the finest in the world. - George Eliot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have never felt in tune with the whole rock industry.  - Robert Wyatt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's face it: The teeth are getting more and more British every day. I look in the mirror and see Austin Powers staring at me.  Hugh Grant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BACON shaped themed Adhesive Bandages - Love It! http://t.co/AdYWfeNE7n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take care of your body. It's the only place you have to live. - Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dogs are not our whole life, but they make our lives whole. - Roger Caras]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Ohio Players    http://t.co/k6LmjzHP0K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get a Minecraft Enderman! http://t.co/BTcKNYtpMZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one gets very far unless he accomplishes the impossible at least once a day. - Elbert Hubbard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seniors Gain from Social Networking Technology  http://t.co/Bo1lWEkt1e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So cool and elegant - what is the history behind Ballet shoes?  http://t.co/NIdxWEAC24]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harness The Power of Twitter for Business to Business Internet Marketing  http://t.co/kkyyxY8A3w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of that Odd Olympic Sport – Curling  http://t.co/l9ImfROXuV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Formal education will make you a living; self-education will make you a fortune.  Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adults are always asking little kids what they want to be when they grow up because they're looking for ideas... Paula Poundstone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome biking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the biking lovers in your life!  http://t.co/cQ9kWubffe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To know when you have enough is to be rich]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science fiction writers foresee the inevitable, and although problems and catastrophes may be inevitable, solutions are not. - Isaac Asimov]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is the transmission of civilization. - Will Durant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poets are like baseball pitchers. Both have their moments. The intervals are the tough things. - Robert Frost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Leif Garrett  http://t.co/h3o68tkrO6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can an EMP really wipe us out?  http://t.co/rBvXtZVbKT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who are the Three Degrees oldies group?  http://t.co/zb5RlNg82M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is what survives when what has been learned has been forgotten. - B. F. Skinner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Paul Simon - His Biography  http://t.co/zvAnPFOoHx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome kayaking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the paddling lovers in your life!  http://t.co/NfldoINjAN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of 'em, any of 'em that have been in front of me over all these years.  Sarah Palin on the newspapers she reads]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NERD POWER Pin Button - Must Wear! http://t.co/1NkMszQ8ej]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The time has come the Walrus said, To talk of many thing’s Of shoes and ships and sealing-wax of cabbages and kings - Lewis Carroll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today fitness equipment is something we take for granted - ever wondered about its history?  Read more --&gt; http://t.co/XPNXARMGmw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for great resources on Beer?  Check out our top 10... http://t.co/R4Kt4oOBaO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blow off some steam, or rather, shoot some smoke rings. The Zero Fog Blaster is a ray gun - totally cool!  http://t.co/rGtsrfOkX4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome burgers and beer t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the beer &amp; beer lovers in your life!  http://t.co/w3RjZmBHYo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anthony “Tony” Harris, CSECO President and CEO, receives an Honorary Doctorate in Engineering from Purdue University  http://t.co/iXPYz5PqJA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advertising is the life of trade. - Calvin Coolidge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fool and his money are soon accepted into the highest social circles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be successful, the first thing to do is fall in love with your work. - Sister Mary Lauretta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would rather entertain and hope that people learned something than educate people and hope they were entertained. - Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Triple Crown Sports Organization  http://t.co/rFRdPQwo2z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We live in a dark and romantic and quite tragic world. --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If opportunity doesn't knock, build a door. - Milton Berle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Kalin Twins  http://t.co/xkVyBqRTZI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Hire a Strategy Consulting Firm?  http://t.co/RN4OuOFcrv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Barbara Acklin a Great Singer http://t.co/lAOLIaXLj2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool Batman Comfy Throw - Stay Warm and Cool :&gt;)  http://t.co/T2BDtuu8NQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heredity:  what makes the father and mother of a teen-ager wonder about each other]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may be dumb, but I'm not stupid.  Terry Bradshaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of David Gates  http://t.co/ZKfTQxnAXA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Mary Hopkin  http://t.co/SdTfDaGbDx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He looks like a girl.  Marlon Brando on Leonardo DiCaprio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not anorexic. I'm from Texas. Are there people from Texas that are anorexic? I've never heard of one. And that includes me. Jessica S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I prefer the company of peasants because they have not been educated sufficiently to reason incorrectly. - Michel de Montaigne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bank is a place that will lend you money if you can prove that you don't need it. - Bob Hope]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes as much energy to wish as it does to plan!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The purity of a person's heart can be quickly measured by how they regard animals - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[History of Mojang - The makers of Minecraft - http://t.co/40yNO1hwTP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of High Heel Shoes  http://t.co/4xMNIxj6vU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You could get rich manufacturing crutches for lame excuses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A baseball game is simply a nervous breakdown divided into nine innings. - Earl Wilson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of James Brown  http://t.co/6cLnaG9Lzb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is tool cool a LED Kitchen Sink Faucet Sprayer Nozzle - make the water turn blue!  http://t.co/BxQi5UtEpI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Supertramp  http://t.co/3syhastvMQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Tips on Using Other Websites for Link Building  http://t.co/EjVFsszlcW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the math geek in your life - the math clock... http://t.co/UZ9PAow64c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your Business Guide for Small Business Internet Marketing  http://t.co/pS7EpVU81m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating history of Wrigley Field!  http://t.co/L8ifDwzJdy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet!  A 3D Printer - Very Awesome!  You have to check this out! http://t.co/JVZGdaIK3o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To me, true rock 'n' roll has a lot of bottom in it.  - Little Richard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Don Henley  http://t.co/lPewiWEtvv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What you don't know won't hurt you but it provides a lot amusement for other people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To fill the shoes of rock 'n' roll, because of the family I have, is a really hard thing. - Kelly Osbourne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never expected to be anybody important.  - Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is Renter's Insurance?  http://t.co/4G1RA60Gei]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was twelve when I read my first scifi magazine - Philip K. Dick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cheap Divorce Lawyers: Avoiding Exorbitant Legal Costs  http://t.co/F16zke2TCC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Dave Mason  http://t.co/S5vgzRjl69]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It ain't over 'til it's over - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome baseball t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the baseball lovers in your life!   http://t.co/4iGSWcFthl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Paul Simon - His Biography  http://t.co/zvAnPFOoHx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A cat is a puzzle for which there is no solution. - Hazel Nicholson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The noblest search is the search for excellence - Lyndon B. Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I went through baseball as a player to be named later." - Joe Garagiola]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Allman Brothers Band  http://t.co/jbusLPUyD4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Beverly Hillbillies – An American Classic TV Series  http://t.co/8HEjqIVIbZ]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>