<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The only reason anyone thinks I'm worth anything is because of you. –Aladdin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're my ohana, and I'll always love you. –Lilo (Lilo &amp; Stitch 2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Extraordinary things happen to extraordinary people. –Reepicheep (The Chronicles of Narnia)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't forget, if the future should take you away, that you'll always be part of me. –Toy Story 3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't you think there are more wishes inside of you? –Piglet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's time to take charge, live your own. –Goofy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even when you grow old, home should be where the heart is. –Belle (Beauty and the Beast Broadway)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you smile, it's pure perfection. It shines through everything you do. –Ariel (Little Mermaid Series)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you don't know where you are going, any road will get you there. –Cheshire Cat (Alice in Wonderland)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A whole new world. That’s where we'll be. A thrilling chase, a wondrous place, for you and me. –Aladdin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am who I am. Why can’t you accept that about me? –Miss Piggy (The Muppets)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am a princess. I am brave sometimes, I am scared sometimes. Sometimes I am brave even when I’m scared. –Disney Princess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life may be swift and fleeting. Hope may die yet love's beautiful music comes each day like the dawn. –Bambi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My heart's an open book. You'd see it all at once if only you would look. –Ariel (Little Mermaid Broadway)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tod: “You're my very best friend.” | Copper: “And you're mine, too.” –The Fox and the Hound]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why can't they understand the way we feel? They just don't trust what they can’t explain. –Tarzan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not every superhero has powers, you know. You can be super without them. –Buddy (The Incredibles)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love doesn't wanna miss the future or stay in the past. It will always hold on, but never hold you back. –Hannah Montana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[KIM. KARDASHIAN. WHAT. ARE. YOU. THINKING: http://t.co/D95JugB9mv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russell: “But I want to help!” | Carl Fredricksen: “I don't want your help, I want you safe.” –Up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Start at the beginning, and when you come to the end, stop. –Mad Hatter (Alice in Wonderland)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any life worth living isn't life just filled with ease. –Toaster (Brave Little Toaster)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My arms around you will keep you safe and warm. This bond between us can’t be broken. –Kala (Tarzan)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where do words go when they are not spoken? Are they hiding, shy or frightened, crying or smiling? –Book of Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The truth sounds insane sometimes, but that doesn't mean it's not the truth. –Linguini (Ratatouille)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With a friend, it's just a little easier. You'll see, it's a little bit more fun. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dreams do come true, and maybe something wonderful will happen. –Giselle (Enchanted)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know it's tough, but heroes have to make the tough choices, don't they? –King Candy (Wreck-It Ralph)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's no smile. That's a mask of pain. –Mushu (Mulan II)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What we want and what we need are entirely different things. –Pleakey (Lilo &amp; Stitch 2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are never too old for a Disney movie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There was a lot left in me. I just never got a chance to show them. –Doc Hudson (Cars)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just needed to get out on my own, live my own life. And I did, and it’s great. –Simba (The Lion King)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wish a little wish. Hope a simple hope. Dream a happy dream. –Pinocchio (Disney Hallmark)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sing a happy song whenever things go wrong. Just sing and play the day away. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest treasures cannot be held in your hands. They're held within your heart. –Disney Fairies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish I knew the way to fix a friendship to put together what has come apart. –Piglet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need to live my own life, follow my own path. I wish for things to change, and that's the problem. –Merida (Brave)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Without inspiration, we would perish. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lilo: “You think I can do it?” | Stitch: “We do together.” –Lilo &amp; Stitch 2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes the impossible can become possible if you're awesome. –Rhino (Bolt)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can only dream of you wherever you are. I’ll hear you laugh. I’ll see you smile. I’ll be with you just for a while. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As the years go by, our friendship will never die. You're gonna see it's our destiny. You've got a friend in me. –Toy Story]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes the things that you’re looking for, you can’t see with your eyes. You have to see them with your heart. –Peter Pan (Disney Dreams)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He'll find his own way to tell you with the little things he'll do. That's how you know he’s your love. –Giselle (Enchanted)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You won't believe this law: http://t.co/Zylt016lEL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the morning comes and the sun begins to rise, I will lose you because it's just a dream. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perhaps, someday the dreams that I wish will come true. –Cinderella]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You’re only a fool if you give up. –Jafar (Aladdin)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I tried to fit in. I really do. I just can’t. Sometimes I feel like I really don’t belong here. –Hercules]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friendship is a very comforting thing to have. –Christopher Robin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just because you haven’t found your talent yet, doesn’t mean you don’t have one. –Kermit (The Muppets)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You've always been there for me. You've never given up on me. I just need you back. –Merida (Brave)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I’m way up here, it’s crystal clear that now I’m in a whole new world with you. –Jasmine (Aladdin)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You dream about going up there, but that is a big mistake. Just look at the world around you. –Sebastian (Little Mermaid)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There’s no more powerful force in the world than true love. –The King (Cinderella 3)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes when you lose your way, it’s really just as well ‘cause you find yourself. –Cars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I kept saying how much I needed you, but you needed me more. –Lilo (Lilo and Stitch 2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hunny is sweet, but friendship is sweeter. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What makes someone special? I suppose it all depends. It's what's unique in each of us. –Ariel (Little Mermaid Series)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people talk to animals. Not many listen though. That's the problem. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you're true to who you are, you will always find your star. –Disney Fairie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That awkward moment when Adolf Hitler is actually a big fan of this Disney character: http://t.co/DlsXRSBPtV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're only in trouble if you get caught. I'm in trouble. –Aladdin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s just no use, no use at all. I can’t believe, not anymore. There’s nothing left to believe in. Nothing. –Cinderella]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I always like to look on the optimistic side of life, but I am realistic enough to know that life is a complex matter. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Believe in the future. The world is getting better. There still is plenty of opportunity. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just because you can’t understand something, it doesn’t mean it’s wrong. –Arthur (The Sword in the Stone)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When life gets you down, you know what you gotta do? Just keep swimming, just keep swimming. –Dory (Finding Nemo)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Piglet: “How do you spell love?” | Pooh: “You don’t spell it. You feel it.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don’t stress over anything that you can’t change. –Mickey Mouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never say goodbye, because saying goodbye means going away. And going away means forgetting. –Peter Pan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you can’t say something nice, don’t say nothing at all. –Thumper (Bambi)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yesterday is history, tomorrow is a mystery, but today is a gift, that’s why its called the present. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For every laugh, there should be a tear. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Phillip: “We've met before.” | Aurora: “We have?” | Phillip: “Of course. Once upon a dream.” –Sleeping Beauty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You’ll always be part of my favorite story. –Belle (Enchanted Tales)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can only dream of you wherever you are. I’ll hear you laugh. I’ll see you smile. I’ll be with you just for a while. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dreams are like stars. You can't touch them, but if you follow them, they will lead you to your destiny. –Spudnick (Space Buddies)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You want something done, you've got to do it yourself. –Sebastian (Little Mermaid)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When there's too much to do, don't let it bother you. Forget your troubles. –Snow White]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s kind of fun to do the impossible. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Simba: "But you're not scared of anything." | Mufasa: "I was today. I thought I might lose you." –The Lion King]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please tell me why anyone would get this tattoo: http://t.co/zdCfmNqvQY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dreams do come true, and maybe something wonderful will happen. –Giselle (Enchanted)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could be worse. Not sure how, but it could be. –Eeyore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Miracles are real but they need someone to believe, so they can happen. –Disney Fairies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The miracle is to make a friend who will stand by you when millions are against you. –Mickey Mouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When You See It... http://t.co/7zpggBQe5H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am bad, and that's good. I will never be good and that's not bad. There's no one I'd rather be than me. –Ralph (Wreck-It Ralph)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My heart's about to break. Come and find me. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'll be in my heart from this day on, now, and forever more. –Kala (Tarzan)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listen to your mother. It's a scary world out there. Mother knows best. –Mother Gothel (Tangled)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am who I am. Why can't you accept that about me? –Miss Piggy (The Muppets)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There must be somebody who understands out there, somewhere. –Tarzan (Tarzan Broadway)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone can be superheroes. Everyone can be super. –Buddy (The Incredibles)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just you and me, and I could be part of your world. –Ariel (Little Mermaid)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A true hero isn't measured by the size of his strength, but by the strength of his heart. –Zeus (Hercules)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one should marry someone they don't love. –Shang (Mulan II)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's time to let go. Everything's gonna be all right. –Dory (Finding Nemo)]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>