<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Never make fun of the geeks, one day they will be your boss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like wrestling a gorilla- you don't quit when you're tired, you quit when the gorilla is tired - Robert Strauss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Media is a Helpful Tool in Connecting with Customers  http://t.co/3dTzJyQl7m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The winner ain't the one with the fastest car, it's the one who refuses to lose. - Dale Earnhardt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The dog was created especially for children. He is the God of frolic. - Henry Ward Beecher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of Skylanders: Spyro’s Adventure  http://t.co/Tr3wlHyQNQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Early History of Marvel Comics  http://t.co/gvb2tJOpjI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Resources for Home Brewing  http://t.co/IB1zkhcZ7q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Advanced Weight Scales and Body Monitoring – Keeping Track of your Body Weight  http://t.co/YY9CtuMnHu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The noblest search is the search for excellence - Lyndon B. Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time is a friend. Do not kill it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But I'm a rock 'n' roll singer; that's my livelihood, my occupation.  - Little Richard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Air Supply  http://t.co/p4MmAI9oMt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Design is a constant challenge to balance comfort with luxe, the practical with the desirable. - Donna Karan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was a science fiction junkie for a long time. - William Hurt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She's got double D's! You can't cover those suckers up! Jessica Simpson's Dad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A computer lets you make more mistakes faster than any invention in human history - with the possible exceptions of handguns and tequila.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man has never really tested his strength until he tries to lift a mortgage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't steal second base and keep one foot on first. - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A classic TV sit-com - the fascinating history of Andy Griffith - they didn’t get along with sweet Aunt Bee?  http://t.co/aGbLnghass]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future is always beginning now. - Mark Strand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating Introduction to Marmalade Insurance: How to Select an Insurance Agency  http://t.co/YaVAkXqpCw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winning is everything. The only ones who remember you when you come second are your wife and your dog. - Damon Hill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get a Hunger Games Mockingjay Pin - http://t.co/CkTHt1gQ16]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Don Henley  http://t.co/zZfLVxmF57]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips on Getting the Cheapest Car Loan  http://t.co/BVwxORPFC3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Gloria Gaynor - The Queen of Disco  http://t.co/NUk54INe63]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriousness is stupidity sent to college. P. J. O'Rourke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The Official How I Met Your Mother Premium Grey Silk Suit Jammies http://t.co/ULLzMnOrwn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the sun refused to shine I would still be loving you. When mountains crumble to the sea there will still be you &amp; me - Led Zeppelin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't pay good wages because I have a lot of money; I have a lot of money because I pay good wages. - Robert Bosch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to focus on my salad.  Martha Stewart when asked about her stock dealings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I mean, we're lost on an island, running from boars and monsters -- freakin' polar bears.  Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Strategy Consulting Firms to Avoid  http://t.co/Tj6jbwuzMl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prometheus is reaching out for the stars with an empty grin on his face. - Arthur Koestler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Firefighters recently rescued two people from an industrial clothes dryer. They were listed in stable condition but missing one sock!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I grew up in a world that told girls they couldn't play rock 'n' roll. - Joan Jett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love any movie that has a retarded person working at Starbucks.  Chris Kattan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Adoption Part II - the Bulgaria Phase  http://t.co/AOBV8ATvDz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dis Be Da Place]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't get too caught up in making money or having a job, get excited about the fact that you can design your life. Darren L. Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spock. This child is about to wipe out every living thing on Earth. Now, what do you suggest we do? spank it? - Dr. McCoy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Skiing in Canada - learn more!  http://t.co/DeDgbZtvXu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Green Acres is an American sitcom classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/iD75ae5I5W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 15 - The Cowden Protocol  http://t.co/NfoVyLRaaI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make it so! - Engage! - Captain Picard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am the best in baseball. - Reggie Jackson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was twelve when I read my first scifi magazine - Philip K. Dick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Cool History of Mustard  http://t.co/vwGEjbUvLm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A classic TV sit-com - the fascinating history of Andy Griffith - they didn’t get along with sweet Aunt Bee?  http://t.co/aGbLnghass]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As far as I'm concerned, there won't be a Beatles reunion as long as John Lennon remains dead. - George Harrison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awe cool - A Lock N' load target alarm clock/Gun alarm clock - shoot the dang thing! http://t.co/RFAMk0C34a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I actually don't understand a word Paula's saying anymore. It's like a new language.  Simon Cowell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is what remains after one has forgotten everything he learned in school. - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The good Lord gave you a body that can stand most anything. It's your mind you have to convince. - Vincent Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think MTV should consider using subtitles. Half the time, even I can't understand what the **** I'm talking about.  Ozzy Osbourne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is not the strongest of the species that survive, nor the most intelligent, but the one most responsive to change. - Charles Darwin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Shelley Fabares  http://t.co/5wUEQgfFEE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Whispers  http://t.co/UtALohqArz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Leapy Lee the Classic Rock Artist?  http://t.co/FPyw3Ykf5b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think too little, you are sure to talk too much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Andy Kim  http://t.co/SFpfHGL3sh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Home is where -- . You hang your head]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Star Wars  http://t.co/v8sUL1g7kk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I could walk a mile in ur shoes but I already know they are just as uncomfortable as mine. Lets walk next to each other instead Lynda Meyers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can Archery Be a Great Fitness Activity?  http://t.co/9b7wOXuD0d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of France Joli  http://t.co/5viqhDBTU6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Old age means realizing you will never own all the dogs you wanted to. - Joe Gores]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Music of Hot Chocolate  http://t.co/6XEdPITFOA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[London Weight Loss Salon sign: "We value the pound."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Modern Glo Night Light - Night Light Fashion!  http://t.co/5NWdEy9JNK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Interesting History of Dos XX Beer  http://t.co/7UZEahwTvT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are three things you can do in a baseball game. You can win, or you can lose, or it can rain. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to C.S. Lewis  http://t.co/Rf9Q4zu0TN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating Introduction to Tom's Shoes Company  http://t.co/JbmjQrYjxh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Interesting Burger Facts and History  http://t.co/vwGEjbUvLm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The absolute fundamental aim is to make money out of satisfying customers. - John Egan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If having a soul means being able to feel love and loyalty and gratitude, then animals are better off than a lot of humans - James Herriot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is where you &amp; I are different. Because this is all I want to talk about. Letterman to Paris when she didn’t want to talk about jail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Clash  http://t.co/vqVQcZa9DV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The trick is to stop thinking of it as your money - IRS auditor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Cat. He walked by himself, and all places were alike to him. - Rudyard Kipling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rock and roll is here to stay. - Neil Young]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suitor: A guy who thinks he's throwing a girl a line when all the time he's being roped in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep your face to the sunshine and you cannot see the shadows. - Helen Keller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The one thing my mom will let me get is a nice shoe sometimes. - Chloe Moretz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My own mother told me I didn't have a shot in hell of winning tonight.  A shocked Katherine Heigl upon winning an Emmy for Grey's Anatomy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't be melancholy in fashion because people don't respond to it. - Isaac Mizrahi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dammit, man! I'm a doctor, not a physicist! - Leonard 'Bones' McCoy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Credit card sized took kit with 2-Inch Serrated Knife, can/bottle opener &amp; Flat screwdriver, tweezers &amp; toothpick! http://t.co/y3j0zGkU1P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about Oakland, California  http://t.co/XA6oCRRDsR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Religion Both Protestant and Catholics  http://t.co/sAvFEkO58d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many a man doesn't start living until he's married. And then he's finished.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Do Parents Pick Favorite Things for their Kids?  http://t.co/kpZcqARaVM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If opportunity doesn't knock, build a door. - Milton Berle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Gladys Knight and the Pips  http://t.co/x0GswqEW5W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't see pitches down the middle anymore - not even in batting practice. -  Hank Aaron]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have never let my schooling interfere with my education. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Musical Legend – Johnny Adams  http://t.co/CIbfPZ9Ior]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think education is expensive, try ignorance - Derek Bok]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>