<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Telecommunications Analyst: Senior Telecommunications Analyst Job Locations US-DC-Washington Job ID 8983 Minimum Clearance Required US Citizen Responsibilities Migration of voice telecommunications circuits to SIP trunking. Integration of Avaya… https://t.co/3KMkbxMqEz https://t.co/LslGM3fIrx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Product Manager / Data Analytics – Franklin, TN or Eden Prairie, MN: Be a driver of change and run part of the marketing machine at Optum. Optum is part of UnitedHealth Group and a key leader across most major segments of the U.S. health care… https://t.co/O6YbMq26Ch https://t.co/EhpSghZGOJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Healthcare Economic Consultant – Southern California: No industry is moving faster than health care. And no organization is better positioned to lead health care forward than UnitedHealth Group. We need attention to every detail with an eye for… https://t.co/omHxQ1F7mb https://t.co/dfzandDq3Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Software Engineer: Principal Software Engineer Embedded Systems (Belmont, CA), responsible for shaping and strengthening the electronics development for Audi and the VW Group; targeted towards Audi electronics; development, optimization, and… https://t.co/vh9MkG5mri https://t.co/T2H8sWdl20]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Softwr Dvlpr, IBM Corp, San Jose, CA: Provide scalable &amp; high performing cloud srvcs, incl IaaS, PaaS, &amp; SaaS. Review functional UI reqs, w/ focus on workflow &amp; usability. Implement UI functionality. Eval &amp; resolve defect tix. Utilize… https://t.co/guP7hBx372 https://t.co/Y6UvEPbyi7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analytics Data Integration Developer: Senior Healthcare Analytics Data Integration Developer (Memorial Health Services, 17360 Brookhurst Street, Fountain Valley, CA 92708) POSITION DUTIES: Develop data integration solutions to end user and application… https://t.co/LUKZDSqnnE https://t.co/cD9WmYZuAM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Service Delivery Manager – Infrastructure Platform: Description: THE COMPANY Are you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart… https://t.co/Z2lLPtGxRE https://t.co/jkswULcFDx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spotify Subscriptions Helped The Streaming Company Win Listeners: The streaming company proved it could get the Napster generation to subscribe. But will Spotify's paywall make it profitable? https://t.co/qCq2XEHCkR https://t.co/CmlAetEyOO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JRSS Network Operation Controller: Description:The Defense and Intelligence Group of Leidos, has an opening for Network Operation Controller for JRSS NOC at Scott AFB, IL. PROGRAM SUMMARY: Defense Information Systems Agency (DISA), located at Scott AFB,… https://t.co/ABwefQOSPF https://t.co/OPORS4J6VS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Applications Specialist (Business Intelligence and Data Analyst): Senior Applications Specialist (Business Intelligence and Data Analyst) Puget Sound Workers’ Compensation Trust and Unemployment Pool has an exciting opportunity for a Senior… https://t.co/Uxxr5O58PL https://t.co/iQYcQEcztV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Project Manager #80165P: IT Project Manager (Vacancy #80165P) IT Services (ITS) at Iowa State is seeking qualified applicants for an experienced IT Project Manager. This position will be responsible for managing small to large technology related… https://t.co/6AQFo8e1n8 https://t.co/exqUjS7DtR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Technology Systems Technician: Information Technology Systems Technician Eden Foods seeks a motivated, detail oriented individual to join the Information Technology team here in Clinton, Michigan. Information Technology systems are built… https://t.co/43Jt0CvOqv https://t.co/CtyCi8Xl9J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering: ENGINEERING Applied Materials, Inc. has openings in Santa Clara/ Sunnyvale, CA: Process Engineer (Req #8C91007) Design, collect data, analyze and compile reports on a variety of difficult process engineering experiments; Process Engineer… https://t.co/LIun9gFhT8 https://t.co/Mve7uaaHNz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Level III, File Transfer Engineer # 180031119: Associate Level III, File Transfer Engineer Columbus, OH. Design, Develop &amp; maintain various MFTS platforms (Secure Transport, AXWAY API gateway, File Mover, IBM Sterling secure proxy etc.).… https://t.co/t32vAvIyHt https://t.co/Tbg6nitjUP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software QA Engineer: Palo Alto Networks, Inc. is seeking applicants for the following positions in Santa Clara, CA: Sr. Software QA Engineer(s) (Job #442) &amp; Software QA Engineer(s) (Job #180): Dvlp &amp; execute sw test plans for ntwk security firewall… https://t.co/AzcVfCY6TR https://t.co/YkY4R5LLWo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer I, ITD (Job# PT-0121): Senior Software Engineer I, ITD (Job# PT-0121) position available in San Diego, CA. Equal Employer Opportunity: Race, Gender, Veteran, Disabled. recblid 56wccihcu8q14vj7mvweuvxmcz4e1u https://t.co/Qj5bWnPoRP https://t.co/X5RW1MlS1m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Design Engineer: Design Engineer Application Software sought by RGB Systems DBA Extron Electronics in Anaheim, CA. Work on team of highly skilled software engineers to build cutting-edge software applications focused on the AV industry. recblid… https://t.co/p3GodMB6Hv https://t.co/b5t7M1ew72]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Engineer – Software Quality #2018-43102: Senior Engineer – Software Quality Software Quality sought by DISH Network, LLC in Englewood, Colorado. Design, develop, and maintain DISH digital TV and movie delivery software; participate in release… https://t.co/bwFXbxQGD6 https://t.co/oDwhWA5yW1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Specialist #4137: Information Specialist – (Rural Health Information Hub) The Center for Rural Health (CRH) at the University of North Dakota is seeking experienced and talented applicants to serve as an Information Specialist for the Rural… https://t.co/98t9CtsFYe https://t.co/dPH2XWdou2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Scientist: PROJECT SCIENTIST sought by University of California, Irvine in Irvine, CA. Conduct research on human-computer interaction applied to the “Internet of Things” including electronic devices and software applications for advancements in… https://t.co/m5ckIu7y4j https://t.co/4c69d26JzO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Groups Allege YouTube Is Violating Law That Protects Kids: In complaint to the FTC, child-health, privacy, and consumer groups say YouTube is targeting kids improperly. https://t.co/7xNmXwELBO https://t.co/IA8U6LLA0p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Operational Risk Oversight Leader Consultant 5-End User Computing Tools Leader: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented people who will put… https://t.co/RnfWCAkDeT https://t.co/76nBqqtOI6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C++ Software Engineer – Santa Clara, CA: C++ Software Engineer Santa Clara, CA Full Time Position Job Description: Software engineer with 5 years experience to work on modem interfacing layers and modem interfacing SW communication protocols for clients… https://t.co/MXAEH7nbxu https://t.co/hmL7hWYMcW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front End Developer (must have TS/SCI): An analytics and data solutions company that delivers customized solutions to clients, is seeking a qualified Front End Developer with an active TS/SCI clearance to join their growing team. This person will serve… https://t.co/HMCXMBBeqD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Integration and Test Engineer: 109224BR Senior Integration and Test Engineer CO – Aurora Would you like to work in a collaborative environment at a state of the art facility in Colorado? Then join our Raytheon team of engineers solving problems… https://t.co/v4N8Q2u9ZQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Entry Level Hyper-Converged Infrastructure (HCI) Software Developer: Entry Level Hyper-Converged Infrastructure (HCI) Software Developer at Hewlett Packard Enterprise CompanyTo top Skip Navigation Hewlett Packard Enterprise Careers – Overview – Search… https://t.co/JzWKGYbE9z https://t.co/XBdKn7DfyH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Administrator: IT Partners is seeking Junior to Mid tier resources with System Aministrator experience. We desire people who want to belong to a successful team and who want to support our Nation in their vital mission. We value professionalism,… https://t.co/nuubKCMKAX https://t.co/VPrHrB6q2O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proposal Developer/Writer – Grant Writer III: Job Details: Proposal Developer/Writer – Grant Writer III – USU home – A-Z index – calendars – MyUSU – contact – directory – Home Page – Search Jobs – View All Jobs – Internal Jobs – Applicant Login – How to… https://t.co/hCYxnSwGCi https://t.co/5c581ehbME]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Data Analytics Engineer- Sr Cons I: Where good people build rewarding careers. Think that working in the insurance field can’t be exciting, rewarding and challenging? Think again. You’ll help us reinvent protection and retirement to improve customers’… https://t.co/SoaKxNd49X https://t.co/hGHFjZRWhB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director Clinical Relationships – Business Process Offshoring – US Telecommute: Optum is a health services business dedicated to making the health system work better for everyone. We serve people throughout the entire health system. This allows us to… https://t.co/H9YznUyYX4 https://t.co/KEkZ2bO4zg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Healthcare Economics Analyst – Irvine, CA: You are a thought leader who thrives on developing new solutions to solve tough challenges. As a critical member of our business analysis team, you will help rewrite the future of UnitedHealth Group. Here, your… https://t.co/y0Nf5cdIdY https://t.co/O3yF80iVhv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advisory SAP Technical Manager: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about us at… https://t.co/ePazHams9D https://t.co/aK4mIYgCRJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feds Seize https://t.co/eFfI3ZnVRM, Site Linked to Sex Trafficking: A notice on the website of https://t.co/eFfI3ZnVRM said it had been seized by multiple federal agencies. The site was at the center of a debate over amending a bedrock internet law. https://t.co/K6UfwqrCto https://t.co/7VFZ8OCCzd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Healthcare Data Analyst – Irvine, CA: You are a thought leader who thrives on developing new solutions to solve tough challenges. As a critical member of our business analysis team, you will help rewrite the future of UnitedHealth Group. Here,… https://t.co/w7xRLglpJ0 https://t.co/gXlXacJuEf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Healthcare Economics Consultant – Telecommute in Minnesota: As the Sr. Healthcare Economic Consultant you will support and validate provider network (physicians, hospitals, pharmacies, ancillary facilities, etc.) contracting including value based… https://t.co/eAVvqk81aT https://t.co/eqDHaBh4gN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Healthcare Economic Consultant – Southern California: No industry is moving faster than health care. And no organization is better positioned to lead health care forward than UnitedHealth Group. We need attention to every detail with an eye for… https://t.co/iyjBFhYy9w https://t.co/46PQZfP1kg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Requirements and Technical Analyst – Telecommute from anywhere: When your work is as critical as ours, there’s nothing left to chance. At UnitedHealth Group, we’re changing the future of health care and we have the expertise, advanced technology and… https://t.co/OoYfFInrYG https://t.co/skrKHo4dHO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst III: Description: THE COMPANY Are you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable,… https://t.co/bqvh3FwfC5 https://t.co/62RaxOjX58]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instructional Designer – US Telecommute: Here at UnitedHealth Group, you’re expected and empowered to be your best, to grow and to develop your skills. Join us and help people live healthier lives while doing your life’s best work.(sm)   This position is… https://t.co/JfKMtA5Rj3 https://t.co/enMpqjagph]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Business Analyst – West Valley City, UT or US Telecommute: You believe data can help reshape the future, and you find yourself loving the thrill of diving into challenging analysis. At UnitedHealth Group, you’ll find an organization that will… https://t.co/i0D6UIggly https://t.co/lj6Ps3V3oI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advisory Financial Services Oracle Accounts Payable: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more… https://t.co/hKKeVY0qNl https://t.co/JVfmTHpByg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Operations Technician – II: CenturyLink (NYSE: CTL) is a global communications and IT services company focused on connecting its customers to the power of the digital world. CenturyLink offers network and data systems management, big data analytics,… https://t.co/BDEKpDbXF0 https://t.co/AvBfvEMnW5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Reporting, BI Business Analyst – Eden Prairie, MN: How do you invent the future of health care? It takes the dedication of thousands of people all pulling in the same direction. OptumCare Care Services is seeking a Senior Reporting/BI Business… https://t.co/Dobldzn6Y4 https://t.co/CW7neY5zkN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YouTube Shooting Spree Injures 4, Kills 1: Police say 1 dead and 4 wounded in shooting at YouTube headquarters in San Bruno, California, Tuesday afternoon. https://t.co/ztJ8dg0TJ7 https://t.co/HR39qnkx2v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle EBS Business Analyst (Chelsea): *** No one with less than 2 years industry experience will be considered. *** *** No third party candidates will be considered. *** Candidates MUST have a minimum of specific domain experience and no resumes will be… https://t.co/k9t4RWs8FC https://t.co/H9WU4WsTUv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager- Real Estate: Company Summary Crown Castle works around the country to build and maintain the infrastructure behind the worlds most revolutionary technologies. Crown Castle owns, operates and leases more than 40,000 cell towers and over… https://t.co/WwHA5tdVtz https://t.co/kXa6kgS1VM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Underground Utilities Construction Project Manager: Ripple Effect Consulting is currently in search of a Project Manager for a underground utilities (wet) large Infrastructure Construction Company in Denver, CO. This is a Permanent / Full-Time role.… https://t.co/zKYmHToZqH https://t.co/2xIS8CJpUs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Underwriting Data Analyst: The Underwriting Data Analyst primary responsibility is to design, draft, and perform audits for underwriting, assuring company standards are maintained with a focus on developing and implementing solutions for improvement. In… https://t.co/HIT8m1r7pi https://t.co/nm4Qru8Oiu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer – Curriculum Management: Kuali builds open source higher ed solutions in a competitive space where users are just waiting to be delighted. Why join us? Our work matters were helping our customers improve the quality of education by… https://t.co/M2aP0da0IZ https://t.co/OMfVUHXjUZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Embedded Software Engineer: We are looking for an Senior Embedded Software Engineer with extensive experience in the design, development, and implementation of software, primarily in C, in embedded applications, specifically avionics. The main… https://t.co/J8SNGCfEsh https://t.co/2Ky1OnrIs2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager: We are seeking an experienced Senior Project Manager to join our growing team. Responsibilities include: * Development and management of project timelines with adherence to agreed-upon milestones * Budget tracking, bi-weekly… https://t.co/nDbpxKbqRB https://t.co/xOrmkTGufz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pega Architect: Job Description: Pega certified CLSA with more than 8 years strong exp in Pega along with Decisioning or marketing skill set for location Dallas, TX Top 3 responsibilities you would shoulder and execute: * Pega Decisioning solution and… https://t.co/yYjGB70OOH https://t.co/QpJJs0WSz8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Real Estate and Construciton Project Manager: PURPOSE AND SCOPE: Provides project leadership for the building of FMCNA dialysis clinics. Manages multiple construction projects in a fast paced environment from conception to post occupancy. Coordinates… https://t.co/rPN5fPvZxF https://t.co/lh8F3Pf9JO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Program Manager – Telecommute: Expanding access to affordable, high quality health care starts here. This is where some of the most innovative ideas in health care are created every day. This is where bold people with big ideas are writing the… https://t.co/dwSBtyZKOM https://t.co/pv5rFnHQIs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Reporting Analyst – Development Focus – Telecommute: We’ll put you in the driver’s seat on vital projects that have strategic importance to our mission of helping people lead healthier lives. Yes, we share a mission that inspires. We need your… https://t.co/09ziq1daqb https://t.co/8vojPY92xG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Business Process Analyst / Project Manager – Eden Prairie, MN (Preferred) or Franklin, TN: Be part of something daring and bold and help rewrite the history of Optum. We’re changing the landscape of health care with people like you, who really… https://t.co/nmn9Gt0oW0 https://t.co/dCV3jMk6Yh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-Google Executive Opens a School for AI, With China's Help: Kai-Fu Lee, head of the investment firm Sinovation Ventures, is training Chinese professors to teach artificial-intelligence techniques. https://t.co/7nUCKQdX5k https://t.co/LNr8qL46g7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CCM Technical Trainer – US Telecommute: Energize your career with one of Healthcare’s fastest growing companies.     You dream of a great career with a great company – where you can make an impact and help people.  We dream of giving you the opportunity… https://t.co/2zXhgAR80s https://t.co/GJILdexLjc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Services Advisory Cloud Senior Associate: PwC Advisory helps our clients with their most challenging imperatives from strategy through execution. We combine the breadth of knowledge of over 48,000 global professionals with deep industry… https://t.co/fLUemndnP1 https://t.co/ugr9wfnsIv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Salesforce Business Analyst – HRIS – Minnetonka, MN: Here, you’ll help attract, lead, support and reward our most valuable asset: our high caliber people. Here, you’re expected and empowered to be your best, to grow and to develop your skills. Be… https://t.co/8K84c6QKiP https://t.co/aHQVmWVB68]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Content Writer – Minnetonka, MN: If you want to achieve more in your mission of health care, you have to be really smart about the business of health care. Challenge yourself, your peers and our industry by shaping what health care looks like and doing… https://t.co/QTcptEL8My https://t.co/9j1NZxmIuz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chief Information Officer, UnitedHealthcare Global:           The Chief Information Officer (CIO) for UnitedHealthcare Global (UHCG) is responsible for providing overall leadership, establishing and maintaining technical roadmaps, and representing all… https://t.co/Ih7jvKYT0n https://t.co/FXqykzcVA6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Business Analyst / Project Manager – San Antonio, TX: As a Senior Business Analyst / Project Manager, you will be an integral part of the WellMed Network Operations team. This role will manage initiatives to control cost, increase revenue and… https://t.co/vG1PJgagaF https://t.co/vsKgZefPnS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/oc9IvDI3kv User Support Specialist: Combine two of the fastest-growing fields on the planet with a culture of performance, collaboration and opportunity and this is what you get. Leading edge technology in an industry that’s improving the… https://t.co/gCPuNXoni0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interim Service Owner – Voice: Interim Service Owner – VoiceVITA91557511*Chester, VA*Oversight of the client’s Telecommunications Services.  The Service Owner – Voice and Video functions as the business owner for delivery of Voice and Video strategies,… https://t.co/NTklxwjXJC https://t.co/nx34uCQwpQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Provider Network Reporting Analyst – Minnetonka, MN: There are changes happening in health care that go beyond the basics we hear in the news. People like you and organizations like UnitedHealth Group are driving ever higher levels of sophistication in… https://t.co/9KrIBMrwMu https://t.co/95qk6Jv1zb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manager – Salesforce Business Process / Systems Analyst – Multiple Locations: Reviews assigned business processes from end-to-end to identify and address operational, financial and technological risks.  Identifies opportunities to improve efficiency or… https://t.co/K62bL2jLVj https://t.co/WoK0767zxp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Report Analyst, Talent Analytics – Minnetonka, MN: If you want to achieve more in your mission of health care, you have to be really smart about the business of health care. Which is why your performance and innovation will find a reception here like… https://t.co/kSiLyfq3EB https://t.co/GFHhcM9Mzt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook Exposed 87 Million Users to Cambridge Analytica: Racebook CEO Mark Zuckerberg says the fixes to Facebook's data-sharing woes will be a "multi-year" process. https://t.co/4YyWonF8Xl https://t.co/v8jzUXIMHL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SalesForce Director- Advisory Financial Services: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more… https://t.co/qDYPmjCkjM https://t.co/nZyBkvektK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Systems Analyst – Division of Supervision and Regulation: The Information Systems is responsible for assisting with the implementation, maintenance, and support of automated distributed processing systems and their components. The Analyst… https://t.co/mW02JYuWI8 https://t.co/1udL5GyWvc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer Evangelist and Trainer – USA / Europe: Apache Flink is one of the most active and fastest-growing open-source projects in the Apache Software Foundation and is used in production by enterprises including Alibaba, Uber, ING, Netflix, and more.… https://t.co/e87v4rR7dR https://t.co/uXatBnD1XJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Ethics Analyst: 110836BR Principal Ethics Analyst AZ – Tucson Headquartered in Waltham, Massachusetts, Raytheon is a technology leader specializing in defense, homeland security and other government markets throughout the world. With more than… https://t.co/hh1QBiVKcD https://t.co/25bthamsVD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mgr Programs 2:   Job Description – Mgr Programs 2 (18006374) Mgr Programs 2 Requisition ID : 18006374 Location : United States-Maryland-Linthicum US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation Assistance: Relocation assistance may be… https://t.co/ahAmckyTiH https://t.co/I680yzvUjn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer Title: Software Engineer??Mandatory skills:?Software Engineer, Scala Developer, Scala Programmer ,Government, State of, federal, county, Department of ,AJAX, Javascript, JQuery, JQueryUI ,Scala ,Funcational Language,… https://t.co/fwAkc60m9C https://t.co/X1NtEn6nDb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Construction Project Manager (#3597AB032218): COMPANY DESCRIPTION * Company has nearly 20 years of industry experience * Specializes in managing construction products for institutional and commercial clients * Position is open due to company expansion!… https://t.co/Ko1DrXOv39 https://t.co/jw1hCRJcgW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python developer: Python developer Ref No.: 18-14001 Location: Costa mesa, California Hi, Hope you are doing great! Please have a look at the job description below and let me know if you are interested:. Role: Python Developer Location: Costa Mesa, CA… https://t.co/ME5g9oXqVM https://t.co/FeMD9pjCUi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Data Analysis Manager #R43299: Associate Data Analysis Manager – Capital One Services, LLC in Richmond, VA; Multiple positions available: Perform quantitative &amp; quality analysis of economic data, relating constants &amp; variables, restrictions,… https://t.co/WDK7DtcZc6 https://t.co/HhNoyjhYkN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Desktop Support Technician: Grand Lake Mental Health Center, Inc. Claremore, OK Desktop Support Tech We are currently seeking a Desktop Support Technician with at least three (3) years of experience in computer repair and maintenance. Some basic… https://t.co/BoUjREi0Zr https://t.co/eCpdjZkgx7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer: Development Expert for SAP Labs, LLC (Palo Alto, CA) resp for dvlpmnt focus on dsgn, codng, tstng, &amp; qlty assur of cmplx prod features in dvlpmnt team. Bach in Comp Sci, Eng, Math, or rltd field &amp; 7 yrs exp req’d, or alt Master’s &amp; 5 yrs of… https://t.co/kbI86j5509 https://t.co/5XGJTSwC7i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police Say YouTube Policies Motivated Shooter Nasim Aghdam: San Bruno police identified the attacker as Nasim Najafi Aghdam, a woman in her late thirties from San Diego. https://t.co/71KYhxNDWe https://t.co/SklOYlCsvW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Integration Developer: LinkedIn Corp. has openings in our Mtn View, CA location for Software Engineer (All Levels/Types) (SWE0318MV) Design, develop &amp; integrate cutting-edge software technologies. LinkedIn Corp. has openings in our Sunnyvale, CA… https://t.co/ktE1FJgAdI https://t.co/nq9I9Vbsax]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Patent Engineer: Patent Engineer, IBM Corporation, Research Triangle Park, NC: Analyze security software and other software commercial products to identify patents needed for each feature of the product. Develop evidence to prove identified patent being… https://t.co/9DxqvGLuVh https://t.co/FTMt8RjjWA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Sr. Engineer: Data Domain LLC (a Dell Technologies company) is seeking a Software Sr. Engineer at our Santa Clara, CA facility to develop software solutions for external clients based on detailed specifications from technology/ systems… https://t.co/MxW9AgsI2Y https://t.co/WjxEZcwIaz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Project Manager: Technical Project Manager With Masters Degree or foreign equivalent in IT, Computer Science, or Computer Engineering, and 1 year experience in job offered. (or) Bachelor’s Degree or foreign equivalent in IT, Computer Science,… https://t.co/YuWWNMSzdy https://t.co/BMWEcuGqjf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Software Engineer: Principal Software Engineer Embedded Systems (Belmont, CA), responsible for shaping and strengthening the electronics development for Audi and the VW Group; targeted towards Audi electronics; development, optimization, and… https://t.co/R8QqV2xWH7 https://t.co/j99XaNekj6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Program Manager: A2Z Development Center, Inc. seeks candidates for the following positions: Technical Program Manager II, Job Code AZ0082: Provide sophisticated technical program management for the build-out of massively scalable, robust,… https://t.co/VTRO5o24i0 https://t.co/oWdluqwTdb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer: Senior Software Developer, Austin, TX, General Motors. Develop, deploy, &amp; test GM Cimplicity based solutions within manufacturing environment, such as Production Routing &amp;Tracking, Production Pull System, &amp; Electronic Pull… https://t.co/S8g2Fubc6y https://t.co/jGF2dAxhkw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Solutions Consultant: Database Architect (Mountain View, CA) Evaluate business needs to design on point database architectures for Google technology. #1615.5956 Exp Incl: C++, Java, or Python; partnering w/ business owners to gather &amp; document… https://t.co/vMAkEm5lWo https://t.co/iG8fafZz3P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate, Software Engineering – Job #: 180028050: Job #: 180028050 Associate, Software Engineering Columbus, OH. Provide high quality tech. solutions that address business needs by developing applications within mature technology environments. Duties:… https://t.co/3INhusG91b https://t.co/g80wQvZZl3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Program Manager II: Information Technology positions available at the following California locations: Sunnyvale, Cupertino, San Jose, Mountain View, East Palo Alto. A2Z Development Center, Inc seeks candidates for the following positions:… https://t.co/Kx6sOVFCzo https://t.co/lrl6VOV0sY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test Technician: Test Technician F/T: Test mobile device and Analyze results. Resume: BS/equiv &amp; 5 yrs exp w/ Java/J2EE, EJBs, Struts, Servlets, Hibernate JPA, CSS, Ajax, Angular JS, Bug trackr &amp; JTrack. Travel/reloc req’d. recblid… https://t.co/ohA7zOhcVU https://t.co/dv3JjttATx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Business Analyst – HHP: Software Business Analyst – HHP Raleigh, NC Company Overview: Brightree, the leading provider of cloud-based software for the post-acute care industry, is seeking a team-player with a natural propensity to share concepts… https://t.co/CXB3XAgI65 https://t.co/EMy1VjgTF5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Comcast-NBC Merger Offers Little Guidance for AT&amp;T-Time Warner: The Justice Department is in court trying to block AT&amp;T's planned purchase of Time Warner. Both sides cite Comcast's 2011 acquisition of NBC Universal, but the earlier deal is an… https://t.co/DQgT6ZQxBl https://t.co/bZqbrlQSuY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Traffic Engineer: Come join the Farnsworth Group team and find out why our employees earned us the Great Place to Work certification!   Farnsworth Group is a full-service engineering and architecture firm with offices and employment opportunities located… https://t.co/NvSuuCov0V https://t.co/N5JtLTrhiJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SIGINT Operations Analyst Support Technician – 16585: SIGINT Operations Analyst Support Technician Huntington Ingalls Industries Technical Solutions division is a professional services organization providing mission-critical and practical solutions to a… https://t.co/0mZYn4S60T https://t.co/rR08Pw54Qm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quantitative Modeler: Does your dream job include the following? * Friendly and respectful work environment. * Open, supportive, collaborative, team focused environment. * Opportunities to grow within your job and grow with the company. * Recognition for… https://t.co/7uaqpK6GkG https://t.co/F8BHaRevYO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Designer/Assistant Project Manager: The Assistant Project Manager works for the Sleeping Dog Properties Project Managers, Site Superintendents, Field Staff and Executive Staff to assist in the following: acts as a liaison with Owners, Architects,… https://t.co/49ObssuTrc https://t.co/ddyPus4tgw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer 2: Excited to be part of Microsoft’s data-driven transformation? Want to leverage over 1.8 billion users to show causal impact of features? Have a passion for finding simple and innovative solutions to difficult engineering problems?… https://t.co/O0Z1B00MoH https://t.co/P8ZC87K55L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Systems Administrator: Nantucket Island Resorts is currently accepting applications for the position of IT Systems Administrator. The position’s primary functions are the management and support for all Audio/Visual equipment at all company hotels and… https://t.co/wAtLnq2iAg https://t.co/jq2JZrml6t]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>