<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Only once in your life, I truly believe that you can find someone who can completely turn your world around.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True love is when someone accepts your past, supports your presents, and encourages your future.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are so many things I'm not sure of in life, but with all certainty at this very minute, all I know is that I miss you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't ask me why I love you, just accept the fact that I do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't feel sad over someone who gave up on you. Feel sorry for them because they gave up on someone who would have never given up on them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jika kamu hanya melakukan sesuatu yang berada di dalam zona nyamanmu, kamu tidak akan berkembang.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest weakness of most humans is their hesitancy to tell others how they love them while they're alive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love him more than anything else in this world and there is nothing that I would like better than to hold on to him forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope is wishing something would happen. Faith is believing something will happen. Courage is making something happen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything that I want to tell you, is everything I wish I would have the courage to say.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find love with your heart, not with your eyes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pisces_sign 双鱼不喜欢向恋人说出自己的一些想法，因为害羞或是别的什么原因，双鱼自己也说不好。他们更喜欢或是希望对方能猜出他们的心思来，只可惜对方不是每次都能那么幸运地猜中并付出行动，若对方没有能猜中双鱼的想法，双鱼便会对恋人很失望，觉得恋人不了解自己。]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel really happy when I see you, because when I look at you and see your smile, it also makes me smile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Promises are worse than lies. Cause you make people hope for something that you're not sure you can give.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You made mistake? So what? We all make them. Nobody is perfect. Live it, learn from it, move on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you are unsure about your future, just keep doing what you know is right. What is meant to be will find you. God will make sure of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apapun mimpimu, luangkan waktu selalu untuk berdoa dan memastikan mimpimu sejalan dengan kehendak Tuhan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every little smile can touch somebody's heart. No one is born happy, but all of us are born with the ability to create happiness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes, we just have to be happy with what people can offer us. Even if it's not what we want, at least it's something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God is my provider today, tomorrow, and always.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always forgive and love yourself, have the courage to live your life the way you wish, and never be afraid to speak the truth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is too short to waste one single second with someone who doesn't appreciate your value.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've learned to see with my heart and not with my eyes. The heart can see so much that the eyes can't. Appearance isn't everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not what happens to you that determines how far you will go in life, it is how you handle what happens to you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop checkiing your phone, he's not going to text you, but guess what? He doesn't deserve anyone as damn good as you are anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is about laughing and living in good and bad times. Getting through whatever comes our way and looking back with a smile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never settle for being someone's other, when you have the potential to be someone's only.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I might be smiling on the outside, but I'm crying on the inside.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life it is what it is, count everyday a blessing, make someone happy, including yourself!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just because you can't get what you want, doesn't mean you can't be happy. You create your own happiness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Real LOVE won't die. You go through and get through any and everything together... That's unconditional LOVE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Semua percintaan akan melalui masa-masa sulit, hanya cinta sejati yang bisa melaluinya dan bahkan menjadi semakin kuat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are no perfect people. Only imperfect people who are perfectly content to live with and love other imperfect people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Treat people with respect. Be the person that makes others feel special. Be known for your kindness and honesty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When things didn't go as you planned, don't be let down. Make new plans. The sun doesn't stop shining just because of dark clouds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a girl wants: Not just someone to talk to, but someone that can understand her.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'll never really understand a person until you consider things from their point of view.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never think that you are not good enough for anyone always. Ask yourself if they are good enough for you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jangan beri seseorang harapan, jika akhirnya kamu tinggalkan. Kenyataan bahwa kamu tak mencintainya telah cukup menyakitinya.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't choose someone if they have to think twice about choosing you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are not happy? Then... make a smile on your face, you'll know you don't need any reason to be happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I tell you I love you, can I keep you forever?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God, You know my situation and You know I can't make it without You. Thank You for always being here by my side through it all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love you not because of who you are, just because of who I am when I am with you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God gave you two hands for a reason. One is to help yourself and the other is to help others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you feel like you've been waiting forever, remember that God's perfect blessings always come in God's perfect timing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love isn't about what's happening in your life, it's about what's happening in your heart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you can't get someone out of your head, then it's probably because they are supposed to be there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happiness doesn't belong to those who has everything, but belong to those who can appreciate what they have.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My room may be a mess, but I know where EVERYTHING is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know you like someone when they're the last person you think about at night and the first person you want to say "good morning" to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never ignore a person who loves and cares for you because one day you may realize you've lost the moon while counting the stars.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When someone judges you, it's not because you're not better than them. It's because they wish they were better than you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How come sometimes the things you want to say the most are the things you couldn't possibly put into words?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find the one who makes your heart smile and keep them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the people you are with, until you can be with the people you love most. This is the way we find happiness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be strong now because things will get better. It might be stormy now, but it can't rain forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A great way to communicate sometimes is to just listen. It's more about what's right not who's right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The one for you will always be for you. You'll never have to questions their intentions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women are sensitive. They overthink every little thing and they care way more than they should, but that's what makes their love so strong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Real men stay faithful. They don't have time to look for other women, because they are too busy loving the one they have.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is a test and a trust, and the more God gives you, the more responsible He expects you to be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In order to have a healthy relationship you need trust, and always let the other person explain before you assume things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes we waste too much thinking about someone who doesn't even think about us for a second.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a couple you guys should be able to continue loving each other and forgive each other after big arguments.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having God as my source of strength gives me enough assurance that I'll pass through anything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good things come to those who wait. Greater things come to those who are willing to work for what they want.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A smile is a choice, not a miracle. Don’t wait for people to smile. Show them how. A genuine smile makes u &amp; everyone around u feel better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's hard to determine whether you really have feelings for someone or you are just carried away by the good things they do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prayer does so many things. It heals, comforts, strengthens, and brings you faith. God hears every single prayer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People will always fear what they don't understand, hate what they can't conquer, and secretly admire anyone who's doing better than them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please follow my other accounts @aiqingfenxiang &amp; @pisces_sign. ⌒(*＾-ﾟ)v Thank you!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The more you compare yourself to others, the more you find out life isn’t fair. Stop comparing. Be grateful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A friend can replace any precious treasure, but all the world's treasures can never replace a friend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's more important than having everything is having someone who values you more than anything even when you're nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop looking for perfect partners. Just find someone who know how lucky they are when they have you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some believe in destiny, some believe in fate, but I believe that happiness is something we create.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is deaf. You can't just tell someone you love them, you've to show it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you a Pisces? Please follow my new account @pisces_sign ^^. ⌒(*＾-ﾟ)v Thank you!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There comes a moment each day when we must simply drop what weighs on us and hand it over to God.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making mistakes is not a big failure. It's just human nature. The key is to learn from it so you can do better next time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes you have to take a step back and remember where you came from to get where you want to go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not about how many mistakes you make in your life. It's about how many things you learn from all those mistakes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The worst pain is when you smile just to keep the tears from falling, and sleep just so you don't have to think about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A creative man is motivated by the desire to achieve, not by the desire to beat others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every tears from your eyes are precious. Don't waste it for something that not worth it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Often when we lose all hope and think this is the end, God smiles from above and says, "Relax dear, it is just a bend, not the end."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't even want to think about how different my life would be if I had never met you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't really know what love is until you meet that only boy/girl. The one who makes you smile and completes your world .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You never know how long we have, so enjoy life and make your own happiness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not everything is meant to be, but everything is worth a try. Trying is not having everything, it is enjoying what's meant to try.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is the condition in which the happiness of another person is essential to your own.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Music is important to me, because even on my darkest days, it always brightens my day, just by a single song.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd rather live my life knowing that I'm not perfect, than spending my whole life pretending to be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Faith tells me that no matter what lies ahead of me, God is already there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never forget, no matter what our circumstances in life, we always have something to be thankful for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One thing I know for sure is that God loves me everyday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn to deal with the fact that you are not a perfect person, but you are a person that deserves respect and honesty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If she's jealous, that means she cares.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ketika jatuh cinta kita melihat semuanya menjadi hal yang baik, tetap pertahankan itu meski kekurangannya perlahan akan muncul.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>