<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[All arguments have two sides, but some have no ends.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of McDonald's  http://t.co/CQaXEr9rUJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Blue Origin - A Profile of This Emerging Space Company  http://t.co/51qgIHV04c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never go in against a Sicilian when death is on the line! - Vizzini, The Princess Bride]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The Music of L.T.D.  http://t.co/UAtU1YcZGW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Review of The Little House on the Prairie Episode Called "Four Eyes"  http://t.co/EbWCTkQnhI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to David Bowie  http://t.co/SJt6fOrSDD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Those SEO Google Animals - Panda and Penguin - How They Affect Your Site  http://t.co/GMz6EypZWZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Triple Crown Sports Organization  http://t.co/6SHulWYSX7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Understanding Government Resources for Small Business  http://t.co/L9B5Uiv9mq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome marriage t-shirts &amp; gear - give the gift of marriage!  http://t.co/uUmv3T7aCH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The worst examples of snap judgment are usually found in the old family album]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The attention economy is not growing, which means we have to grab the attention that someone else has today.  Brent Leary - CRM Essentials]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One deer to another:  "I wish I had his doe"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ELVIS - The King - One Person's Thoughts  http://t.co/g7VWjVFEkP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think nobody cares if you're alive, try missing a couple of car payments. - Earl Wilson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lot of people love Oreos. So their manufacturer is making money. That means more dividends for shareholders. Maria Bartiromo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My life is an open book. With illustrations.  Hugh Hefner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the business world, everyone is paid in two coins: cash &amp; experience. Take the experience first; the cash will come later - Harold Geneen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Emmylou Harris  http://t.co/DUzRnWlwN7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nobody remembers the guy who finished second but the guy who finished second. - Bobby Unser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have to have a lot of little boy in you to play baseball for a living.  - Roy Campanella]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Hamstring Rehab  http://t.co/VBI7rxFrje]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What --  is the air-speed velocity of an unladen swallow? - Bridgekeeper, Monty Python and the Holy Grail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You win some, you lose some, you wreck some. - Dale Ernhardt Sr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Magic texting glove with conductive yarn finger tips for iPhone, iPad and all touch screen devices - 4 colors  --&gt; http://t.co/uRBvfus3GD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the way society functions. Aren't you a part of society? - Kramer, Seinfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The box said 'Requires Windows 95 or better'. So I installed LINUX.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think about it... Mistakes are just small steps to perfection...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ability is the art of getting credit for all the home runs somebody else hits. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plano Texas is an up and coming area of Dallas - read more here!  http://t.co/8I6Vmo5yGB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do I set a laser printer to stun?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A horse gallops with his lungs, Perseveres with his heart, And wins with his character. - Tesio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space is the stature of God. - Joseph Joubert]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People who enjoy what they are doing invariably do it well. - Joe Gibbs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Cooking – An Effortless Way to Bond with Kids  http://t.co/EBxp9AgwUH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good introduction to Minecraft Mods - http://t.co/eeKgEchSSQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Search Engine Optimization (SEO) to Drive Traffic to Your Website  http://t.co/v7O9BYl5tq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That which is bitter to endure may be sweet to remember. - Thomas Fuller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to win at golf:  cheat!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you are thin, don't eat fast. If you are fat, don't eat fast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The iPaperPad is not magical or revolutionary. It's a paper pad. A poor man's iPad LOL http://t.co/7oXV0uBGKS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About DotNetNuke for Corporations  http://t.co/UL0fLzYlLy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Profiles of Major Watch Designers  http://t.co/PmZHp0yuxM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Beverly Hillbillies – An American Classic TV Series  http://t.co/C6BJBXYB8a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doctor, giving prescription to a patient "Let me know if this stuff works. I'm having the same trouble myself."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Linda Ronstadt  http://t.co/M635Y2Reqi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The great difficulty in education is to get experience out of ideas. - George Santayana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really &amp; truly you can never have 2 many pairs of shoes. You need a pair for every mood &amp; everyone knows women have lots of moods. Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drill sarge to recruit:  "wipe that opinion off your face!”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Billy Joel  http://t.co/kZO40hyKwD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winners never quit and quitters never win. - Vince Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People all over the world recognize me as a spiritual leader.  Steven Seagal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may have said the same thing before... But my explanation, I am sure, will always be different. - Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Life? Cool! Where can I download one of those?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Windows has detected you do not have a keyboard. Press 'F9" to continue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have to have a lot of little boy in you to play baseball for a living.  - Roy Campanella]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 6 - Follow-up Appointment  http://t.co/jTPIXfiVZ7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think the last 4 words of the national anthem are gentlemen, start your engines, you might be a redneck. - Jeff Foxworthy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Joe Tex  http://t.co/I3pNmWw5YI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need to be able to rock out.  - Bryan Adams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helpful Hints for Web Building from the Experts  http://t.co/tHS2fjvKTj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Father, forking out reluctantly for daughter's wedding dress:  It's not enough to have to give her away --  she has to be gift wrapped.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always wear expensive shoes. People notice. - Brian Koslow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money cant buy happiness, but it sure makes misery easier 2 live with!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love Cute Kids Watches - Having A Watch Can be Fun for Kids!  http://t.co/XjMQIxWlXv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sports do not build character. They reveal it. - Heywood Broun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Jay Ferguson  http://t.co/kvuAmHpwGp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Use SEO on Multiple Websites to Drive Traffic in Your Direction  http://t.co/sDyTmpOc5d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame Quakecraft: FAILURE IS AN OPTION!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! http://t.co/vAFyPvUgjH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instead of giving myself reasons why I can't, I give myself reasons why I can. - Unknown Author]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peter Townshend shows us it's all right to grow up. There is dignity after rock'n'roll. - Sting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Tin Can Robot Kit - Kids Have a Blast Building a Fun Robot! http://t.co/yYjXwZQzxz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have the end in mind and every day make sure your working towards it - Ryan Allis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes as much energy to wish as it does to plan!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attitude: It is our best friend or our worst enemy. - John C. Maxwell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of America  http://t.co/tLiBQxwuKT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We thought you was a toad! - Delmar, O Brother Where Art Thou?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Dave Mason  http://t.co/KnbuKmqgp6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The way you can understand all of the social media is as the creation of a new kind of public space - Dana Boyd, Social Media Research MSFT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Building Experts - Get Some Free Tips  http://t.co/tifRV7zFc2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Simplicity is the ultimate sophistication. - Leonardo da Vinci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Card playing is no more expensive than any other game where you hold hands.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turbochargers are for people who cant build engines. - Keith Duckworth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By the time a person gets to greener pastures, he can't climb the fence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you wish to grow thinner, diminish your dinner. - Henry Sambrooke Leigh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Paul Davis  http://t.co/SHxQrfLXqW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A wife doesn't mind seeing a man make a fool out of himself as long as some other woman isn't helping him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes you can play 3 Man Chess - Check It Out! http://t.co/Bbbo5baG8K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this chicken what I have, or is this fish? I know it's tuna but it says 'Chicken of the Sea'.  Jessica Simpson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You miss 100% of the shots you never take. - Wayne Gretzky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love cats because I enjoy my home; and little by little, they become its visible soul. - Jean Cocteau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And now, I'm just trying to change the world, one sequin at a time. Lady Gaga]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Ben E. King - his story and music  http://t.co/TO8KtmPSXu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 2 - Road Trip!!!  http://t.co/sBJ1aQM0pq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is a skilled game. It's America's game - it, and high taxes. - Will Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am for conversations.  But you need to have a message.  Rennee Blodgett - President Blodgett Communications]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The dog was created especially for children. He is the God of frolic. - Henry Ward Beecher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft: "You've got questions. We've got dancing paperclips."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Victory belongs to the most persevering. - Napoleon]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>