<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager/Environmental Health and Safety – Plainville, CT Office: Project Manager/Environmental Health and Safety – Plainville, CT Office Loureiro Engineering Associates, Inc. (Loureiro) has an immediate opening for a Project Manager/Environmental… https://t.co/bU3OJGgmKC https://t.co/B5iyoaDghd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cisco Enterprise Solutions Architect: The Cisco Enterprise Solutions Architect is a PreSales resource based in the Danbury, Connecticut or Hartford, Connecticut area travelling 35% regionally that leads the consultative discovery of the client’s business… https://t.co/7Zdrjxjq0w https://t.co/TrNQ571dWv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer:   Job Description – Software Developer (00020353) Job Description  Software Developer – (00020353) Description   Software Developer, Full Stack Development, Gartner‘s Eloqua PlatformJob Description Gartner is in need of a well-rounded… https://t.co/bX0VeK3hmO https://t.co/mj4bMCHvWL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electrical Development Project Manager: Job Description LocationWilton – CT, US LevelBachelor Experience&gt;10 Senior Available since4/13/2018 Functional area Background Referencereq2297 Introduction ASML US, LP brings together the most creative minds in… https://t.co/MCptoWHbn2 https://t.co/qD2fAjnRoG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Projects can also include support of Oracle database schemas, PL/SQL packages, scheduled batch processing, Java applications and servers. Degree in Computer Science, Engineering or MathematicsStrong knowledge of Object Oriented… https://t.co/57GBie9g1C https://t.co/KzW3gCi643]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Network Engineer: TheSENIOR NETWORK ENGINEER delivers day-to-day operations support and participates, as well as leads, key projects to deliver network-related services to clients and ensures continued overall success. Frequent travel to our… https://t.co/2brwFsvQUp https://t.co/kpkcFn1Ccd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Avionics Systems Engineer: Req ID : 417585BR Job Code/Title : E1461:Systems Engineer Asc Job Description : Seeking an Avionics Engineer with a demonstrated ability to design, develop, integrate, and qualify Avionics systems for the world’s leader in… https://t.co/lMWjAM0s4G https://t.co/9NajSDx1yb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Security Programmer: Qualifications Minimum of Bachelors degree in a technology related field5+ years of IT experience3+ years of IT security experience 2+ years of Linux experience 2+ years of C programming or equivalent skill level (at least… https://t.co/GchblF6NcM https://t.co/m03KtI1eRt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales Enablement Director- Mid Size Enterprise:   Job Description – Sales Enablement Director- Mid Size Enterprise (00020309) Job Description  Sales Enablement Director- Mid Size Enterprise – (00020309) Description   SALES ENABLEMENT DIRECTOR – ExP… https://t.co/BEGhe47f4F https://t.co/0EwPk32nyr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Program/Project Analyst: Job Details Company Medtronic Job Title Senior Program/Project Analyst JobId 39996 Location: North Haven, CT, 06473, USA Description Senior Program/Project Analyst Location: North Haven, Connecticut, United States… https://t.co/gEqTsLjsQ6 https://t.co/tHRYCfao4M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – New Grads: The Big Willow is radically improving how sellers find buyers. Would you like working at The Big Willow? Answer that by peering inside our DNA (some people call it core values): * Be ambitious and audacious * Value… https://t.co/5xllISj5lv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Network Engineer: COMPANY OVERVIEW: ChimeNet is a data networking service provider offering innovative information technology (IT) solutions and 24/7/365 support for businesses where data transfer and security cannot be compromised. ChimeNet… https://t.co/iBXebo5BId https://t.co/eKCWHHo0O7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Job Title Project Manager Requisition # 8836 Location New York – New York, NY 10016 US Norwalk – Norwalk, CT 06851 US (Primary) Job Type Temporary/Contract Career Level Experienced (Non-Manager) Category Project Management Education… https://t.co/h5e1kVbqY9 https://t.co/BDB3sdWl30]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Embedded Software Engineer: Senior Embedded Software Engineer Innovate to solve the world’s most important challenges Home and Build Technologies is seeking an Experienced Software Developer to grow our back office cloud development team. The… https://t.co/0NzSwnTVKV https://t.co/fl5SR5dDHf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Cloud Software Developer: Summit Technologies, Inc. has a full-time position for Sr. Cloud Software Developer with Life Insurance, Annuities and Retirement work experience. In this senior hands-on development position, you will be working with… https://t.co/fSH93wxGtL https://t.co/NuqBQddJZK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embedded Software Developer: Embedded Software Developer Innovate to solve the world’s most important challenges This position will be located at our Honeywell Facility in Northford, CT, working On-Site. Design, document, and implement firmware and… https://t.co/xZGxaGqaVv https://t.co/UaxfJjU8lk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learning Manager:   Job Description – Learning Manager (00016704) Job Description  Learning Manager – (00016704) Description   The purpose of this role is primarily focused on the creation, delivery and execution of identified core learning deliverables… https://t.co/CU9oyuDIkf https://t.co/hQoFHwpGy3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federal IT Audit Consultant: Recruiter Deloitte Location Norfolk Norfolk United States Salary Competitive Posted 27 Apr 2018 Closes 25 May 2018 Job role Audit Sector Accounting and public practice Contract type Permanent Hours Full time You need to sign… https://t.co/KIMNbaIqye https://t.co/GOh4UsGs3w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Research Director, Server and Operating Systems Analyst, Gartner Research, Work at Home:   Job Description – Research Director, Server and Operating Systems Analyst, Gartner Research, Work at Home (00019572) Job Description  Research Director, Server and… https://t.co/3FEnbUAm15 https://t.co/sVDfoBAxmV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Graphic Designer:   Job Description – Sr Graphic Designer (00020496) Job Description  Sr Graphic Designer – (00020496) Description   Gartner Creative Center of Excellence is a dynamic, energetic, in-house creative team within a global organization… https://t.co/WPdeOQx6Ji https://t.co/EvSPVoDAh5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer – Full Stack – Portfolio Services: Job Title Senior Software Engineer – Full Stack – Portfolio Services Requisition # 8338 Location New York – New York, NY 10016 US Norwalk – Norwalk, CT 06851 US (Primary) Job Type Full-time… https://t.co/qBpf6MmMqL https://t.co/HwQ7cd9gVo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aftermarket Forecasting Analyst: Req ID : 425680BR Job Code/Title : E4612:Demand Analysis Planner Job Description : The RMS Global Sustainment Team is responsible for ensuring aftermarket supportability of Lockheed Martin RMS products, Sikorsky… https://t.co/dZ3pitpyIc https://t.co/uV9YUHsAZl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hybris Tech Lead: Hybris Tech Lead Ref No.:18-07739 Location: Stamford, Connecticut Position Type:Contract Start Date: 04/25/2018 – Interpret written business requirements and technical specification documents. – Perform coding to written technical… https://t.co/VUlgH3RIxJ https://t.co/KGhQaNhMeT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Software Engineer: The Big Willow is radically improving how sellers find buyers. Would you like working at The Big Willow? Answer that by peering inside our DNA (some people call it core values): * Be ambitious and audacious * Value… https://t.co/qr3EaiOGyb https://t.co/PB9RqwbbVc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Business Systems Analyst: Title Senior Business Systems Analyst Requisition Number 18-0047 Post Date 4/17/2018 City Any Great Lakes Location Description Great Lakes Higher Education Corporation and Affiliates, a leader in the student financial… https://t.co/9anZmi3y94 https://t.co/TMXFwNQAnt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test Automation Engineer (Automation Tester (Hartford, CT): Test Automation Engineer (Automation Tester (Hartford, CT) : 18-01238 Ref No.:18-01238 Location: Hartford, Connecticut Primary Skills: Automation Testing, Selenium, Java, Java Script, GIT… https://t.co/COILPikogf https://t.co/tdOk00zVeB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electronic-Systems-Architect: Location Wilton – CT, US Level Bachelor Experience &gt;10 Senior Available since 4/4/2018 Functional area Background Reference req2016 Introduction ASML US, LP brings together the most creative minds in science and technology… https://t.co/8hl0OfXumM https://t.co/FpsLp9r8iO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Node.js Developer: Node.js Developer Ref No.:18-06487 Location: Hartford, Connecticut Position Type:Full Time/Contract Start Date: 04/10/2018 *******–Node.js Developer – TRAVELERS- ONLY FT Importance: High Please find below (also attached) NodeJS JD for… https://t.co/mV4BAw3izl https://t.co/3LWyAd8j9r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Optical Data Analyst: Job Description LocationWilton – CT, US LevelBachelor Experience2-5 Professional Available since1/31/2018 Functional areaResearch &amp; Development, Mechanical Engineering BackgroundOptics, Other- Technical Referencereq5 Introduction… https://t.co/0zmcMsYlsf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cisco Enterprise Solutions Architect: The Cisco Enterprise Solutions Architect is a PreSales resource based in the Danbury, Connecticut or Hartford, Connecticut area travelling 35% regionally that leads the consultative discovery of the client’s business… https://t.co/nLjdDTZG8s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Civil Engineer/Project Manager: Civil Engineer/Project Manager The selected candidates would serve as a Project Engineer/Project Manager for civil/site design, land planning and permitting for industrial, institutional, commercial, multifamily… https://t.co/xTlfTYcP1b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big Data Developer/Analyst: Big Data Developer/Analyst Danbury, Connecticut – United States Job Start Date – 04/16/18, Posted Date – 04/16/18 Primary SkillsBigDataTax TermsC2COverview Must haves: 7-10+ years of database design/development 5+ years of… https://t.co/lVLQG2nleQ https://t.co/zBbdJCOOIh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[software engineer in test: About AQR Capital Management AQR is a global investment firm built at the intersection of financial theory and practical application. We strive to deliver concrete, long-term results by looking past market noise to identify and… https://t.co/TIPzxsgrZb https://t.co/2OKedIboDQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Labeling Project Manager: Job Details Company Medtronic Job Title Sr Labeling Project Manager JobId 38992 Location: North Haven, CT, 06473, USA Description Sr Labeling Project Manager Location: North Haven, Connecticut, United States Requisition #:… https://t.co/nN7eEca8Pw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Job Title Project Manager Requisition # 8836 Location New York – New York, NY 10016 US Norwalk – Norwalk, CT 06851 US (Primary) Job Type Temporary/Contract Career Level Experienced (Non-Manager) Category Project Management Education… https://t.co/FSDD6GzI7S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager – Workday Finance: Job Title Senior Project Manager – Workday Finance Requisition # 8545 Location Norwalk – Norwalk, CT 06851 US (Primary) Job Type Full-time Career Level Manager Category Project Management Education Bachelor’s… https://t.co/MUBqjzTZjp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Program Manager:   Job Description – IT Program Manager (00020397) Job Description  IT Program Manager – (00020397) Description    A seasoned Project or Program Manager, managing a project or program to provide a complete solution for a business… https://t.co/2TPvHruwn1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CrossLab Project Manager: Date Posted: 13/Apr/18 Requisition: ******* Job Title: CrossLab Project Manager Description: Agilent inspires and supports discoveries that advance the quality of life. We provide life science, diagnostic and applied market… https://t.co/PnFC6GoEhk https://t.co/k16mNMB26J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automation Software Engineer: We have an immediate opening for an Associate Software Engineer who will be assisting in the development of applications for laboratory automation/robotic systems. This is a hands-on position working with robots and… https://t.co/mG6iW3rL3g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Risk Analytics Product Developer: Job Title Risk Analytics Product Developer, FSPD02 Requisition # 8712 Location Norwalk – Norwalk, CT 06851 US (Primary) Job Type Full-time Career Level Experienced (Non-Manager) Category Product Development Education… https://t.co/GICMt5XW7a https://t.co/6An5H2pMKq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Solutions Architect: Summit Technologies, Inc. has several full-time positions for Sr. Application Architects with Life Insurance, Annuities and Retirement work experience. You will be part of a team responsible for designing and developing… https://t.co/rtbzoPpVN4 https://t.co/FQQcs4QKYK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Optical Data Analyst: Location Wilton – CT, US Level Bachelor Experience 2-5 Professional Available since 1/31/2018 Functional area Research &amp; Development, Mechanical Engineering Background Optics, Other- Technical Reference req5 Introduction ASML is… https://t.co/KH1aLIIdCB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cisco Solution Architect: The selected Cisco Solution Architect will be covering Hartford, CT and Danbury, CT so ideally candidates will be somewhat commutable to either location. They won’t be required to go into the office much but they will have to… https://t.co/e1KO6Khn4y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/FbPWJoAYc1 Developer: Analyze and develop specifications for the enhancement, maintenance and problem solving for the most complex applications or operating system (s). Provide in-depth consulting to IT management and staff at the highest… https://t.co/NkPls7tuUA https://t.co/jVQFK2uOIq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Network Engineer: COMPANY OVERVIEW: ChimeNet is a data networking service provider offering innovative information technology (IT) solutions and 24/7/365 support for businesses where data transfer and security cannot be compromised. ChimeNet… https://t.co/obZTktePHZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .NET SQL Developer: The Senior SQL Developer creates the overall structure and workflow of a software solution and is responsible for leading and/or handling the development of one to multiple components. The Senior Developer will work with the… https://t.co/XD6Ts9h96a https://t.co/mtncILQ6r8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Director, Business Planning: Client Reference Code: 216999 JOB TITLE: Sr. Director, Business Planning – Cable Operations JOB SUMMARY Responsible for the budgeting and forecasting consolidation process, business analysis and modeling, monthly… https://t.co/PnQwsNRmTd https://t.co/DjseZJRzUd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Operations Specialist: POSITION SUMMARY: The Operations Specialist reports to the Director of Patient Financial Services and is responsible for the coordination of activities as they relate to the processes and procedures of the Patient Access Department… https://t.co/KOgoFQLRjk https://t.co/lvCwpJoUmw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager -IT: 1 Year Contract We are actively seeking an IT Technical Project Manager. The IT Technical Project Manager will be responsible for planning and managing company resources to develop and launch innovative technological solutions. This… https://t.co/kQ3xBws5tJ https://t.co/xU7dSj0Ig1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Embedded Software Developer: Sr. Embedded Software Developer Innovate to solve the world’s most important challenges Home and Build Technologies within Honeywell is seeking an expert Sr Embedded Software Developer to grow our back-office cloud… https://t.co/oxV56wNKwJ https://t.co/48cAicsszn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cytologist: POSITION SUMMARY: The skilled Cytologist examines human cell samples under the microscope looking for early signs of cancer and other diseases.# The Cytologist processes and examines Cytologic smears for malignant cells, normal cells and… https://t.co/hesl32oqLd https://t.co/1SNlMlRClE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electronic Systems Architect: Location Wilton – CT, US Level Bachelor Experience &gt;10 Senior Available since 4/4/2018 Functional area Background Reference req2016 Introduction ASML US, LP brings together the most creative minds in science and technology… https://t.co/gYcfOXuQjq https://t.co/zxusaxBoxa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Design and develop real time clearing and banking applications and services for integration with continually expanding business relationships such as Clearing Corporations, Banks and Regulatory EntitiesWork on the implementation and… https://t.co/rwZe7gObPz https://t.co/thgen2x8jb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Solutions Architect: Summit Technologies, Inc. has several full-time positions for Sr. Application Architects with Life Insurance, Annuities and Retirement work experience. You will be part of a team responsible for designing and developing… https://t.co/2x4Ptlri4o https://t.co/Fze5s00eyh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer – Analytics Reporting and APIs: Job Title Senior Software Engineer – Analytics Reporting and APIs Requisition # 8693 Location New York – New York, NY 10016 US Norwalk – Norwalk, CT 06851 US (Primary) Job Type Full-time Career… https://t.co/SjLH3Dx4L5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big Data Developer/Analyst: Big Data Developer/Analyst Danbury, Connecticut – United States Job Start Date – 04/16/18, Posted Date – 04/16/18 Primary SkillsBigDataTax TermsC2COverview Must haves: 7-10+ years of database design/development 5+ years of… https://t.co/FfJ0d3u0on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Projects can also include support of Oracle database schemas, PL/SQL packages, scheduled batch processing, Java applications and servers. Degree in Computer Science, Engineering or MathematicsStrong knowledge of Object Oriented… https://t.co/trLGPGUSkZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, Open:FactSet DataExchange Integration: Job Title Software Engineer, Open:FactSet DataExchange Integration Requisition # 7736 Location New York – New York, NY 10016 US Norwalk – Norwalk, CT 06851 US (Primary) Job Type Full-time Career… https://t.co/1oyGW9zx8F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federal IT Audit Consultant: Recruiter Deloitte Location Norfolk Norfolk United States Salary Competitive Posted 27 Apr 2018 Closes 25 May 2018 Job role Audit Sector Accounting and public practice Contract type Permanent Hours Full time You need to sign… https://t.co/qkpVtMiU1j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electronics Project Manager: Location Wilton – CT, US Level Bachelor Experience &gt;10 Senior Available since 4/11/2018 Functional area Project Management Background Electronics Reference req1781 Introduction ASML US, LP brings together the most creative… https://t.co/SfmWuoviiy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CrossLab Project Manager: Date Posted: 13/Apr/18 Requisition: ******* Job Title: CrossLab Project Manager Description: Agilent inspires and supports discoveries that advance the quality of life. We provide life science, diagnostic and applied market… https://t.co/eMF49hacE1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Informatica developer-Powercentre: Informatica developer-Powercentre Ref No.: 18-17993 Location: Bloomfield CT, Connecticut Strong working experience in Informatica, Shell Scripts/Perl Scripts, Business Objects. Good knowledge in PL/SQL Store… https://t.co/h1Sw9mi4np]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mobile Developer: This is a great opportunity to expand your Mobile Development skills. In addition to maintaining and enhancing legacy applications, you will be involved with building out the mobile applications needed to better serve our manufacturing… https://t.co/IZxkDdtht7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Architect / Sr. Java Developer / Java Developer: Architect / Sr. Java Developer / Java Developer Ref No.: 18-18252 Location: Jersey City, New Jersey Hi Hope you are doing well Number of position : 42 (Not Contract or C2C) I, Salman Shaikh (Enterprise… https://t.co/0jKZlLSu1Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Integration Project Manager: Location Wilton – CT, US Level Bachelor Experience 2-5 Professional Available since 2/15/2018 Functional area Project Management, System Engineering, Design Engineering Background System Integration, Other- Technical… https://t.co/LQbKaF0Z06]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Business Systems Analyst: SUMMIT TECHNOLOGIES, INC. has a full-time position for a SR. BUSINESS SYSTEMS ANALYST experienced with Agile Methodology, as a product owner. Our client prefers candidates with Property &amp; Casualty Insurance, Finance and/or… https://t.co/lQR7WQ76P1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Job Title AV Systems Administrator – Media Services: * AV Systems Administrator – Media Services Posted Date 18 hours ago(4/24/2018 3:09 PM) Job ID 2017-2372 # Positions 1 Department Information Services Category Administrator Overview Quinnipiac… https://t.co/LfBtnizyHI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electrical Development Project Manager: Location Wilton – CT, US Level Bachelor Experience &gt;10 Senior Available since 4/13/2018 Functional area Background Reference req2297 Introduction ASML US, LP brings together the most creative minds in science and… https://t.co/O4g1EdZBef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electronic System Architect: Job Description LocationWilton – CT, US LevelBachelor Experience&gt;10 Senior Available since4/4/2018 Functional areaElectrical Engineering, Electrical Engineering, Research &amp; Development BackgroundElectronics, System… https://t.co/UJknQJKeII]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C#/.net Database Programming Analyst, Reporting Team: Job Description Database Programming Analyst, McLagan Reporting Team Aon is looking for a Database Programming Analyst to work in the Stamford, CT office As part of an industry-leading team, you will… https://t.co/CDUY4eAhcK https://t.co/QfdCpK7wp8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electronics Project Manager: Job Description LocationWilton – CT, US LevelBachelor Experience&gt;10 Senior Available since4/11/2018 Functional areaProject Management BackgroundElectronics Referencereq1781 Introduction ASML US, LP brings together the most… https://t.co/fKPLysKRYt https://t.co/nR4WAIIsCS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Optical Data Analyst: Job Description LocationWilton – CT, US LevelBachelor Experience2-5 Professional Available since1/31/2018 Functional areaResearch &amp; Development, Mechanical Engineering BackgroundOptics, Other- Technical Referencereq5 Introduction… https://t.co/vqTFtpQ9Nn https://t.co/fP6x4xoyrh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test Automation Engineer (Automation Tester (Hartford, CT): Test Automation Engineer (Automation Tester (Hartford, CT) : 18-01238 Ref No.:18-01238 Location: Hartford, Connecticut Primary Skills: Automation Testing, Selenium, Java, Java Script, GIT… https://t.co/WhKMLdWz09 https://t.co/Ec6j6AbZZT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Controls Engineer – Systems Integrator Experience (2930): OneSource is in search of a Senior Controls and Automation Engineer who is exceptional in using technology to oversee or manage the manufacturing process. If you are a skilled engineer who… https://t.co/JsZf6bE7On https://t.co/m662n4mbGj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer: The majority of development will be using Java and Java Script with some exposure to PL/SQL, Python, unix shell scripts and other general purpose languages and tools.QualificationsBS/MS Computer Science, Engineering, MathematicsStrong… https://t.co/9KhkLiSps4 https://t.co/e6wwHLqPtr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Design Automation Engineer: Careers that Change Lives Your dedication to quality is important to our customers and, most importantly, to their patients. As an important member of engineering team in Manufacturing you will be part of the… https://t.co/VkQzA0adKG https://t.co/S72aW1CXYn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Cloud Software Developer: Summit Technologies, Inc. has a full-time position for Sr. Cloud Software Developer with Life Insurance, Annuities and Retirement work experience. In this senior hands-on development position, you will be working with… https://t.co/dUxXxfXK75 https://t.co/yhswplRAZD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle DBA: ******/Oracle DBA Ref No.: 18-18219 Location: Danbury, Connecticut JD: Primary Skill ORACLE 11g, 12c – 7+ years Database administration experience with minimum 5+ years ORACLE 11g, 12c. – Experience in administering Oracle ASM, RAC,… https://t.co/GndZHuTrf2 https://t.co/cLX0NmQ4HL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electronic Systems Architect: Job Description LocationWilton – CT, US LevelBachelor Experience&gt;10 Senior Available since4/4/2018 Functional area Background Referencereq2016 Introduction ASML US, LP brings together the most creative minds in science and… https://t.co/UdgqpAlwqA https://t.co/LHuKkWJhDw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test Automation Engineer (Automation Tester (Hartford, CT): Test Automation Engineer (Automation Tester (Hartford, CT) : 18-01238 Ref No.: 18-01238 Location: Hartford, Connecticut Primary Skills: Automation Testing, Selenium, Java, Java Script, GIT… https://t.co/zq5BxCWYdD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Java Developer: Sr. Java Developer Ref No.: 18-19100 Location: Hartford, Connecticut Hi Hope you are doing well Number of position : 32 (Not Contract or C2C) I, Salman Shaikh (Enterprise Solution Inc.)would like to share a job opportunity asSr. Java… https://t.co/APwXS05AF0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Technical Support Associate: Senior Technical Support Associate Innovate to solve the world’s most important challenges Provide reliable technical assistance to internal and external customers. You will provide professional coverage of Technical… https://t.co/vwwHirMGEN https://t.co/74xEVbc8BU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Optical Data Analyst: Job Description LocationWilton – CT, US LevelBachelor Experience2-5 Professional Available since1/31/2018 Functional areaResearch &amp; Development, Mechanical Engineering BackgroundOptics, Other- Technical Referencereq5 Introduction… https://t.co/PvhYRRibAm https://t.co/SjSCmAsiad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Migration Developer: Job Summary Visa: GC and USC TITLE: Data Migration Developer LOCATION: Wethersfield, CT DURATION: FTE / Permanent Visa: GC and USC Job Description: Key words: Data Migration, SQL, PLSQL, IBM DataStage Technical/Functional Skills… https://t.co/BatDO0ZP32]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teradata Developer: Teradata Developer Ref No.: 18-16125 Location: Bloomfield, Connecticut Title:- Teradata Developer Location:- Bloomfield CT Contrac W2 Role Must have Unix Scripting Python experience is desired Thanks and Regards Tarun Arora Sr. IT… https://t.co/8SyJb25ZRz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Support Analyst: Country: United States Work Location: Newington State: Connecticut Advertising End Date: Not Specified Job Type: Regular About The Opportunity What you’ll do Job Summary The role supports the usage of business applications,… https://t.co/9NtS23aXY3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Healthcare Financial &amp; Operations Analyst: POSITION SUMMARY: The Financial and Operations Analyst will develop and provide management based reporting and analysis to support# daily operations and projects for Prospect Physician Enterprise (PPE), a… https://t.co/v0W4p53MJU https://t.co/OBmhSDDBiP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Minimum qualifications:BS degree in Computer Science or related technical field involving coding (e.g., physics or mathematics), or equivalent practical experience.Solid knowledge of Linux OS. Able to troubleshoot performance-related… https://t.co/HMHeLfzqeO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, FSECT52118: Job Title Software Engineer, FSECT52118 Requisition # 8958 Location Norwalk – Norwalk, CT 06851 US (Primary) Job Type Full-time Career Level Experienced (Non-Manager) Category Engineering Education Bachelor’s Degree Job… https://t.co/eo4wayfC0J https://t.co/EwKTVPMJ5e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Interaction Designer: Job Title Senior Interaction Designer Requisition # 7387 Location New York – New York, NY 10016 US (Primary) Norwalk – Norwalk, CT 06851 US Job Type Full-time Career Level Experienced (Non-Manager) Category Product… https://t.co/pco4QcR795]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer – Analytics Reporting and APIs: Job Title Senior Software Engineer – Analytics Reporting and APIs Requisition # 8693 Location New York – New York, NY 10016 US Norwalk – Norwalk, CT 06851 US (Primary) Job Type Full-time Career… https://t.co/doeDwOSPMz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager for Building Enclosures: Senior Project Manager for Building Enclosures Seeking a Registered Senior Project Manager in our Towson, MD office. Key Responsibilities * The selected candidate would provide building enclosure… https://t.co/w8YjOpjmpl https://t.co/WMmaqsaOmz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Python Developer Ref No.: 18-21884 Location: Groton, Connecticut Job title: Python Developer Location: Groton, CT Duration: 12 months Total IT experience is expected to be 8+ yrs (Mostly Java / Unix / Web based) Minimum one project on… https://t.co/s3hoXr9ydH https://t.co/8NjhGeEpbi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IA (Intelligent Automation) Software Developer: IA (Intelligent Automation) Software Developer, #15618BR, Hartford, CT, USMenu ToggleMenu Hide Home Life at Travelers Who We Are What We Do Why Join Travelers Community Involvement Diversity Locations… https://t.co/ZfGI1rbn0S https://t.co/4dxhh3aPbF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manufacturing Engineering Project Manager: New Product Introduction: Job Description LocationWilton – CT, US LevelBachelor Experience5-10 Experienced Available since4/11/2018 Functional areaManufacturing, Mechanical Engineering BackgroundOther- Technical… https://t.co/taCgONnIiq https://t.co/FBcQy1z7DT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solution Architect – Big Data a plus: Solution Architect – Big Data a plus, #15567BR, Hartford, CT, USMenu ToggleMenu Hide Home Life at Travelers Who We Are What We Do Why Join Travelers Community Involvement Diversity Locations Experienced Professionals… https://t.co/6IwJi3kvQq https://t.co/Y65ViSl2Jt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle EBS Consultant: Oracle EBS Consultant Ref No.: 18-21197 Location: Mountain View, Connecticut Position Oracle EBS Consultant Location Windsor, CT Job Length W2 JOBS Description: Oracle EBS Personalization and Optimization-L3 (Mandatory)As a Lead,… https://t.co/qEj4cQB5Lt https://t.co/LJObsXMWHL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electronic-Systems-Architect: Location Wilton – CT, US Level Bachelor Experience &gt;10 Senior Available since 4/4/2018 Functional area Background Reference req2016 Introduction ASML US, LP brings together the most creative minds in science and technology… https://t.co/pZffvMKrKa https://t.co/qVPzd3qlbs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CTS Product Developer: Job Title CTS Product Developer Requisition # 8640 Location Boston – Boston, MA 2109 US New York – New York, NY 10016 US Norwalk – Norwalk, CT 06851 US (Primary) Job Type Full-time Career Level Experienced (Non-Manager) Category… https://t.co/9AAysYVXKh https://t.co/fCdAYyJnoE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical lead: Technical lead Ref No.: 18-24267 Location: Berlin, Connecticut Position : Technical Lead / Senior Developer Duration: Fulltime Permanent Location: Berlin, CT Job Description BIPM : Informatica Powercentre Experience Required Technical… https://t.co/7ppEKV7tIl https://t.co/aP01QPsrMj]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>