<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps/ Platform Engineer: DevOps/ Platform Engineer is focused on: * Retail, Operating Systems, systems hardening, Virtualization and Automation. * 4 or more years of Linux or Windows systems administration experience. * Experience with modern… https://t.co/MB76t58w0m https://t.co/rflY2wyv3O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Android Application Software Engineer| Detroit MI| Positions-2: QUALIFICATIONS REQUIRED: BS in Computer Science or other field of study along with applicable work experience Experience as developer on App(s) publicly available in the Google Play App… https://t.co/lBqIYiqiq1 https://t.co/18dXCMUwOB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OnSite Android Developer: Detroit Labs OnSite is looking for an Android developer to join one of our projects in downtown Detroit. This role is with our OnSite business unit; successful applicants will be working at the client location in Detroit. The… https://t.co/zROrHtvtdy https://t.co/nzt6juvba4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Outside Sales Representative: Detroit, MI: SalesDetroit, Michigan As an Outside Sales Representative, you’ll be part of an award-winning culture in a family-oriented environment where employees are valued and rewarded. RevLocal is the leader in… https://t.co/UDKRrRfdsJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infotainment Application Software Engineer – Android|Detroit MI|10 Months | Positions-3: QUALIFICATIONS REQUIRED: BS in Computer Science or other field of study along with applicable work experience Experience with Android UI design (including custom… https://t.co/SEHnvytTSV https://t.co/6xDVWJkXgx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager: Job Details (*Employee Referral Program applies to this job) Job No. PM00001 Job Title Senior Project Manager Description Summary: Position Description: AD – Deployment manager will coordinate with hardware installers, network… https://t.co/FsU0RR5ed0 https://t.co/0QR2EOmcHM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spotify Subscriptions Helped The Streaming Company Win Listeners: The streaming company proved it could get the Napster generation to subscribe. But will Spotify's paywall make it profitable? https://t.co/4RlggqVkp8 https://t.co/YYClNRVGGm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps/ Platform Engineer: DevOps/ Platform Engineer is focused on: * Retail, Operating Systems, systems hardening, Virtualization and Automation. * 4 or more years of Linux or Windows systems administration experience. * Experience with modern… https://t.co/3Nmn0UjmPO https://t.co/NJmCRRPg8h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Support &amp; UNIX Administrator| Detroit MI | 1 Year| Position- 1: MANAGER REQUIRED MINIMUM Software SkillsBEA WeblogicYes 1-3 https://t.co/sFVU8g9u3A SkillsJ2EEYes4-6 yrs. Software SkillsJavaYes4-6 yrs. Software SkillsPerlYes1-3 yrs. Software… https://t.co/zBrV06vSfG https://t.co/z8Eoius1dh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Ace of Cakes' star gets engaged with twine: We suspect Duff Goldman is forgiven for not producing a ring. https://t.co/H2CHxaiRJb https://t.co/UAA8j3as2Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Project Manager Ref No.: 18-10731 Location: Detroit, Michigan Role : Project Manager Duration : 12 Months Location : Detroit, MI Job Description : Experience in legacy to SAP rolloutsData Migration End user testing,integration test… https://t.co/9yozwzK262 https://t.co/IRl1NBo5hn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YouTube Shooting Spree Injures 4, Kills 1: Police say one dead and four wounded in shooting at YouTube headquarters in San Bruno, Calif., Tuesday afternoon. https://t.co/eRjTjyCDp8 https://t.co/KCDIG78Zyn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Quality Analyst III| Detroit MI| 10 Months| Positions-1: Test Case Authoring: Develop detailed Test Cases based on the Functional Requirements and Design Documents. Execute the Test Cases and Analyze the Test Results. Usage of test tools as ALM… https://t.co/4v9MOBt06B https://t.co/cz1s3yuGkl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[General Labor – Construction: Detroit Lakes, MN, USAFull Time Arvig seeks General Laborers who want to make a difference, grow their future, and have fun in the process AND who want competitive pay ($16.50/hr to start), overtime potential, multiple pay… https://t.co/4QVWnxnIoi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Cloud Infrastructure Automation Lead: 3046693 Senior Cloud Infrastructure Automation Lead Oil &amp; Gas Headquarters GE Oil &amp; Gas United States Provide IT leadership on multiple automation build projects. Help prioritize and drive results for the… https://t.co/2sUo6Ufcgs https://t.co/rjX5E697MI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT/Cable Technician (100% Nationwide – Great Pay): JOB TITLE: Level 2: Lead Cable / Hardware Installation Technician Level 3: Certified Lead Cable / Hardware Installation, Telco and Troubleshooting Technician SUMMARY BY LEVEL: Level 2: Leads and manages… https://t.co/oJsQEmwrdz https://t.co/TSgpmBPIyH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spotify Shunned an IPO. Now It's Just Another Public Company: The music-streaming service listed its shares Tuesday without the traditional bankers or ceremony. https://t.co/c9cAqbc3Wb https://t.co/85MZaHUwm4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT/Cable Technician (100% Travel – Nationwide): JOB TITLE: Level 2: Lead Cable / Hardware Installation Technician Level 3: Certified Lead Cable / Hardware Installation, Telco and Troubleshooting Technician SUMMARY BY LEVEL: Level 2: Leads and manages a… https://t.co/FjZZf1RLUQ https://t.co/vVO07CYMuP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales Engineer – Telecommunications: Detroit, MI Full-time Compensation Unspecified Posted Today Job Title: Sales Engineer – Telecommunications Job Location: Detroit, MI Located in beautiful Downtown Detroit my client is a Detroit-based internet service… https://t.co/mv0YaKmR0g https://t.co/Us1nKKMY7I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Solution Architect: Cloud Solution Architect Microsoft envisions a world where passionate innovators come to collaborate, envisioning what can be and taking their careers places they simply couldn’t anywhere else. This is a world of more… https://t.co/xudtOUseAC https://t.co/5AcNnSo3Bi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer (Java Spring) – Detroit: ABOUT US TribalScale is an innovation firm that brings organizations – from the startup to the enterprise – into the future. We build digital products, transform teams, and grow startups. Were… https://t.co/jS0MWuFn52 https://t.co/36Xzg95dS1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Security &amp; Access Control Technician (Perham, MN): Detroit Lakes, MN, USAFull Time Join a winning company who has just been named one of the top 50 places to work in the northern plains area and a company that is owned by its employees! We are a growing… https://t.co/KtsgTRs7ZY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Script and HTML5 Front End Developer|Detroit MI| Positions – 1: Participate in and lead requirements analysis, specifications and design of custom-developed applications. Assist in the development of implementation/rollout plans. Ensure that… https://t.co/URdxVZxG5I https://t.co/vP8MxXA7gS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Software Engineer II| 118640| Detroit MI| 1 year| position -1: ENTERPRISE SOFTWARE ENGINEER II 1. Major Duties and Responsibilities a. Define, design, build, test, deploy, and support software products b. Consistently follow the specified… https://t.co/gnLz9C5niv https://t.co/RxeqcJpuQ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Content Marketing Networks Are Changing Because of #MeToo: Content Marketing Networks, like RevContent, draw eyeballs for ads with outrageous words and images. But post #MeToo, that strategy might be bad for business. https://t.co/qVRGs15y8Z https://t.co/HQXqO99NYZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Systems Security Specialist: **This is a Full Time position (not a contract). Must be authorized to work in the U.S. without sponsorship. Must be a US citizen or a green card holder. F1 OPT and Corp to corp candidates will not be… https://t.co/6c5c3ZJK9d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .Net Developer: Senior .Net Developer Senior .Net Developer Company Autobooks Location US-MI-Detroit Opportunity Details What You’ll Do/Need Within this role at Autobooks you will be a senior participant in the design and development of… https://t.co/eMD6N5X8Cr https://t.co/dnpFo4bGDl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republicans open a risky new front in the immigration wars: In the epic struggle between President Donald Trump and the Democratic-controlled California state government, a new front is opening that could prove pivotal to the battle for control of the US… https://t.co/e8dSaMrvEV https://t.co/OAaK62sN0A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Quality Analyst II | Detroit MI| 10 Months| Positions – 2: EXPERIENCE: 5+ years experience in acceptance testing. Minimum of 5 years technical experience in Information Technology TOP SKILLS 5+ years testing experience (combination automated and… https://t.co/vWbiD0RN5e https://t.co/PkXwmc1YTU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Comcast-NBC Merger Offers Little Guidance for AT&amp;T-Time Warner: The Justice Department is in court trying to block AT&amp;T's planned purchase of Time Warner. Both sides cite Comcast's 2011 acquisition of NBC Universal, but the earlier deal is an… https://t.co/zKRGQM76vQ https://t.co/XagQL30173]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tier I Help Desk Technician: Detroit Lakes, MN, USAFull Time Arvig offers a competitive wage and an excellent benefits package, including health and dental insurances, Employee Stock Ownership Program, 401k, profit sharing, PTO, holidays, education… https://t.co/OaW90purmi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce Technical Architect: Job Description: * Technical architecture design of multiple complex deployments on Salesforce * Function as SFDC Technical Architect with experience in the following: + Thorough understanding of Web Services in general… https://t.co/XBokK6OGbu https://t.co/pnZsugKjCN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle Financial consultant: Title: Oracle Financial consultant Type of Employment: Direct Hire/Permanent Job Description: An experienced consulting professional who has a broad understanding of solutions, industry best practices, multiple business… https://t.co/RonGg4XsbX https://t.co/r3H2EkGO8C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infotainment Application Software Engineer – Android|Detroit MI|10 Months | Positions-3: QUALIFICATIONS REQUIRED: BS in Computer Science or other field of study along with applicable work experience Experience with Android UI design (including custom… https://t.co/cZP1yREP9I https://t.co/suUGFDQbMg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embedded Software Engineer: Job Description We are AAM. We have the POWER to move the world. At AAM, we’re looking for associates who push boundaries and drive solutions for the future. Innovators. Thinkers. Dreamers. Doers. No matter the role or… https://t.co/ZTwGE84cpE https://t.co/7fdBn70JwG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[React Native Developer (Android/i OS) | Detroit MI| 6 Months| Positions – 1: TOP SKILLS: 1. Minimum 1 year of experience writing code for iOS/Android apps in React Native, or a minimum of 2 years experience building applications using JavaScript… https://t.co/7JM6W5eQC1 https://t.co/ELuUeQlVLJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Android Application Software Engineer| Detroit MI| Positions-2: QUALIFICATIONS REQUIRED: BS in Computer Science or other field of study along with applicable work experience Experience as developer on App(s) publicly available in the Google Play App… https://t.co/4MdnsuYF7n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[General Labor – Construction: Detroit Lakes, MN, USAFull Time Arvig seeks General Laborers who want to make a difference, grow their future, and have fun in the process AND who want competitive pay ($16.50/hr to start), overtime potential, multiple pay… https://t.co/Ab0e2v6mP8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce Technical Architect: Job Description: * Technical architecture design of multiple complex deployments on Salesforce * Function as SFDC Technical Architect with experience in the following: + Thorough understanding of Web Services in general… https://t.co/MZtlUEKpNn https://t.co/em2HKWly8l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master II (Project Manager II)| Detroit MI| 10 Months| Position -1: MAJOR DUTIES AND RESPONSIBILITIES SCRUM MASTER Facilitate Scrum events (Daily Scrum, Sprint Planning, Sprint Review, Retrospective, Backlog Grooming) Coach Product Owner and… https://t.co/BMiYHZ4b5P https://t.co/87chi8sYl6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Android Infotainment Software Engineer |Detroit MI| Positions- 1: KEY RESPONSIBILITIES: The Software Engineer will be responsible for application development and support including story elaboration, estimation, analysis, design, programming,… https://t.co/k5mQnUplyZ https://t.co/CiuwNMIa0C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps/ Platform Engineer: DevOps/ Platform Engineer is focused on: * Retail, Operating Systems, systems hardening, Virtualization and Automation. * 4 or more years of Linux or Windows systems administration experience. * Experience with modern… https://t.co/3stb5RmPyv https://t.co/VeqhOWybBN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager / Sr. Civil Engineer: PROJECT MANAGER GENERAL SUMMARY The Project Manager is responsible for managing multiple projects for private land development clients. Projects include planning, design and management for our industrial, commercial,… https://t.co/mo2hpj4VJe https://t.co/HdeimMzOtD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Bachelor' star slammed for April Fools' Day pregnancy joke: "The Bachelor" star Arie Luyendyk Jr. pulled an April Fools' Day pregnancy prank that some fans didn't find funny. https://t.co/fM7jqpBiLT https://t.co/oqlwPBl1g9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT/Cable Technician (100% Nationwide – Great Pay): JOB TITLE: Level 2: Lead Cable / Hardware Installation Technician Level 3: Certified Lead Cable / Hardware Installation, Telco and Troubleshooting Technician SUMMARY BY LEVEL: Level 2: Leads and manages… https://t.co/4Rrk7K2rcy https://t.co/pe4ivMx5cX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Engineering Specialist: Job Summary:Plans and develops engineering projects with unique or controversial problems which may impact ma-jor Corporate programs. Responsible for interpreting, organizing, executing and coordinating complex technical… https://t.co/VKFSGXpZ36]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[React Native Developer (Android/i OS) | Detroit MI| 6 Months| Positions – 1: TOP SKILLS: 1. Minimum 1 year of experience writing code for iOS/Android apps in React Native, or a minimum of 2 years experience building applications using JavaScript… https://t.co/roNsynTVvx https://t.co/ZR8spChZbu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager: Job Details (*Employee Referral Program applies to this job) Job No. PM00001 Job Title Senior Project Manager Description Summary: Position Description: AD – Deployment manager will coordinate with hardware installers, network… https://t.co/dqdK5XazUB https://t.co/PToZ3QG5JS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Devops Engineer: Job Overview: Provide end-to-end DevOps solution by employing the most appropriate tools for CI/CD set up, continuous feedback, continuous monitoring, continuous planning, and continuous testing. Responsibilities: * Consult to provide… https://t.co/nJyvpy7QsO https://t.co/xSYwe96ziJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering Project Manager: Job Description We are AAM. We have the POWER to move the world. At AAM, we’re looking for associates who push boundaries and drive solutions for the future. Innovators. Thinkers. Dreamers. Doers. No matter the role or… https://t.co/Lgs67u90hn https://t.co/4ID56qk9dx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .Net Developer: Senior .Net Developer Senior .Net Developer Company Autobooks Location US-MI-Detroit Opportunity Details What You’ll Do/Need Within this role at Autobooks you will be a senior participant in the design and development of… https://t.co/kj4YQZkzeU https://t.co/SYAcgtmEwO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Quality Analyst III| Detroit MI| 10 Months| Positions-1: Test Case Authoring: Develop detailed Test Cases based on the Functional Requirements and Design Documents. Execute the Test Cases and Analyze the Test Results. Usage of test tools as ALM… https://t.co/qAlOUM8DKj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Installation Technician (Detroit Lakes, MN): Detroit Lakes, MN, USAHourlyFull Time Inside Out provides competitive compensation, health insurance, PTO, and retirement benefits! Inside Out is an installation contracting company headquartered in Detroit… https://t.co/YFG4HBTCYi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Engineering Specialist: Job Summary:Plans and develops engineering projects with unique or controversial problems which may impact ma-jor Corporate programs. Responsible for interpreting, organizing, executing and coordinating complex technical… https://t.co/noeXmcgqNw https://t.co/TYXHQpFHfN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Assistant Project Manager-South East Michigan: We are looking for an Construction Assistant Project Manager to help plan, supervise, and handle the administrative duties on a wide range of construction projects from start to finish. You will assist with… https://t.co/k4nmjCiC15 https://t.co/xlLYfvqvP0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How GrubHub Analyzed 4,000 Dishes to Predict Your Next Order: Online food-delivery service spent eight years resolving a classic problem of unstructured data. https://t.co/q1GK2CJBGt https://t.co/wkOgY1Wd6w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Software Engineer II (JSE)| Detroit MI| 1 Year| Position- 1: Enterprise Software Engineer II 1. Major Duties and Responsibilities a. Define, design, build, test, deploy, and support software products b. Consistently follow the specified… https://t.co/0qBLqTFEOG https://t.co/YHqGLAvjXD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Systems Security Specialist: **This is a Full Time position (not a contract). Must be authorized to work in the U.S. without sponsorship. Must be a US citizen or a green card holder. F1 OPT and Corp to corp candidates will not be… https://t.co/wKiZThiVyV https://t.co/L47rLYl7BJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why the universe shouldn't exist at all: "Why is there something, rather than nothing?" could be the oldest and deepest question in all of metaphysics. Long exclusively the province of philosophy, in recent years this question has become one that can be… https://t.co/4poJNMO55R https://t.co/rzEgYObGfm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT/Cable Technician (100% Travel – Nationwide): JOB TITLE: Level 2: Lead Cable / Hardware Installation Technician Level 3: Certified Lead Cable / Hardware Installation, Telco and Troubleshooting Technician SUMMARY BY LEVEL: Level 2: Leads and manages a… https://t.co/Isp2fIJ92Q https://t.co/vRmc9vNmBk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Script and HTML5 Front End Developer|Detroit MI| Positions – 1: Participate in and lead requirements analysis, specifications and design of custom-developed applications. Assist in the development of implementation/rollout plans. Ensure that… https://t.co/Lq6Af8Ofp5 https://t.co/mF29EvgKNI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: Dynatrace is actively growing our digital business team to drive modern cloud services forward. Our drive for innovation in product and services is unparalleled, and thats why customers like Apple, Delta, SAP and others succeed with our… https://t.co/xavU0Pm2xZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Cloud Infrastructure Automation Lead: 3046693 Senior Cloud Infrastructure Automation Lead Oil &amp; Gas Headquarters GE Oil &amp; Gas United States Provide IT leadership on multiple automation build projects. Help prioritize and drive results for the… https://t.co/viYdKZaHxf https://t.co/jdoM4NqEhx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior iOS Developer| 9 Months | Detroit MI| Position -3: YOU HAVE: Most likely 3+ years of experience on a team developing native iOS app(s) available in the app store Proven experience/responsibility for design and architectural decisions of app… https://t.co/aemh5Ko9Lk https://t.co/EWHgVktfnb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Software Engineer II (JSE)| Detroit MI| 1 Year| Position- 1: Enterprise Software Engineer II 1. Major Duties and Responsibilities a. Define, design, build, test, deploy, and support software products b. Consistently follow the specified… https://t.co/LK1vFQw27O https://t.co/f6Lkta3Zlg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Solution Architect: Cloud Solution Architect Microsoft envisions a world where passionate innovators come to collaborate, envisioning what can be and taking their careers places they simply couldn’t anywhere else. This is a world of more… https://t.co/gK2J9gBkEO https://t.co/FpwfqRrkay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .Net Developer: Senior .Net Developer Senior .Net Developer Company Autobooks Location US-MI-Detroit Opportunity Details What You’ll Do/Need Within this role at Autobooks you will be a senior participant in the design and development of… https://t.co/lYmxx56866 https://t.co/lMGVZ1SfXE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Installation Technician (Detroit Lakes, MN): Detroit Lakes, MN, USAHourlyFull Time Inside Out provides competitive compensation, health insurance, PTO, and retirement benefits! Inside Out is an installation contracting company headquartered in Detroit… https://t.co/D4kKmRrYJM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid to Senior Software Engineer – React: At Sift we take a consumer approach to B2B software: emphasizing understanding of the user experience and building beautiful and easy to use software that delights our clients. Were looking for a talented engineer… https://t.co/67wGlr0upA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Android Application Software Engineer| Detroit MI| Positions-2: QUALIFICATIONS REQUIRED: BS in Computer Science or other field of study along with applicable work experience Experience as developer on App(s) publicly available in the Google Play App… https://t.co/AJjieiAXJD https://t.co/HsKxBCKzgL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Quality Analyst II | Detroit MI| 10 Months| Positions – 2: EXPERIENCE: 5+ years experience in acceptance testing. Minimum of 5 years technical experience in Information Technology TOP SKILLS 5+ years testing experience (combination automated and… https://t.co/ZSb8T5aOxF https://t.co/TRX6S4Hb4A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer (Java Spring) – Detroit: ABOUT US TribalScale is an innovation firm that brings organizations – from the startup to the enterprise – into the future. We build digital products, transform teams, and grow startups. Were… https://t.co/zV44zVIIRu https://t.co/qPsK4pKMQm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Legend as Jesus: What to expect: In just a few hours John Legend will take the stage as Jesus Christ in NBC's live musical "Jesus Christ Superstar Live in Concert." https://t.co/J6qVQEaFjZ https://t.co/28DOJ3coKP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infotainment Application Software Engineer – Android|Detroit MI|10 Months | Positions-3: QUALIFICATIONS REQUIRED: BS in Computer Science or other field of study along with applicable work experience Experience with Android UI design (including custom… https://t.co/jc0vnvGrXE https://t.co/6c4fJsgslz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Software Architect: The Lead Architect will lead the architecture team in our digital transformation of our Application Performance Management solution. The candidate will have unmatched experience in software architecture and will place business and… https://t.co/OmEvA6r2Io]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OnSite iOS Developer: Detroit Labs OnSite is looking an iOS Developer to join one of our projects in downtown Detroit. This role is with our OnSite business unit; successful applicants will be working at the client location in Detroit. This team member… https://t.co/FJEmZ5e6PW https://t.co/qkehJflQBv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Quality Analyst III| Detroit MI| 10 Months| Positions-1: Test Case Authoring: Develop detailed Test Cases based on the Functional Requirements and Design Documents. Execute the Test Cases and Analyze the Test Results. Usage of test tools as ALM… https://t.co/BdClyjPkHt https://t.co/0nMLGzG6Rt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master II (Project Manager II)| Detroit MI| 10 Months| Position -1: MAJOR DUTIES AND RESPONSIBILITIES SCRUM MASTER Facilitate Scrum events (Daily Scrum, Sprint Planning, Sprint Review, Retrospective, Backlog Grooming) Coach Product Owner and… https://t.co/aWAmdty5Qy https://t.co/VWBJ46gIsa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Devops Engineer: Job Overview: Provide end-to-end DevOps solution by employing the most appropriate tools for CI/CD set up, continuous feedback, continuous monitoring, continuous planning, and continuous testing. Responsibilities: * Consult to provide… https://t.co/oGzgHwbNck https://t.co/AjZN2LHdMW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Software Engineer II| 118640| Detroit MI| 1 year| position -1: ENTERPRISE SOFTWARE ENGINEER II 1. Major Duties and Responsibilities a. Define, design, build, test, deploy, and support software products b. Consistently follow the specified… https://t.co/YfQ8LIC71i https://t.co/3FC00gs8V7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT/Cable Technician (100% Travel – Nationwide): JOB TITLE: Level 2: Lead Cable / Hardware Installation Technician Level 3: Certified Lead Cable / Hardware Installation, Telco and Troubleshooting Technician SUMMARY BY LEVEL: Level 2: Leads and manages a… https://t.co/nH8MbjwOgI https://t.co/5ah6o9wrl5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tier I Help Desk Technician: Detroit Lakes, MN, USAFull Time Arvig offers a competitive wage and an excellent benefits package, including health and dental insurances, Employee Stock Ownership Program, 401k, profit sharing, PTO, holidays, education… https://t.co/C03KzLAG4c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Project Manager Ref No.: 18-10731 Location: Detroit, Michigan Role : Project Manager Duration : 12 Months Location : Detroit, MI Job Description : Experience in legacy to SAP rolloutsData Migration End user testing,integration test… https://t.co/tEj832WYvM https://t.co/oolzkZ8fwY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front End Developer (Mobile Device) |Detroit MI|1 Year| Positions- 3: JOB SUMMARY Responsible for front-end design and development at the product application layers. Requires a good understanding of programming web based applications in order to meet… https://t.co/Y8wEWXtkcS https://t.co/offorXW8Hw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager / Sr. Civil Engineer: PROJECT MANAGER GENERAL SUMMARY The Project Manager is responsible for managing multiple projects for private land development clients. Projects include planning, design and management for our industrial, commercial,… https://t.co/rFzh0BP2JY https://t.co/lxCDjHQgUH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Software Engineer – Automotive: Ready to turn the wheel in the _AUTOMOTIVE _industry with a _HYPERGROWTH STARTUP_? MULTINATIONAL AUTOMOTIVE MANUFACTURER has already established connected car technologies abroad and are on the verge of the biggest… https://t.co/tz0RBcXUO1 https://t.co/1xfQ2zr6JD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The President isn't as pro-business as he claims https://t.co/ra9kyyWGdM https://t.co/xLvglEpIZy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Assistant Project Manager-South East Michigan: We are looking for an Construction Assistant Project Manager to help plan, supervise, and handle the administrative duties on a wide range of construction projects from start to finish. You will assist with… https://t.co/6MOg1KG5ME https://t.co/kEZn4LzuTm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Systems Security Specialist: **This is a Full Time position (not a contract). Must be authorized to work in the U.S. without sponsorship. Must be a US citizen or a green card holder. F1 OPT and Corp to corp candidates will not be… https://t.co/KJDjjp8srA https://t.co/G6k5qgnEUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Security &amp; Access Control Technician (Perham, MN): Detroit Lakes, MN, USAFull Time Join a winning company who has just been named one of the top 50 places to work in the northern plains area and a company that is owned by its employees! We are a growing… https://t.co/uaie8F58y5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Support &amp; UNIX Administrator| Detroit MI | 1 Year| Position- 1: MANAGER REQUIRED MINIMUM Software SkillsBEA WeblogicYes 1-3 https://t.co/sFVU8g9u3A SkillsJ2EEYes4-6 yrs. Software SkillsJavaYes4-6 yrs. Software SkillsPerlYes1-3 yrs. Software… https://t.co/C2gLbqvg3T https://t.co/eIAd46QEny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle Financial consultant: Title: Oracle Financial consultant Type of Employment: Direct Hire/Permanent Job Description: An experienced consulting professional who has a broad understanding of solutions, industry best practices, multiple business… https://t.co/oTE6S6aZei https://t.co/IqU1sTlosz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer (Java Spring) – Detroit: ABOUT US TribalScale is an innovation firm that brings organizations – from the startup to the enterprise – into the future. We build digital products, transform teams, and grow startups. Were… https://t.co/t0GIbldjk9 https://t.co/bJtP0k7URv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce Technical Architect: Job Description: * Technical architecture design of multiple complex deployments on Salesforce * Function as SFDC Technical Architect with experience in the following: + Thorough understanding of Web Services in general… https://t.co/kvFqMWn8xh https://t.co/EGK3uTEr7V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Systems Security Specialist: **This is a Full Time position (not a contract). Must be authorized to work in the U.S. without sponsorship. Must be a US citizen or a green card holder. F1 OPT and Corp to corp candidates will not be… https://t.co/0V0xVcaMcx https://t.co/l8acfaO9Wi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[React Native Developer (Android/i OS) | Detroit MI| 6 Months| Positions – 1: TOP SKILLS: 1. Minimum 1 year of experience writing code for iOS/Android apps in React Native, or a minimum of 2 years experience building applications using JavaScript… https://t.co/7H6OSBvWZ8 https://t.co/ONvaMSmC8V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adobe Campaign Developer: Job Description: Position Description We have an immediate need for an Adobe Campaign Manager (ACM) Developer to join our team to work in our Detroit, MI location. The ACM Developer uses technical expertise to ensure successful… https://t.co/6H5v3ADDKU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Assistant Project Manager-South East Michigan: We are looking for an Construction Assistant Project Manager to help plan, supervise, and handle the administrative duties on a wide range of construction projects from start to finish. You will assist with… https://t.co/PABYlzMgt7 https://t.co/islXmwvOmK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales Engineer – Telecommunications: Detroit, MI Full-time Compensation Unspecified Posted Today Job Title: Sales Engineer – Telecommunications Job Location: Detroit, MI Located in beautiful Downtown Detroit my client is a Detroit-based internet service… https://t.co/6g2vhJpsII https://t.co/xvtP9J99oO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OnSite iOS Developer: Detroit Labs OnSite is looking an iOS Developer to join one of our projects in downtown Detroit. This role is with our OnSite business unit; successful applicants will be working at the client location in Detroit. This team member… https://t.co/GFIRrUdGbB https://t.co/qyt7vs1vBM]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>