<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to Tumblr Blogging  http://t.co/CHHvhJOp8t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Who is The Grass Roots Classic Rock Group?  http://t.co/3sB9ZaMgGY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Cheryl Lynn  http://t.co/DaipV0blzw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn The Importance of a Good Pitching Repertoire for Young Pitchers  http://t.co/QkjHLvIATP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're told to pay as we go! But where are we going?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mama always said you could tell an awful lot about a person by the kind of shoes they wear. - Forrest Gump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes are just made from leather, rubber and cloth - read about exotic shoes... http://t.co/GSxfTGGCBD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Flying Alarm Clock - COOL!  http://t.co/FUiJDt0Mge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Rush  http://t.co/ecsmo9qifD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome disco t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the disco lovers in your life!   http://t.co/yToOvC0fXj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The worst examples of snap judgment are usually found in the old family album]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not whether you get knocked down; it's whether you get up. - Vince Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome biking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the biking lovers in your life!  http://t.co/4sT6rWKjzP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome - An Easy Toilet Seat Lifter - keep the girls happy :&gt;) http://t.co/sRJLSRfvyn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A teacher affects eternity; he can never tell where his influence stops. - Henry Brooks Adams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are flirting with danger when you buy high-heeled sandals - Eileen Allen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome ping pong &amp; table tennis tshirts &amp; gear - get something for the paddle lovers in your life! http://t.co/HJPqg5bQn6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sovereign invigorator of the body is exercise, and of all the exercises walking is the best. - Thomas Jefferson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Neil Diamond  http://t.co/CqoOn4VFeH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His pockets always outlast his suits...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Bee Gees  http://t.co/SG7aakWm8l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women should look like women. A piece of cardboard has no sexuality. - Alexander McQueen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Mars Exploration Project with Mars One  http://t.co/oWoz3aSVEs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spring is when you feel like whistling even with a shoe full of slush. - Doug Larson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The thing about science fiction is that it's totally wide open. But it's wide open in a conditional way. - Octavia Butler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about necessary foods for your prepper pantry!  http://t.co/pnlyMj8Zbs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here I Am T-Shirt What Are Your Other Two Wishes http://t.co/a5yQ1XRTAc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good teaching is one-fourth preparation and three-fourths pure theatre. - Gail Godwin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Cheryl Lynn  http://t.co/cJTi3gLuLs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[College isn't the place to go for ideas. - Helen Keller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Different Types of Beer  http://t.co/IRDacMaWHK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All My Friends Are Dead - Kids Book - Darkly Hilarious!  http://t.co/fminFlYcGc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't tell you what I had for breakfast, but I can sing every single word of rock and roll. - Patty Duke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hold fast to dreams, for if dreams die, life is a broken winged bird that cannot fly. - Langston Hughes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill, strange things are afoot at the Circle K. - Ted, Bill &amp; Ted's Excellent Adventure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space Invaders Video Game - Men's Silk Necktie - Cool! http://t.co/oSs9w6HMVz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Paul Evans the Classic Rock Artist?  http://t.co/enASs7NvtX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the Kane Chronicles  http://t.co/OnZiUTGD7E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dammit, man! I'm a doctor, not a physicist! - Leonard 'Bones' McCoy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With four pairs of shoes I can travel the world. - Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating History of American Idol   http://t.co/tDExOOjZ78]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These Messenger Bags are stylish and practical - cool! http://t.co/BSuHXVrBFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Paul Evans the Classic Rock Artist?  http://t.co/enASs7NvtX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education costs money, but then so does ignorance. - Sir Claus Moser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of LA Gear  http://t.co/GA8gJ43BAP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China has blocked Twitter!!  Now 2 billion people will have no idea what I'm having for lunch.  Bummer!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Barbara Acklin – “Love Makes a Woman”  http://t.co/gWc97dsp2o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heredity:  what makes the father and mother of a teen-ager wonder about each other]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bonsai Trees Are So Cool --  http://t.co/RSG4Pg6Z0K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It isn't necessary to blow out the other person's light in order for yours to shine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence is no match for Natural Stupidity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is not the answer to the question. Education is the means to the answer to all questions. - William Allin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The trick is to stop thinking of it as your money - IRS auditor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is one AMAZING Kate Upton poster - gorgeous http://t.co/AcG8uAkfAh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is the mark of an educated mind to be able to entertain a thought without accepting it. - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Firefall  http://t.co/BAvuSZmyZ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never wear the same shoe twice. - Dion Sanders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Media is a Helpful Tool in Connecting with Customers  http://t.co/4s2lgpP7MZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dress shabbily and they remember the dress; dress impeccably and they remember the woman. --&gt; Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money cant buy happiness, but it sure makes misery easier 2 live with!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The average dog is a nicer person than the average person. - Andrew A. Rooney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michael, I did nothing. I did absolutely nothing, and it was everything that I thought it could be. - Peter Gibbons, Office Space]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[History of Mojang - The makers of Minecraft - http://t.co/PUG61n1uLu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first and the best victory is to conquer self. - Plato]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a rock and roll singer.  -  Adam Ant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft House Showcase: Touring the Winning House  http://t.co/J66roc9J2s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He who opens a school door, closes a prison. - Victor Hugo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over the years I have learned that what is important in a dress is the woman who is wearing it. - Yves Saint Laurent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instead of giving myself reasons why I can't, I give myself reasons why I can. - Unknown Author]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some of the greatest Hollywood actors are not the award winners, but those congratulating them on their triumph]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one really knows who created Bitcoin - read about the fascinating history of Satoshi Nakamoto... http://t.co/XKuV8R62KF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know money is the root of all evil if you would like to find out more - just send me $10 - DM me ASAP !!  :&gt;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The History of Lyme Disease  http://t.co/G9r148f4g0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would not invest in any shoe that is too trendy. - Rachel Roy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eat, drink and be merry, for tomorrow ye diet. - William Gilmore Beymer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone can steer the ship when the sea is calm. - Publilius Syrus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fellow who rocks the boat is never the fellow at the oars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wasn't satisfied just to earn a good living. I was looking to make a statement. - Donald Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Bob Seger  http://t.co/ljVtme5nc6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Badfinger - The Godfathers of Power Pop  http://t.co/AWeG44RHUo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History Of Samuel Adams Beer  http://t.co/PUid4e932X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To win without risk is to triumph without glory. - Pierre Corneille]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool iPhone 4 Review  http://t.co/AH4To753ny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame Turf Wars: Them Hackers Though  http://t.co/SWjiSxFd3a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After the third flip, I lost control - Don Roberts after crashing in the Jade Grenade at New England Dragway in 1975.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, never mind the fashion. When one has a style of one's own, it is always 20 times better. --&gt; Margaret Oliphant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some of the worst mistakes in my life were haircuts --&gt; Jim Morrison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Cascades  http://t.co/vzba1lHgrP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Who Invented the Modern Watch?  http://t.co/8JV4Qyiu3K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every great batter works on the theory that the pitcher is more afraid of him than he is of the pitcher. - Ty Cobb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I'm going dancing, then I wear the highest heels with the shortest dress. - Kate Moss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes as much energy to wish as it does to plan!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world of achievement has always belonged to the optimist. - Harold Wilkins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Music from this Bose Blue Tooth system - iPad, iPhone and more - easy great sound -&gt; http://t.co/QQmDw3XMnT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know money is the root of all evil if you would like to find out more - just send me $10 - DM me ASAP !!  :&gt;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter what, the very first piece of social media real estate I'd start with is a blog.  Chris Brogan - New Marketing Labs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Libby: How'd you get shot, anyway? Sawyer: With a gun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is better than poverty, if only for financial reasons. - Woody Allen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Life Gives You Questions, Google has Answers - AJ Carpio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding good players is easy. Getting them to play as a team is another story. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>