<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Documentation Specialist: Documentation Specialist Allied Blending LP is currently looking for an experienced, personable individual to serve as a Documentation Specialist. The successful candidate is responsible for ensuring compliance in quality… https://t.co/BEs8Lk6O7G https://t.co/ULNj7pySJT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Content Writer: The Content Writer is responsible for brainstorming, writing and transforming ideas into compelling messaging through multi-channel platforms to include: websites, social media, blogs, brochures / collaterals, publications, ads, and other… https://t.co/YAzRXqYtk7 https://t.co/CBKxrqN2pj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales Engineer, Marking &amp; Coding for LATAM:   Job Description – Sales Engineer, Marking &amp; Coding for LATAM (38719) Job Description  Sales Engineer, Marking &amp; Coding for LATAM-38719 Description   Company: Hitachi America, Ltd. Division: Industrial… https://t.co/c1LGJfwcHj https://t.co/BxXkzEV5ZY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Information Assurance Cyber Specialist II – ISSM, Andover: 111937BR Sr Information Assurance Cyber Specialist II – ISSM, Andover MA – Andover 111937BR Raytheon IDS Andover, MA – Security Organization, Information Assurance/Cyber Sr Information… https://t.co/MWQoRQKygO https://t.co/1UPzALBkiV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Relationship Functional Consultant: Business Relationship Functional Consultant =========================================== Req #: ******Location: Washington, DC USJob Category: ConsultingSecurity Clearance: DOJ MBIClearance Status: Must be… https://t.co/jCIufUYygp https://t.co/cXjCPvwcNg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager, Fraud Analytics-IHM: Discover. A more rewarding way to work. At Discover Financial Services, you’ll find yourself in the company of some of the industry’s smartest and most reliable professionals. And at a company that rewards… https://t.co/uRcQjFjI4D https://t.co/HhIPf0DBv0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automation Engineer – Centralia, MO: Corporate Overview Hubbell Incorporated is an international manufacturer of quality electrical and electronic products for a broad range of non-residential and residential construction, industrial and utility… https://t.co/x2rxJd8Vxw https://t.co/fFwGGgvtBg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[COMPUTER SYSTEMS ANALYST: COMPUTER SYSTEMS ANALYSTS Southlake, TX area. Analyze science, eng., bus., &amp; other data processing problems for app. to electronic data processing sys. Analyze user reqs., procedures, &amp; problems to automate or improve existing… https://t.co/ms3WznaBzU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Information Security Analyst: Join our Winning Team as a Senior Information Security Analyst At CARFAX we are constantly EXPANDING our product and technology offerings!  This means we are continually bringing new, innovative products to market… https://t.co/cwj544INsm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst: Enterprise Data Office Data Analyst III, F/T, (Charlotte, NC) Gather, review, analyze, profile, validate, &amp; map system data into the data warehouse to meet reporting &amp; analytical business needs. Dvlp solutions &amp; recommendations for… https://t.co/U2BlLOVGe5 https://t.co/w8ynI4BvkV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staff System Engineer: Engineering: Staff System Engineer Develop/maintain firmware to control RFIC &amp; handle interface with wireless baseband; Validate and debug RF transceiver devices on customer platforms. Work site in Irvine, CA.   recblid… https://t.co/7hHCI1zp03 https://t.co/UAAyuowUDo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Java 16604: Huntington Ingalls Industries – Technical Solutions Division, Integrated Mission Solutions Group (Camber Corporation) provides mission-critical engineering and technical service to Information Technology, Federal Civilian,… https://t.co/hOpjE1oDrH https://t.co/FxLLT5g2PC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vehicle Engineering Section Manager – Electrical Engineering Manager 2:   Job Description – Vehicle Engineering Section Manager – Electrical Engineering Manager 2 (17029000) Vehicle Engineering Section Manager – Electrical Engineering Manager 2… https://t.co/gwy1fzYUdc https://t.co/7Dogzh0Unm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Systems Business Analyst: Job Description: The Information Systems Business Analyst plays a critical role in providing administration, operational, and project management support for the Business Systems at company. Computer Systems used in… https://t.co/3FCqIuZ0Dd https://t.co/QkoTaELuM5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal QA Engineer: Principal QA Engineer Description at Raytheon Skip Navigation Raytheon – Cyber – News – What We Do – Who We Are – Global – Investors – Careers – Visit:Cyber – Who We Are – Leaders – Businesses – Corporate Responsibility – Culture –… https://t.co/L7dy6B3Kxf https://t.co/OXRDTQAXci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Security Lead Technician: NETWORK SECURITY AUTOMATION ARCHITECT The Network Security Automation Architect is responsible for designing and engineering global solutions to include FW, Proxy, End User and Automation as a primary focus. OUR CLIENT’S… https://t.co/prBtM40reE https://t.co/yHYlmxmsR6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supply Chain Systems Analyst: PURPOSE AND SCOPE: The Supply Chain Systems Analyst will be responsible for overseeing the national transportation routing program from a distribution user’s perspective as well as the business/technical support side of… https://t.co/bfTIPIiplr https://t.co/RTxcdDrTRo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MTS Developer: Nutanix Inc. has openings in San Jose, CA: MTS Developer (Req #8CA01); Member Technical Staff (Req #8CA02); Member of Technical Staff (Req #8CA03); Member of Technical Staff, QA (Req #8CA04); Sr. Member of Technical Staff (Req #8CA05);… https://t.co/Zq21fYb0OH https://t.co/f1POfL20Ao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Technician: Moorhead Public Service (MPS) is accepting applications for an Information Technology (IT) Technician. This position assists in the day-to-day support and operations of the data and communication systems at Moorhead Public Service… https://t.co/vhBfXZYIiG https://t.co/ot3RuQcSOK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior DevOps Engineer: San Francisco, CA Full-time Compensation Unspecified Posted Today If you are a Senior DevOps Engineer with experience, please read on! What You Will Be Doing 1) Architect, implement and manage our infrastructure in the AWS cloud,… https://t.co/FeyejWJ8Aj https://t.co/0DYSSDP2Or]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UX designer: Job Title: UX Designer-Store Applications Company:GAP Inc Duration:6-9 month contract role Location: San Francisco W2 Contract Requirements: ?Minimum of 5 years of professional UX Design experience ?Previous experience creating and launching… https://t.co/62wR8S55ep https://t.co/i34PPXji56]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Acquisitions and DeNovos: PURPOSE AND SCOPE: The Project Manager, AIDI oversees and manages the assimilation of the FMCNA methodology of daily operations of the facility ensuring cost-effective facility operations in accordancewith all… https://t.co/l1jrBsNPqV https://t.co/WWHxKy8GsV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer II: Position Description Our ideal candidate: Versatile and eager to tackle new problems Agile, detail oriented, and driven to engineer awesome solutions Superior verbal and written communication skills Strong organizational skills… https://t.co/hvvmncPEMp https://t.co/93ytrRYYXq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Northrop Grumman Mission Systems is hiring Embedded Software Engineers and Digital Design Engineers–Join our Webinar on April 11th or April 24th!: This position description does not represent a current opening but may be used to identify candidates with… https://t.co/O34nR59r7B https://t.co/ftsGDDDxd4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer – Raiser’s Edge NXT: About Blackbaud: Leading uniquely at the intersection point of technology and social good, Blackbaud provides software, services, expertise, and data intelligence that empowers and connects people to advance… https://t.co/qUXWYTpO8h https://t.co/Obol219oXh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cosmetic Injector: This position is for a part-time cosmetic injector, This person MUST be licensed as an NP or PA in the state of Virginia. This person MUST have a minimum of 2 years experience in a medspa, plastic surgeon, or dermatology office using… https://t.co/yeHVRYh737 https://t.co/caR4JMaxIw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UI Engineer: At YapStone, we approach payments with the same startup mentality that we had when we launched our first payment solution in 1999. We are now focused on combining our entrepreneurial spirit with our immense payment expertise to take our… https://t.co/PIrzj5DFEb https://t.co/LIHoacg1Zb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Manager: Manhattan based, financial services company seeks skilled manager to assist senior management in leading software development and business operations. You will be essential to the day to day activity of our skilled programmer team. You’ll… https://t.co/MpfU8AmzIa https://t.co/1uHFPghBf4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Support / Scientific Container Engineer: Switzerland, Argovia, Kaiseraugst United States, California, South San Francisco As a core member of the Roche Scientific Infrastructure (RSI) team the Application Support / Scientific Container… https://t.co/AnSY0uPePm https://t.co/wX6uCaqziC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: Location: Alexandria, VA Job Description: Are you interested in working as part of a polyglot team to develop, coordinate, and support the automation of system configuration management to include server builds, changes and deployment of… https://t.co/as0qRpF4V7 https://t.co/szlaspdMzt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UX Designer – Search and Browse: Job posting details. UX Designer – Search and Browse Dick’s Sporting Goods Coraopolis, PA 15108 United States Description Join a team of award winning UX thinkers to build user-centered experiences that set the standard… https://t.co/ZAl1m66Lur https://t.co/7l7bdZ4ttr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java developert: Java developert st louis, Missouri – United States Job Start Date – 04/09/18, Posted Date – 04/09/18 Primary SkillsJava,ci,cdTax TermsC2COverviewclient – mastercard skype 6 months linked in Keys: ** Jenkins ** Any CI/CD experience ** Any… https://t.co/3DqXzIDbIB https://t.co/KZuq4cTrCC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Public Sector Business and Technology Experienced Associate: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities.… https://t.co/LfNTPp1Iox https://t.co/9peHDWxcmg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PeopleSoft Technical Trainer: PeopleSoft Technical TrainerDOA030557924*Richmond, VA*PeopleSoft Technical Trainer supporting agencies and the Cardinal Payroll Implementation CLIENT MINIMUM REQUIREMENTS: (ONLY APPLY IF YOU MEET ALL MINIMUM… https://t.co/FN3GyQcM04 https://t.co/shIV3pSeHc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IP – Customer – Manager: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about us at… https://t.co/o9f2nAnAev https://t.co/rRejz09cRo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft Dynamics AX Manager: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about us at… https://t.co/pE5FsAAObR https://t.co/q0sbWyGuAP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer (Full-Stack, Web): The Role and Team DataFox is the real-time source of truth on over 2 million companies around the world. Sales, marketing, and finance professionals all rely on DataFox to understand their markets and… https://t.co/A70sjrh7q2 https://t.co/tRI31c4u9b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Full-Stack Engineer (Ruby): Requirements: * 3+ years experience in software engineering with recent experience developing in Ruby on Rails (or other open source technologies but willing to learn Ruby on Rails) * HTML/CSS experience, including… https://t.co/WsylT6DfIY https://t.co/TvZY0ZcuxV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager-DoD/Federal Agency Portfolio: Tetra Tech is a leading provider of consulting, engineering, and technical services worldwide. Our reputation rests on the technical expertise and dedication of our employees16,000 people working together… https://t.co/5MnhZJuEgj https://t.co/IEs9YmW4iY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales Representative – Marketing Developer: Treetop Trekking Construction (TTT) builder and operator of Ziplines, Canopy tours, Aerial Adventure Parks, Treetop Trails, and Tree Walk Villages. TTT seeks a qualified candidate to serve as a Salesperson with… https://t.co/eu89vx57Wt https://t.co/PPLKuLsvsb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager-Mid Level: Project Manager-Mid Level ========================= Req #: ******Location: Quantico, VA USJob Category: Project and Program ManagementSecurity Clearance: TS/SCIClearance Status: Must Be Current Job Description POSITION SUMMARY… https://t.co/n9wRxzF6G0 https://t.co/ct2eSjw14k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Global Product Support Engineer: Applied Materials, Inc. has openings in Santa Clara/ Sunnyvale, CA: Process Engineer (Req #8C91007) Design, collect data, analyze and compile reports on a variety of difficult process engineering experiments; Process… https://t.co/kPrZ0s7xTs https://t.co/d8k5ALMEuP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Program Managers: Program Managers   Information Technology Microsoft Corporation currently has the following openings in Irvine, CA (job opportunities available at all levels, e.g., Principal, Senior and Lead levels). Program Managers: Coordinate… https://t.co/SunUurRJtu https://t.co/GSYifmS2Xz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Building Engineer – Oriskany, NY: JOB SUMMARY Utilizes advanced skills to perform complex preventive maintenance and corrective repair of buildings, industrial systems, vehicles, equipment and grounds. Working under limited supervision, monitors building… https://t.co/ldELCQOykV https://t.co/KKBOmwwiwJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Range Safety Manager: 82152BR Range Safety Manager Marshall Islands – Kwajalein Range Safety Manager Kwajalein Atoll This position is contingent upon contract award Raytheon has an exciting opportunity for you to be included in our key personnel as a… https://t.co/UeafYAacEk https://t.co/8W9GOhYNQh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Engineer Senior TS/SCI Herndon, VA: Req ID : 424888BR Job Code/Title : E1464:Systems Engineer Stf Job Description : This position is part of the Mission Planning team as the Lead Enterprise Scheduler. This position operates in a highly dynamic… https://t.co/CHJnPgSOje https://t.co/KlRViXvy7e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Data Engineer, Advanced Analytics Solutions: 112926BR IT Data Engineer, Advanced Analytics Solutions MA – Andover, MA – Tewksbury, MA – Woburn 112926BR Raytheon IDS – Tewksbury, MA; Andover, MA; or Woburn, MA (Boston Metro) IT Data Engineer – Advanced… https://t.co/scmRSlTxmh https://t.co/wUEu4BeaKO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software QA Engineer: Palo Alto Networks, Inc. is seeking applicants for the following positions in Santa Clara, CA: Sr. Software QA Engineer(s) (Job #442) &amp; Software QA Engineer(s) (Job #180): Dvlp &amp; execute sw test plans for ntwk security firewall… https://t.co/C8SIrgGc8T https://t.co/tYaQLG0CI4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Support Engineer-Kronos: Application Support Engineer – KronosRT010604020*Santa Barbara, CA*An APPLICATION SUPPORT ENGINEER responssible for the client’s campus Electronic Timekeeping system (Kronos application), with emphasis on developing Kronos… https://t.co/iv7uKMP5kj https://t.co/X6DmD8WzZk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Developer, CICD: Do you dream of a world where you can outsource all the mundane and repetitive tasks to machines and robots?  So do we and we’re making it happen through automation!  We believe that human brain-cycles should not be wasted… https://t.co/Q6xQN8rBmc https://t.co/b2zY6ONxrA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Software Developer – API Engineering: CenturyLink (NYSE: CTL) is a global communications and IT services company focused on connecting its customers to the power of the digital world. CenturyLink offers network and data systems management, big data… https://t.co/C9g03YW98o https://t.co/wvE4ImK6UT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Security Engineer: Description:The Advanced Solutions Group (ASG) at Leidos currently has an opening for an Information Security Engineer to work in Abingdon, MD to support a critical modernization effort of the Advanced Field Artillery… https://t.co/kyBgjkg3vf https://t.co/cn0spIfoLO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Facebook Debacle Proves It’s High Time for Stronger Privacy Laws: Opinion: The Cambridge Analytica scandal makes it clear: The US needs to pass a privacy law that gives consumers the protections they deserve. https://t.co/YgJtZer73c https://t.co/gheKzzEkrE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Secure DevOps Operational Risk Consultant 4: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we invest in our people. Our diverse lines of business offer unique opportunities to expand your knowledge and advance your career. This is an exciting opportunity to join a… https://t.co/5oTeAeofzQ https://t.co/78rMKKEu5O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Delivery: Semafone is the market leader in delivering secure voice transaction solutions to contact centers and other telephone payment channels across the globe. Our continuing growth and product innovation has created a new… https://t.co/p0uiMZNchC https://t.co/XsdQLMrb02]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Administrator: MUST BE A US CITIZEN WITH A U.S. GOVERNMENT CLEARANCE – TS/SCI WITH POLYGRAPH NOTE:Must have an active TS-SCI with poly. No sponsorships or upgrades are available. Submissions without this requirement will not be considered. H1-B… https://t.co/i0AC17guCZ https://t.co/aHV8xWyimr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Product Manager, Digital Markets:   Job Description – Product Manager, Digital Markets (00018909) Job Description  Product Manager, Digital Markets – (00018909) Description   Job Description: Gartner Digital Markets is the world’s most comprehensive… https://t.co/I81y6fA95T https://t.co/cV7zU8ikZp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst/ Data governance: Data Analyst/ Data governance Ref No.: 18-12885 Location: Elk Grove Village, Illinois Hi, This is Vatan from Enterprise Solutions, Inc. I came across your resume on a job board and wanted to check if you are available for a… https://t.co/evcbIdfSum https://t.co/dO9qtbcnfJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Analyst: The Business Systems Analyst will be gathering and analyzing data related to insurance product rating models, calculations, and business workflow processes in order to document requirements, build models, and code… https://t.co/vZxwGZQgzc https://t.co/CNQJr3X4Yb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer Senior: Software Engineer Senior ========================== Req #: ******Location: Fort Sill, OK USJob Category: EngineeringSecurity Clearance: SecretClearance Status: Must Be Current Job Description CACI’s Mission Solutions and… https://t.co/xTbgcxEG6z https://t.co/tjL4XJotsM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analytics Data Integration Developer: Senior Healthcare Analytics Data Integration Developer Develop data integration solutions to end user and application specifications independently and in collaboration with management and team members, as well as… https://t.co/azlMMvD1aE https://t.co/g6mQs4aG6w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mark Zuckerberg's Congress Testimony Day One: Simple Questions, Hard Answers: The basic lines of questioning Congress pursued show just how inscrutable Facebook remains to most Americans. https://t.co/JXwZL0OEX4 https://t.co/ABhiJfIZN6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Program Managers: Microsoft Corporation currently has the following openings in Irvine, CA (job opportunities available at all levels, e.g., Principal, Senior and Lead levels). Program Managers: Coordinate program development of computer software… https://t.co/jBDVpXCqKy https://t.co/4oAnfLOrAn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Master Software Engineer #R44354: Master Software Engineer – Capital One Services, LLC in Richmond, VA; Multiple positions available: Lead overall technical design, development, modification, &amp; implementation of comp apps using existing &amp; emerging… https://t.co/5HLTNUO50o https://t.co/Qwacaia7pt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer: Populus Group seeks a Developer in Irvine, CA. Must have a Master’s degree or equiv plus post-baccalaureate exp. Send resumes to Sarah Larson/ Ref#238591 at: slarson@populusgroup.com or Populus Group, 3001 W. Big Beaver Rd, Ste 400, Troy, MI… https://t.co/kzOJlaaNsB https://t.co/gmh4t9YmUV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Lead: Proj Lead, IBM Corp, San Jose, CA: Define &amp; dvlp UNIX S-TAP release test plan &amp; execution process. Design &amp; implement quality processes &amp; metrics. Anlyze changes &amp; new features based on functional &amp; design reqs. Recommend test strategies.… https://t.co/7BH6rGW4JO https://t.co/FT1Gc3pHVj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Master Software Engineer #R44563: Master Software Engineer – Capital One Services, LLC in Richmond, VA; Multiple positions available: Lead overall technical design, development, modification, &amp; implementation of computer apps using existing &amp; emerging… https://t.co/DQ7Z5RsowU https://t.co/9P60NHY12Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Program Manager: A2Z Development Center, Inc. – Irvine, CA. Technical Program Manager – Coordinate &amp; manage technical program development of large-scale, distributed software applications, systems, platforms, services &amp; technologies using… https://t.co/24AHss3cmY https://t.co/SYM2LqIvTg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineers: Careers At Raytheon One Global Team Creating Trusted, Innovative Solutions to make the world a safer place. Use your engineering skills to make the world a safer place with a career at Raytheon. We partner with our global customers to provide… https://t.co/0Sp9JgY1ZV https://t.co/AGXrpXib1z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer (Payspot, Inc. dba epay North America, Leawood, KS): Maintain &amp; devlp BackOffice system for US/ AU/NZ businesses. Reqs BS in Elect Eng or Comp Sci or frgn equiv. Resume to 3500 College Blvd, Leawood KS 66211 recblid… https://t.co/fCNr6mts8O https://t.co/NPZ6hHsLL3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch Mark Zuckerberg Testify Before Congress Live Right Here: On Tuesday and Wednesday, Mark Zuckerberg will testify before the Senate and House of Representatives. Here's how to make sure you don't miss a minute. https://t.co/lHWvJQUr8Y https://t.co/02ZliUBMBv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle EBS Business Analyst (West Bridgewater): *** No one with less than 2 years industry experience will be considered. *** *** No third party candidates will be considered. *** Candidates MUST have a minimum of specific domain experience and no… https://t.co/dHlYWRHlts https://t.co/0reLzNztMW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack JavaScript Software Engineer: ClearView Audit is looking to hire a Full Stack Software Engineer to join our rapidly growing software development team. On our team, you will be designing, developing, and supporting the core functionality that… https://t.co/Vvq6VGthAn https://t.co/msyHxFOZFL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FMV Analyst: FMV Analyst Location: McLean, VA Req Type: Pipeline Job Req ID: 2598 Description Altamira brings a commercial mindset to solving the most complex national security problems by delivering mission application development, multi-intelligence… https://t.co/1GUv7ewrDm https://t.co/UqYzmQsA7T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microwave Design Engineer RF 2/3:   Job Description – Microwave Design Engineer RF 2/3 (18000370) Microwave Design Engineer RF 2/3 Requisition ID : 18000370 Location : United States-California-San Diego US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes… https://t.co/elwND3muvB https://t.co/TF6bXgA8gk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Product Support Analyst:   Job Description – Product Support Analyst (1800003F) Job Description  Product Support Analyst – (1800003F) Why choose American Tower? It’s where you want to be. Today’s American Tower is a dynamic, performance-driven… https://t.co/9L5JfZesCw https://t.co/SRSnScK6HN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: The Software Engineer is responsible for maintaining and developing software used in the development and manufacture of fiber based lasers and optical amplifier products. Duties: Primary responsibilities include new product development… https://t.co/DjlE7HPHgC https://t.co/hJ4XuzjIWs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Software Engineer: Employers Pro Advantage Inc. is a Native Alaskan Women owned sdb specializing in the placement of highly skilled professionals in Accounting and Finance, IT/MIS and biomedical. Employers Pro Advantage Inc. has been in business… https://t.co/etTQvdyTAM https://t.co/Gh84ukYgsq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer III Non-IT (Cloud Application Operations Engineer): Careers Center | Software Developer III Non-IT (Cloud Application Operations Engineer) Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the… https://t.co/pUBYHSVEcU https://t.co/S3kO9Qj4SR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Administrator: Network Administrator Roaring Fork Transportation Authority Hiring a full-time Network Administrator to upgrade and support connectivity of RFTA’s network. Must provide technical oversight of WAN, monitor network performance,… https://t.co/fbvcx6TI8z https://t.co/KusjsWE99K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Expert II (DCS ULN Build Engineer) #69406: Technical Expert II (DCS ULN Build Engineer) Austin, TX. Duties: Install &amp; config Red Hat Enterprise Linux 6.x, 7.x, SuSe Enterprise Linux 11.x, 12.x &amp; Solaris 11 servers as per requirement. Config &amp;… https://t.co/rbrSEtYu6A https://t.co/T1aautZ8Tc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist-Global Strategic Pricing: CooperVision, Inc. seeks a Data Scientist-Global Strategic Pricing in Pleasanton, CA to support global pricing strategy and compliance through analysis of pricing data, tracking of competitive pricing/promotional… https://t.co/3dqjVMpaGG https://t.co/015JD5NdK9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One Woman Got Facebook to Police Opioid Sales On Instagram: After years of media reports and complaints, Instagram recently moved to restrict hashtags related to opioids and deleted some accounts. https://t.co/nuozAFrc5I https://t.co/lqvOiZE8Tv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead System Architect: IT/SOFTWARE Lead System Architect. Configuration of complex enterprise software systems, including Pegasystems PRPC, design and architectural oversight of software solutions. Bachelor’s or higher in comp. sci. 5 yrs exp. Exp with:… https://t.co/hdmjFrIFDF https://t.co/fVJgS7YMhx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Payspot, Inc. dba epay North America (Leawood, KS) – Software Engineer to dvlp secure transaction process sys, enterprise apps, sys admin apps, sys integration &amp; distributed WAN sys incl embedded terminal apps. Req’s Bach in IT or Soc… https://t.co/BJcK28i63C https://t.co/ffZSMl0Sf3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer #15-1133: Software Engineer (Code 15-1133) Responsibilities: Software Engineer sets directions of web frameworks, software methodologies and technology selection along with guiding the organization in building a robust, stable, and… https://t.co/zbisX5nuLJ https://t.co/APcw6AiFZo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Solutions Consultant: Google LLC, job # below: Database Architect (Mountain View, CA) Evaluate business needs to design on point database architectures for Google technology. #1615.5956 Exp Incl: C++, Java, or Python; partnering w/ business… https://t.co/fQ3IWBkE7x https://t.co/tRsR94sVHK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Princip Sftwre Engg (Santa Clara, CA) Prfm code mdfctn, tstng &amp; debggng &amp; analysis for APM solutn. Tst cmplte intgrtd APM prod &amp; bld apps. Dply &amp; srve vrtl comps. Implmnt tst scenarios simulating cust applics &amp; envrnmnt. Automte… https://t.co/cUXu34QdUu https://t.co/Cl1fScwOp6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analysis Manager: Data Analysis Manager Req ID R44556 Data Analysis Manager position with Capital One Services, LLC in Richmond, VA; Multiple positions available: -Manage quantitative and qualitative analysis and development of complex data… https://t.co/LesY4DVWxB https://t.co/e9ctrEcmEi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Applications Specialist (Business Intelligence and Data Analyst): Senior Applications Specialist (Business Intelligence and Data Analyst) Puget Sound Workers’ Compensation Trust and Unemployment Pool has an exciting opportunity for a Senior… https://t.co/e3eysiMTcT https://t.co/CJfCWHe17i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Help Desk/Technical Support Specialist: FHLBank Topeka’s products, services and programs help our member financial institutions provide affordable credit and support housing and community development efforts. We are accepting resumes for the position… https://t.co/9yj2YdkAAa https://t.co/1IK3h2P8Io]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SOFTWARE ENGINEER: Siemens PLM Software Inc. has an opening in Arlington, TX for Software Engineer Advanced to design, develop, modify &amp; implement software programming for Teamcenter Application products. Mail resumes to Attn: Tiara Robinson /Req#223896,… https://t.co/7WySxFATax https://t.co/ouFINxAGIn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer Analysts: Oracle America, Inc. has openings for the following positions (all levels/ types) in San Mateo County, including Redwood Shores, CA and San Bruno, CA; Alameda County, including Pleasanton, CA; San Francisco, CA; Santa Clara County,… https://t.co/vdS8AAO28R https://t.co/0HWMgH45F5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Design Engineer: Quality Assurance Engineer sought by RGB Systems dba Extron Electronics in Anaheim, CA. Complete manual &amp; automated testing of Extron’s products. recblid afhwn73zkcos9qqbbw3srlk8v5v6tm https://t.co/WUWfI2Yu0C https://t.co/PVCvv2prMk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook Imposes New Restrictions on Ads and Popular Pages: The social network will now require ads about political issues, not just elections, to be verified. It will also begin vetting Pages with large numbers of followers. https://t.co/sAoquisv7q https://t.co/cJu8OQOGHK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle EBS Business Analyst (Swampscott): *** No one with less than 2 years industry experience will be considered. *** *** No third party candidates will be considered. *** Candidates MUST have a minimum of specific domain experience and no resumes will… https://t.co/bWDp1ri7XS https://t.co/wapBTpT0dj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inside Plant (ISP) Engineer I: Client Reference Code: 212714-1Job Scope: Assist ISP personnel with troubleshooting, support and maintenance of network elements and connections required to support Charter’s revenue generating networks. Work to provide… https://t.co/TGFGQHyEo5 https://t.co/WuehU75iOR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer: Based in Boston, MA with offices internationally, we are a big data analytics Start-up that has revolutionized the way companies in the finance sector find new customers. By looking at behavioral data tracked through a consumer's… https://t.co/fzVNfx1FXe https://t.co/Tymtf41asY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Identity Management Architect – Sailpoint:   Job Description – Senior Identity Management Architect – Sailpoint (179590) Job Description  Senior Identity Management Architect – Sailpoint – (179590) Remote: Yes Primary Location : US-CA-Long… https://t.co/cEJYFyPrT2 https://t.co/inTouQWpHO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front End Developer (React, JavaScript, CSS): San Francisco, CA Full-time Compensation Unspecified Posted Today Based in San Francisco, CA we are a innovative FinTech company purely focused on streamlining the home buying experience for consumers. We've… https://t.co/ohIJOiAPsT https://t.co/CzxcNcjIWO]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>