<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Security Manager: Are you the best in your field and always excited about creating solutions that protect our information and privacy? Our client is an industry leader in electronic brokerage whose platform provides clients access to more than 100… https://t.co/cBiOxOY8UP https://t.co/5etx0kVIim]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Quality Assurance Engineer: EDUCATION and EXPERIENCE: Broad knowledge of a general technical field such as quality assurance involving the use of a broad theoretical knowledge. BS degree in related engineering field. Working knowledge of computer… https://t.co/FkbPBbAeIx https://t.co/mMq0SkBipb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: As Senior Application Developer, your role is to participate in the design and development of our new investment services initiatives. This is a role with significant growth potentials within a fast-paced business environment.… https://t.co/V3i6LeLEQc https://t.co/HqEqhv9dxG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Administrator: Belimo isa globalleader in the development, production andmarketing ofactuator solutions for controlling heating, ventilation and air conditioning systems. Actuators, control valves and sensors make up the company’s core business.… https://t.co/aoEP6tVanI https://t.co/hUx4vEdo23]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Cloud Software Engineer: Summit Technologies is looking for a Senior Cloud Software Engineer. The ideal candidate should have experience with hands-on design, development and engineering positions. Candidates should also have experience working with… https://t.co/Ujql4RywoG https://t.co/wRdVPDivwG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Site Transformation: Position Project Manager – Site Transformation Location Bloomfield, CT 06002 Duration 6 months or longer Pay Rate $50.00 – $60.00 DOE Start Date ASAP Project Manager JOB DESCRIPTION Position will manage the IT… https://t.co/WZ0XmV2GqT https://t.co/WhOUSBRKN1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UX Designer: Category: Development/Engineering City: Bloomfield, Connecticut, United States Position ID: J0318-2017 Employment Type: Full Time Meet our professionals CGI: An employer of choice offering a global health and wellness program Position… https://t.co/9dxlD32HZT https://t.co/9AHFsDv5Zn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Analyst with Healthcare – Windsor CT: Category: Business Consulting, Strategy and Digital Transformation City: Windsor, Connecticut, United States Position ID: J0218-1525 Employment Type: Full Time Meet our professionals CGI: An employer of choice… https://t.co/0K4g9FBcNz https://t.co/8UnPur2WpB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: Infosys HCADM Technology Lead – US Mainframe – CT Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to create and execute strategies for their digital transformation. From… https://t.co/pI26xhppl8 https://t.co/4oxf8Wrmb8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer Job Title :?Software &amp; Computer EngineerLocation :?Farmington, CTDuration :?9 -12 months contractcandidates must be US Citizens or Green Card holder.?Job Responsibilities:?Evaluate communications and connectivity… https://t.co/ltz8brF6AY https://t.co/fsHPSzLtU5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Support Analyst: Position: Support Analyst Location: Enfield, CT Job Id: 645 # of Openings: 1 Eppendorf is looking for a Support Analyst; an integral member of the IT-Applications team in Enfield, CT! What Eppendorf offers: – Robust total rewards program… https://t.co/XxugnzMHap https://t.co/FVrB3cBxZy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Engineer / Data Analytics Specialist, ASC: Businesses Pratt &amp; Whitney Job ID 63521BR Date posted 03/27/2018 City East Hartford State Connecticut Country US The sky has no limits. Flight is an instrument of human progress. It not only gets people… https://t.co/nLhIx96rs2 https://t.co/xdgcuXp9gt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cluster PMO – Project Manager Coordinator: Location Wilton – CT, US Level Bachelor Experience 2-5 Professional Available since 2018-01-11 Functional area Planning &amp; Logistics Background Others – Non Technical Reference US03628 Recruiter: Kamille Garcia… https://t.co/EkRn3SJ9vN https://t.co/8DV5jvmdW6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce Commerce Cloud Developer – Consultant: Salesforce Commerce Cloud Developer – Consultant | BrandShopContact Us BrandShop Digital Commerce Contact Us – About Us – What We Do – Commerce Technology – Marketing Services – Operations – Payments &amp;… https://t.co/yZCoIiPjmb https://t.co/PTurtMCBdm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Pega Architect: Category: Architecture City: Bloomfield, Connecticut, United States Position ID: J0318-1467 Employment Type: Full Time Position Description: CGI is looking for a Senior PEGA Architect to join our team in Hartford, CT for a Healthcare… https://t.co/9F0BzGW7Iy https://t.co/av1pPvmtkv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Controls and Automation Engineer: Job Description: This position requires an individual with introductory level engineering experience in the manufacturing industry. He or she will provide engineering support for continuous improvement Overall Equipment… https://t.co/bcrIiDYTOF https://t.co/earNmceTPG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer – Intern: Title Java Developer – Intern Requisition Number 18-0014 Post Date 2/27/2018 City Madison,WI;Eau Claire,WI;Aberdeen,SD;Rocky Hill,CT Description Great Lakes Educational Loan Services, Inc. is seeking Java Application Developer… https://t.co/FmJl3IAmlY https://t.co/X5OidC4H3H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: Role Technology Lead – US Auto req ID 29769BR Domain Utilities Skillset Sharepoint Application Migration , Country USA State / Region / Province Connecticut Work Location Berlin, CT Company ITL USA Job Description Infosys – MSWTPU –… https://t.co/k3LH1qlxt2 https://t.co/Mpw48Iz4FG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Mobile Platforms (Leading Brokerage Firm): Job Synthesis and Description Our client is a direct access electronic broker catering to the needs of professional and frequent traders, institutional investors, financial advisors, and… https://t.co/HsbiikeEfU https://t.co/OypizcZScm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Controls and Automation Engineer: Job Description: This position requires an individual with introductory level engineering experience in the manufacturing industry. He or she will provide engineering support for continuous improvement Overall Equipment… https://t.co/eveZUhu2Vn https://t.co/cZ7KwUTKYt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Category: Project Management City: Windsor, Connecticut, United States Position ID: J0318-1804 Employment Type: Full Time Meet our professionals CGI: An employer of choice offering a global health and wellness program Position Description:… https://t.co/J64qr8V960 https://t.co/o2KSte0SjV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: Infosys MSWTPU Technology Lead – US SharePoint Application Migration – Berlin, CT Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to create and execute strategies for… https://t.co/WnuBnJ9FsG https://t.co/f1LWkkYgnd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Full Stack: About the position *********************************************************** Developer/ZP0007 The Digital Team within Prudential’s Retirement division is looking for talented individuals to help drive Business value. If… https://t.co/7GeLhSHb3y https://t.co/kmxuONsjyd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Network Engineer: COMPANY OVERVIEW: ChimeNet is a data networking service provider offering innovative information technology (IT) solutions and 24/7/365 support for businesses where data transfer and security cannot be compromised. ChimeNet… https://t.co/sfi1X90Msx https://t.co/xBoBTKgpfd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer Hardware Engineer: Stratford Solutions is assisting their client with finding aComputer Hardware Engineerto add to their team located in Stamford, CT. This is a full-time, direct hire, W2 position with our client; cannot accept 3rd party… https://t.co/GxJbAE1ukW https://t.co/zh9IdDOyxE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – C++ (Leading Brokerage Firm): Job Synthesis and Description Our client is a direct access electronic broker catering to the needs of professional and frequent traders, institutional investors, financial advisors, and introducing… https://t.co/5YiGoZQDF3 https://t.co/PNlD5MycX3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: As Senior Application Developer, your role is to participate in the design and development of our new investment services initiatives. This is a role with significant growth potentials within a fast-paced business environment.… https://t.co/vWhWTcfJKo https://t.co/OrxhdizplL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior Quality Assurance Engineer (Leading Brokerage Firm): Job Synthesis and Description Our client is a direct access electronic broker catering to the needs of professional and frequent traders, institutional investors, financial advisors, and… https://t.co/asQh2jyn0B https://t.co/wtPUVPD0dD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network / Systems Administrator: Join one of CTs 2015, 2016, 2017 and 2018 Best Places to Work! We are an expanding IT company that is recognized as one of the Inc 5000s fastest growing companies and the MSPs Top 501. Exceptional Service. Unmatched… https://t.co/3BDz7GVDeD https://t.co/SnblHZGvXN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stamford IT Search Recruiting Manager: JOB REQUISITION Stamford IT Search Recruiting Manager LOCATION CT STAMFORD JOB DESCRIPTION Job Summary As a Recruiting Manager your responsibilities will include: * Business development: Develop and grow your own… https://t.co/idE9Gkiulb https://t.co/C14Msyn1Ag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Firmware/Software Engineer II: Position: Firmware/Software Engineer II Location: Enfield, CT Job Id: 540 # of Openings: 1 Eppendorf is looking for an energetic, hands-on Firmware/Software Engineer II in Enfield, CT! What Eppendorf offers: – Robust total… https://t.co/8FpW6BnT0t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hartford IT Search Recruiting Manager: JOB REQUISITION Hartford IT Search Recruiting Manager LOCATION CT HARTFORD JOB DESCRIPTION Job Summary As a Recruiting Manager your responsibilities will include: * Business development: Develop and grow your own… https://t.co/P5Mn2qYPJ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: Role Technology Lead – US Auto req ID 29769BR Domain Utilities Skillset Sharepoint Application Migration , Country USA State / Region / Province Connecticut Work Location Berlin, CT Company ITL USA Job Description Infosys – MSWTPU –… https://t.co/gN5hxK4p47 https://t.co/CaNIzYSwOo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Market Research Data Analyst: Kantar Worldpanel Shopcom is a data integration, activation and analytics firm connecting what consumers see, feel and do to help marketers, advertisers and publishers grow their brands through more impactful media… https://t.co/1Sk9j7mm7E https://t.co/Ce7kabJiLY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: InfosysHCADM Technology Lead – US Java – CT Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to create and execute strategies for their digital transformation. From… https://t.co/XgbZSTnR8q https://t.co/JR9bdV5qjz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Back end – Full time: We are seeking skilled Software Engineers with the following qualities: * Problem solver * Attention to details * Fast learner * Self-motivated and directed RESPONSIBILITIES * Enhancing automation of Back Office,… https://t.co/vfQKXLQB5v https://t.co/0BFank3xTh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Careers – Python Developer | ******* Skip to main content Experience the commitment – Careers sites – Global careers site – Visit our careers sites by country – Australia – Belgium – Brasil – Canada – Cesk Republika – Danmark –… https://t.co/fTFQU05iNm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Controls Engineer – Systems Integrator Experience: OneSource is in search of a Senior Controls and Automation Engineer who is exceptional in using technology to oversee or manage the manufacturing process. If you are a skilled engineer who has the… https://t.co/bNJRtwKH6H https://t.co/DDisF8Cfcl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Systems Developer: This position is a full lifecycle development opportunity, allowing the employee to participate in system design, development, documentation, testing, implementation, deployment, integration and support of all necessary… https://t.co/yhrdeAGIfT https://t.co/wsqfEZt8dI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grains and Oilseeds Data Analyst: The purpose of this role is to support the global oilseeds and grains research teams to provide timely information and accurate estimates of US and Global supply and demand estimates to the traders. Specifically, it aims… https://t.co/DfIWHo1K4i https://t.co/6lv3CaiTIm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agile Coach: Title: Agile Coach Location: Hartford, CT ,Jersey City , NJ , Minneapolis, MN, Boston MA &amp; Schaumberg, IL, H Duration: 6+ months H1B also accepted but good comm skill / Tech skills Job Description This role requires and Enterprise Level… https://t.co/3rcX13HtcU https://t.co/GuiYw3YB5k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CNC Programmer: Programmer – CNC Department: Manufacturing Position Summary: Supports Manufacturing operations by developing, editing &amp; updating programming for CNC manufacturing equipment utilizing CAD/CAM programs such as Unigraphics (UG) NX 7.… https://t.co/abJKyGaRX5 https://t.co/1DDv5IFsok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master Job: Scrum MasterLocation: Bloomfield, CTDuration : 6+ months?Scrum Master CertificationPMP certification is a plus, agile?Raeela ******************************************?? – provided by Dice Scrum Master Certification – ID#:… https://t.co/zuXtJzm49Z https://t.co/X9lcDBStCe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Analyst with Healthcare – Windsor CT: Category: Business Consulting, Strategy and Digital Transformation City: Windsor, Connecticut, United States Position ID: J0218-1525 Employment Type: Full Time Meet our professionals CGI: An employer of choice… https://t.co/8ttu3kkmIU https://t.co/7CvyR0hz9D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Car Install (MECP Basic, Geek Squad): Our technicians are passionate electronics experts and are especially impassioned when talking about the connected car. As a Geek Squad Autotech, youll go through the typical onboarding, job shadowing and new hire… https://t.co/I8U2XMHMRx https://t.co/Jg2yG8Pcow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer – Athlete Req: Category: Development/Engineering City: Bloomfield, Connecticut, United States Position ID: J0318-0203 Employment Type: Full Time Meet our professionals CGI: A place to build an IT career Position Description: CGI is looking… https://t.co/YfEh92AFSj https://t.co/HEbMUd3Wtl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cisco Solution Architect: The selected Cisco Solution Architect will be covering Hartford, CT and Danbury, CT so ideally candidates will be somewhat commutable to either location. They won’t be required to go into the office much but they will have to… https://t.co/pD2wKTKGEC https://t.co/xJhvvAIGow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Controls Engineer – Systems Integrator Experience: OneSource is in search of a Senior Controls and Automation Engineer who is exceptional in using technology to oversee or manage the manufacturing process. If you are a skilled engineer who has the… https://t.co/4fhQHZJgOP https://t.co/HC4nChBVox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer: This position is responsible for continuous improvement, implementing, testing and ongoing support of IT NAM infrastructure Services for North America. This includes Network, UC and Workplace, Site Infrastructure, Security and manage… https://t.co/2Y3JnS03zJ https://t.co/hFzMyYKOLZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Haven Accountemps Salaried Professional Services: JOB REQUISITION New Haven Accountemps Salaried Professional Services LOCATION CT NEW HAVEN JOB DESCRIPTION Job Summary The Staffing Executive is a very unique role within RHI, combining the best of… https://t.co/5Ec5QV9jbw https://t.co/GYJ17Yca62]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAFs Scrum Master/Project Manager: Position: SAFs Scrum Master/Project Manager Location: Enfield, CT Job Id: 554 # of Openings: 1 Eppendorf is looking for an energetic, hands-on SAFs Scrum Master/Project Manager in Enfield, CT! What Eppendorf offers: –… https://t.co/Oiwiq1BxoT https://t.co/OOG1bw4tVi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Pega Architect: Category: Architecture City: Bloomfield, Connecticut, United States Position ID: J0318-1467 Employment Type: Full Time Position Description: CGI is looking for a Senior PEGA Architect to join our team in Hartford, CT for a Healthcare… https://t.co/5ZsYC3PHYY https://t.co/0eDkQ1xAev]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Businesses Pratt &amp; Whitney Job ID 61936BR Date posted 02/27/2018 City East Hartford State Connecticut Country US The P&amp;W Military Engines Digital Strategy team is looking for individuals capable of carrying out its charter of… https://t.co/j4jne2tOK9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Site Transformation: Position Project Manager – Site Transformation Location Bloomfield, CT 06002 Duration 6 months or longer Pay Rate $50.00 – $60.00 DOE Start Date ASAP Project Manager JOB DESCRIPTION Position will manage the IT… https://t.co/Z9bPp0dFYh https://t.co/WuEg8bahFX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer Hardware Engineer: Stratford Solutions is assisting their client with finding aComputer Hardware Engineerto add to their team located in Stamford, CT. This is a full-time, direct hire, W2 position with our client; cannot accept 3rd party… https://t.co/XmMBKeseuh https://t.co/HZzM6t7qhI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Operations Analyst: Senior Operations Analyst Location US-CT-Westport Posted Date 5 days ago (3/15/2018 1:42 PM) Job ID 2017-35534 # Positions 1 Category Information Technology Overview: About the Position: Title: Senior Operations Analyst Reports… https://t.co/OA3zrkr0GF https://t.co/NuDqhkULtw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: InfosysHCADM Technology Lead – US Java – CT Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to create and execute strategies for their digital transformation. From… https://t.co/cGjfT7c0OG https://t.co/cpEsGcZlFw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Avaya Telecom Engineer: Job Details: Position Title: Network and Voice Specialist Duration: 12 months contract Qualifications: * Telecommunications Network Capability – Must Have * Candidate must have minimum 3 years of working experience on Avaya… https://t.co/2XqKpBbE1o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Support Analyst: Country: United States Work Location: Newington State: Connecticut Advertising End Date: Not Specified Job Type: Regular About The Opportunity What you’ll do Job Summary The role supports users the usage of business… https://t.co/s39GzfWYWY https://t.co/6u3ewQe6EL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net tech lead/architect: .Net tech lead/architect Ref No.: 18-12117 Location: Hartford, Connecticut .Net tech lead/architect Hartford CT Long term NO JD Thanks and Regard’s Atul Malviya Sr. Technical Recruiter Enterprise Solutions, Inc. 500 E. Diehl… https://t.co/im8jQq7q5X https://t.co/Umh0mNzgbC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Firmware/Software Engineer II: Position: Firmware/Software Engineer II Location: Enfield, CT Job Id: 540 # of Openings: 1 Eppendorf is looking for an energetic, hands-on Firmware/Software Engineer II in Enfield, CT! What Eppendorf offers: – Robust total… https://t.co/YTlTeMQasD https://t.co/GEx7Ejp5hl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Developer – Campus Recruiting: Category: Development/Engineering City: Hartford, Connecticut, United States Position ID: J1017-1264 Employment Type: Graduate Position Description: CGI is seeking students interested in careers in the… https://t.co/g27VabO8JM https://t.co/TDwiLD1pL9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[F135 Technical Graphics Developer/Illustrator: Businesses Pratt &amp; Whitney Job ID 62073BR Date posted 03/05/2018 City East Hartford State Connecticut Country US The sky has no limits. Flight is an instrument of human progress. It not only gets people… https://t.co/tgJvgPs2Ya https://t.co/luhHPAlHs0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Visiting Faculty Position, Non-Tenure Track: Business Analytics and Data Science: Position Information Job Title Visiting Faculty Position, Non-Tenure Track: Business Analytics and Data Science Rank Visiting Faculty Tenure Information Non-Tenure Track… https://t.co/8KZfAZtVd8 https://t.co/wfLKBLF2Nx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test Analyst – US: Role Test Analyst – US Auto req ID 29487BR Domain Independent Verification and Validation Testing Skillset Automation Testing Service , Automated Testing Country USA State / Region / Province Connecticut Work Location Hartford, CT… https://t.co/xXG4CwrurO https://t.co/jkBZX3SsO8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Coach: Category: Project Management City: Bloomfield, Connecticut, United States Position ID: J0318-0078 Employment Type: Full Time Meet our professionals CGI: A place to build an IT career Position Description: CGI is looking for a DevOps Coach… https://t.co/dlE5eNBTH1 https://t.co/MyeU4jFnUC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: As Senior Application Developer, your role is to participate in the design and development of our new investment services initiatives. This is a role with significant growth potentials within a fast-paced business environment.… https://t.co/iGW33480q1 https://t.co/H959PYKQGv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Support Analyst: Country: United States Work Location: Newington State: Connecticut Advertising End Date: Not Specified Job Type: Regular About The Opportunity What you’ll do Job Summary The role supports users the usage of business… https://t.co/ooDo7sgNOm https://t.co/LvCkznx0Sl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Visiting Faculty Position, Non-Tenure Track: Business Analytics and Data Science: Position Information Job Title Visiting Faculty Position, Non-Tenure Track: Business Analytics and Data Science Rank Visiting Faculty Tenure Information Non-Tenure Track… https://t.co/Tadaz3mO26 https://t.co/q2Fe4N4A8t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ERP System Manager – Retail / Manufacturing: ERP System Manager – Retail / Manufacturing Responsibilities * Meet the goals and KPIs and ensure that they are done. * Directs the team by providing enterprise systems for Point-of-Sale, Purchasing, Inventory… https://t.co/2DZXVjqGiP https://t.co/Pu1An1QLhp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DPHM, ATG Software Engineer: Businesses Pratt &amp; Whitney Job ID 62177BR Date posted 03/02/2018 City East Hartford State Connecticut Country US Pratt &amp; Whitney, a recognized leading producer of the world’s most advanced jet engines, is looking for… https://t.co/TkJnVmQpk0 https://t.co/P4DSXNzwcC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Businesses Pratt &amp; Whitney Job ID 61794BR Date posted 02/27/2018 City East Hartford State Connecticut Country US The P&amp;W Military Engines Digital Strategy team is looking for individuals capable of carrying out its charter of… https://t.co/WkWRmJBXkK https://t.co/xEaS8g0BrO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Avaya Telecom Engineer: Job Details: Position Title: Network and Voice Specialist Duration: 12 months contract Qualifications: * Telecommunications Network Capability – Must Have * Candidate must have minimum 3 years of working experience on Avaya… https://t.co/GzHd4KDzys https://t.co/2nAhatg3Wc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[F135 Technical Graphics Developer/Illustrator: Businesses Pratt &amp; Whitney Job ID 62073BR Date posted 03/05/2018 City East Hartford State Connecticut Country US The sky has no limits. Flight is an instrument of human progress. It not only gets people… https://t.co/RftKxps1qd https://t.co/PD9wMRqakY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network / Systems Administrator: Join one of CTs 2015, 2016, 2017 and 2018 Best Places to Work! We are an expanding IT company that is recognized as one of the Inc 5000s fastest growing companies and the MSPs Top 501. Exceptional Service. Unmatched… https://t.co/U5CzKcpQUz https://t.co/X0V689IQOi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Hardware Engineer: Sr. Hardware Engineer Design solutions to drive safe living and quality of life Use your advanced knowledge of the hardware engineering discipline, processes and tools to help Honeywell Fire Systems deliver innovative solutions… https://t.co/pnJrUWCrLY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electronics Project Manager: Job Description LocationWilton – CT, US LevelBachelor Experience&gt;10 Senior Available since4/11/2018 Functional areaProject Management BackgroundElectronics Referencereq1781 Introduction ASML US, LP brings together the most… https://t.co/Y2zs2kyfeC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: QualificationsBachelors in EE, CS, Math, Physics or similar (Masters/PhD a plus).Technically oriented, proactive, and enthusiastic, with extreme attention to detail.Working experience with core Java.Knowledge of Java Swing and/or… https://t.co/zcraPJbnnp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Managers/Civil Engineers for Aviation Projects: Project Managers/Civil Engineers for Aviation Projects We seek highly motivated civil engineers with aviation experience who are in search of work in a challenging, dynamic, and caring work… https://t.co/2jkswsW7il]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electronic Systems Architect: Job Description LocationWilton – CT, US LevelBachelor Experience&gt;10 Senior Available since4/4/2018 Functional area Background Referencereq2016 Introduction ASML US, LP brings together the most creative minds in science and… https://t.co/9LcHfGQ3a0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[software engineer in test: About AQR Capital Management AQR is a global investment firm built at the intersection of financial theory and practical application. We strive to deliver concrete, long-term results by looking past market noise to identify and… https://t.co/EEvSarqBhB https://t.co/SjJ9ccR2LQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Developer: Sr. Software Developer Innovate to solve the world’s most important challenges Home and Build Technologies is seeking an Experienced Software Developer to grow our back office cloud development team. The candidate will be working… https://t.co/7tx4xwE6Do https://t.co/UIgRcaRGkN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Engineer: Front end: Java Swing. End-user facing trading platform.Back end: Core Java. Data model and transport layers. Multi-threaded/high throughput. XML.QualificationsBachelors in EE, CS, Math, Physics or similar (Masters/Ph.D. a… https://t.co/3QXUiqf8qZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Backend Engineer: Core Java. Data model and transport layers. Multithreaded/high throughput. Work on one of the core brokerage processes that deals with user authentication to access trading, account management and other customer applications.Adding… https://t.co/1qPKiotIsq https://t.co/OaK4Re6kYT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federal IT Audit Consultant: Recruiter Deloitte Location Norfolk Norfolk United States Salary Competitive Posted 27 Apr 2018 Closes 25 May 2018 Job role Audit Sector Accounting and public practice Contract type Permanent Hours Full time You need to sign… https://t.co/l4nTItEZmO https://t.co/4dsJ9hjZqJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager for Building Enclosures: Senior Project Manager for Building Enclosures Seeking a Registered Senior Project Manager in our Towson, MD office. Key Responsibilities * The selected candidate would provide building enclosure… https://t.co/rs5bZqzQAV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .NET Developer: Senior .NET Developer – What We Do Featured Using React Native to Build Two Native Apps &amp; Increase Paid B2B Subscriptions for Itemize Customer Story – Consult – Operate – Design – Optimize – Engineer – How We Do It – Our Work –… https://t.co/c7vJr5pmJ2 https://t.co/PLCTOATOAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Embedded Software Developer: Sr. Embedded Software Developer Innovate to solve the world’s most important challenges Home and Build Technologies within Honeywell is seeking an expert Sr Embedded Software Developer to grow our back-office cloud… https://t.co/qK7W5wF9px https://t.co/FulUa9APNQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: QualificationsBachelors in EE, CS, Math, Physics or similar (Masters/PhD a plus).Technically oriented, proactive, and enthusiastic, with extreme attention to detail.Working experience with core Java.Knowledge of Java Swing and/or… https://t.co/aLcVdM7RAR https://t.co/TCvzmcKdv0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Software Engineer: The Big Willow is radically improving how sellers find buyers. Would you like working at The Big Willow? Answer that by peering inside our DNA (some people call it core values): * Be ambitious and audacious * Value… https://t.co/AVBorBNZZx https://t.co/hB71i0CrTO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager/Environmental Health and Safety – Plainville, CT Office: Project Manager/Environmental Health and Safety – Plainville, CT Office Loureiro Engineering Associates, Inc. (Loureiro) has an immediate opening for a Project Manager/Environmental… https://t.co/0kLGyMOMv1 https://t.co/QNH8B5rBv6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hybris Tech Lead: Hybris Tech Lead Ref No.:18-07739 Location: Stamford, Connecticut Position Type:Contract Start Date: 04/25/2018 – Interpret written business requirements and technical specification documents. – Perform coding to written technical… https://t.co/FeBadIQCj0 https://t.co/IX4W4wCvWw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Design and develop real time clearing and banking applications and services for integration with continually expanding business relationships such as Clearing Corporations, Banks and Regulatory EntitiesWork on the implementation and… https://t.co/JCLzJu9cf6 https://t.co/oQTqcSPrLW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Security Programmer: Qualifications Minimum of Bachelors degree in a technology related field5+ years of IT experience3+ years of IT security experience 2+ years of Linux experience 2+ years of C programming or equivalent skill level (at least… https://t.co/CEXcgEXME7 https://t.co/B0E7Jz9n4K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technician/Agent. Geek Squad Advance Repair: Our Agents quickly and accurately diagnose client technology issues using specialty software and make solution-based recommendations to our clients in a timely fashion. This is a highly-coveted technology role… https://t.co/28HqoXCV7s https://t.co/6SfoSlZw5W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle DBA: ******/Oracle DBA Ref No.: 18-18219 Location: Danbury, Connecticut JD: Primary Skill ORACLE 11g, 12c – 7+ years Database administration experience with minimum 5+ years ORACLE 11g, 12c. – Experience in administering Oracle ASM, RAC,… https://t.co/TNhkS2OrlN https://t.co/lbzOnUeAMQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Geek Squad Consultation Agent: Geek Squad Consultation Agent Our Agents are the first point of contact for clients and command the check-in and check-out experience of client devices. They ask the right questions, listen to client needs, take detailed… https://t.co/1VqYWs8vkv https://t.co/Gx1JZ76IWJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Title Data Scientist: – Data Scientist Job Locations US-CT-Greenwich | US-CT-Greenwich ID 1650 Department Information Technology Company Overview IBG LLC, a subsidiary of Interactive Brokers Group, Inc. (NASDAQ: IBKR) is a direct access electronic broker… https://t.co/oZoe2NmQiv https://t.co/6tFzQTIdHE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Network Engineer: Job Title Senior Network Engineer Requisition # 7531 Location New York – New York, NY 10016 US Norwalk – Norwalk, CT 06851 US (Primary) Job Type Full-time Career Level Experienced (Non-Manager) Category Engineering Education… https://t.co/U98pRx469u https://t.co/qfv0D0ZWOd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technician/Agent. Geek Squad Advance Repair: Our Agents quickly and accurately diagnose client technology issues using specialty software and make solution-based recommendations to our clients in a timely fashion. This is a highly-coveted technology role… https://t.co/3J2o5PBeYW https://t.co/fKDquo4J8e]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>