<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Jeffrey Tambor Is Not Returning To "Transparent" After Sexual Harassment Allegations, Amazon Says https://t.co/6OrZ3NnNq6 https://t.co/hZ87cfZKFN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Difficult Men Meet Their Match In “Fifty Shades” And “Phantom Thread” https://t.co/G9xfNaUUbi https://t.co/5O7UWuierT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Black Panther” Is A Pan-African Medley Aiming To Reframe The Narrative https://t.co/0WSGAy5zw8 https://t.co/gMyjDsrggs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kelly Ripa Gave A Powerful Speech On Her Morning Show About Gun Violence In America https://t.co/TRe6ii72t9 https://t.co/EGntA6OwOX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @blackmon: "There needs to be a bigger, better dialogue because we are failing in this area." https://t.co/mQhlzMiN4D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @blackmon: Kelly Ripa on the recent Florida school shooting:

“And people are gonna say, ‘Oh, you’re a talk show host, shut up.’ In this…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[33 "The Good Place" Moments That Are All Funny, No Filter https://t.co/QxCNLP9yL6 https://t.co/BckyIrrZ3A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If You Get 6/10 On This Movie Title Quiz, You Have A Huge Vocabulary https://t.co/p3DyMHSxZ8 https://t.co/U3AoDKXaGL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Many Of These Top 50 Romantic Films Have You Seen? https://t.co/afZHVUh0xF https://t.co/F7wLYdgWaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have No Fear, There Will Be A Fifth Season Of "Grace And Frankie" https://t.co/1cul4TacU2 https://t.co/YhdFVmJ7DS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lena Waithe Is Making A New Show About A Queer Black Woman https://t.co/mtWk9yxcWa https://t.co/4Yo8QFxrnY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another Scott Baio Co-Star, Alexander Polinsky, Has Accused Him Of Misconduct https://t.co/UDTMfYX3Sm https://t.co/NnSq9rItIf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These Recently Canceled Queer Shows Deserved So Much Better https://t.co/INu4PRRQh9 https://t.co/PUn7wzsKV4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here Are The "Queer Eye" Transformations That Were The Most Challenging https://t.co/m4AvzXKOAU https://t.co/X4mX00ps2w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Is What It Was Like At The African Premiere Of "Black Panther" https://t.co/Xe7VWvuUOw https://t.co/ktVindeG6x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[19 TV Show Endings That Properly Annoyed The Fuck Out Of People https://t.co/CedClTtYoY https://t.co/OpUuLvUNQ8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's How They Filmed The Most Intense Episode Of "Queer Eye" https://t.co/1vyhMSIXQM https://t.co/L3yJ9j6RFV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Shooting Is Being Investigated Near The National Security Agency's Headquarters https://t.co/rBTSvZjm65 https://t.co/Ertz19c5Hh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which "The Big Bang Theory" Character Are You? https://t.co/gSsDNaW7pG https://t.co/50AQGL2vRe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tessa Thompson Is Going To Star As Famed Jewelry Thief Doris Payne In A Biopic https://t.co/siE8ibn3LJ https://t.co/ylCF0nXjkw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The “Thirteen Reasons Why” Author Says He's Being Harassed After Having "Affairs With Consenting Adults" https://t.co/4vqVqf0jkd https://t.co/I9KXeqjy5r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chrissy Teigen Dragged Kevin Sorbo From "Hercules" On Twitter And People Are Here For It https://t.co/XKip4RBLBG https://t.co/EJzXN6VvVY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[31 "Brooklyn Nine-Nine" Moments That Are All Funny, No Filter https://t.co/xnapFXvleq https://t.co/hKhv6JZegJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["American Horror Story" Fans Keep Trespassing On The "Murder House" Property And The Owners Have Had It https://t.co/SiW66C0aon https://t.co/yh0OJxMSYl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @blackmon: "American Horror Story: Tourists" https://t.co/hYgm692JKZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Danielle Herrington Got A Surprise Message From Tyra Banks After Her S.I. Swimsuit Cover Reveal https://t.co/RbxMZgdGbS https://t.co/Y83AbbITcn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New York State Has Filed A Civil Rights Lawsuit Against Harvey Weinstein https://t.co/JFKHQIvwPK https://t.co/eUspBr5Mj1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chris Hemsworth Reveals Why He Moved His Family To Australia https://t.co/HiDvd5b1sa https://t.co/3hhTvdfta7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Popular Are Your Movie Franchise Opinions? https://t.co/k5sqU0jvEL https://t.co/5S8MhwsUP2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[22 Things That Would Definitely Happen If "The Office" And "Parks And Rec" Crossed Over https://t.co/cCswy3RSX8 https://t.co/K8lTnKUhCn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[26 Times The "Friends" Characters Had No Clue How To Live In An Apartment https://t.co/Sl8TQJSRtw https://t.co/ilLMxzg7xN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[23 Times Jack Pearson From “This Is Us” Proved To Be The Best Character On TV https://t.co/S30qGL0Lsq https://t.co/Gbj0TfCqrH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone Has A Netflix Show That Matches Their Personality — Here's Yours https://t.co/uJWrsSNjwo https://t.co/L0dCCccwWy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember That Scene Where Ellie Dies In "Up"? Yeah, I Just Learned Something That Makes It EVEN SADDER https://t.co/ZBFzq13xso https://t.co/PakKn8fhzo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[25 Films Approved By Rotten Tomatoes And All Directed By Women https://t.co/ly8v0QpsI5 https://t.co/TLcdhvgyd6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[19 Life Lessons Only Kids Who Grew Up Watching Disney Movies Will Understand https://t.co/6gZ5IgR3Mf https://t.co/c5nMkbibOr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[George Clooney Was Apparently Kinda Embarrased About His First Date With Amal https://t.co/0aopJBbkty https://t.co/b8zMMVuKgd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @arianelange: So many of the people who talked to me for this story wanted anonymity not because they feared their former boss, but beca…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Country Music Has Found Its Weinstein Scandal. So Why Hasn’t There Been A Reckoning? https://t.co/7QncSA6sOp https://t.co/7Jt9L9Xsqz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BuzzFeedNews: Three more people have accused country music publicist Kirt Webster of sexually harassing employees, but saying #MeToo ha…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People Are Mourning The Death Of "House Of Cards" And "The Wire" Actor Reg E. Cathey https://t.co/F1pDO8PZT1 https://t.co/uXnAm8qflz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gloria Allred Thinks #MeToo Hasn’t Made It Necessarily Safer For Victims To Come Forward https://t.co/Auk8fuvXre https://t.co/I79PhHpe9g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go On A Top Secret Mission And We'll Recommend A Spy Movie https://t.co/0fcszOTDcm https://t.co/JYVs4BxSp4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gloria Allred thinks #MeToo hasn't made it necessarily safer for victims to come forward: https://t.co/HHxdfs6d0m via @adambvary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[17 Jokes You'll Only Relate To If "High School Musical 4" Is All You Think About At Night https://t.co/8RNrle7hxa https://t.co/JrPbcbxEWS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The "Black Panther Challenge" Has Raised More Than $300,000 For Kids To See The Upcoming Marvel Film https://t.co/1MSKF2uFOr https://t.co/VjztOwlT3E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which Netflix Character Matches Your Personality? https://t.co/EYEqV8zswG https://t.co/Awx6QPwY31]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Comedian Rob Delaney's Toddler Son Has Died Of A Brain Tumor https://t.co/Kg5wMdByHf https://t.co/QWdZHOEUhp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone Is A Combination Of Two Characters From "The Good Place" — Here's Yours https://t.co/7DajkHEUE9 https://t.co/liIxdl0cxM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 Reasons You'll Fall In Love With The "SpongeBob" Musical https://t.co/QHkj8m10zY https://t.co/gojV835Ft7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plan A Galentine's Day Party And We'll Reveal Your Celeb BFF https://t.co/IKxyPGpwtd https://t.co/VjtDkSfVA0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tell Us About The TV Show Ending That Massively Pissed You Off https://t.co/Easa1vHTIZ https://t.co/JD8gDAqNnE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[26 Historically Accurate Drawings Of Disney Princesses Worth Looking At https://t.co/unyl2TChga https://t.co/UaZ3QbK7pX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marvel Studios Released A 10th Anniversary Class Photo Including Every Single Hero And It Will Make You Emotional https://t.co/Kc9DhkvZBZ https://t.co/uTKr7e72zX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Omarosa Said She Would Never Vote For Donald Trump Again, Not "In A Million Years" https://t.co/h5sEA7mxUM https://t.co/haVJXDiO5i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Omarosa Spilled Tea About Trump On "Big Brother," Saying "It's Not Going To Be OK" https://t.co/b1KdxsbkTN https://t.co/CgFfsVlRV3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our First Look At Tom Hardy In "Venom" Is Here Just In Time For Thirsty Thursday https://t.co/yBzKcJTUGC https://t.co/EKjlOcaU1Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Black Panther” Will Screen In Lupita Nyong’o’s Kenyan Hometown Before It Opens Worldwide https://t.co/3KhLl9U4Fr https://t.co/AhfQcI3tV8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[27 Podcasts You Need To Start Listening To In 2018 https://t.co/LaGfb1XRAk https://t.co/GQBgRs6fxG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I Watched The Entire "Fifty Shades" Series In One Day And Had Many Thoughts https://t.co/tMdaMHx848 https://t.co/bBzlcETgJ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salma Hayek Told Oprah More Details About Harvey Weinstein's Alleged Abuse https://t.co/IEzzsAilDt https://t.co/MJyykxqGeV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Netflix Movie Doesn’t Need To Be Good — It Just Needs To Be There https://t.co/67DzZrMIGJ https://t.co/CBVEn9OFWA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[13 Huge Celebrities Who Guest-Starred In "The Fresh Prince Of Bel-Air" https://t.co/kPWjtRONnk https://t.co/s0F7RAIuAq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quincy Jones Gave A Really Bizarre Interview And It's...A Lot https://t.co/duywhFBpTs https://t.co/ZskobzmDeS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Call And Beep Everyone You Know, Because There's Gonna Be A Live-Action "Kim Possible" Movie https://t.co/BS5AuPf9fc https://t.co/3GvqW8DO4Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#MeToo Moves Front And Center At The Oscar Nominee Luncheon https://t.co/r9rA2Fc22Y https://t.co/e1azkXOdx6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Vanderpump Rules” Is The Worst Show On TV That You Should Be Watching https://t.co/DuprB5iWHc https://t.co/LnwqbddD2n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kian Lawley Was Fired From "The Hate U Give" After A Racist Video Surfaced https://t.co/kpzuLY0GCv https://t.co/VCNY3GA316]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pick Who's Hotter And We'll Guess What Makes You Horny https://t.co/fhuCwOrohv https://t.co/bQ8tvGxhdg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People Are Sharing What "Black Panther" Means To Them And It Will Give You Chills https://t.co/vnafjrfFAM https://t.co/i49O8pRWKq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kylie Jenner Just Revealed The Name Of Her Baby Is Stormi https://t.co/DYmMWpXLYu https://t.co/CSsDUF0JRf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quentin Tarantino Said Roman Polanski's 13-Year-Old Victim "Wanted To Have It" https://t.co/n4LqstMEtI https://t.co/KEj2iMHILI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[32 Of The Best Martin Crane Moments In Honor Of John Mahoney https://t.co/kGe2D3Sb9v https://t.co/P7TY61OblX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's What Quentin Tarantino Said About Choking Uma Thurman And Diane Kruger For His Movie Scenes https://t.co/8wPzkjX2wB https://t.co/EFNKaNfoUB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People Are Veeery Happy About Who Got Sent Home On "The Bachelor" Last Night https://t.co/QuscZpghhp https://t.co/opbc3eNMQM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Netflix Released The First Trailer For "Everything Sucks" And It's Chock-Full Of '90s Nostalgia https://t.co/bKhvcvGtEA https://t.co/8rFQz1pWV9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quentin Tarantino Gave His Side Of The Story About That Crash On The Set Of "Kill Bill" https://t.co/r76ESmgUor https://t.co/9wicwmwTME]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People Are Calling This The Most Empowering Moment In "Bachelor" History https://t.co/I33RCwPSc7 https://t.co/qFDHx9y6sX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Melissa McCarthy's New College Comedy Looks Hilarious And Charming https://t.co/E4qZzwld3w https://t.co/CkRGGuEcah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @adambvary: Annnnnd here is my report from the #OscarsLunch, at which #MeToo was brought front and center — along with Kobe Bryant: http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What % Metal Are You? https://t.co/xupHSXQbSp https://t.co/AxZz8KsRl6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The New "Jurassic World: Fallen Kingdom" Trailer Is Literally The Stuff Childhood Nightmares Are Made Of https://t.co/YAe72naUii https://t.co/c2OvcmwbY7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Milo Ventimiglia Revealed What He'd Write On Jack's Gravestone And It'll Destroy You https://t.co/q9fZuu0Emh https://t.co/c3dBrT6QIA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[23 Post-Super Bowl Episodes By The Numbers https://t.co/PT9YtUyVNK https://t.co/SlJH1o0X9x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @adambvary: Oscar nominee Kobe Bryant (for best documentary short) at the #OscarsLunch. https://t.co/AYio2wcYCn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @adambvary: And now the main event at the #OscarsLunch, when each nominee is announced at takes to risers for a class photo, and then wa…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @adambvary: .@pattonoswalt tells Oscar nominees to think twice about thanking their agents and managers: “You don’t want to have to expl…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KateAurthur: #ThisIsUs drew 27 million viewers after the #SuperBowl last night, making it the most-watched post-Super Bowl episode in s…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's Gonna Be A Lifetime Movie About Prince Harry And Meghan Markle https://t.co/WVZinEfZN9 https://t.co/HwNgswshI6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uma Thurman Posted Footage Of Her "Kill Bill" Set Crash That She Says Was Covered Up https://t.co/wGC37cNaUb https://t.co/eJLk1bqp1B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @adambvary: Academy president John Bailey says that as “a 75-year-old white man” he is thrilled “the fossilized bedrock of Hollywood’s w…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @adambvary: Academy president John Bailey marks the start of the #OscarsLunch by noting the awards are at “the crossroads of change and…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I Just Realized Why That "Friends" Episode Was Called "The One After The Super Bowl," And I'm Embarrassed AF https://t.co/XwujhSjgN4 https://t.co/2QgnDPcrAO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @adambvary: At the #OscarsLunch, from which I’ll be tweeting this afternoon. I expect schmoozing and a studious effort to avoid talking…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The New "Solo" Movie Posters Are Here And They Have A Lot Of Suspicious Details https://t.co/A0YHrDLtCn https://t.co/PShVzVvvka]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#SelfieKid's Name Is Ryan McKenna And I'm Pretty Sure He Googled Justin Timberlake Before Posting The Pic https://t.co/Qdo8Sl6m1o https://t.co/FEwndoTHJb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kylie Jenner Has Given Birth To A Baby Girl https://t.co/wBNr7gR3sC https://t.co/Fpmd4d8LAK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kelly Clarkson Got Day Drunk With Seth Meyers And It's Absolute BFF Goals https://t.co/g94oR84Ok7 https://t.co/9BOI2ML7s9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[33 Facts You Probably Didn’t Know About "This Is Us" https://t.co/VWGIz69TxI https://t.co/zTvpU6bsOs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who Would You Recast In These Popular Movie Roles? https://t.co/rBTqCSZR0x https://t.co/fwD6pwkEkt]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>