<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Fiat Chrysler CEO says Jeep, Ram are strong enough brands to follow in Ferrar.. #branding #brands https://t.co/JwzcDwP1SF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju ANC dares former Durban municipal manager to take them to court - Business Day.. #manager #leader https://t.co/dzdv6mJfo4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Losers visualize the penalties of failure. Winners visualize the rewards of success. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju The State of the Internet in Q2 2017 #socialcommerce https://t.co/4BHDOok1vB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Scientists Brew Up the Creepiest Batches of Brain Balls Yet #technology #geek https://t.co/INE9rhaVsR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Man livestreams murder of baby daughter on Facebook before committing suici.. #facebook #internet https://t.co/z6Ty7zmjh3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's no secret about success. Did you ever know a successful man who didn't tell you about it? Kin Hubbard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju 5 eCommerce Models To Consider Before Selling Online - https://t.co/xjEdh0DeuN #ecommerce #tech https://t.co/h5mhTn0RnL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Internet firms gearing up for a fight over 'net neutrality' - The Mercury News #internet #web https://t.co/bd710N5GL2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju How Entrepreneurs Can Hone Their Management Skills to Fuel Production #entrepreneur https://t.co/4klaFeOVwD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Dunkin' Brands Primed For A Buyout - Seeking Alpha #branding #brands https://t.co/bEKe4WJUgO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Deeds not Words" via Bernord Hor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Uber Really Seriously Promises Flying Cars by 2020 #technology #geek https://t.co/5gDZ0Gbj8I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Thai man kills baby on Facebook Live then takes own life - BBC News #facebook #internet https://t.co/9vjeceaYco]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The difference between ordinary and extraordinary is that little extra.- Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Can ecommerce marketplaces expand a brand? | Practical ... - Practical Ecommerce #ecommerce #tech https://t.co/CAqPbwDoVc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Here's how Richard could build his 'new internet' on 'Silicon Valley' - Mashable #internet #web https://t.co/1es4qLsvMJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju How to Quickly Create Expert Content for Your Online Business #entrepreneur https://t.co/HczxrlgzcC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Ivanka Trump's Brand Was Purposely Mislabeled Under Another Name At Stein Mar.. #branding #brands https://t.co/Altkh3nrpH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want your life to be a magnificent story, then begin by realizing that you are the author and everyday….Mark Houlahan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju We Are Social's Monday Mashup #350 #socialcommerce https://t.co/gPuXgXGWVl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Just a Pair of These $11 Radio Gadgets Can Steal a Car #technology #geek https://t.co/RyZSHZPZHI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Facebook doesn't want to be the 'arbiter of the truth', Sheryl Sanberg says.. #facebook #internet https://t.co/lwI0CrliM4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Some people dream of great accomplishments, while others stay awake and do them" via Danielle Luedtke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju How ecommerce can go green with flexible packaging - Packaging Digest #ecommerce #tech https://t.co/5wv0aDwpWX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Jack Ma Sees Decades of Pain as Internet Upends Old Economy ... - Bloomberg #internet #web https://t.co/C8rKiOQxBk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju 3 Habits of Exceptionally Productive Leaders #entrepreneur https://t.co/hJYDP27yPi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["People are not lazy. They simply have important goals – that is, goals that do not inspire them." Tony Robbins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju In the Age of Trump, China Eyes Electric Car Dominance #technology #geek https://t.co/dRE6pOA8YI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Anger as footage of Cleveland Facebook killer shooting dead man remains onl.. #facebook #internet https://t.co/uTBdXXhLrl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju These are the biggest e-commerce acquisitions of all time - Recode #ecommerce #tech https://t.co/H4tDVrCKKd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju A scholar asks, 'Can democracy survive the Internet?' - The ... - Washington Post #internet #web https://t.co/iqo51xnBWw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju 3 Ways Being a Bookworm Translates to Career Success #entrepreneur https://t.co/roB58PEIuG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Why Brands Are Clamoring To Partner With Influencers - Forbes #branding #brands https://t.co/PIgzp2erTo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju How to Become The Outstanding Middle Manager - Small Business Trends #manager #leader https://t.co/nMIhQFfHUY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju March for Science: Live Updates from Washington DC and Around the US #technology #geek https://t.co/f3xy2gUdZA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Murder Video Again Raises Questions About How Facebook Handles Content - NPR #facebook #internet https://t.co/00ekqOfCzZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To accomplish great things, we must not only act, but also dream; not only plan, but also believe. Anatole France]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju How a Brick-and-Mortar Store Can Be the Foundation of Ecommerce Success - Entr.. #ecommerce #tech https://t.co/IYmItF59C7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Statewide internet outage disrupts, delays Georgia Milestones tests - Atlanta Jo.. #internet #web https://t.co/OVff8N2OSY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Stress Kills! 5 Ways to Keep Your Stress Levels Low. #entrepreneur https://t.co/QatdbgQ3Uv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju How Brands Build Authority To Win With Millennial Consumers - Forbes #branding #brands https://t.co/p8SjcWR7YG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Desire is the starting point of all achievement, not a hope, not a wish, but a keen pulsating desire which….... - Napoleon Hill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju SNAP, SHARE, CRUNCH #socialcommerce https://t.co/3Dhe021se7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju The Hidden Laborers Training AI to Keep Ads Off Hateful YouTube Videos #technology #geek https://t.co/NSdGatVwnr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Facebook Gunman Steve Stephens' Ex-Girlfriend Questions Site's Role - NBCNe.. #facebook #internet https://t.co/vdum7g39VS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Identify your problems but give your power and energy to solutions." Tony Robbins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Increasing E-Commerce Sales Continue to Drive Industrial Construction - Nation.. #ecommerce #tech https://t.co/4zdKOGTwoO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju The internet shutdown in English-speaking parts of Cameroon is finally over - Qu.. #internet #web https://t.co/tPI07bBPTj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju 3 Customer Service Strategies You Should Steal From, Would You Believe, Lyft Driv.. #entrepreneur https://t.co/RkA1noS32z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju The 7 Characteristics of Social Commerce - JOSIC - Digital Intelligence #socialcommerce https://t.co/IJhUj1giCm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju For Brands, It's Harder To Be Seen As Green - MediaPost Communications #branding #brands https://t.co/kC8hnVClvy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Failure defeats losers, failure inspires winners." Robert T. Kiyosaki]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Mad Men &amp; Bad Men: When British Advertising Met Politics #socialcommerce https://t.co/eAyCXTOMqc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Lilium's Funky 'Jet' Could Make Our Dreams of Flying Cars Come True #technology #geek https://t.co/cmCPDz0ZIS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Facebook Is Working on Some Brainy Technology - Fortune #facebook #internet https://t.co/82wMD3kAtp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't hit a target you cannot see, and you cannot see a target you do not have. Zig Ziglar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Alibaba's Ambitious Plan For Indonesia's eCommerce Industry And What It Signal.. #ecommerce #tech https://t.co/ULBmNLyuga]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Facebook wants to beam the internet down from helicopters - CNNMoney #internet #web https://t.co/LbOJ5lRDHf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju How to Reduce Operational Costs #entrepreneur https://t.co/QVNhZM5jg3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Five Misconceptions I Had To Abandon Fast As A New Manager - Fast Company #manager #leader https://t.co/xMImcR0Dhe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life has no limitations, except the ones you make. Les Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Assistants, Please #technology #geek https://t.co/hPEUK4Qxyi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Facebook's latest ambition: becoming a hub for TV-style content - Los Angel.. #facebook #internet https://t.co/MMPQUuzIOt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I will tell you how to become rich. Close the doors. Be fearful when others are greedy. Be greedy when others are fearful." Warren Buffet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Planned EU Law Looks to Boost Cross-Border Ecommerce - eMarketer #ecommerce #tech https://t.co/CBEILg6l0Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Britain's May asks G7 to back moves to tackle internet extremism - Reuters #internet #web https://t.co/6IHwKst5pm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju 3 Ways to Rethink Your Hiring Process #entrepreneur https://t.co/dBcmlZOdwQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju 6 Snapchat Tools To Level Up Your Brand's Marketing - Forbes #branding #brands https://t.co/RBnOkFGYCp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Success is going from failure to failure without loss of enthusiasm. Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju AI, VR and mind-reading: how brands can learn from Facebook #socialcommerce https://t.co/4c1J67ao4Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju California's Daunting Plan to Clean Up the Big Sur Landslide—and Stop the Nex.. #technology #geek https://t.co/khwYzNnLmz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Facebook Reportedly Signs BuzzFeed, Vox and Others for Original Video Shows.. #facebook #internet https://t.co/a9m65xa59u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The road leading to a goal does not separate you from the destination; it is essentially a part of it. Charles DeLint]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju How to Implement Ecommerce Personalization - Practical Ecommerce #ecommerce #tech https://t.co/EtpuNzsDc9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju How other countries are trying to censor the Internet - The Boston Globe #internet #web https://t.co/6YFZDbuCrx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Taking 'Focus on Users' Advice Can Kill Your SEO Traffic #entrepreneur https://t.co/wzQAaLEHnc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Tears, faith in emotional small-business competition awards - Wichita Eagle #competition https://t.co/cayQKxa6cM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What you do speaks so loudly that I cannot hear what you say” — Ralph Waldo Emerson”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju The Discerning Drinker &amp; the Future of Alcohol #socialcommerce https://t.co/CwLlg6tCqe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Cool Spacewalk, Right? Get Ready for More—ISS Will Need Fixin' #technology #geek https://t.co/OeBArvEc7t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Facebook shakes up Live with new social chat features - TechCrunch #facebook #internet https://t.co/djL6P8LOcM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Be content to act, and leave the talking to others." Baltasa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Google Assistant will make money from e-commerce - Recode #ecommerce #tech https://t.co/Hi85NKMUTJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Rocket Internet sells 51% of fashion site Namshi to Dubai's Emaar Malls for $151.. #internet #web https://t.co/g2a5tdvXJl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Find An Industry and Make It a Vocation #entrepreneur https://t.co/s1LhsMYpY1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Apple Heads The World's Most Valuable Brands Of 2017 At $170 Billion - Forbes #branding #brands https://t.co/egEMQHxhPJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's taking this company to hell, and we're riding shotgun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Roger Moore Had the Greatest Gadgets in the History of Bond #technology #geek https://t.co/qtG9hJZWwT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Can Facebook overcome its darker side? - CNET #facebook #internet https://t.co/17R9krxn2C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't say you don't have enough time. You have exactly the same number of hours per day that were ....Einstein.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Mobile Fraud a Blind Spot for Ecommerce Merchants - Entrepreneur #ecommerce #tech https://t.co/bZl4mmIujL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju 2 Most Wildly Overvalued Stocks in the Internet of Things - Motley Fool #internet #web https://t.co/raMaqenbBI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Leveraging Micro-Moments in Your Content Campaign #entrepreneur https://t.co/J1kFzCIjiP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Lazada launches new social commerce channel Lazada TV - Digital News Asia #socialcommerce https://t.co/ZVZZpWFeVu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju 50 Marketing Tools to Help Your Business Crush the Competition - Entrepreneur #competition https://t.co/iHezqkSdjH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Nearly half UK consumers abandon brands due to poor corporate behaviour, find.. #branding #brands https://t.co/goRQ5ixPqX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Victory goes to the player who makes the next-to-last mistake. Savielly Grigorievitch Tartakower]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju We Are Social's Monday Mashup #353 #socialcommerce https://t.co/pE3zSzZW2C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju A Curious Plan to Save the Environment With the Blockchain #technology #geek https://t.co/iB7Rg4wVud]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>