<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Fired officer who refused to shoot suspect settles lawsuit - CBS News https://t.co/KcjoI0iOyy https://t.co/XENo2aRRv5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EPA boss suggests climate change could benefit humans https://t.co/ElCyS8VKJ4 https://t.co/KNEXDzkJFj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why parents are boycotting 'Peter Rabbit' https://t.co/A09NeSBM4l https://t.co/iUKsyeGNsc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House denies US-Israel discussing settlement annexation - https://t.co/B3KTN0TMxD https://t.co/vk9tQOpJw9 https://t.co/0odsuLetg5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 cops accused of brazen robberies https://t.co/Yl9jqDidTU https://t.co/XNX6oOwcBm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Jr wife in hospital after opening white powder envelope - BBC News https://t.co/vWxMErs9GQ https://t.co/0CWHNxOWPO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[11 officers have been shot to death in 2018 https://t.co/AJSRnS5TLT https://t.co/nszzQgcucK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schumer: Trump's plan doesn't help infrastructure https://t.co/IzCjvxhli1 https://t.co/vgphzHDhea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Latest: More Than $270000 Raised for Slain Officers - U.S. News &amp; World Report https://t.co/PeZmAG4OCd https://t.co/fa4auVkzi2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sessions invokes 'Anglo American heritage' of sheriff's office https://t.co/CTAcqlQ52k https://t.co/Hprmv1HZFL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Daryle Singletary, Nineties Honky-Tonk Singer, Dead at 46 - https://t.co/EutHuD6px4 https://t.co/TEwMqLEpVb https://t.co/dZ0wqut5xF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Obamas' cutest moments https://t.co/zXvht9Pmuy https://t.co/3nF6F8yLtU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: Why the Obamas' portraits matter https://t.co/wD0avhL7AV https://t.co/VfgshRvVot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former Yankees pitcher arrested on felony drug charges - https://t.co/QX46gIIC0y https://t.co/k2Da7I6zSj https://t.co/98FlieP3th]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michelle Obama wowed by depiction https://t.co/rx9q0Gzex5 https://t.co/sklgCHVBe8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pentagon added 4284 names to the gun ban list since the Texas church shooting - Washington Examiner https://t.co/a1cfNCG6mB https://t.co/nIihhwmpBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grand Canyon helicopter crash victims identified, British tourist dreamed of being veterinary nurse - Fox News https://t.co/C02xPAxTLY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flaws in gun background check system cost lives https://t.co/jiF2vT2UYK https://t.co/XxW1FwiCOT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fla. Catholic schoolteacher fired after marrying woman - WTSP 10 News https://t.co/2vYwSsNg0I https://t.co/hlAoxfEWXE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mass shootings in the US a serious issue. These charts show why https://t.co/opycQmCcrb https://t.co/7HzEBP1tbi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These Texans say guns are still the answer https://t.co/UPGzIenruH https://t.co/vKq9Whm7yR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two dead, Detroit police officer shot - https://t.co/KqIIsRppOo https://t.co/QEv04Hj0mK https://t.co/L7XrrI1JVz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pence raises prospect of talks with North Korea amid 'intensified' pressure - Reuters https://t.co/ad4mOKlvx6 https://t.co/XTQPhfzVNv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Immigration debate to grip Senate https://t.co/agIx9MDwxP https://t.co/AWUiXHGaiA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harvard professor: Democracy in danger https://t.co/PdV21BCNYj https://t.co/e8JolHZKEW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonga braces as powerful Cyclone Gita bears down - Reuters https://t.co/7FkAfEeVIQ https://t.co/fZkLF4aD9o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The administration remains tone deaf to a world now hearing the long-silenced voices of abuse victims https://t.co/pzdtk3Buz3 https://t.co/4tz5ekZOeO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After the Olympics, the real games with North Korea begin - Charleston Post Courier https://t.co/EM57NKUcBV https://t.co/28vB9ARKuK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jamie Anderson defends slopestyle snowboarding gold on windy PyeongChang course - Washington Post https://t.co/TQGqJoEC6z https://t.co/IO0SjnCgsC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: Trump may be the most anti-women US President ever https://t.co/KZcnEDuRp5 https://t.co/0qA8wUTQvg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What the justice wants to tell her granddaughters https://t.co/B5BjhEjKnK https://t.co/4k1q1mT5Uq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Puerto Rico hit with partial blackout after power plant explosion - Fox News https://t.co/XCRo7vICQa https://t.co/4qgDnD1aJw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#MeToo will have staying power, Ginsburg insists https://t.co/GvSF9ug7ep https://t.co/TAAGo2bK6w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One man navigates the rural health care system https://t.co/NKBwF1MrRy https://t.co/uBUCrdTh3R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adam Rippon dazzles with performance, wardrobe on ice - USA TODAY https://t.co/tjsDMpjLyw https://t.co/jmsiUvaGdc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump in 1994: 'I go through the roof' when dinner's not ready https://t.co/IgPQgepHuo https://t.co/ULfJyOEONA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[49ers first-rounder Reuben Foster reportedly arrested for second time in a month - https://t.co/XTNEr956fF https://t.co/VqB4wO1tp9 https://t.co/xo1eAbYWGi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's big infrastructure plan has a lot of detail on everything but how to pay for it - Washington Post https://t.co/EancEIe88p https://t.co/nfVIPYKb84]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nearly Everyone Loses If Immigration Deal Fails - Bloomberg https://t.co/ouYij02sx4 https://t.co/K5YdIHa4fu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mattis: North Korea can't drive wedge between the US and South Korea https://t.co/WZ51UwWEcX https://t.co/GTxdp7bc0e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GOP senators introduce version of White House immigration proposal https://t.co/GqjJBpcj8C https://t.co/CWSE630tMQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: America's unyielding plague of gun violence https://t.co/uMi0vGRVkK https://t.co/HS6ENNfqzr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GOP Rep Jordan: 'Big Concerns' With Paul Ryan Over Spending Increase - Breitbart News https://t.co/KLrDhFrzzk https://t.co/nMDI4G8PwM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump touts higher paychecks, worker bonuses as tax cut success https://t.co/T5gDWn4ON1 https://t.co/l6Prcwp8XX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schiff says he'll meet with FBI to discuss Democratic memo redaction - CNN https://t.co/vxugDBTXre https://t.co/v2kx72ITDf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump admin reportedly may privatize International Space Station https://t.co/xkEptGjKvl https://t.co/AmYtEIpNDq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harvard names Lawrence S. Bacow as 29th president - Harvard Gazette https://t.co/eVcCZ4dfdM https://t.co/Qptti1A9zB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[International Space Station could be privatized under Trump administration plan - New York Daily News https://t.co/30GRim0Na0 https://t.co/5k5NTzZeXa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israel claims 82,000 fighters are under Iranian control in Syria https://t.co/ClKZn6pBGV https://t.co/469T5cCscq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GOP Rep.: Paul Ryan has 'got problems' https://t.co/wqcG3uPaD1 https://t.co/od2Wa6o7q4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kim Yo Jong Fascinates, And Puzzles, In South Korea - NPR https://t.co/WyXkGZdBlG https://t.co/WPWzZlOapb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Corker has second thoughts on retiring https://t.co/x9vsGoBvya https://t.co/UZECXLFRAx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bannon: #MeToo movement could take down Trump https://t.co/Pa5MV6nnwn https://t.co/3l6KhTs3n5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wardrobe malfunction mars routine of South Korean ice dancers - Yahoo Sports https://t.co/0Y7orGeY8r https://t.co/CcOjusPeQT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch Kellyanne Conway's full interview https://t.co/uy24EK2nyB https://t.co/pELIlpT5yd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Questions Israel's Interest in Making Peace - U.S. News &amp; World Report https://t.co/H8crE8jIjr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Axios: Rob Porter claims WH told him to 'stay and fight' https://t.co/JnaK5EB06w https://t.co/FAyX4cP2lN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Video shows plane wreckage https://t.co/1im3WjXc1n https://t.co/JRY3DsjSrP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As Olympics shift to sports, what on Earth just happened? - Washington Post https://t.co/G8lvBGQL9q https://t.co/QAMBCCxwju]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The plane went down near Moscow and had 65 passengers and six crew members on board, Russian officials and media report https://t.co/94XKRzduDG https://t.co/aVWi9DY0wW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian jet 'crashes' after Moscow take-off - BBC News https://t.co/7P1KKttCZP https://t.co/HhTlUgWgST]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hispanic Trump voter defends President's rhetoric https://t.co/FywkrTKmoM https://t.co/jwa2K5riJ4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fact check: Nunes makes dubious claims about Hillary Clinton colluding with Russians - Chicago Tribune https://t.co/oMxZUwJRWu https://t.co/sPBZeIaFOb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK threatens to cut off aid cash to charities after Oxfam sex report - Reuters https://t.co/ktjdanoxl4 https://t.co/W4KMU9pTpB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As Olympics shift to sports, what on Earth just happened? - ABC News https://t.co/ERUUUSbBFj https://t.co/ll387oU5Fh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[North Korea sent cheerleaders to the Olympics. Here's what they're saying. - Washington Post https://t.co/NMURED5ymT https://t.co/aTHkWFSdqv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OxyContin maker will stop marketing opioid products to doctors amid scrutiny - The Hill https://t.co/7DXywf3aJE https://t.co/bEAKF3Kgoe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[[PyeongChang 2018] Joint women's hockey team looks to bounce back - The Korea Herald https://t.co/zo5408SydX https://t.co/uinvOyOCmI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kentucky shooting spree leaves 5 dead, including gunman - Fox News https://t.co/CFIWqjjd4R https://t.co/Zj9BLfu9Lo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Slain deputy remembered as a 'great hero' at funeral - SFGate https://t.co/3LOALmYEl3 https://t.co/vtonwFKE83]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senators want answers on Rob Porter https://t.co/C3p8e7EZVQ https://t.co/q4hqFeR4bY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats, Pressured by Trump, Plan to Revise Rebuttal Memo - New York Times https://t.co/zfwFMPfEiQ https://t.co/hCDDXWngb5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senator wants to see records on Trump's sale of Palm Beach mansion to Russian https://t.co/fl7Kw6AJ0X https://t.co/0z38hTYKgB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bernstein: No modern president lied like Trump https://t.co/wKLMr8kgNW https://t.co/m2RXnTzMEq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[North and South Korea Compete as One for the First Time in Olympic History - TIME https://t.co/0Kb4xxHs3c https://t.co/1jEiGfLJMa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The White House adviser says she has 'no reason not to believe' women who accused ex-aide Rob Porter of domestic abuse https://t.co/cWG3qL5vpk https://t.co/tkVGB0zdCg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump responds to article on US intel operation: 'Drain the swamp' https://t.co/4GcHawoHq9 https://t.co/yALwwvEFXS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When women accuse men of assault or abuse, Trump sides with the men. *Unless they're Democrats. https://t.co/YFWjUJt3Lp https://t.co/HPS1YjEBkC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Couple sells all for Florida sailboat venture, it sinks on Day 2 - https://t.co/PyLvjFLghd https://t.co/iFpzQQ4N8O https://t.co/BFtToWCZQj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysis: Trump's memo block and what it means for the Russia investigation https://t.co/IkBAntG2eo https://t.co/XqpRQ16iGy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MLB Hot Stove: Cubs reportedly sign Yu Darvish to bolster rotation - https://t.co/XTNEr956fF https://t.co/KwrCQvHBi7 https://t.co/c3ZMcM3A3L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kim Cattrall blasts SJP: 'You are not my friend' - Page Six https://t.co/NNVr2EXhWE https://t.co/1vZmzs9ltQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NYT: Trump defends Hicks as Porter fallout continues https://t.co/fm8Srh85fc https://t.co/F0MQ8FXpvv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysis: Trump's incredible hypocrisy https://t.co/jup7EXBKjT https://t.co/2gHsCDoRRB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump will not declassify Democrats' current memo, White House says - CBS News https://t.co/93776p5dxT https://t.co/U3K83ruuEu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meghan McCain sees 'a lot of gray' with Trump voters https://t.co/kqIIaIf9pV https://t.co/eQHgUY8lIS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If "diplomatic dance" were an event at the Winter Olympics, Kim Jong Un's little sister would be favored to win gold https://t.co/uvFnupr7oJ https://t.co/ce2Kl82qHU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hong Kong Bus Crash Kills at Least 18 and Injures Over 60 - New York Times https://t.co/JetQwBA9Ah https://t.co/1JlKOC2ogG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump: Lives shattered by mere allegation https://t.co/B9RP2nBXe7 https://t.co/ApIkyPhYmX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toobin: Trump censoring Democrats' argument https://t.co/bnc1vGcwX6 https://t.co/O6lRrCYn00]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vice President Pence shows up at short-track, and so do some singing North Koreans - USA TODAY https://t.co/oaUj4y1kuR https://t.co/pQ3IfN9A2r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nunes' hometown split on FBI memo controversy https://t.co/iTJeX66riA https://t.co/mankWsZU5g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Modi visits Ramallah in landmark Palestine visit - https://t.co/KFeOspBvDk https://t.co/gkbhYVVINo https://t.co/bKUeOu7KWg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kim Jong-un Invites South Korean Leader to North for Summit Meeting - New York Times https://t.co/V6qI0QGxFM https://t.co/sg1T727MnX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The invitation was presented by Kim Jong Un's younger sister during a historic meeting https://t.co/fsb1tp48Pl https://t.co/JBaMPChNkf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Officer slain, deputies wounded, suspect dead near Atlanta - Fox News https://t.co/17B5TQZx7n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Syria war: Israeli fighter jet crashes under Syria fire, military says - BBC News https://t.co/qhOeTbT5vY https://t.co/WHZC287BY2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South Korea's Moon hosts North Korean talks as Pence keeps up pressure - Reuters https://t.co/OLHERtAq9O https://t.co/djpcjFJsfj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Omarosa on Trump White House: It's not going to be OK https://t.co/4agrQt4qis https://t.co/P5a3zkP2EZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Autopsy Finds Gunman Who Killed 58 People in Las Vegas Took Anti-Anxiety Drug - U.S. News &amp; World Report https://t.co/m538eLyJZI https://t.co/5xDDqw7lin]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>