<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Assurance Engineer: 20-Sep-2018 Info Assurance Engineer Enterprise Operations Pennsylvania 450978BR • Knowledge of computer vulnerabilities and exploits • Experience with OS/system vulnerability assessment/scanning tools like MacAfee vulnerability… https://t.co/oSzZr8qCoU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Teleprompter Trump' vs. real Trump: CNN's Don Lemon compares President Donald Trump's rhetoric when he is using a teleprompter to when he is speaking freely. https://t.co/tjt4UE2wbY https://t.co/OkhGPzvRrJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programme Manager (Windows 10): Programme Manager to work for a FTSE 100 organisation. Our customer is one of the largest British companies in the world and due to a major transformation initiative and the upcoming roll-out of Windows 10 they are now… https://t.co/heOePJAj4v https://t.co/omlxW2LaHG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automation Engineer: Automation Engineer Job Locations US-CO-Aurora Job ID 10625 Minimum Clearance Required Secret Responsibilities Functional Responsibilities:  ISYS Technologies is hiring an Automation Engineer. Clearance: Secret Job Duties:… https://t.co/lFo1aUZEnk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PMO Analyst: PMO Analyst Cambridge Our client develops a big data software application, which provides behavioural and predictive analysis based on consumer data. The software allows their customers to capture vast amounts of data and visualises the key… https://t.co/HycW6edS9Z https://t.co/kurcp7wy55]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst – Retail Banking: My client is a global banking organisation with offices in London. They are actively recruiting for a Junior Business Analyst with 3+ years’ experience of business requirement documentation experience gained within a… https://t.co/dRCY54csvX https://t.co/FnMVodi0gQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior Software Developer: Ellisonpeople Recruitment are recruiting for a Junior Software Developer. This role is ideally suited to a recent graduate with 1 year's experience however candidates who have recently graduated but not worked within the… https://t.co/M5OEfBtu2A https://t.co/i9mRZhWHjJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Business Systems Analyst (UW): Job ID: ********-11902-EF Company Name: ISO Description: Verisk Analytics has an amazing story to tell. In 2016, Forbes magazine named Verisk Analytics to its World’s Most Innovative Companies list and to its… https://t.co/nyuuAInIok https://t.co/8kW7X35pwW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A timeline of the pipe bomb scare https://t.co/jOGuL923bV https://t.co/3YUbcaJPNz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Prof. Systems Administrator: Job Description: Summary Installs, investigates and resolves matters of significance with computer software and hardware equipment. Essential Job Functions Analyzes, logs, tracks and resolves software/hardware… https://t.co/jgRoMnK159 https://t.co/d9GAb2tGza]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test Engineer – Payments: Overview My client provides a leading cloud based Payment Processing Platform on the Issuer side. This platform is for Credit, Debit, and Prepaid card issuance, authorisation and settlement. They're aim is to replace legacy bank… https://t.co/QLOUFjOWPo https://t.co/HaaQARyJpg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suspect threatened people on Twitter, and Twitter didn't act: On October 11, a little less than two weeks before the discovery of the first of 13 improvised explosive devices he is suspected of sending to prominent Democrats and CNN's New York offices,… https://t.co/Wamm4vYdJV https://t.co/YqWaiPptka]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer: Full Stack Developer – Up to 55K + Bonus + Flexible Working + Games Room We are looking for a highly motivated and Full Stack Developer to join a specialist, award winning Digital Agency based in Tonbridge. This exciting opportunity… https://t.co/jOQMxPCNrt https://t.co/2SUoZ3qORz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meet Shuttle, the company that’s building a booking agent for spaceflight: Avery Haskell says he first knew he wanted to be an astronaut ever since he was a boy growing up in Houston near NASA’s Johnson Space Center. The 24 year-old Stanford graduate who… https://t.co/bcATWZF50T https://t.co/96VDgMudfy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cesar Sayoc had been kicked out by his parents and was living in the sticker-covered van at the time of his arrest, official says https://t.co/wAW7Swq5kF https://t.co/oOmCpf5Nxb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Third Line Team Leader: The LTE group structure encompasses the strengths of each of our individual organisations allowing them the freedom to focus on their own learners, colleagues, stakeholders and communities, whilst providing the support and added… https://t.co/9ZkIb1dD8k https://t.co/bmzfGokmXN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hearing underway in CNN lawsuit over White House press access: An initial hearing is underway in CNN and Jim Acosta's federal lawsuit against President Trump and several top White House aides. https://t.co/F5HRQS5yZ1 https://t.co/uL2itVEF6r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Engineer: Job Title: Big Data Engineer Location: London Contract Length: 6 Months Day Rate: £600 – £700 Jefferson Frank are currently on the hunt for a Big Data Engineer to work for a consultancy specialising in the retail industry. Required Skills:… https://t.co/pwc3iJXPFx https://t.co/3J0Gb5K5Gw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior BI/Data Insights Developer: Job title: Senior BI Developer (Events Industry) An exciting opportunity has arisen for a Mid- to Senior-Level BI Developer at an established events company based in Marylebone, (Zone 1) Central London. The Company: My… https://t.co/XeXfS2slF5 https://t.co/q78Hncc4RU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Administrator: DBA- Cambridge- Finance- Permanent- £40k-£50k I am working with one of our longest standing financial clients based in Cambridge to help them build their data management and database teams. They are currently looking for a DBA to… https://t.co/wV1IYnot9P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[API Integrations Analyst: Business Analyst (Business Intelligence API Integrations) Permanent £50,000 per year Kingston-upon-Thames, Greater London Skills and Experience: * Experienced at building API Integrations preferably using Jitterbit or similar… https://t.co/rsPruZwiwo https://t.co/HIN3mFiMRE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Services Engineer (AWS Engineer): Global IT Technology company require a Cloud Services Engineer (AWS Engineer) As a member of the Cloud Services team, you will be building upon the managed services, APIs and expertise of Amazon Web Services and… https://t.co/WAh2A4SFjc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HQ2 gave Amazon data on 238 cities -- for free: Amazon's search for a second headquarters was never just about finding a new home. https://t.co/KSEyeRLvcC https://t.co/IioKxBjI5H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: GBR Recruitment Ltd are working in partnership with a progressive manufacturing business based in Lincolnshire, recruiting for an experienced Software Developer who is strong in https://t.co/UHQRtK3Hf0, https://t.co/QLOVMK1yTs, Java… https://t.co/t52SyVbUBd https://t.co/k8ikNSiWwT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Key legal battles to unfold as Florida races toward recount deadline: Democrats and Republicans have fought for days in the court of public opinion over the hotly contested recounts in Florida's Senate and gubernatorial contests. https://t.co/fdiUB5Q1nM https://t.co/0InTTGTDou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infrastructure Solutions Architect: Infrastructure Solutions Architect required to join a rapidly expanding global business who are currently going through a major period of growth in the Watford area. Joining as an Infrastructure Solutions Architect… https://t.co/MovoMwraGI https://t.co/sydbByMOgn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Operations Manager Job: Network Operations Manager (Job Number:438744) Description: SAIC is seeking a Network Operations Manager to support the implementation of IT shared services for a large government agency. The Network Operations Manager… https://t.co/65md8FsVm9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Architect (Tech Start up): Lead Architect (Tech Start up) £100’000-£110’000 + Bonus + Progression + Healthcare + Pension + More Twickenham, Greater London Perfect position for someone looking for more autonomy in a tech start-up whilst remaining… https://t.co/Flh8Xc1JzC https://t.co/99wSXWKeNf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even compared with the senior staff knifings and the chaos in Trump's White House, Melania Trump's sudden move against a top official was a bombshell: In this White House, no one knows when the ax will fall or who will be swinging it. https://t.co/JhWKeWQbFf https://t.co/AFfQrT2IVs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer – Sheffield – Cloud Development: Senior Software Developer – Sheffield – Cloud Development Senior Software developer required for a software provider in Sheffield. It is an exciting time for the company as they have seen several… https://t.co/ZkNyvNQ6AH https://t.co/N59TjUbH7E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator-MS Windows, UNIX/Linux operating system environments: 03-Oct-2018 Systems Administrator-MS Windows, UNIX/Linux operating system environments Rotary and Mission Systems Colorado 455332BR – An active Secret clearance is required. –… https://t.co/lbxTrlVYge https://t.co/DONIO9MGGb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test Manager ( Dynamics): I have an immediate requirement for a Test Manager (Dynamics) to join my client on an initial 6 month contract (Outside of IR35) . You will be working on a major Dynamics 365 project for a leading organisation based in… https://t.co/wLymfHdBUc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer: Infrastructure Engineer (Network) £18-£21 per hour Newcastle Permanent Immediate Start Infrastructure Engineer Summary Infrastructure Engineer to work within the public sector. The ideal candidate will have NHS experience as well as… https://t.co/RTdX55ELHA https://t.co/cOkXNJ8EAX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prince of Wales has no intention of slowing down: At 70, most people in the UK are settling into retirement but the Prince of Wales is working harder than ever. More public engagements, more international tours and daily paperwork that often keeps him at… https://t.co/9oB74eu3tH https://t.co/XN5TmIkbkq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Digital Marketeer: Senior Digital Marketeer Salary to £35,000 p/a plus benefits We are looking for a skilled Senior Digital Marketeer to join our growing Uttoxeter based client. They've grown dramatically in size and turnover over the last few… https://t.co/aEqI83AK7u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Information Analyst Internship: Save job Job ID ******* Primary Location Boise, Idaho, United States of America Date posted 11/08/2018 At HP, talent is our criteria. Join us in reinventing the standard for diversity and inclusion. Bring your… https://t.co/vJW93Ca184 https://t.co/EySy1KAXNn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Head of DevOps – Kubernetes l AWS – Head Up the function: Head of DevOps – Kubernetes l AWS l – Head Up the function (EdTech) Are you a DevOps engineer that feels like the education system is broken? Want to be part of the solution? Built the next… https://t.co/2mQNVXvIPy https://t.co/428Z57YOCm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer 4: Software Developer 4 ******GJ No Visa Sponsorship is available for this position. The Oracle Single System Management Security Team, responsible for all product level security features, is seeking a Senior Product Security Engineer.… https://t.co/lhhkcRfQSu https://t.co/BD7aByL9bk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C++ Software Developer – create technology that helps millions: C++ Software Developer – create bleeding edge technology that helps millions! Are you a high calibre C++ Software Developer or C++ Software Engineer? Do you have excellent agile experience… https://t.co/xL3x5EjBTu https://t.co/bbQvnBwPT4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former NYC mayor to decide on 2020 presidential bid by February: Former New York City Mayor Michael Bloomberg plans to decide on a 2020 presidential bid no later than February 2019, a spokesperson confirmed to CNN. https://t.co/I4ugdkBVnM https://t.co/8rWEQARreK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[European Counterparty Manager Product Lead and Regional Head of Client Engagement: European Counterparty Manager Product Lead and Regional Head of Client Engagement Position summary The role will be primarily focused on the support and build-out of our… https://t.co/tcRWOwdLrM https://t.co/MWXm5Tx7PL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programme Controls Consultant: Excellent position available for a permanent Programme Controls Consultant, successful individual will provide business process and systems advise to a range of clients across a range of industry sectors (including… https://t.co/nvorUcNn2K https://t.co/mRUKW19rFP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michelle Obama opens up about her marriage - and helps us all https://t.co/eW1VWilPuz https://t.co/0BhBaVwjpF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WeRecover, the Kayak for addiction recovery, raises $2M: Los Angeles-based WeRecover raised the funds from Crosslink Capital, Box Group, Wonder Ventures, Struck Capital and others. https://t.co/wxI2gp8BS9 https://t.co/RGrHfocTeU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IAM Senior Consultant: IAM Senior Consultant – Identity and Access Management, PAM – Salary £70,000 – £85,000 + Benefits – London The company: A global consulting firm who work with a range of companies all over the world to solve problems across areas… https://t.co/6fSFXjpLRg https://t.co/hgm8IEfv3Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a remarkable move, the First Lady publicly pushed for the dismissal of the deputy national security adviser: First lady Melania Trump, in a remarkable move carried out by her spokeswoman, publicly pushed for the ouster of deputy national security… https://t.co/jiGzyet6gZ https://t.co/uJXxaZgTGC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Security Consultant – Senior: Senior Security Consultant – ISO27001, PCI DSS, CISSP – Salary £70,000 – £85,000 + Benefits – London The company: A global consulting firm who work with a range of companies all over the world to solve problems across areas… https://t.co/gn0AH5thS6 https://t.co/jGxBc2hrSB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Support Engineer: IT Support Engineer An opportunity is available to join a growing and exciting IT team within a leading software business which works with the medical sectors. As a member of the IT Team you will be responsible for assisting the Head… https://t.co/KegBJkMuiq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Draft Brexit deal reached more than two years since divisive vote: British Prime Minister Theresa May has called an emergency Cabinet meeting for Wednesday to discuss a draft Brexit deal, Downing Street announced. https://t.co/rrrY74wf69 https://t.co/YRMdn98128]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Contract Senior Software Developer – £400 Per Day: Contract Senior Software Developer | £400 Per Day – Clinical Software House (Lifesciences) Southampton, UK £400 Per Day ++ .Net, MVC, Angular 2+ and SQL ++ Picture yourself working with a company that is… https://t.co/aOOt9IPRd2 https://t.co/jWOZtWdaW5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst: Business Analyst Blackpool £30,000 – £35,000 We are working with a leading Financial Services company with an impressive portfolio of financial solutions for both business and consumers. Due to impressive and continued growth, they are… https://t.co/aUyEvfOM0h https://t.co/N3cf3psL9q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack PHP Developer: FULL STACK PHP DEVELOPER ROLES – UP TO £40k DOE – PERMANENT – PRESTON PHP – SYMFONY – LARAVEL – SQL – RESTFUL API – LINUX // $jobtitle = “Enter your job title here”; if ($jobtitle = "PHP Developer") { echo "Apply now!"; } ?&gt; The… https://t.co/RBC7nAvAPr https://t.co/IrCCMAk60b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CNN sues President Trump and top White House aides for barring Jim Acosta: • Trump threatens to pull more reporters' credentials https://t.co/NvQr0yWAN2 https://t.co/BjWevsZgky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C++ Developer: . Please contact ******************** if you need further instruction on how to do that. C++ Developer Client Development / Client Delivery | Los Angeles, CA | Full Time Job Description WE ARE A TRANSFORMATIONAL PARTNER We marry design and… https://t.co/EAgmWOE1Wc https://t.co/vH06o2vYhG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior / Lead Java Developer – Java Software Developer: Senior / Lead Java Developer – Software Engineer – Java Agile – New Tech – Bristol £45-70,000 depending on level / experience Are you a skilled Senior or Lead Java Software Developer / Java… https://t.co/KnMu7ppnTv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior Account Manager: Our Client is an Independent B2B/EDI service provider addressing the increasing demand for B2B software and services. They are looking to recruit a Junior Account Manager based in Woking, Surrey The Junior Account Manager is… https://t.co/dtEkFQXonG https://t.co/L9AXSjhBGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pilots report 'very fast' UFO above Ireland: The view from the airplane window just got a little bit weirder -- or at least it did over Ireland. https://t.co/S6cBCvKHA5 https://t.co/QxRvNoZ7ZX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remote Backend Developer: Backend Developer required for a growing SaaS startup offering a fully remote working environment, with the team spread across London, Manchester and Vancouver – working with some of the nicest and most passionate people you… https://t.co/DnNpqLQ4hx https://t.co/myrOm6zLgU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fluidly, the ‘intelligent’ cashflow management SaaS for SMEs, picks up £5M Series A: Fluidly, the London-based fintech that offers an “intelligent” cashflow management SaaS for SMEs, has raised £5 million in Series A funding. The round is led by New-York… https://t.co/HK97TMokDm https://t.co/p4LRyI5glq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: ISE (Identity Services Engine) is a fast growing product within Cisco’s Core software group. ISE is winner of Cisco Pioneer award and have been awarded the best NAC solution by SC magazine for 2015, 2016. Cisco Identity Services… https://t.co/36QjQMj0IN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Security – Penetration Testing: Cyber Security – Penetration Testing – Dublin €30-75,000 DOE Our Dublin based client is currently seeking talented Security Professionals to join their newly established team. You will be joining one of Irelands… https://t.co/WDYuWmJ3Zu https://t.co/e1AIIZcFem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Towers Crescent (12066), United States of America, Vienna, Virginia At Employer, were building a leading information-based technology company. Still founder-led by Chairman and Chief Executive Officer Richard Fairbank, Employer… https://t.co/CCihqYG4Qr https://t.co/qr0Vr1CAT3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Developing Executive: Business Development Executive Manchester Up to £25K A global success, this fascinating software company have offices in Europe, America, Australia and Asia who focus on Virtual &amp; Augmented Reality. I am looking for a… https://t.co/Ja669P37NH https://t.co/5oBmgqRnP8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Test Analyst/ Test Lead / Hands-on Test Manager: Senior / Lead Software Tester / Test Engineer / Test Lead / Hands-on Test Manager Bristol – Agile – £45-65,000 – Automation, Open Source Are you a Senior/ Lead Software Tester / Lead Test… https://t.co/YyTipTKJih https://t.co/Co1niNG1aO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UX Designer: UX Designer (eCommerce) Bradford £30,000 – £34,000 (DoE) Interaction IT are proud to be partnering with one of the worlds largest home shopping organisations based in Bradford, on their search for a tenacious and analytical UX Designer to… https://t.co/Q93iUaV52L https://t.co/Hus4PLekup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer Java SQL: Job Description The Johns Hopkins Applied Physics Laboratory (APL) is a national leader in scientific research and development. APL is actively seeking a Software Engineer to support the National Health Mission Area. The NHMA… https://t.co/ZPFC3GiRaD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon reportedly picks NYC and Northern Virginia for HQ2: After running a year-long competition that drew interest from hundreds of cities and states, Amazon has reportedly chosen New York City and Northern Virginia to split duty as its second… https://t.co/soEzDg7hBv https://t.co/F0GekgeVSG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer – £35k – £55k – Burgess Hill, West Sussex: Java Developer – £35k – £55k – Burgess Hill, West Sussex A Java Developer is required by a leading company based in Burgess Hill, West Sussex. They are currently going through a large expansion… https://t.co/NdEavgbUWx https://t.co/8Y4WOp6d0O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior/Lead Java Developer: Planet Forward have been engaged by an exciting, dynamic business which is part of a global FTSE 100 organisation. Currently recruiting for a Senior/Lead Java Developer to join their office in Nottingham. Position Overview: As… https://t.co/REy2KZasLK https://t.co/r6vhiG4TWA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Security Software Engineer: Database Security Software Engineer ******NW The Database Security Program Office aims to provide database customers with the most secure products and services for their enterprises. We work on projects that make our… https://t.co/RGB55RbrxI https://t.co/4GqIWqALMG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[iOS Developer: iOS Developer | London Albert bow is currently on the lookout for an iOS Developer for a client who is an industry-disruptive Fintech organisation. Our client is one of the most well-known and hottest FinTech’s in the world and due to… https://t.co/tDcPEYnQTn https://t.co/BKvnFLBonL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. IT Project Manager, SAP Finance: Description A career at New York Life offers many opportunities. To be part of a growing and successful business. To reach your full potential, whatever your specialty. Above all, to make a difference in the world by… https://t.co/5GAalpnwGn https://t.co/suOVR0bDqE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysis: Karl Rove is right: Say what you will about Karl Rove -- and people say all sorts of things -- but his political track record makes clear that he's someone who should be listened to. Rove was, after all, the architect of George W. Bush's two… https://t.co/i0ilikpsiY https://t.co/hyMNvx3NLY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michelle Obama says Melania Trump turned down her offer of help: In her new memoir, "Becoming," former first lady Michelle Obama writes a passage explaining how her predecessor, Laura Bush, had extended her help to Obama when she was an incoming first… https://t.co/VO0gwmjufX https://t.co/35Ww3A2rwN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay, one final Form D note: Some more comments from readers on the changing culture around startups filing their Form Ds with the SEC, and then a short update on SoftBank and a bunch more article reviews. We are experimenting with new content forms at… https://t.co/dxopwkBbvI https://t.co/DVhkSszlk0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staff Software Engineer: Staff Software Engineer, IBM Corporation, Austin, TX: Design, implement, and troubleshoot L3 routing for hardware and virtual cloud networking. Deploy and manage cloud environment. Troubleshoot issues. Create operator and… https://t.co/a6QbSOhcS7 https://t.co/X2SgfymlMw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/2fii6ej1TC WebForms Developer Beaconsfield to £50k: Our client provides bespoke, professional and cost effective services and solutions for organisations across all business sectors in the UK. They are a highly innovative organisation and… https://t.co/jRJANeZI2b https://t.co/BNh0oGUxmx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Product Manager – Technical: https://t.co/7K1R1MXO8W Services, Inc. seeks candidates for the following position(s): Senior Product Manager – Technical (Job Code: GM-STPM-PA). Assume end-to-end product ownership for various technical product… https://t.co/PbrZ2OvSbf https://t.co/9qxc4M3zTF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Office 365 Consultant: This organisation recognise that their people are at the core of their success. Not satisfied with the status quo, their team are proud to deliver award-winning customer service and enjoy taking on new challenges as the IT industry… https://t.co/0GOzUsCAwq https://t.co/GesZSunHyE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Mobile Developer – Android: McClatchy, a national leader in digital media, is growing rapidly in the digital space and delivering award-winning journalism in innovative ways. We are experiencing the most transformative period in our history. Come… https://t.co/ef20Lu8hDc https://t.co/XjIgFBZ5lQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Client Relationship Executive (Entry-level): Client Relationship Executive (Entry-level), London Our client are a company focused on delivering exceptional customer experience strategies and solutions. They offer is a unique software that helps… https://t.co/zq93rcl1FK https://t.co/NK85AXMTwi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer Systems Analyst: LVGMP LLC seeks a Computer Systems Analyst to manage software implementation and analysis projects for pharm/biotech mfg. Create/update technical documentation including user business requirements, functional specifications… https://t.co/D6k4iSMoFz https://t.co/vLDRaUR1tz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application and Database Administrator: Job Title: Application and Database Administrator Location: Guildford Salary: Competitive, depending on experience Job Type: Full Time, Permanent The company is a leading Software and Data Services provider working… https://t.co/YSJ1VO9sGv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Security Architect – IAM: Do you want to join an incredible financial services team that is challenging the way the world pays!? Our client has an important mission to change and connect the world. They value their teams and the tens of thousands of… https://t.co/Z33mEGPNXI https://t.co/Uty7DqPrvL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consultant: AVIATION The Boeing Company in Seal Beach, CA seeks Authorized Representative to conduct compliance findings against structural repairs on the 777 aircraft fuselage components. Position req MS degree (or foreign equiv) in Engineering, or… https://t.co/CyNMUn4D4Y https://t.co/YXTJUBF3rq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The real reason the stock market is down: Why are stocks falling again? President Trump says it's because Democrats are gearing up to use their impending control of the House of Representatives to investigate him. As always, when it comes to the markets,… https://t.co/dBzVcRaUac https://t.co/7uIJ1sNHD4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer: Our client is an expanding Scottish organization who are looking to recruit a permanent Developer to their Systems team in Edinburgh. Due to their continued growth, they need a junior Developer who will be working on the development and… https://t.co/KqohQbR4Fd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Technology Consultant: Treinen Associates, seeks a Senior Technology Consultant. Olympia, WA. The position is responsible for architecture, design, development and implementation of information systems that adequately support the enterprise… https://t.co/giSaS70F1R https://t.co/WMfy2V7CgA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Backend Developer – Remote Options: An industry leading Law Tech company are on the lookout for a Backend Developer. They are an online, virtual law firm who work with Start Ups and SME's from idea to ideal as they launch, grow and succeed. They've got… https://t.co/wtt9CphyjP https://t.co/du56ENfMfH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Quality &amp; Support: Position: Software Quality &amp; Support Location: West Midlands Salary: £18-30k Ref: (Apply online only) Our client based in Tamworth are a collective of companies, expertise, and talent assembled specifically to help brands own… https://t.co/qOJ9CbDxaS https://t.co/XX6J15SNZ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3rd Line Support (VMware): 3rd Line Support Engineer (VMware) Cheadle (Manchester) £35,000 + on call allowance Our client, a growing Cloud and Managed Service provider are looking to expand their IT support team with an experienced 3rd line engineer with… https://t.co/SKTo6garCP https://t.co/Hj8BBRso3Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Net – Senior Developer – Liverpool – £45,000 – Microsoft Gol: Net – Senior Developer – Liverpool – £45,000 – Microsoft Gold Partner The definition of ‘Rare’ – (of an event, situation, or condition) not occurring very often. Once in a while, every so… https://t.co/FBXtvfaxoy https://t.co/U0kqTfcB96]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UX Lead: Leading technology platform provider is going through major growth and is now seeking seasoned User Experience brilliance and creative minds to join their established team. UX in this technology company: * We are a very diverse bunch. Each of us… https://t.co/mH2IYA9WgD https://t.co/SWkmICuzOq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: What we can learn from SNL's message of unity: Something unusual and possibly even instructive happened on "Saturday Night Live" this weekend. https://t.co/H9n3DcbN7C https://t.co/OrywoxZHCo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1st Line Support / IT Support / IT Helpdesk: Our client are based in Thorpe and are looking for a 1st Line Support technician to report into the IT Manager. You will be supporting all internal users of the IT infrastructure with all areas of IT including… https://t.co/WBVokLltk6 https://t.co/uOQfEDucXe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Director: New York Foundation for the Arts xThis is staging just to let you know ABOUT ABOUT NYFA LEADERSHIP STAFF CAREERS NAMES YOU KNOW HALL OF FAME ANNUAL REPORT FINANCIAL STATEMENTS PROGRAMS FISCAL SPONSORSHIP ONLINE RESOURCES NYFA LEARNING… https://t.co/KVxbCQGhq7 https://t.co/LLc2d6aDTj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scala Software Engineer – Bristol – microservices, Scala: Scala Software Engineer – Bristol – microservices, Scala – To £70,000 + bonus + substantial benefits A great new opportunity to join a highly successful and growing technology organisation as they… https://t.co/UVAnfCj2Mp https://t.co/Ub2WvFFkBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Systems Solutions Analyst: We are actively seeking to develop the Information Systems department of an award-winning global FMCG business based at their Grimsby head office. “We set our standards high in the exceptional levels of service we… https://t.co/lyycci1VgF https://t.co/cLKnsjGbY4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rep. Jerry Nadler says hush payments 'might very well be an impeachable offense': New York Democratic Rep. Jerry Nadler said Sunday that if President Donald Trump is found to have violated campaign finance laws with hush payments, it "might very well be… https://t.co/Dgjte4DAa0 https://t.co/yPBbu0bke7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Security Consultant – GRC – Financial Services: Our client, the global leaders in the electronic payment industry are growing their Cybersecurity Consultancy team here in London. The Role: * You’ll be working as a member of the European Cybersecurity… https://t.co/ecxkgpC4Fn https://t.co/5p4xm0U0AO]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>