<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Steny Hoyer admitted to hospital, diagnosed with pneumonia: House Minority Whip Steny Hoyer was admitted to the hospital Tuesday and diagnosed with pneumococcal pneumonia, a spokeswoman said. https://t.co/EwmU2FGeYa https://t.co/fQj71WJjw0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remote Cloud Solutions Sales Executive: Columbus, OH Full-time $80k – $120k Posted Today If you are a Cloud Solutions Sales Executive with IT sales experience, please read on! We're looking for a self motivated Cloud Solutions Sales executive that is an… https://t.co/uPl979kZvW https://t.co/K54qpC7ezD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scientists create 'test-tube rhino' in hopes of saving dying species: Scientists have used IVF techniques to develop hybrid rhino embryos, which could help save the endangered northern white rhinoceros species, according to a new study. https://t.co/5SHG7YOgVf https://t.co/2J9xy0v48U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Half the country thinks Donald Trump is a racist. HALF.: A new Quinnipiac University poll has a striking result: 49% of people said they believe President Donald Trump to be a racist while 47% believe he is not. https://t.co/A0xBxqsvjj https://t.co/BlyHM1AIaH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Angela Merkel: US auto tariffs could start trade war: German Chancellor Angela Merkel has warned the Trump administration that hitting auto imports with new tariffs would have dire consequences. https://t.co/Yignk9bpow https://t.co/zA7nw3H8Y7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rail Crewperson: Back to search results Search by Keyword or Job ID More Search Options Search by Location or Country Search by Postal Code (US ONLY) Search by Location or Country Search by Postal Code (US ONLY) Distance Search by Postal Code (US ONLY)… https://t.co/6Z3fPhiOTT https://t.co/junFlISNWq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Consultant, Business Analyst (Lean and Business Process Optimization): At Cardinal Health, were developing the innovative products and services that make healthcare safer and more productive. Join a growing, global company genuinely committed to… https://t.co/eFZPWEETa3 https://t.co/duq42vL1tc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chairman of China's HNA Group dies in accident in France: Wang Jian, the chairman of giant Chinese conglomerate HNA Group, has died in an accident, the company said Wednesday. https://t.co/mASqPcmZg6 https://t.co/KzRqzAZUYp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump is not the first US President to bemoan NATO spending ... but no one did it like this: President Donald Trump has a good point when he rages about America's NATO partners failing to meet even their own burden sharing targets for the alliance's… https://t.co/tljIanD5ja https://t.co/PJ0jM7OyvZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Engineer: COMPANY PROFILE Talis Clinical, LLC provides health technology supporting clinicians to impact patient safety and improve outcomes. The team at Talis Clinical is committed to developing technologies that provide enhanced… https://t.co/LIWchMgSkD https://t.co/m99vJTDrv4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CEO of LaCroix maker sued for unwanted touching: Nicholas Caporella, CEO of the company that makes LaCroix, has been sued by two former pilots alleging unwanted sexual touching. https://t.co/F3SuxNZ7I2 https://t.co/OxIzUqHgAv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer, IT Client Systems Management (SCCM): Job Description What IT Client Systems Management contributes to Cardinal Health IT Client Systems Management is responsible for end user compute engineering, virtualization, and real-time communications. –… https://t.co/VMLdeQ2RV0 https://t.co/8GrMibVji6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge orders extension of FEMA housing aid to displaced Puerto Rico families: A federal judge on Tuesday ordered the Federal Emergency Management Agency to continue paying temporary hotel stays for another 20 days for hundreds of Puerto Rican families… https://t.co/n3wewrLpaY https://t.co/RH0aYVBq0c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Business Analyst: Location US-OH-Cincinnati Posted Date 1 month ago(5/4/2018 3:07 PM) Job ID 23582 # Positions 2 Category Technology Position Type Full Time Overview Be Here. Be Great. Working for a leader in the insurance industry means… https://t.co/xVkd87gidc https://t.co/yD9rDqtoon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst CAT Modeling: Location US-OH-Cincinnati Posted Date 20 hours ago(5/30/2018 3:29 PM) Job ID 23661 # Positions 1 Category Product Position Type Full Time Overview Be Here. Be Great. Working for a leader in the insurance industry means… https://t.co/g7KcEkwf8S https://t.co/gxyAJebKtx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An unmoving woman fell from an SUV into an intersection. The driver calmly picked her up and drove off: Video out of Tampa, Florida, shows what appears to be an unconscious woman fall out of a moving SUV into a busy intersection on Monday afternoon. https://t.co/kRc0tEDvOz https://t.co/06NCEek1JL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liberals can't handle the Asian factor in affirmative action: The NY Times reflexively mis-characterized Justice Dept.'s affirmative action initiative as discrimination against whites, reflecting liberals' discomfort with the Trump administration… https://t.co/5G32Yv6yFE https://t.co/iZxWmnQKVR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Cardinal Health seeks Engineer, Software Engineering (SAP OTC) (Requisition ********) in Dublin, OH to design, develop, implement, and support applications, systems, and Information Technology products. Plan and execute system… https://t.co/aUKuKGr0O0 https://t.co/oejNROrzAw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook shutters the teen app it just bought: Facebook shut down a teen app called tbh that it bought about 8 months ago. https://t.co/8uHkAZbR2D https://t.co/BpauZbnG9G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL BI Developer (SSMS) / QA ETL Testing: SQL BI Developer (SSMS) / QA ETL Testing – CareWorks TechCareWorks Tech CareWorks Tech Menu – Services – IT Consulting – Enterprise Service Management – Infrastructure – Security – Interactive – Events – Careers… https://t.co/fk7uNUoeoe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Analyst Manhattan: Job Description Job Title: Systems Analyst – Manhattan Requisition Number: 23510 Position Type: Full Time City: Columbus Campus: Columbus State/Province: Ohio Job Description: The Systems Analyst I – Manhattan is responsible… https://t.co/r3Ub04kgaC https://t.co/OtF4AYjykg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Courtney Love Fast Facts: View CNN's Fast Fact on Courtney Love, and learn more about the singer, actress and widow of Kurt Cobain. https://t.co/J29DM8nQAL https://t.co/15DZQEPa60]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer Student Co-op (PES, PP): For Siemens Software Engineer Student Co-op (PES, PP) job – Internal Services – Milford, Ohio Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard – Toggle navigation – My Dashboard – Our Stories –… https://t.co/Wmk3VUgWgr https://t.co/mB9az8B4tw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Consulting Engineer Cisco Network/Data Center: Senior Consulting Engineer – Cisco Network/Data Center in Columbus, OH – CDW – Home – Teams – Life at CDW – Benefits – Transitioning Military – Join our Talent Network Join the CDW COMMUNITY true Home… https://t.co/kGvFoqGAdX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heat wave turns deadly and expected to last through 4th of July: Nearly 60 million people remain under a heat advisory or warning Tuesday, with scorching temperatures and humidity expected through the Fourth of July. https://t.co/S68RNmu1zO https://t.co/3Lh2pkkJDY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL/SQL Oracle Developer | experience writing highly optimized functions, procedures, and complex queries: PL/SQL Oracle Developer | experience writing highly optimized functions, procedures, and complex queries – CareWorks TechCareWorks Tech CareWorks… https://t.co/yOX2RRNiB9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon is expanding Prime Day: Amazon's fourth annual day of extra savings for Prime members is coming later this month. https://t.co/NFJWPAESe2 https://t.co/jQDECrRf5F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook's Cambridge Analytica scandal draws growing federal scrutiny: The company faces an expanding inquiry from three federal agencies and the Department of Justice. https://t.co/P37FUfAROl https://t.co/EQUBLhDQuP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IIS Senior Programmer: 5/17/2018 IIS – Senior Programmer Tracking Code 3392-736 Job Description Senior Report Automation Specialist – Reporting Services/Data Visualization At Ipsos, we make market research work. We understand people. We know data. And we… https://t.co/mNATiAcwTb https://t.co/gGvGlBWHA2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Confirmation of Trump's Supreme Court pick could be shaped by Russia and Roe: Supreme Court confirmation hearings often develop their own tenor, depending on the nominee and the issues of the day. Even without a choice yet from President Donald Trump,… https://t.co/EeikuR55yJ https://t.co/2mLRrYqgYJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Belgium completes stunning comeback to eliminate Japan: Belgium mounted a remarkable comeback to rescue its World Cup hopes against Japan when all looked lost. https://t.co/XauHVMoGRr https://t.co/Njx4IN6ac1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer | must be certified as Sun Certified Java Programmer, Oracle Certified Java Associate, or higher cer: Java/J2EE Developer | must be certified as Sun Certified Java Programmer, Oracle Certified Java Associate, or higher certification… https://t.co/cYDv6zWGUO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lyft acquires Citi Bike parent company, Motivate: Lyft announced Monday it will acquire the largest bikeshare operator in North America. https://t.co/e2FhzhjqgH https://t.co/YEepnAj97u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A road collapses as rains and landslides batter China: A road in China's Sichuan Province collapsed on Sunday after days of heavy rain. https://t.co/38PWp8VCPS https://t.co/yBNduq3WCv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer EDI: Software Developer – EDI / Cincinnati , OH Overview:Seeking a Software Developer to build and maintain Microsoft BizTalk 2013/2016 applications, and C# .NET applications for use within an EDI/SOA environment. Along with modifying,… https://t.co/NAsSGCKFPw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer, Software Engineering (SAP LE/MM Supply Chain): At Cardinal Health, we are developing the innovative products and services that make healthcare safer and more productive. Join a growing, global company genuinely committed to making a difference… https://t.co/Iizmcxo4rj https://t.co/eRKFuY7hzn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Developer: Location US-OH-Cincinnati Posted Date 1 month ago(5/8/2018 9:58 AM) Job ID 23585 # Positions 1 Category Technology Position Type Full Time Overview Be Here. Be Great. Working for a leader in the insurance industry means opportunity… https://t.co/Q2THu87w0m https://t.co/YGUTwYi8Ht]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 things for July 2: Mexico presidential election, immigration protests, Lebron James: Here's what else you need to know to Get Up to Speed and Out the Door. https://t.co/TUqXceN2GE https://t.co/6OOTlpnOUs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer, Software Engineering, Run Support: Accountabilities This position is a Run Support subject matter (SME) position on the Manufacturing Run IT Team. The main Applications supported are Camstar, Enovia, Maximo, JDEdwards and BPCS. Experience with… https://t.co/BCPQ8SR17L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesco and Carrefour join forces to keep prices down: Tesco and Carrefour are planning a long-term, strategic alliance covering their relationship with global suppliers. https://t.co/R2VfZVnSgs https://t.co/uIOWb9wbsH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Util Systems Specialist – Kent, OH MRE: Job Description Util Systems Specialist – Kent, OH MRE #31680 Date: Jun 22, 2018 Location: Kent, OH, 44286 Company: The Davey Tree Expert Company Requisition Number: 31680 Company Name: DRG Inc Service Line: 1UAM –… https://t.co/gxQEGOA94H https://t.co/BofKW40RGc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hedge fund billionaire Dan Loeb slams Nestle's 'muddled' strategy: Dan Loeb, who runs the activist hedge fund Third Point, is unimpressed with Nestle's efforts to up its game. https://t.co/hAo8EvBEo3 https://t.co/fyVPFqnzfw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7-year-old reunited with her mom after nearly 2 months in immigration detention: Her mother's message to other mothers: if you're thinking of claiming asylum here, find another country. "The laws here are harsh. And people don't have hearts," she said. https://t.co/gfHvYwjQBt https://t.co/gcjje6w9lT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your guide to the top Fourth of July sales to shop this week: Looking to score great deals and discounts this Fourth of July? Shop these sales from popular retailers, such as Amazon and Nordstrom, now. https://t.co/WFhK2ABInr https://t.co/52qo0W1Rpx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shooting won't deter Capital Gazette journalists: Rachel Pacella and Phil Davis described Thursday's shooting in a television interview with CNN's Brian Stelter. https://t.co/wLDY0AmIt0 https://t.co/84RKvORNbi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunday shows roundup: North Korean denuclearization, the Supreme Court's vacancy, abolishing ICE: Trump administration officials and members of Congress addressed some of the nation's hottest political issues on the Sunday morning shows this week,… https://t.co/GIw9wEMSzz https://t.co/jrwK9wWYTe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Informatica Developer | strong technical knowledge in the areas of Informatica Developer Components – Parser, Match, Com: Informatica Developer | strong technical knowledge in the areas of Informatica Developer Components – Parser, Match, Comparison,… https://t.co/bVZK2AaZrt https://t.co/kGEi0MxUG9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Intelligence Tester | MapR/Hive – Big Data Hadoop – MSI – Spark: Business Intelligence Tester | MapR/Hive – Big Data Hadoop – MSI – Spark Columbus, OH 06-03-2018 Location: Columbus, OH For more than 18 years, CareWorks Tech has been delivering… https://t.co/xGnH5ziNpp https://t.co/cZWJw2ZUXM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump should pick a woman for Supreme Court: Picking another white male would be a waste of an extraordinary opportunity, writes Mark D. Weinberg. Trump could make history and force detractors to take a second look at him by nominating a female justice. https://t.co/gJtNpnFlDy https://t.co/J7G8qd2QCH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: L3 and its divisions are committed to expanding access to employment for people with disabilities and disabled veterans. If you are a qualified individual with a disability or a disabled veteran, and your disability prevents you from… https://t.co/zHxEvHAJcV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Spider-Man's' first day on the job at Paris Fire Brigade: Mamoudou Gassama, the Malian migrant nicknamed "Spider-Man" after rescuing a child dangling from a balcony in May, on Sunday had his first day at a new job at the Paris Fire Brigade. https://t.co/SuN83nrHe0 https://t.co/9QBDwZ9VXd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Assurance Engineer: USfalcon – Careers USfalcon, Inc – Benefits – Employees &amp; Returning Candidates – New Candidate Information Assurance Engineer LocationOhio Job Description and Requirements: USfalcon, Inc., recognized as one of the fastest… https://t.co/VWaXnYkbBx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Data Warehouse Developer: Brief Description: This role is on the Enterprise Information Management (EIM) team, which is responsible for supporting Huntington’s (HNB) Enterprise Data Warehouse, ETL and Business Intelligence tools. The role will ensure… https://t.co/PPzrkbICNq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Dayton, OH Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/14/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management and technology… https://t.co/1xZgMDQVX3 https://t.co/VCAyxQu0dY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is Canada Day? We explain: Canada Day is coming up, and it's what it sounds like: a federal holiday to celebrate the country and show off national pride. https://t.co/RbIqk7QY8n https://t.co/dz6y5Y6Ks4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Job ID 2018-9179 Overview Insituform Technologies, LLC is looking for an experienced Project Manager to be based in our Columbus, OH office. Insituform Technologies LLC, a subsidiary of Aegion Corporation, is a leading worldwide provider… https://t.co/cUetaIjscT https://t.co/zghbvhqPds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man charged with murder of missing teen found dead in barrel: Police in Australia have charged a man with the murder of a 16-year-old girl whose body was found stuffed in a barrel on the back of a pickup truck, sparking a manhunt and 27-hour siege at an… https://t.co/BHqzTfRzPZ https://t.co/XQIGC8tfQX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator: TITLE: Systems Administrator LOCATION: DAYTON, OHIO DURATION: FULL TIME CLIENT- FEDERAL AGENCY JOB DESCRIPTION The contractor shall provide a team member that demonstrates a proficient understanding of medical software testing and… https://t.co/CkI8eBpjP8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embedded Software Engineer – Mohnton, PA: Corporate Overview Hubbell Incorporated was founded in 1888 and has grown into an international manufacturer of quality electrical, lighting and power solutions with more than 75 brands used and recognized around… https://t.co/iwKwcu5JDi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iran protest turns violent; at least 1 death reported: A peaceful protest over a water shortage in the southern Iran city of Khorramshahr turned violent Saturday, after clashes between police and protesters broke out, Iran's state-run Islamic Republic… https://t.co/BuIvbgrhaP https://t.co/LFpQ9iLSRU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Talend Developer: Sr. Talend Developer Cleveland, Ohio – United States Job Start Date – 06/25/18, Posted Date – 06/11/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview Title: Sr. Talend Developer Length: 6+ month contract Location: Cleveland, Ohio Apex… https://t.co/hhsLRLN5AR https://t.co/o20YL2FYit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LGCT Monaco: Irishman Shane Breen pulls off shock first win: Irishman Shane Breen clinches his first win in the Monaco leg of the Longines Global Champions Tour for the world's top show jumpers. https://t.co/RcfAdE2BYf https://t.co/iGaoXhc4X0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America Ferrera and Alicia Keys read letters from families of detained children: Actress America Ferrera and singer Alicia Keys put their own stamp on Saturday's immigration rally in the nation's capital, reading from letters from a grandfather and a… https://t.co/YYwFGtLlFB https://t.co/QkLTCjAIiI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kylian Mbappe scores twice as France knock Lionel Messi's Argentina out of World Cup: With Lionel Messi now in his 30s, his often seemingly supernatural ability visibly waning at what could be his final World Cup, many fear the fate of the game once he… https://t.co/PVIGxLGxTr https://t.co/XgWYvwSVfV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior IT Support Analyst: Multi-Color Corporation is seeking a Senior IT Support Analyst to join our Corporate Information Technology team, located in Batavia, Ohio! As a member of the Helpdesk Team, the support analyst will be responsible for… https://t.co/0UxvFKVW98 https://t.co/PtNfX1N79w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The movement to 'Abolish ICE' is heating up -- and going mainstream: Calls to eliminate the Immigration and Customs Enforcement agency, for years relegated to the far-left corners of progressive activism, have been thrust this week into the mainstream of… https://t.co/vsJotU0Iex https://t.co/pz9gpTcGJ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager I: Job ID 2018-9276 Overview Corrpro Companies, Inc. is looking for an experienced Project Manager, in our Medina, OH office. Corrpro Companies, Inc., a subsidiary of Aegion Corporation, is North America’s largest corrosion engineering,… https://t.co/7TfZLIjaDu https://t.co/K3Lzu7JbOE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anonymous parking offender pays ticket 44 years later: A police chief in Pennsylvania says he wants to track down the person who mailed in a payment for a 44-year-old parking ticket -- just to say "thank you." https://t.co/87PIr8p21X https://t.co/sQbAJ8Yo0x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior PACS Application Specialist – Cleveland: CIIP Certification Required!: Job Description Description Position Summary/Essential Duties: – The PACS Analyst, Applications is responsible for providing direct PACS application support. The support… https://t.co/wyfqmzO1Q0 https://t.co/JCFbAP7YBz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thieves drained entire bank account of America's oldest living veteran: Someone has stolen the identity of the oldest living veteran in America and emptied his bank account. https://t.co/IDsnfPbMMv https://t.co/jT1UIAIb3J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETL Developer, Informatica: ETL Developer, Informatica Ref No.:18-09736 Location: Columbus, Ohio Position Type:Direct Placement Start Date: 05/30/2018 Job TitleETL Developer, Informatica Relevant Experience (in Yrs)4-7 years Technical/Functional… https://t.co/slrPUhd8RS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're probably washing your hands all wrong, study says: Research shows that 97% of the time, we're washing our hands incorrectly which can lead to contamination of food and surfaces, and result in foodborne illness. https://t.co/ycUAin2sR2 https://t.co/C4rjrRHDM7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – C# Programmer: **Software Engineer – C# Programmer** Locations:Johnson City, Tennessee Job Family: Research &amp; Development New Search Apply English (US) **Job Description** **Division:** Digital Factory **Business Unit:** Country… https://t.co/zGbd7UWzqL https://t.co/uMdDORMgoQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump economic adviser 'can't confirm or deny' he said tariffs would hurt economy: Kevin Hassett, the chair of the Council of Economic Advisers -- a White House panel that provides President Donald Trump with economic advice -- told CNN's Erin Burnett… https://t.co/GzgVppH3rj https://t.co/NPciE7fqib]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior IT Support Analyst: Senior IT Support Analyst Multi-Color Corporation is seeking a Senior IT Support Analyst to join our Corporate Information Technology team, located in Batavia, Ohio! As a member of the Helpdesk Team, the support analyst will be… https://t.co/B0ZJlRftev https://t.co/CjUGCMCvMI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer Credit Card: Developer Credit Card (Acquirer) + Mainframe / COBOL and CICS Columbus, Ohio – United States Job Start Date – 05/16/18, Posted Date – 05/16/18 Primary SkillsDB2,COBOL,VSAM,CICSTax TermsC2COverview Developer Credit Card (Acquirer) +… https://t.co/3NUavmJNoy https://t.co/eYxFucV456]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data analyst: Job TitleData analyst – ID:31412 Duration3 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsSAS, SQL, PL/SQL LocationHilliard, OH Date Posted04/05/2018 Our client, a Fortune 50, global telecommunications company is looking for Data analyst to join their… https://t.co/0tTPRlmqeM https://t.co/oYFFzC9SFT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm marching to make America the country my parents dreamed of: I remember when I was a toddler and my family had to flee Haiti's oppressive regime, Karine Jean-Pierre writes. I'm walking at the Families Belong Together march because my story is similar… https://t.co/sW4eJjo6R6 https://t.co/hc885OQMEg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Rudd promises 'Ant-Man' is a break from the bleak news cycle: Paul Rudd, who stars in Marvel's latest superhero movie "Ant-Man and the Wasp," says the film can provide an escape for moviegoers in the midst of the current news cycle. https://t.co/q730fbAg38 https://t.co/Lixh6yxcEk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lessons you can learn in business school that aren't taught in class: Sure, learning how to value a company down to the stock price is important. But there are other lessons you should learn in business school if you're going to succeed. https://t.co/yeCIzKPfPz https://t.co/0AjbSVpEgT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Consulting Engineer – Cisco Network/Data Center: Senior Consulting Engineer – Cisco Network/Data Center in Columbus, OH – CDW – Home – Teams – Life at CDW – Benefits – Transitioning Military – Join our Talent Network Join the CDW COMMUNITY true… https://t.co/2YYLDD6EpT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Representative Tier I: Windstream is seeking entry level Specialist’s for Tier I Repair. Our Specialist will assist Windstream Broadband Internet customers with troubleshooting and incident creation to resolve customer trouble. In this… https://t.co/xwb6PsOD7m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What you should know about this weekend's protests against Trump's immigration policy: Demonstrators are expected to gather in cities across the United States on Saturday to protest the White House's "zero tolerance" immigration policy that has prompted… https://t.co/a2ENA6qFeh https://t.co/RYyNlJLNZH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Front End Developer $120k: Cincinnati, OH Full-time $110k – $140k Posted Today If you are a Lead Front End Developer with experience, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us We are one of the fastest growing companies in the country that invest… https://t.co/0RdMtDWmm5 https://t.co/bR9wsMlXTY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: **Software Engineer** Locations:Milford, Ohio Job Family: Research &amp; Development New Search Apply English (US) **Job Description** **Division:** Digital Factory **Business Unit:** Product Lifecycle Management-PLM **Requisition… https://t.co/UcZg3tdEgs https://t.co/HI7PQHdeY2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The plan to overturn Roe v. Wade at the Supreme Court is already in motion: State legislatures in Iowa, Louisiana and Mississippi have advanced strict limits on abortion that some lawmakers hope can trigger a successful challenge to the landmark 1973… https://t.co/fLO7JJuEud https://t.co/lfV4O0drbx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Analyst (SAP, Accounts Payable): What Financial Systems contributes to Cardinal Health Financial Systems is responsible for overseeing the design, modification, installation and maintenance of accounting and financial systems to ensure the accuracy… https://t.co/TKDEVZeU5p https://t.co/vOhVGYfSMk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Business Analyst: Headquartered in Dublin, Ohio, Cardinal Health, Inc. (NYSE: CAH) is a global, integrated healthcare services and products company connecting patients, providers, payers, pharmacists and manufacturers for integrated care coordination… https://t.co/SYh8iRhbya]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jahi McMath, California teen at center brain-death controversy, has died: The teen who was declared brain-dead after a December 2013 surgery sparking a debate about brain-death, died June 22 from complications associated with liver failure. https://t.co/blRCHCqDjp https://t.co/nKJuNbvmQy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suspect in newsroom shooting had past court battle with paper, documents show: Court documents show the man suspected of killing five people at a Maryland newspaper Thursday had filed a defamation suit against the paper for an article detailing his… https://t.co/fOvgAo2P2t https://t.co/A9O1ktRXsD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Master Data Analyst: Job Title Master Data Analyst Requisition # PCC-US.****** Job Type Full-time Shift Type Location TIMET – Toronto – Toronto, OH 43964 US (Primary) Job Description Summary The Master Data Analyst will play a critical role in all facets… https://t.co/h4DwNsviAi https://t.co/73s2vrSLT2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House puts Supreme Court search on overdrive to announce pick by July 9: White House Counsel Don McGahn reconnected with his raison d'être on Wednesday, after Justice Anthony Kennedy announced his retirement. https://t.co/mNCOLqYwxG https://t.co/XlxpVKV4rD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Farm bill passes in the Senate before weeklong recess: The Senate passed their version of the farm bill on Thursday, with a 86-11 vote. https://t.co/5ncEJUQ8g8 https://t.co/2ZWDAIvqQj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Web Developer: Description Founded in 1866, The Sherwin-Williams Company is a global leader in the manufacture, development, distribution, and sale of paints, coatings and related products to professional, industrial, commercial, and retail… https://t.co/GV9Ny5DimF https://t.co/XBAdFnw2oC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pick Basic Developer: Pick Basic Developer Ref No.: 18-24933 Location: Cincinnati, Ohio Pick Basic Developer Trevose, PA/Cincinnati OH Contract Thanks &amp; Regards. Vatan Kumar Enterprise Solutions, Inc Phone : ************ Email:… https://t.co/DhwxygiyUf https://t.co/szmmAE6xh8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Millennials are much more open to socialism: Millennials are just starting to be elected to Congress, but they could one day make up the largest generational group there, bringing a distinctly Millennial approach to policy and governing. And that might… https://t.co/t78HEt5wgC https://t.co/MHI75sPGyD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Functional Manager, IT Business Services: SAP Functional Manager, IT Business Services – Home – About Us – Careers – Contact Us – Sign in – Products &amp; Services – Bearings – Power Transmission – Engineered Surfaces – Lubrication – Chain &amp; Auger –… https://t.co/zUgyRoCJQ0 https://t.co/u55kmQfKrg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full-Stack PHP/WordPress Developer: **Full-Stack PHP/WordPress Developer** Locations:Milford, Ohio Job Family: Information Technology New Search Apply English (US) **Job Description** **Division:** Digital Factory **Business Unit:** Product Lifecycle… https://t.co/y1q1AodAxJ https://t.co/8Cm1ZcIKMg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[France is bringing back mandatory national service for all 16-year-olds: President Emmanuel Macron's original vision for the service was much more militaristic. https://t.co/8r6TkRLxFG https://t.co/aB2O1ectxJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer/Analyst: ‘ at the bottom of the page. edit this text Job Description :: PA – Programmer/Analyst Job Title: Programmer/Analyst Status: Exempt Department: Operations Reports to: Operations Manager Office Hours: 8:30 a.m. – 5:30 p.m. (Monday… https://t.co/OY2lM3n2H8 https://t.co/4S96yZfu3l]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>