<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter Users Are Analytical in the Morning, Angsty at Night: What an analysis of 800 million tweets and 7 billion words published to Twitter between 2010 and 2014, across the 54 largest cities in the UK, reveals (and doesn't) about the British state of… https://t.co/T4FNcwU5BP https://t.co/uxbL5r4oXg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Operations Project Manager: What you’ll be doing. Verizon Connect is guiding a connected world on the go by automating, optimizing and revolutionizing the way people, vehicles and things move through the world. Our full suite of industry-defining… https://t.co/kEIg4pX2Oz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NASA’s New Plan: Do More Science With Small Satellites: A new NASA program aims to turn the gaze of small, traditionally Earth-monitoring satellites outward toward the cosmos. https://t.co/xo3p6Hgnbf https://t.co/CJnLonqvmP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Web Developer – Global IT (Boise, ID): Job Title: Senior Web Developer – Global IT (Boise, ID) Location: Boise, ID, West United States, USA Company: J.R. Simplot Company Industry Sector:Agribusiness Industry Type: Plant &amp; Soil Sciences, Seed and… https://t.co/Fvn6VuNfMx https://t.co/34N3vokGBT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Security Engineer Scott AFB, IL: Job Description Troubleshoot network access problems and implements network security policies and procedures. Ensure network (LAN/WAN, telecommunications, and voice) security access and protect against… https://t.co/VKGKJfcI0y https://t.co/Cc9xVBFjCi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill Could Give Californians Unprecedented Control Over Data: Lawmakers in California have introduced a sweeping privacy bill that could reign in the power of their Silicon Valley neighbors. https://t.co/mAfjiTweHa https://t.co/V9fqSx0g9h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Architect: Rochester, NY Full-time $120k – $140k Posted Today If you are a Registered Architect and you're looking for your next great career opportunity in Rochester, NY… then this message is for you!! We're one of the world's leading… https://t.co/Phe5plp4h1 https://t.co/4SSXjNYWbs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AWS Cloud Solution Architect: AWS Cloud Solution Architect Location US-IL-Chicago Employment Type Contract to Permanent Experience Level Senior Position Description/Responsibilities (CCC/Vendor) Client is in the midst of a multi-year, strategic… https://t.co/qL78X8pmV1 https://t.co/31hZqXux29]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pain Is Weird. Making Bionic Arms Feel Pain Is Even Weirder: Researchers get a robotic prosthesis to feel pain. But is that something amputees would even want? https://t.co/pGurmLBDiR https://t.co/eJU9PpOdjC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Ford Is Buying Detroit’s Derelict Central Depot: It’s a savvy PR move, but it also sends a big message. The carmaker wants to show it can compete with Uber and Waymo and all the Silicon Valley tech giants. https://t.co/prTgXF7d7W https://t.co/grg5TyNbut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer Senior: Req ID : 434348BR_1 Job Code/Title : E1153:Network Engineer Sr Job Description : ** Anticipated Award and ATP in 3Q18 ** We are seeking a Network Engineers for GRIMLOCK Enterprise Information Technology (IT) Security Services… https://t.co/EDsMQJRYt4 https://t.co/JhnvPqEhxs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Are the Velociraptors in 'Jurassic World' So Big?: In reality, they were about the size of a large turkey. On the big screen? Not so much. https://t.co/CYBSoUYHVG https://t.co/vPCOXQUI6D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer: COMPUTER/IT SAP Labs, LLC seeks a Senior Developer at our San Ramon, CA location to be responsible for development focusing on design, coding, testing, quality assurance of complex product features in a development team. Bach dgr in Comp Sci,… https://t.co/xveX7ARAsp https://t.co/YkBCHiPfpI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering: ENGINEERING: GlobalLogic has mult. openings in San Jose, CA: *SW Engineers (GLSW)-Dsgn &amp; define new feat for sw apps. *Programmer Analysts (GLPA)-Create, write &amp; test programs. *Lead SW Engineer (GLLSW)-Dvlp mobile app sltns. *Sr. Test… https://t.co/zmKNNXThyD https://t.co/71oABuz9wM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology: TECHNOLOGY Interested candidates send resume to: Google LLC, PO Box 26184 San Francisco, CA 94126 Attn: A. Johnson. Please reference job # below: Account Strategist (Multiple Positions); Mountain View/Palo Alto/ San Bruno, CA; Perform market… https://t.co/Ih1AbEqYEK https://t.co/y1slEHqe0g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inside the Science of Apeel, the Clever Coating That Saves Your Avocados: A coating doubles the ripeness window of avocados. How? By supercharging the defenses that evolution crafted on its own. https://t.co/8wccAl1EnQ https://t.co/ZiENRSYxqt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Title Bioinformatics Programmer, Immune Response: Job ID 11428 Type Regular Full-Time Company Fred Hutchinson Cancer Research Center Location US-WA-Seattle Category Biostatistics, Bioinformatics and Computational Biology Overview Cures Start Here. At… https://t.co/bap9w07Tpy https://t.co/FqKXHCb7z5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business/System Analyst: Business/System Analyst in Santa Maria, CA | CACI International – Small Business | – Suppliers – About Us – | – What We Do – | – Media &amp; Events – | – Investors – | – Careers – | – Contracts – | – Contact Us Join Our Talent… https://t.co/rxkOlT1xY8 https://t.co/xuHWXB5LUB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Principal Systems Administrator: Requisition ID 2018-41886 # of Openings 2 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Top Secret/SCI Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description Contract: I2TS 3 Position: Sr. Principal Administrator,… https://t.co/mQ6UOCZNvA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Solutions Architect: Job Title: Database Solutions Architect – ****** Primary Location United States-California-San Jose Job: Engineering Services Schedule: Full-time Description Xilinx is the leading provider of All Programmable FPGAs, SoCs,… https://t.co/5uMcuFBugn https://t.co/vGnYriIIe0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Testing Coordinator: Your user session will timeout in 5 minutes. Please click OK to continue with your application. QA Testing Coordinator Tracking Code 124-****** Job Description Position Highlights: – Recognized leader: Rated #1 Prepaid Wireless… https://t.co/lvWJWDxexF https://t.co/YdsFzIA9QE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack java developer: Key Skills – Angular 2.0 or 4.0, Java/J2EE, JPA, Oracle, HTML5 / CSS3, TypeScript, Web Services, Bootstrap or Knockout, Agile- SCRUM, Git / BitBucket / Bamboo, JIRA, Junit, JSF/PrimeFaces Job Description – Java developer must… https://t.co/DIA9HF8uFf https://t.co/QZrLnCtQAW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deputy Program Operations Manager – TUHP: Req ID : 424785BR Job Code/Title : E1754:Prj Mgt &amp; Plng Opns Rep Stf Job Description : A high energy, proactive, independent and motivated candidate is needed to manage and coordinate the Global Operations for… https://t.co/CL7llXTGOL https://t.co/YxCQMMpN7F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director, Solution Delivery: Applause enables companies to deliver high-quality digital experiences on their apps, websites, IoT devices and more. We do this by leveraging our community of over 300,000+ digital experience experts across the globe through… https://t.co/nvZ55pZNlN https://t.co/yC3vj2nBBd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Olympic Destroyer Hackers May Have Returned For More: A recent spate of attacks against biological and chemical threat protection agencies bears the hallmarks of the group hacker group behind Olympic Destroyer. https://t.co/Jl9UadssjG https://t.co/bVSH6VdJcZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Legacy Systems Specialist Gc/usc): Job Summary – The role of the Legacy Systems Specialist is to provide a variety of services related to supporting of systems and technologies that are no longer considered state-of-the-art or that require subject matter… https://t.co/EPVXYIfmGY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Telecom Engineer I/II/III-OSP: The Engineer – OSP (Outside Plant) is responsible for designing and developing moderately complex Outside Plant equipment installation, modifications, and upgrades and/or construction activities. The candidate will be… https://t.co/BtwblSZZWc https://t.co/VIxZTLTCfd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior User Assistance Developer: Senior User Assistance Developer Job Close By continuing to use and navigate this website, you are agreeing to the use of cookies. Accept – SAP Careers home – SAP employees – Join our talent community Search by Keyword… https://t.co/vUJQ8Pq5VD https://t.co/JOBZSIDJbU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Configuration Manager: Req ID 98170BR Business Title Configuration Manager Group MSS Location USA MARYLAND Bethesda Clearance Level Needed None Category Engineering &amp; Support Services Job Duties and Responsibilities Responsibilities: Responsible for… https://t.co/izobivCL8F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Hasn't Signed a Space Force Into Being—Yet: A brand-new sixth military branch lacks political support. https://t.co/XPEvQ404lZ https://t.co/vMrqqXS6Vd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Application Scientist: TECHNOLOGY Nanometrics, Inc. has an opening for a Sr. Application Scientist in Milpitas, CA, to develop innovative scatterometry solutions for complex materials &amp; structures. Req 20% international travel. Pls mail resume to,… https://t.co/aHlA2SRGrn https://t.co/2cCb3unQRu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Manager, Customer Success: Inspire and Motivate our Customer Success Team: The Senior Manager, Customer Success will play a critical role in shaping our growing Customer Success organization by leading and developing a high-performing team of… https://t.co/Z3TM879Fve https://t.co/4fjEl29Xsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Volvo's Making the Polestar 1 From an Old Concept: Five years after showing off the Concept Coupe, Volvo has resurrected the much-loved design as the first offering from its newly electric-focused brand, Polestar. https://t.co/iQRAt4C5Y1 https://t.co/ZR2FA8s15o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Creative Designer: Creative Designer Photon Infotech, Inc. Dallas, TX Photon Infotech, Inc. has opening for Creative Designer (Sets visual communication strategies that promote marketing objectives. Apply appropriate metrics and customer insight to the… https://t.co/w2Iepyxtc0 https://t.co/hCxZjhLux5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Specialist, IT Architecture: Nationwide Insurance. Columbus, OH. Specialist, IT Architecture Provide application systems &amp; project architecture support throughout the enterprise. Define application system architecture, application design, database… https://t.co/F5jiWv2jx7 https://t.co/4HR2R5vddF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer Ruby on Rails: MAP Digital: MetaMeetings is seeking an experienced full stack Ruby on Rails developer with excellent communication skills to join our team in MetaMeetings, a unique platform for the event industry. You will support us… https://t.co/IGFBBjxE6a https://t.co/h0rSIgCV3y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Contract PHP Engineer: We are looking for a Sr. Full Stack Engineer that knows PHP inside and out and would love to work with GO! Do you want new development work from scratch in the field of digital media and digital advertising? If you said Yes to any… https://t.co/936FVJegyK https://t.co/bwqoLRSuDa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ellen Pao on the Perverse Incentives Helping Incels Thrive at Tech Companies: Incels are well-represented at tech companies, raising challenging ethical issues for leaders who want to create a safe workspace. https://t.co/yvwqBDMCYr https://t.co/Q2YCWCcOnc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advisory Business Process Analyst: Advisory Business Process Analyst (Automation) at Fiserv, Inc. Skip Navigation Fiserv Menu – Solutions – Industries – About – Careers – Where you fit in – Technology – Accounting &amp; Finance – Contact Center – U.S.… https://t.co/wilIYYg8il]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Systems Analyst – JDE Financials: Job ID 2018-9221 Overview Aegion Corporation is looking for a Sr. Systems Analyst Aegion combines innovative technologies with market-leading expertise to maintain, rehabilitate, and strengthen infrastructure around… https://t.co/5geUyddPSp https://t.co/luCs7673i9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Product Release Specialist: Company Information PACCAR is a Fortune 500 company established in 1905. PACCAR Inc is recognized as a global leader in the commercial vehicle, financial, and customer service fields with internationally recognized brands such… https://t.co/u3ip0UPyOo https://t.co/05uNaIqfqh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETL Developer: Location US-OH-Cincinnati Posted Date 3 months ago(3/21/2018 1:26 PM) Job ID 23198 # Positions 1 Category Technology Position Type Full Time Overview Be Here. Be Great. Working for a leader in the insurance industry means opportunity for… https://t.co/Tn0205bVy9 https://t.co/lgVfg87u2C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst, Cloud: Job Description Business Analyst, Cloud – Tysons, VA, USA – Full-time Company Description Leading Products – Innovative Ideas – Exceptional People ….MicroStrategy, A Dynamic Place to Work! At MicroStrategy, we are passionate… https://t.co/CrRizouGWQ https://t.co/8q6reX1dop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LOGISTICS SPECIALIST I: Req ID 96670BR Business Title LOGISTICS SPECIALIST I Group MSS Location USA VIRGINIA Quantico Clearance Level Needed None Category Logistics Support Services Job Duties and Responsibilities ManTech is actively seeking talented… https://t.co/kPLmsj07xW https://t.co/p1pyfMTbHd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Management Analyst: Trimble is recruiting for a Data Management Analyst to fill an opportunity in Westminster, CO. Job Summary: The Data Management Analyst is responsible for Global Support issues and Projects for Trimble’s Product Lifecycle… https://t.co/qXRGNotteP https://t.co/HyZbczyLzi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer – Development Expert: Development Expert for SuccessFactors, Inc. (South San Francisco, CA) to be responsible for development focusing on concept, design, coding, testing, quality assurance of complex product features in a development team or… https://t.co/bfZuuPD5AB https://t.co/WTpgrxkWdq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Collapse of a $40 Million Nutrition Science Crusade: The Nutrition Science Initiative promised to study obesity and diabetes the right way. Now it’s broke, president-less, and all but gone. https://t.co/bJ6jkLAVrw https://t.co/XTWElGf4VK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Job Fair: JOB FAIR Wednesday, June 6, 2018 9am – 12pm Laguna Hills Mall 24155 Laguna Hills Mall Laguna hills, CA 92653 Please call 949-341-8000 or visit https://t.co/8vGNHrWzdz https://t.co/6ng9vAi3B0 recblid ffo6fgzvndj5uo40zxdg3kl4ab6hvo https://t.co/O4SOCkVMMN https://t.co/T7deLD6ltQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The End of Dyslexia: Innovations in brain research and AI-fueled assistive technologies could level the playing field for those with language-based learning disabilities. https://t.co/4CeifXLk5K https://t.co/XZvMsGFlhE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staff Engineer – Software Developer: Job Description What you’ll be doing… – Developing and maintaining the Fios TV ads portal using SPA framework to support ad operations and sales teams using .NET core and Angular JS 5. – Building an ad insertion… https://t.co/reSb4N0N2C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 19th-Century Crank Who Tried to Tell Us About the Microbiome: Today’s understanding of the importance of microbes to health was anticipated by a rival to Louis Pasteur. https://t.co/hCAWTWOjYI https://t.co/DOkY7zEQ42]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager Tampa, FL: Back to search results Search by Keyword or Job ID More Search Options Search by Location or Country Search by Postal Code (US ONLY) Search by Location or Country Search by Postal Code (US ONLY) Distance Search by Postal Code… https://t.co/sya8HMZ3sP https://t.co/nPHc69sVqd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Sales Operations Analyst: Sr. Sales Operations Analyst Join a team recognized for leadership, innovation and diversity Responsible for providing reporting and data analytics support for the Retail organization while developing, deploying, and… https://t.co/J4ln6XPlym https://t.co/Pr3oNscKGD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Principal Technology Architect – US: Role Senior Principal Technology Architect – US Auto req ID 28698BR Domain Analytics Skillset Grid Computing Platforms , HADOOP Country USA State / Region / Province California Illinois New York Texas Work… https://t.co/q1bln5B7ga https://t.co/R3kowwsf9J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Windows System Administrator 3:   Job Description – Windows System Administrator 3 (18010312) Windows System Administrator 3 Requisition ID : 18010312 Location : United States-California-San Diego US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation… https://t.co/8cOuoy947f https://t.co/KpW5tgoRbp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the New Season of 'Queer Eye,' Learning Goes Both Ways: Since the show's original Bravo incarnation, the conversation around gender and sexuality has evolved in fundamental ways—and in new episodes is refreshingly nuanced. https://t.co/nWFoXkS3GG https://t.co/vWFmgDtTlG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[eLearning Developer–Storyline and animation specialist: We are seeking a dynamic and professional Creative Specialist who is self-directed, detail oriented, and an independent learner. Creative Specialists are talented individuals who are both innovative… https://t.co/HMvfvE3oym]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAQ Project Manager: Position Summary This position drives the completion of site acquisition functions through lifecycle of project into construction. This position leads, motivates, directs, and assists all site acquisition team efforts including… https://t.co/j0jIXGaa97 https://t.co/x2ugvUJdBF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Member of Technical Staff Software Engineer: Sr. Member of Technical Staff – Software Engineer job description at VMware Skip Navigation MENU VMware Search Jobs – MENU – Home – Life at VMWare – Careers – Sales – Engineering &amp; Technology – University… https://t.co/jLmRy8VwHw https://t.co/UvKydc0foU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Snooping Soccer App, a Decades-Old Bug, and More Security News This Week.: Encrypted email, a 20-year-old bug, and more security news this week. https://t.co/76CSRZqVEX https://t.co/7ohCDBnBT1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer IV: Job Description Requisition: #43863 Location: Seattle Grade Level: 44 With more than $2 billion in revenues, CDK Global is a leading global provider of integrated information technology and digital marketing solutions to the… https://t.co/ZHV5lBcRtn https://t.co/QI92DlNRHS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: H &amp; R Block seeks a Senior Software Engineer in Kansas City, MO. Provide technical expertise to design and develop software components and products. Bach CS, CIS, IT, Electronic Eng+ 5 years desktop app &amp; web development exp.… https://t.co/JPEOh7jglG https://t.co/dcRbbPzWit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Zoox vs. San Francisco, Good News for Tesla, and More Car News This Week: Plus: BMW goes after Uber, robo-cars get new rule books, the dream of a solar-powered car, and more. https://t.co/RAda3gv5Cq https://t.co/jwGPkkxeZJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Representative: Job Description: – Our Technical Support Representatives are the front line support for more than 290 million customers. As a Technical Support Representative, you will: – Maintain exceptional customer service while… https://t.co/fRWWQoRRPC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud DevOps Developer, Senior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Arlington, VA Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 7/2/2018 Job Description Job Number: R******* Cloud DevOps Developer, Senior Key Role: Perform various… https://t.co/iccbhiUv8n https://t.co/qEFasYiFD8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst: Job Description At Ariens Company, we build more than exceptional products – we create opportunities that impact careers. Our culture values innovative thinking, hard work and determination. We interact in teams, collaborate together and… https://t.co/VfOMLoUVEt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Project Manager: IT Project Manager : 18-01736 Ref No.: 18-01736 Location: Oakland, California Akraya is looking for an IT Project Manager for one of our clients. If the job description below is a fit, please apply directly or call Sachin Naik at… https://t.co/Id8USbBhmx https://t.co/bXJTXKmjVV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Devops Engineer: ******/Devops Engineer Ref No.: 18-30557 Location: FREMONT CA, California LEAD-ADMINISTRATOR-L1 Job Description(As per hiring manager) Key skills required for the job are: DevOps – Continuous Delivery-L3 (Mandatory) Apache Maven-L2… https://t.co/9e9qN8wbK6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Zoox Flashes Serious Self-Driving Skills in Chaotic San Francisco: The secretive startup has released a video showing its car facing down some of San Francisco’s gnarliest thoroughfares and San Franciscans’ most befuddling behaviors. https://t.co/DPX5xFgEvF https://t.co/cM5ZKuSYex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instructional Design Project Manager, Training – Telework: Requisition ID 2018-43659 # of Openings 1 Job Function Program Management Security Clearance Level None Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description General Dynamics Information Technology is… https://t.co/mvYMqcSPpb https://t.co/RPXyGvKJSe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Midterm Elections Are Already Under Attack: Phishing attempts and DDoS attacks have begun hitting 2018 campaigns. The US seems ill-prepared to meet the challenge. https://t.co/L9riSko6Oa https://t.co/Dld7kTT8eg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some Scientists Work With China, but NASA Won't: NASA's ban on scientific contacts doesn't apply to all academics. https://t.co/ss3Xf4froh https://t.co/uiX8Vxbadm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer I Back End: IGT is the global leader in gaming. We enable players to experience their favorite games across all channels and regulated segments, from Gaming Machines to Lotteries to Interactive. We have a well-established local presence… https://t.co/yCqgipt1ec https://t.co/3W9hJXfulW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Program Manager – Remote Services: Job Description Senior Program Manager – Remote Services (WD***********) What you will do Under minimal supervision, this position is responsible for managing innovative service programs leveraging that Internet… https://t.co/EDfWz3XYr3 https://t.co/fp4LtAe5Qh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Ref No.:18-11723 Location: Buffalo Grove, IL, Illinois Start Date: 07/03/2018 AngularJS, Digital : Spring Boot, Foundation : Hibernate ORM, Core Java, GUI &amp; Rich Clients, Foundation : Java – JDBC Diverse Lynx LLC is an… https://t.co/FAjrevrOdF https://t.co/B6HhP4T4zX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Administrator – DCGS – California: Requisition ID 2018-37504 # of Openings 1 Job Function Science and Engineering Security Clearance Level Top Secret/SCI Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description Sr. Field Engineer / WSFE13 / E05 Contract:… https://t.co/6fWIxcwq5L https://t.co/mZ1GWn6rMd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Engineer in Test iOS Voice Messaging Applications: About GoDaddy GoDaddy powers the world’s largest cloud platform dedicated to small, independent ventures. With nearly 17 million customers worldwide and over 73 million domain names… https://t.co/UIIu2ked0g https://t.co/LUQmBlZUs1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Ref No.: 18-27571 Location: Westchester, Pennsylvania Title:- Java Developer Location:- Westchester, PA Duration: 12 Months Must be an Expert Level Java developer with a deep understanding of Core java and object oriented… https://t.co/U84IxMj58u https://t.co/MxLbEJ6irc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['No Man's Sky' Finally Gets Multiplayer, and Everything Else in Games This Week: This week, we've got some big growth for some big games, alongside a very late bug fix and an excellent Nintendo Switch port. https://t.co/xHvGWARR2h https://t.co/4lW1KF0M9p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Claims Data Analyst: Employee Type: Seasonal/Temp Location: Milwaukee, WI Job Type: Policy Operations Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/10/2018 Job Description Essential Duties and Responsibilities: Following is a summary of the essential… https://t.co/qsG6YemqgD https://t.co/RqeVxdDEsJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tired of Waiting For 'Kingdom Hearts III'? Check Your Phone: 'Kingdom Hearts Union χ' hit mobile a couple of years ago—and is the perfect appetizer for the long-awaited console title. https://t.co/hgQVY9H9v5 https://t.co/lXDJcwN7Ue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staff Software Engineer: Staff Software Engineer Ref No.: 18-30464 Location: Santa Clara, California Staff Software Engineer (******) Print Job Title:Staff Software Engineer Duration: 30-Jul-2018 – 25-Jan-2019 Status:Open Business Unit:****** – SV… https://t.co/nfbPsTY2Lg https://t.co/MPeIihdstK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator: Overview ‘US citizens and those authorized to work in the US are encouraged to apply. We are unable to sponsor H1b candidates at this time.’ Job Description: The Systems administrator will be responsible for the following… https://t.co/oyBMrS3Hg7 https://t.co/azdlWB8aPK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advanced Solutions Analyst: Advanced Solutions Analyst Sentinel Technologies, Inc. – Seeks an Advanced Solutions Analyst in Downers Grove, IL. Must have a MS or BS &amp; exp. Applicants must apply online at: https://t.co/LRkBR0gnu5. City , IL No phone calls… https://t.co/foIjj8BpzT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exploji! A Timeline of Emoji's Sudden, Drastic Rise: Apple’s 2011 release of the emoji keyboard may have signaled the start of the spike, but it feels like emoji have been with us forever. https://t.co/nqzbRhZaCR https://t.co/z0J60m30af]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[APPLICATIONS DEVELOPER III: Applications Developer III, Sprint Corporation, Overland Park, KS. Responsible for development and production support for Sprint’s Network Centralized Access Management systems for Sprint’s telecom network. Apply at… https://t.co/t8ZzV1zaST https://t.co/hhIuim00Ml]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NETWORK ENGINEER III: Network Engineer III, Sprint Corporation, Overland Park, KS. Serve as a Microwave Engineer for the cellular/ wireless telecommunications system. Remote work is authorized. Apply at https://t.co/aAz73rZJdX, Req # 245305BR. Sprint is… https://t.co/ZapLOgPlrV https://t.co/9YX8w0J3U3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Elementum SCM, Inc. has multiple positions open in our Mountain View, CA office for the following: Software Engineer(s) all levels, including Senior Levels (Job #40 &amp; Job #80): Dsgn, dvlp, implmt &amp;/or test sw for a multi-tier,… https://t.co/ixaW15M7D1 https://t.co/PWWHyPnEP5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beyond Elon Musk's Drama, Tesla's Cars Are Thrilling Drivers: Look beyond the Twitter antics and the up-and-down stock price, and you'll find a growing mass of happy customers. https://t.co/kduhStrkC7 https://t.co/CngljeUkns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The False Tale of Amazon's Industry-Conquering Juggernaut: Jeff Bezos may be the richest man of the modern age, but he built his e-commerce empire by playing freely with new ideas—not disrupting swaths of industries https://t.co/esVVDvsJqz https://t.co/SLj29zPswf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Search and apply for jobs at Piper Companies | Careers at Piper Companies Careers Search Jobs Connect With Us Software Engineer Job Attributes Job Id: 19107Job Category: Software Applications &amp; ERPJob Location: Morrisville, NC… https://t.co/mmMXCeVryc https://t.co/6SamSScgVE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Security Informatica Developer: Enterprise Identity data warehouse information, power center, strong identity and access management, IAM, sailpoint, IIQ * INFORMATICA ETL KNOWLEDGE/SKILLS – Need someone to be able to convert current BladeLogic… https://t.co/LG6dzgHJe2 https://t.co/qiZiD5DWGk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automation Engineer: Automation Engineer – Language – English – French – Worldwide Careers Site – Sign in – Accessibility – Working at Merck – Why Merck? – Diversity at Merck – From Service to Science – Prepare to Launch – Compensation and Benefits –… https://t.co/9t6wxrEznk https://t.co/N8PBZdLcsW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Program Manager, Global Quality Regulatory: Duties and Responsibilities – Will work with the organizations senior leaders in defining program scope, budget, and resource needs, build the business case of the program under consideration, and… https://t.co/XKKb5GcKaz https://t.co/26PsKXjuyE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[android developer: android developer Ref No.: 18-30648 Location: dallas, Texas Android developer Dallas TX 12 months Data acquisition: Experience working with device drivers Thorough understanding of Android internals and ability to debug OS level issues… https://t.co/OGbSDcZZEG https://t.co/ycWDyn8z8W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Systems Analyst: Job Description The selected applicant will provide overall technical and training support for the Standard Terminal Automation Replacement System (STARS) Department of Defense (DOD) Operational Support Facility (OSF) located in St.… https://t.co/CkuJEEVCVf https://t.co/PjKL8fzIme]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Stars of the Comic-Con 'Predator' Panel? Thomas Jane's Feet: The actor hardly ever wears shoes—a fact his co-stars were all too happy to discuss. https://t.co/D9sYwS9DSV https://t.co/5qox9bKa1M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Randel Solutions LLC seeks SOFTWARE DEVELOPER (full time) in Overland Park, KS: Create, modify, and test codes, write, analyze, and review programs using workflow charts and diagrams, modify and maintain programs, assist in… https://t.co/nMSuyUYSST https://t.co/mRFfgC5Lbj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CLINICAL PROGRAMMER: Pharmaceutical Research Associates, Inc. seeks a Clinical Programmer in Lenexa, KS to produce tables, listings, and datasets to support the analysis of clinical trials by applying SAS programming language to clinical trials data. BS… https://t.co/U44x46DoST https://t.co/os0VnTHvad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MRP Planner/Scheduler: Set up &amp; maintain MRP Software. Plan and organize production schedules. Assessing project resource requirements and insure customer orders are fulfilled correctly and on time. recblid g3swib79d3xg6f4e5crg23vxtf2ehj https://t.co/Y793weAfnR https://t.co/Eul5Ctn9qz]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>