<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA["If your plan isn't working, adjust your plan. Never give up." - Matt Martin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Trust yourself. You know more than you think you do." - Benjamin Spock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There is no greater agony than bearing an untold story inside you." - Maya Angelou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Will you look back on life and say, "I wish I had," or "I'm glad I did"?" - Zig Ziglar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Always forgive your enemies; nothing annoys them so much." - Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It does not matter how slowly you go as long as you do not stop." - Confucius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The human mind will not be confined to any limits." - Johann Wolfgang von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Go as far as you can see; when you get there you'll be able to see farther." - Thomas Carlyle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Let us so live that when we come to die even the undertaker will be sorry." - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Just go out there and do what you've got to do." - Martina Navratilova]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A mediocre idea that generates enthusiasm will go further than a great idea that inspires no one." - Mary Kay Ash]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The ability to speak eloquently is not to be confused with having something to say." - Michael P. Hart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Don't read a book and be a follower; read a book and be a student." - Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Act decidedly and take the consequences. No good is ever done by hesitation." - Thomas Henry Huxley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A goal is a dream with a deadline." - Napolean Hill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Wherever there is a human being, there is an opportunity for kindness." - Seneca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Music in the soul can be heard by the universe." - Lao Tsu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Ability is what you're capable of doing. Motivation determines what you do. Attitude determines how well you do it." - Lou Holtz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A goal properly set is halfway reached." - Zig Ziglar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Tell me and I forget. Teach me and I remember. Involve me and I learn." - Benjamin Franklin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Make no small plans for they have no power to stir the soul." - Niccolo Machiavelli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Alone we can do so little; together we can do so much." - Helen Keller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The mightiest works have been accomplished by men who have kept their ability to dream great dreams." - Walter Bowie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We've got to have a dream if we are going to make a dream come true." - Dennis Waitley.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Reality is merely an illusion, albeit a very persistent one." - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Yes, I sometimes fail, but at least I'm willing to experiment." - Bono]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There is only one success - to be able to spend your life in your own way." - Christopher Morley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Change your thoughts and you change your world." - Norman Vincent Peale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Kind words can be short and easy to speak, but their echoes are truly endless." - Mother Teresa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Goals are not only absolutely necessary to motivate us. They are essential to really keep us alive." - Robert Schuller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What you do speaks so loud that I cannot hear what you say." - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Ask not what your country can do for you - ask what you can do for your country." - John F. Kennedy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Live out of your imagination, not your history." -Stephen Covey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Leadership is based on a spiritual quality; the power to inspire, the power to inspire others to follow." - Vince Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You will not do incredible things without an incredible dream." - John Eliot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Finding is reserved for those that search." - Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I dream of painting and then I paint my dream." - Vincent Van Gogh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I put my heart and my soul into my work, and have lost my mind in the process." - Vincent Van Gogh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Minds are like parachutes - they only function when open." - Thomas Dewar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Whatever advice you give, be brief." - Horace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["All that spirits desire, spirits attain." - Khalil Gibran]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It is not the strongest of the species that survive, nor the most intelligent, but the one most responsive to change." - Charles Darwin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It takes less time to do a thing right, than it does to explain why you did it wrong." - Henry Longfellow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Change is inevitable. Change is constant." - Benjamin Disraeli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You must live in the present, launch yourself on every wave, find your eternity in each moment." - Henry David Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We have to go for what we think we're fully capable of, not limit ourselves by what we've been in the past." - Vivek Paul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Focus on where you want to go, not on what you fear." - Anthony Robbins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["An aim in life is the only fortune worth finding." - Robert Louis Stevenson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["He who is not everyday conquering some fear has not learned the secret of life." - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If your actions inspire others to dream more, learn more, do more and become more, you are a leader." - John Quincy Adams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The starting point of all achievement is desire. Weak desire brings weak results." - Napoleon Hill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The steeper the mountain the harder the climb the better the view from the finishing line." - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["All that we are is the result of what we have thought. The mind is everything. What we think we become." - Buddha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Do not wait for leaders; do it alone, person to person." - Mother Teresa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The past cannot be changed. The future is yet in your power." - Mary Pickford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We are still masters of our fate. We are still captains of our souls." -  Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Pick battles big enough to matter, small enough to win." - Jonathan Kozol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The greatest achievement is to outperform yourself." - Denis Waitley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The key is not to prioritise what's on your schedule, but to schedule your priorities." - Stephen Covey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Optimism is the faith that leads to achievement. Nothing can be done without hope and confidence." - Helen Keller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Every time I've done something that doesn't feel right, it's ended up not being right." - Mario Cuomo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When you believe a thing, believe it all the way, implicitly and unquestionably." - Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Your vision will become clear only when you look into your heart. Who looks outside, dreams. Who looks inside, awakens." - Carl Jung]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Man is made by his belief. As he believes, so he is." - Johann Wolfgang von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you have accomplished all that you have planned for yourself, you have not planned enough." - Meddigo Message]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rainbow Colors Story for Children from Steve and Maggie | Wow English TVt https://t.co/kvlvbZ8S1W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Self-knowledge comes from knowing other men." - Johann Wolfgang von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Success or failure is caused more by mental attitude than by mental capacity." - Walter Scott]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you have zest and enthusiasm you attract zest and enthusiasm. Life does give back in kind." - Norman Vincent Peale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Education is not the filling of a pail but the lighting of a fire." - William Butler Yeats]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Great achievement is usually born of great sacrifice, and is never the result of selfishness." - Napoleon Hill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you're good to your staff when things are going well, they'll rally when times go bad." - Mary Kay Ash]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["For success, attitude is equally as important as ability." - Harry F. Banks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Life's blows cannot break a person whose spirit is warmed at the fire of enthusiasm." - Norman Vincent Peale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Don't hate, it's too big a burden to bear." - Martin Luther King.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Argue for your limitations, and sure enough they're yours." - Richard Bach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The future cannot be predicted, but futures can be invented." - Dennis Gabor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Logic will get you from A to B. Imagination will take you everywhere." - Albert Einstein.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mr Bean Full Episodes ᴴᴰ • The Best Cartoons! • NEW COLLECTION 2016 • PART 4 https://t.co/Ual0PZwOsJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A friend is a person with whom I may be sincere. Before him I may think aloud." - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["And in the end, it's not the years in your life that count. It's the life in your years." - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Only those who attempt the absurd...will achieve the impossible." - M.C. Escher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The wisest men follow their own direction." - Euripides]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Forgive your enemies, but never forget their names." - John F. Kennedy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Most people would rather be certain they're miserable, than risk being happy." - Robert Anthony]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A "No" uttered from the deepest conviction is better than a "Yes" merely uttered to please, or worse, to avoid trouble." - Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Shoot for the moon; even if you miss you'll land among the stars." - Les Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["People don't care how much you know until they know how much you care." - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A wish is a desire without energy." - Paramanhansa Yogananda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's how you deal with failure that determines how you achieve success." - David Feherty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The greatest danger for most of us is not that we aim too high and we miss it, but we aim too low and reach it." - Michelangelo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To climb steep hills requires slow pace at first." - Shakespeare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A candle loses nothing by lighting another candle." - Erin Majors]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Our attitude towards others determines their attitude towards us." - Earl Nightingale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Happiness is inward and not outward; and so it does not depend on what we have, but on what we are." - Henry Van Dyke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Nothing is a waste of time if you use the experience wisely." - Auguste Rodin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The biggest adventure you can ever take is to live the life of your dreams." - Oprah Winfrey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What would life be if we had no courage to attempt anything?" - Vincent van Gogh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Great minds have purposes; others have wishes." - Washington Irving]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["All glory comes from daring to begin." - William Shakespeare]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>