<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@phog6189 Watching on TV Pat I thought yellow was fair enough. Lucky the contact with the ground wasn't worse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nope, can't. So I'll quote instead. https://t.co/gQsS2t7EPY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1. What do you want him to do? 2. Who are you speaking for when you say its not enough? https://t.co/XD3HkpvVHp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@john_mcguirk You'll get your year's entertainment quota filled with Drumpf's tweets just now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeopleofLIMK Definitely unlikely. I think the only way to ever make Limerick to Galway viable is to make it Cork-Limerick-Galway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hopefully build a direct train line alongside? https://t.co/0VMcyQczKS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're alive!!!!!! https://t.co/gTQO6GiLRE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's fake. https://t.co/r4An9Sx3sg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starbucks is the shits compared to independent cafes. https://t.co/qCk2EsTvTQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He looks like a happy camper on the left! Plenty bikkies in the office? :) https://t.co/om06txjg9x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NotoriousJOS @TheWranger The organ version sounds better than the real one!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@djacoby Where's Cian?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@orchidsbudget The problem I see is there will be a number of crazies on the other side too. Shouting won't convince people to vote your way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@orchidsbudget Even better. I will wade through the litterbin to find it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@orchidsbudget I will search. Possibly on YouTube.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@orchidsbudget @CoraSherlock Ooooh got a link?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@orchidsbudget @CoraSherlock Good luck getting an answer to that. Her fundamentalist bosses might put a holy hex on her.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @karolinecelly: ‘And now we move on to ‘Liars’.’ https://t.co/YKzkSEDPBy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@threeredkings The ranty one. :D

I joke. I joke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@threeredkings Great UlsterMunster review pod.

Now post the original version. :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NiamhoNiamh Hah this is true.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NiamhoNiamh Nah. Bannon is a whore for attention. One bandwagon to another.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@john_mcguirk Hillary lost to this lad. What a failure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@john_mcguirk If I'm a miserable bastard...maybe! 
Nah it's long gone past the point of being funny. It's mind numbingly awful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@john_mcguirk Are you entertained or disturbed or both?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andymcgeady What kind of utter shower raised them?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andymcgeady Just read it. 

"locals claim"

That entire Sherl**k family is deranged.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andymcgeady L*o?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fingers crossed for Matt. https://t.co/97saE7P8Bt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@briananglim2 Was there anything in particular you found egregious?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@briananglim2 We should discuss in full some other time....I think he's v good in some aspects and not in others. Very intelligent speaker. He made bits of the TYT host a while back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@briananglim2 Not a Ben Shapiro fan I take it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Dundalk Anyone trying to score political points needs to FRO. We're better than this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bualadh bos @GardaTraffic https://t.co/kDLPwmNWaj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oliver to start at 7? @threeredkings https://t.co/1ylpuMOAAq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@iamjondraper Paytas. The @JoeNumbas impressions were class.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still better than L*DBible. https://t.co/tL2vciYh0R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best of luck with the new venture. https://t.co/MTTMydTNq2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MajorTomSavage Tom, just follow Matt Hardy's advice.
https://t.co/5QfOXsgVuV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phog6189 @timoconnorbl @threeredkings @Leinster2017 Aye. He was following me....now he's not! :D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phog6189 @timoconnorbl @threeredkings @Leinster2017 No worries. It's odd that someone sets up an account to just send DMs....but there you go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phog6189 @timoconnorbl @threeredkings @Leinster2017 But he hasn't tweeted at all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CorkSeashell @lemonsrbitter @NiamhoNiamh @Colliniho @threeredkings Bad nights at the office are inevitable. Regardless of industry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lemonsrbitter @NiamhoNiamh @CorkSeashell @Colliniho @threeredkings Better for it to happen tonight than a playoff game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lemonsrbitter @NiamhoNiamh @CorkSeashell @Colliniho @threeredkings I admit. I'm on the misery side tonight after that second half. Fair enough Glenn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NiamhoNiamh @CorkSeashell @Colliniho @lemonsrbitter @threeredkings He's gone past the age where there is a ceiling to be reached. It looks like the return won't work out. Pity.
I would be investing in Johnston instead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phog6189 @timoconnorbl @threeredkings @Leinster2017 They are probably only following him due to his handle. Natural that some could assume it's an official Leinster account.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tasty. https://t.co/DM5SwL1k6X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They would have barely covered the Pro12. Not sure why they are complaining. A rag. https://t.co/lcEmHZNse1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robbyrichmond @WrestlingSoup Poor Joey :( 
:D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do Trump's feet taste like? https://t.co/9Hp9ot3uYv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Diana's death https://t.co/O7oI4NZUK3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ironman Billy Holland!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An unhealthy lack of self-awareness. https://t.co/VVrYc9w7Vw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Carlsonsports @offtheball What time approx?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeNumbas @WrestlingSoup https://t.co/Q3X6CNE6qX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DustinOfficial: Enough Said. https://t.co/UJd3FF3FRy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oliver was very good last season. Perhaps he gets on the bench with Cloete starting. https://t.co/bwRC1z1u1l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @evertonmatt1878: Boys don't dress as princesses https://t.co/RWDncYjv2T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@threeredkings Another Wycherley in the Munster development lineup.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alert @Cianaf https://t.co/EyG0Des3y4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pro14 Rugby Facebook comments after last night was an entertaining cesspool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If he does a good job, then he's welcome to it. https://t.co/FoVquhf7fU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RTE is garbage. Tax isn't stealing but the TV License is stealing. https://t.co/EdJ9ytHtjc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Giggled at this! https://t.co/eqwSpfdIgp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great bloke and plater to watch. https://t.co/LaSxjpJB1M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeNumbas Harrison signed! Haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeNumbas Gotcha! Happy post Christmas and 2018 Joe!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeNumbas I don't follow? :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NiamhoNiamh I thought at the time that Conway should have let him score.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeNumbas Should be interesting. He's had only 38 snaps this year so Pitt must have thought he was done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ormondlad The last couple of years I've gone it's been very quiet. Way down from pre-2007 years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Considering he wasn't in the original 23, nice one Alex Wootton.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DonoghueODavid Cool. Will check. Thanks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DonoghueODavid The account re-posts a lot of RugbyL*D stuff. They also have fake accounts on Facebook. If I'm wrong I'm happy to be corrected.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daveparkstaz RobPenz is a fake account run by RugbyL*D. @ThumundLark]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still a fake account. https://t.co/AkyszBd9lS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Christmas, evil Lefty! :D https://t.co/miYqvk2sdq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CROOKED LIBERAL.IE IS SO UNTRUSTWORTHY! #SAD https://t.co/jTLSbRCeYv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Ian_madigan: @TxtDrive @JohnnieHammond @Bristol_RFC Yeh was live... good seats too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dublinbusnews Nope. Useless.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dublinbusnews I hope 66 A is on the way!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dublinbusnews 493]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why did the 67 decide to not show up at Merrion Sq just now? @dublinbusnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another Coach for THE BAD GUYS https://t.co/5k6an2tOtp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonderful initative. https://t.co/SIzQtUYFjX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@phog6189 @conorgmcnamara Dolce Sicily on Dawson St for treat and coffee! Their cannoli are delish.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IrishRail Slight smell of fumes coming from heater. 9am service to Cork. Carriage 4110. Seat 65/66/69.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surely L*wry could sort a few brown envelopes to pay for repairs? https://t.co/KDD7IX4kkV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BigDunc123 Crooked Feed v2 en français? Bonne route à Grenoble !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HamillHimself: Another satisfied customer. 💋 https://t.co/qefifX8WU5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeNumbas Tbf Joe he had no team around him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That Walsh lad is quite hilarious. https://t.co/FvCcoZ2AO1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You may not like John or agree with his view on 8th (I don't) but this is scandalous. You can't have state funding of one side of a referendum debate. @NWCI should be called out. No state funding should go to lobby groups. https://t.co/P8BzTObRtQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cianaf YEAH I'LL BE DER IN A MINA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lawl @JoeNumbas @iamjondraper @WrestlingSoup https://t.co/KsFVUJ9yu6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ImKateMc Are you a fan of gender quotas?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Classy. https://t.co/wiKObXE1dR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Offense". That worthless word. https://t.co/gJ1VZsxm1O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ickle snowflake. Keep up the good work Joe. https://t.co/A82EQim4rP]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>