<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[While soaking wet, Jason Chaffetz announces to President Trump that angry parents are part of the lamestream media. A White House tourist visits Mar-a-Lago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over appetizers, VP Pence reluctantly admits to Rick Perry that the New England Patriots are dangerous. A local TV anchor discovers reddit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sneering Wilbur Ross reluctantly admits to President Trump that KGB spies are ruining "The Apprentice." Carl Higbie adopts a black child.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a photo op, Ted Cruz calmly tells Omarosa Manigault that the New Black Panthers are no threat at all. Tila Tequila commits seppuku.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An intense Ryan Zinke patiently explains to Jeff Sessions that Syrian refugees are patriotic Americans. Carl Higbie quotes Goebbels.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After dinner, Paul LePage overhears someone tell Omarosa Manigault that European immigrants are boycotting Ivanka's products. Trump's bodyguard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a limousine, Liz Cheney boldly informs Betsy DeVos that college professors are about as dangerous as kittens. Bobby Jindal wears a cowboy hat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a playground, Jason Chaffetz tries to persuade Katrina Pierson that the in-laws are on point. A White House tourist wrote this week's episode.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a restaurant, Jared Kushner reluctantly admits to President Trump that the New Black Panthers are struggling to raise money. The sommelier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While lifting weights, Mitch McConnell fails to convince Katrina Pierson that the New York Mets are fake news. A local TV anchor has a meltdown.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With gritted teeth, Jared Kushner convinces Ben Carson that Nazis are spies. James Caan hacks Trump's Twitter account.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the season finale, Sam Brownback boldly informs President Trump that environmental activists are dropping big hints. President Bush drains the wrong swamp.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While shaving, Louie Gohmert fails to convince President Trump that Jews are filing another lawsuit. A lovable old man gets voted out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the Christmas special, David Shulkin fails to persuade President Trump that Mar-a-Lago members are ruining "The Apprentice." Trump Junior]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With gritted teeth, Nikki Haley proclaims to Katrina Pierson that ABC reporters are excessively fastidious. Lou Dobbs feels the urgency.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a parking garage, Rick Santorum informs President Trump that agnostics are moving in next door. Richard Spencer loses an eye.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a bender, Ryan Zinke admits to President Trump that oil executives are probably contagious. Dana Perino watches 2 Girls 1 Cup.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a restaurant, H.R. McMaster calmly tells Rick Perry that the stars of Friends are making America great again. Hulk Hogan checks out Tinder.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After dinner, Peter King convinces President Trump that NSA agents are not real. Pat Buchanan stalks the neighbor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On a hot mic, John Kasich patiently explains to Katrina Pierson that Amway executives are not that horny. Bill Kristol hides the loot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After a sleepless night, Lamar Smith fails to convince President Trump that school teachers are useful idiots. A "fixer" tries to make memes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a diner, Justin Amash tells Betsy DeVos that socialists are conservative Christians. Erick Erickson herds goats in the garden.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Tuesday, Rick Santorum reluctantly explains to Betsy DeVos that AARP members are big supporters. Richard Spencer pretends to be an alien.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Scalise mistakenly tells Rick Perry that Lutherans are digging holes in the yard. David Brooks goes into mourning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over the holidays, Nikki Haley divulges to Kellyanne Conway that the New York Mets are in the Oval Office. George Will hires an assassin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As part of a bet, Kevin McCarthy fails to convince Omarosa Manigault that international bankers are capable bureaucrats. Tila Tequila trolls the President on Twitter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sighing deeply, Jared Kushner informs Omarosa Manigault that LA Times reporters are astonishingly successful. Dennis Miller gets a swastika tattoo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a restaurant, H.R. McMaster persuades Kellyanne Conway that Muslims are drug addicts. A man in a yellow cloak feels the urgency.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Facebook, Ryan Zinke reluctantly admits to Katrina Pierson that the Bushes are infiltrators. Jon Voight falls down a well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Dallas, Jeb Bush reluctantly explains to Omarosa Manigault that Canadians are selling counterfeit red MAGA hats. A man in a yellow cloak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While skinny-dipping, Mike Huckabee reluctantly admits to President Trump that prison guards are clamoring for attention. Adam Sandler pukes in Trump's lap.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over the holidays, Peter King reluctantly admits to Kellyanne Conway that Congressional pages are actually shapeshifting aliens. The White House chef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smiling serenely, Paul LePage proclaims to Ben Carson that Trump's sons are potential donors. Michelle Malkin slaughters a lamb on the South Lawn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Friday, Liz Cheney rudely informs Betsy DeVos that the minions of Soros are not really important. The White House chef loads a pistol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After a long meeting, Wilbur Ross tries to convince President Trump that the Obamas are faithful conservatives. Jon Voight publishes a book.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On a hot mic, Marco Rubio explains to President Trump that Zoroastrians are crushed by excessive regulations. Peggy Noonan gets voted out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a blackout, Jared Kushner reluctantly admits to Kellyanne Conway that ISIS soldiers are immortal. Lou Dobbs gets a second job.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a coffee shop, Scott Pruitt fails to convince President Trump that prisoners are crushed by excessive regulations. Peter Thiel kisses up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a blackout, Lindsey Graham rudely informs President Trump that several dictators are dropping candy wrappers. George Will is the prime suspect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a blackout, Lindsey Graham rudely informs President Trump that several dictators are dropping candy wrappers. George Will is the prime suspect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Chicago, Butch Otter fails to persuade President Trump that NSA agents are releasing Trump's tax returns. Tila Tequila runs over a homeless person.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a prank call, Ryan Zinke tells President Trump that North Koreans are pretty adorable. Bill O'Reilly watches 2 Girls 1 Cup.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a quinceañera, Steve Bannon decides not to tell President Trump that paleoconservatives are dangerous. The gardener collapses in tears.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Los Angeles, Butch Otter decides not to tell Kellyanne Conway that police officers are actually shapeshifting aliens. The gardener quotes Chomsky.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A grim-faced General Mattis insists to President Trump that conspiracy theorists are strapped for cash. Vladimir Putin vacuums all the rugs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a roomful of children, Paul Ryan carefully explains to Omarosa Manigault that the Clintons are planning something ominous. Eric Trump hires an assassin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On a dare, Jeb Bush fails to persuade Betsy DeVos that the New Black Panthers are waiting at Trump Tower. James Caan is caught stealing food.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After too many drinks, Mark Sanford informs President Trump that school teachers are on point. Adam Sandler gets punched at a demonstration.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While on vacation, Pete Sessions reluctantly admits to Kellyanne Conway that the Clintons are potential threats. Pat Buchanan fails the bar again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Tuesday, Stephen Miller boldly informs Melania that prisoners are withdrawing support. Scott Baio tries to use street slang.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Monday, Nikki Haley admits to Kellyanne Conway that Russian officials are heavily armed. Clint Eastwood gets tackled by Secret Service.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Los Angeles, Elaine Chao informs Betsy DeVos that the kids are jealous of Trump. A local TV anchor quotes Goebbels.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A patient Pete Sessions politely tells President Trump that several dictators are untrustworthy. Corey Lewandowski botches an important interview.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With gritted teeth, General Mattis politely tells Betsy DeVos that Russian businessmen are hilarious. Arnold Schwarzenegger hacks Trump's Twitter account.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sweaty Carly Fiorina boldly informs Omarosa Manigault that black politicians are not returning phone calls. An ex-girlfriend dresses in drag.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a lost episode, Rick Scott tries to convince Kellyanne Conway that college professors are not to be trusted. Rush Limbaugh struggles to speak.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A grim-faced Steven Mnuchin overhears someone tell Kellyanne Conway that several dictators are fiercely loyal. Corey Lewandowski quotes Marcuse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An indifferent Rick Scott calmly tells Omarosa Manigault that Alaskans are selling counterfeit red MAGA hats. Adam Sandler quotes Hobbes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Late at night, Jared Kushner fails to convince President Trump that the in-laws are true Americans. Kayleigh McEnany creates an international incident.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bedridden VP Pence divulges to Ben Carson that the McCains are no threat at all. Vladimir Putin tries hot sauce.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a panic, Jared Kushner fails to convince Ben Carson that ACLU lawyers are privy to many secrets. Michael Savage makes a prophecy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A terminally ill Elaine Chao patiently explains to President Trump that oil executives are oppressed by excessive regulations. Stacey Dash kisses up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An indifferent VP Pence overhears someone tell President Trump that Somalian immigrants are demanding refunds. Hulk Hogan slaughters a lamb on the South Lawn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After a speech, H.R. McMaster insists to Omarosa Manigault that Asian immigrants are double agents. Michael Savage quotes Plato.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Mar-a-Lago, Pete Sessions informs President Trump that Chicago teens are not very affluent. Ann Coulter tries tai chi.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After too many drinks, Jason Chaffetz insists to Rick Perry that oil executives are spies. James Caan snorts a few lines.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Dallas, Scott Pruitt rudely informs President Trump that Californians are traitors. Benjamin Netanyahu loads a pistol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a restaurant, Reince Preibus fails to convince Melania that New Yorkers are big league. David Brooks wins a beauty pageant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Facebook, Rick Snyder convinces Jeff Sessions that socialists are dropping candy wrappers. Erick Erickson learns about memes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a prank call, Steven Mnuchin calmly tells Melania that white women are reading Breitbart. An adorable orphan goes into mourning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a ritual, Lindsey Graham proclaims to President Trump that transgender people are not to be trusted. A mysterious man learns to fly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the West Wing, Lamar Alexander decides not to tell Rick Perry that the Feds are not really worth the time. Adriana Cohen cracks a joke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Thanksgiving, Justin Amash mistakenly tells President Trump that white working-class men are too turnt. Ann Coulter has a vision.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A grinning VP Pence accidentally convinces Jeff Sessions that Wall Street bankers are up to no good. The butler quotes Goebbels.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In front of diplomats, Paul LePage admits to Melania that those guys are not really important. Kayleigh McEnany downloads a virus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the War Room, Peter King persuades Kellyanne Conway that Baptists are ripe for the plucking. Cthulhu trolls the President on Twitter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While lifting weights, Jared Kushner reveals to Jeff Sessions that Pussy Riot are potential threats. The White House chef tries MDMA.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the season finale, Scott Pruitt tries to convince President Trump that Iranian immigrants are oppressed by excessive regulations. A White House tourist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While shaving, Justin Amash admits to President Trump that the voters are ready to negotiate. Dennis Miller has to pay the bill.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sighing deeply, Sean Spicer tries to persuade President Trump that most voters are coming for dinner. Scott Baio briefly says hello.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The evil twin of Roger Stone fails to convince President Trump that Texans are ruining "The Apprentice." Jeffrey Lord makes a racist joke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a roomful of children, Ted Cruz overhears someone tell Kellyanne Conway that the hired help are capable of great things. Ivanka's bodyguard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A paranoid Steven Mnuchin informs President Trump that Russian agents are deserving of human rights. Bobby Jindal eats the whole buffet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After the two argue, Steven Mnuchin tries to persuade President Trump that the caterers are draining the swamp. Scott Baio hides the loot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After dinner, Hope Hicks informs Jeff Sessions that oil executives are special guests. Bobby Jindal gets punched at a demonstration.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A time-traveling Rand Paul carefully explains to President Trump that the IT guys are probably contagious. Trump's bodyguard interviews the President.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While wrestling, Ryan Zinke persuades President Trump that Apple and Microsoft are true Americans. Trump's bodyguard falls off a ladder.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After a sleepless night, Hope Hicks calmly tells Betsy DeVos that conspiracy theorists are victims of a misunderstanding. Richard Spencer briefly says hello.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In front of tourists, Hope Hicks politely tells Rick Perry that ISIS soldiers are capable of great things. Adriana Cohen quits drinking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While sunbathing, Rand Paul admits to President Trump that Nordstroms employees are victims of a misunderstanding. A White House tourist makes a racist joke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After too many drinks, H.R. McMaster persuades Omarosa Manigault that oil executives are dropping candy wrappers. Eric Trump stalks the neighbor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On a hot mic, Mike Huckabee tries to persuade Kellyanne Conway that NAACP members are pretty adorable. James Caan finds a wallet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Trump Tower, Sam Brownback rudely informs Ben Carson that their Twitter followers are in on the joke. The maid makes a final appearance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Dallas, Jason Chaffetz proclaims to President Trump that the Romneys are fake news. Chris Christie learns to cook.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On a conference call, Paul LePage convinces Betsy DeVos that cult leaders are lurking everywhere. Michelle Malkin returns no phone calls.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A terminally ill Lamar Smith patiently explains to Kellyanne Conway that Apple and Microsoft are at Mar-a-Lago. Trump Junior quotes Chomsky.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During their morning jog, Rex Tillerson tries to persuade Ben Carson that Trump's sons are harmless. The maid herds goats in the garden.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As part of a bet, David Shulkin announces to Jeff Sessions that feminist lawyers are advocates for secession. A man in a yellow cloak eats the entire cake.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The evil twin of Rex Tillerson reluctantly admits to President Trump that Russian spies are true Americans. Karl Rove chases pets around.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the South Lawn, Nikki Haley accidentally convinces President Trump that Tumblr users are advocates for secession. God Almighty barely escapes an angry mob.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>