<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I loved you before, I love you now, I'll love you still.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To keep a girl you have to: 1) Keep your promises. 2) Be romantic no matter what. 3) Be honest with her 100% of the time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is never a time or place for true love. It happens accidentally, in a heartbeat, in a single flashing, or throbbing moment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A real boyfriend and girlfriend stand by each others side on good days and stands even closer on bad days no matter what.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Girls always find things out, they might not say anything right away, but they know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every girl wants that one boy who's not afraid to say, "That's my girlfriend and I love her."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter how strong a person says that they are, they are fragile when it comes to their heart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Girl: If the radio breaks would you sing to me? Boy: I'd break the radio just to sing to you. ♥]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everytime I see your name come up on my phone, I smile and my heart starts to beat a little faster.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I make mistakes, I know I'm not perfect. That's why I'm thankful for the true friends who stick by me knowing how I am.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most touching line said by a best friend: "When I die, don't come near my body, because my hand may not be able to wipe your tears anymore."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't know what or when something will happen. It just happens naturally. Life will always surprise you. That's how everything works.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happiness is not about having what you want. It is about enjoying what you have.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always be thankful in live. Find a way to be thankful for your troubles and they can become your blessings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be with someone who won't stay mad at you, who can't stand not talking to you, and who's afraid of losing you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kamu menjadi bahagia bukan ketika kamu mendapat apa yang kamu mau, tapi ketika kamu bersyukur atas apa yang kamu dapat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Relationships aren't perfect. Perfection is when you and I can go through anything and still stand strong together.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In life you'll realize that there is a purpose for every person you meet. Some will teach you, and some will bring out the best in you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before you say something to someone, always think about how you'd feel if someone told you the same thing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always believe in God because there are some questions that cannot be answered by Google.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True love is when you find someone that fits in your imperfect world perfectly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please add my other accounts @aiqingfenxiang &amp; @AstrologySecret. Thank you ^^ ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's the guy who I'm falling in love with and he's the guy who I know is going to catch me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you fall for personality, everything else about them becomes beautiful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kindness is a language which the deaf can hear and the blind can see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When your heart feels like giving up, let hope whisper one more time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm perfect in my imperfections, happy in my pain, strong in my weaknesses and beautiful in my own way because I'm me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Relationships do not need promises, terms, and conditions. It just needs two people. One who can trust and one who can understand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't think you're the best when you're at the top. Don't think you're the worst when you're at the bottom.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A friend is like a rainbow. They brighten your life when you've been through a storm.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PiscesTweet: #Pisces can never put their feelings into words, so they use music to describe their feelings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is like a snowglobe, often it's prettiest after it's been turned upside-down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes you have to let things go, not because you're giving up, but because you've realized that some things cannot be yours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have learned to care people too much, not because they are good but because I knew the pain of being ignored.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @aiqingfenxiang: 不是「晚安」這兩個字特別甜蜜和特別重要、而是重要在說的那個人是誰。]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PiscesTweet: 【最有结婚狂倾向的星座排名】冠军（巨蟹座）；亚军（双鱼座）；季军（处女座）；第四名（金牛座）；第五名（魔羯座）；第六名（狮子座）；第七名（天蝎座）；第八名（射手座）；第九名（天秤座）；第十名（双子座）；第十一名（白羊座）；第十二名（水瓶座 ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wanna be the girl he can hold hands in public and not care what anyone says.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter how strong of a person you are, there’s always someone who can make you weak.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe she is waiting for you, but no one waits forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't date the most beautiful girl in the world, date the girl that makes your world the most beautiful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love" is when you know that worst side of someone and still love the person with everything you have in your heart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Missing someone is apart of loving them. If you're never really apart, you'll never know how strong your love is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being with you makes me feel like for once in my life I don't have to try so hard to be happy. It can just happen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes just by listening to music can help you feel so much better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd walk a thousand miles just to be in your arms.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He is the reason why I'm always smiling like a fool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are the first thing that comes up on my mind when I wake up every morning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember that someday you're going to meet someone, someone who will stay forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe I hope too much. Maybe I dream too much. But at least I won't give up until I've tried, and I won't regret anything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Menunggu memang bukan sesuatu yang menyenangkan, tapi kadang itu cara Tuhan untuk melatih KESABARAN.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PiscesTweet: 双鱼的人最不势力，从不用薪金的多少来衡量一个人的价值，他可以爱一个贫穷的人，却没办法忍受一颗贫穷的心，他可以接受寒酸婚宴，但没办法忍受没有你的房间，他愿意接受平凡的爱人，但务必给他不平凡的爱情。总之，你可以没房没车没地位，但请你好好爱他认 ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A person who truly loves you will never let you go or give up on you, no matter how hard the situation is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I'm with you, I forget all my worries.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be able to thank God under any circumstance, that is the true measure of a person.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may not be perfect, but God is, and He loves me perfectly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know why, but I fall more in love with you everyday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every time you say "I love you", my heart flutters with joy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish time could just stop when I'm in your arms, because it's the best feeling ever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The purpose of faith isn't always to keep us from having trouble. It is often to carry us through trouble.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving someone who doesn't love you back is like hugging a cactus, the tighter you hold on, the more it hurts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love walking in the rain, for no one can tell if I'm crying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God gives miracles to those who believe, courage to those with faith, hope to those who dream, and love to those who accept.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's nothing more beautiful than gazing into the eyes of your lover and and saying "I love you."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't try to be good in everything. Be good in one thing. That's what makes you special.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may not be all I should be, but I'm not what I used to be, and God isn't finished with me yet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything happens for a reason. Luck and fate are the same thing, it just depends on how you look at life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God gives me strength whenever I am weak.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If someone asks me who I want to be with, I would simply say; Someone who will never leave me because of someone else.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God knew you were going to be special to someone.. That's why He created you. Be happy with yourself, and know you are loved.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyday I thank God for giving me a new day, and another chance to make a difference.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you feel like you can't go anymore just pray. God is listening and everything will be okay in His perfect timing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After you have done all you can.. hand it over to God. Usually the BEST results are when we leave it to Him anyway.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I had to count the reasons why I love you and why I'm so in love with you, I'd have count forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anything worth having requires time, effort, and patience. With a positive attitude you can excel in whatever you put your mind to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy is the person who learns to wait when they pray, because God's time is the best time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find strength through every struggle, because the things you have been through have made you the person who you are today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kesetiaan berarti ketulusan untuk menyimpan satu nama tetap di hati, kemudian berjanji untuk tidak mengkhianati.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love between a man and a woman means being able to trust each other and believe in each other. Its not only to love and tell sweet things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happiness is a perfume you cannot pour on others without getting a few drops on yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jika ia mencintaimu saat kau punya segalanya, itu Kenyataan. Jika ia mencintaimu saat kau tidak punya segalanya, itu Ketulusan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have embraced many beautiful memories in my life, but the one I admire the most was when I met you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best feeling in the world is when the person you like, like you back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everytime I look at the keyboard, I see that "U &amp; I" are always together.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop crying over yesterday and start smiling for tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes you need patience in order to find true happiness. It won't come fast and it won't come easy, but it will be worth it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You speak to me with words, and I look at you with feelings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When a girl fights for you, know that she loves you more than anything else.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beauty isn't always about what's on the outside, but it's what's on the inside.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Distance doesn't ruin a relationship, doubts do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A real man will love you for who you are. He won't love you because you're attractive, but he'll find you attractive because he loves you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He accepts me for me and he loves me for who I am.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He makes me smile and laugh every time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God designed one person special for you... Just be patient until that person shows up in your life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EVERYTHING IS POSSIBLE! Your dreams. Your ideas. Your inventions. Your vision. Never let anyone tell you "You can't"!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God placed our heads ABOVE our hearts so that we can think OVER what we feel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you have a problem with someone, speak to them directly. It's not just about maturity, but also your own character.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's better to enjoy life committing mistakes and learn rather than playing safe in your entire life and learned NOTHING at all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Real men stay faithful. They don't have time to look for other women, because they are too busy loving the one they have.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes you just have to accept the fact that some people only enter you life as a temporary happiness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A real man never stops trying to show his woman how much she means to him, even after he already has her.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>