<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Real-time Control / Power Systems: Open Systems International, Inc. (OSI) ************ [******************************************************* is a fast-paced, growing, high technology company, headquartered in Medina, Minnesota. As… https://t.co/g8J1ia897Z https://t.co/ChKR9zm5Sv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Software Security Engineer: What We Do: The Software Engineering Institute helps advance software engineering principles and practices and serves as a national resource in software engineering, computer security, and process improvement. The… https://t.co/RgWXC3DXpU https://t.co/AXPFcMCnNG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Financial Python Software Engineer: Prestigious Enterprise Company is currently seeking a Sr. Financial Software Developer with Python skills. Candidate will design, develop and support systems within the financial modelling and research area.… https://t.co/Q48JsCsubX https://t.co/leqEN6d2o4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manager, Software Engineer: Job Description Job ID: R45462 West Creek 8 (12080), United States of America, Richmond, Virginia At Capital One, we’re building a leading information-based technology company. Still founder-led by Chairman and Chief Executive… https://t.co/6us4IIQbxC https://t.co/gz0Ai3lGRb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer II: Software Engineer II with Cox Enterprises Skip Navigation – Careers Home – Early Career – Tech Careers – Join Our Talent Community – Blog – Manage Your Profile – Cox Enterprises – Cox Communications – Cox Automotive – Cox Media… https://t.co/Ptke3ZJ9WR https://t.co/zR7Sgn6fm8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: Tyvak Nano Satellite Systems is a leading worldwide provider of nano- and micro-satellite vehicles, services, and solutions. Small satellites are disrupting the space technology realm by providing increased capabilities at a fraction of… https://t.co/3S9ZMJ3p84 https://t.co/ZSdl2d8b9M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (C++ / Python): Join our team | Rogue Wave 1.************ ****************** Skip to main content – Products – All Products – Akana – Klocwork – CentOS Support – Open Source Support – Zend Server – Zend Studio – CodeDynamics – TotalView… https://t.co/5bkp3HDOdz https://t.co/6D9SmL224H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer: Python Automation Engineer San Jose, CA Fulltime Position Job Description: – Should have Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science or equivalent stream – Should have 7-9 years of Experience in PowerShell or Python – Should Have… https://t.co/43nhKJZs5D https://t.co/qXcaCO1iXd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Public Sector – Project Manager – Senior Associate: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more… https://t.co/2QwLM3dID6 https://t.co/W0N620NzTv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Warehouse Architect: Position Overview At PNC, our people are our greatest differentiator and competitive advantage in the markets we serve. We are all united in delivering the best experience for our customers. As a Data Warehouse Architect… https://t.co/KpipgsSqcA https://t.co/FSFEcW3dDl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Lead Software Developer: CenturyLink (NYSE: CTL) is a global communications and IT services company focused on connecting its customers to the power of the digital world. CenturyLink offers network and data systems management, big data analytics,… https://t.co/vVzITUBi6r https://t.co/FRyH1OcuqX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Java, Python, BDA, C++: Req ID : 431266BR Job Code/Title : E1074:Software Engineer Stf Job Description : At Lockheed Martin Space Systems Company (SSC), we are driven by innovation and integrity. We believe that by applying the… https://t.co/8lNLc5vSN7 https://t.co/RKb3gOyENL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python/C++ Developer: Python/C++ Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position JOB DESCRIPTION: Responsibilities: Design and implement automation solution for BIOS validation test cases (in gherkin and python) Debug the test failures in automation and… https://t.co/P53WgqvcRL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist, Junior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: San Diego, CA Job Type: Entry Level, Science Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 4/13/2018 Job Description Job Number: R******* Booz Allen Hamilton has been at the forefront of strategy and… https://t.co/i2UFgDx068 https://t.co/tPzaTcCUxc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Engineer IV- UI: Develops and manages software tools in support of Enterprise Management. Formulates and defines specifications for software applications or modifies and maintains existing applications using engineering releases and utilities… https://t.co/WSTwE04BbX https://t.co/eJxKbNLSb2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer: Python Automation Engineer $110-130K +Bonus *Can be located in Hagerstown, MD; Marietta, GA or Wilmington, DE* Prestigious Fortune 500 Company is seeking an Automation Engineer. Our ideal candidate is highly autonomous, very… https://t.co/idYZN6wRZQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Public Sector Cyber Risk Manager: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about us at… https://t.co/80DqCwM4XS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Security Engineer 5 – Continuous Monitoring Compliance Analysis and Reporting Team: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented… https://t.co/FfkMGWKxcI https://t.co/SgcKW6nn63]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (Back-End): We’re a small team of engineers working to help people build credit and savings. Weve been busy building an in-house banking core that allows us to underwrite and service loans for our customers. With this comes the… https://t.co/i9iDB4goLl https://t.co/jf5dl7IrWJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineering – C/C++, Python, Java, Matlab: Req ID : 430677BR Job Code/Title : E1075:Software Engineer Sr Stf Job Description : We are seeking a Software Engineer to join the dynamic and growing Space Protection Programs Software… https://t.co/fcU14Ljbpo https://t.co/S1WzMHyCer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Lead Software Developer: CenturyLink (NYSE: CTL) is a global communications and IT services company focused on connecting its customers to the power of the digital world. CenturyLink offers network and data systems management, big data analytics,… https://t.co/fGFcKFTnR4 https://t.co/StBuJ8d0QF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Security Policy Orchestration Engineer: Armor, Inc., the leader in Managed Detection and Response, is looking for a talented and highly motivated engineer to join its Security Operations Department. The Security Policy Orchestration Engineer will be… https://t.co/w9u9jA6HKW https://t.co/ArZVnRgLBY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staff Software Algorithms Systems Engineer – Geophysical Signal Analysis: Overview Seeking a highly technical candidate with 10+ years of relevant experience working on the design, integration, and verification of Command, Control, Communications,… https://t.co/SgvwnhIrDU https://t.co/L3ESyphrQK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer – Test: Do you dream of what cars of the future will look like when you combine them with connectivity, a smartphone, and cloud services? Can you imagine uniting those dreams with a company that has the skills and relationships to… https://t.co/9728jTQZwR https://t.co/gf67t5a2q5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Engineer: Technologies &amp; Design Patterns We Use We work with a myriad of different tech buzzwords, and we certainly do not expect candidates to know everything. However, here is a list of the major languages, frameworks, and technologies we… https://t.co/mk7ElchnO6 https://t.co/ncMOOitnMO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Programming Skills – Python (mandatory), Shell Scripting ,OOPS Concepts (Mandatory). Development of Test Script and Execution Hands-on experience… https://t.co/WaeOlteVcI https://t.co/sajqvmohOr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Artificial Intelligence Engineer – Python, TensorFLow, Caffe: San Francisco, CA Full-time $175k – $250k Posted Today If you are a Artificial Intelligence Engineer with experience, please read on! We are based in beautiful San Francisco, CA. We are an… https://t.co/ro2jZDKiVm https://t.co/tWzx1dJo3z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer – Python: Job Description Job ID: R46273 Towers Crescent (12066), United States of America, Vienna, Virginia At Capital One, we’re building a leading information-based technology company. Still founder-led by Chairman and Chief… https://t.co/yrOaF57KQd https://t.co/J1i75U3brs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence (AI) Developer: Artificial Intelligence (AI) Developer Enter job title or location Search menu open clear text Search jobs Recent Searches – Deloitte home – About Deloitte – Job cart – Location: United States – Global (English)… https://t.co/uRbO2JlDWU https://t.co/A0yC08tgg5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Agile Software Engineer: Why choose between doing meaningful work and having a fulfilling life? At MITRE, you can have both. That’s because MITRE people are committed to tackling our nation’s toughest challenges—and we’re committed to the long-term… https://t.co/xOjXBcfy0i https://t.co/wXkQ1eWv6W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer: Python Automation Engineer Bellevue, WA Full Time Position Job Description: Understanding of PC Platform and mother board architecture Good understanding of different power states of system and devices (ACPI S-states,… https://t.co/Xd6JIIec6J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer: Python Automation Engineer Ref No.: 18-15855 Location: Mountain View, California Position : Python Automation Engineer Location : Mountain View, CA Job Role : Full Time Job Description : Strong Python automation with 4 to 6… https://t.co/TawS5zPnFe https://t.co/RzTtvx70tF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Operations Engineer: We’re looking for a system operations engineer to join our Woburn office, playing a pivotal role in our growing global Operations team here at SilverRail. This team provides site reliability services across all technical… https://t.co/PodiPlNyDZ https://t.co/fz2dnc10ug]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VEHICLE DYNAMICS MODELING &amp; SIMULATION ENGINEER: COMPANY PROFILE Oshkosh Corporation is a leading manufacturer and marketer of access equipment, specialty vehicles and truck bodies for the primary markets of defense, concrete placement, refuse hauling,… https://t.co/JnuNvFXw63 https://t.co/Jk3oDwKFhT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Software Engineer- IoT: TVision Insights is a hyper-growth television attention measurement company pioneering the way brands, their agencies, TV networks and OTT platforms determine the true value of their video content and advertising. The… https://t.co/ayO9NTahuj https://t.co/xOZH0R6SKC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GIS Supervisor: GIS Supervisor ============== DEPARTMENT: Land LOCATION: Pittsburgh, PA JOB RESPONSIBILITIES: 1. Supervises the work of the GIS analysts and provides technical guidance and training as necessary regarding all activities associated with… https://t.co/5MAgnAprWh https://t.co/tMFbImDVo5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bitcoin climbs to six-week high as market sentiment improves: NEW YORK (Reuters) - Bitcoin rose to a six-week high on Tuesday on positive headlines that included the possible entry of major financial institutions into the space, lifting sentiment on the… https://t.co/Xa5uH23WBT https://t.co/sH3RBtAgpA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Software Engineer Python: Web Software Engineer $75-140K +bonus Lenexa, KS Prestigious Financial Firm is seeking a Web Software Engineer with strong Python skills or a desire to learn Python. We build websites that handle millions of requests per… https://t.co/rIrcGffJ8O https://t.co/fslWFGw4IH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Avaya Python Automation Engineer: AVAYA AUTOMATION ENGINEER WITH PYTHON PROGRAMMING FOR AUTOMATION FULL RELO Avaya CM, SM,CC Elite, BSR, CMS, AES, AIM (SIP), call centers, IVR, CTI, this is a SME out of a large enterprise environment with automation… https://t.co/nWKw76Ehcr https://t.co/C01vPnwJQx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Engineer IV: THE COMPANYAre you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing reliable, affordable mortgage… https://t.co/gruWumN9DX https://t.co/V7dm6g9Rqp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java/Python Developer: Java/Python Developer Location: Boston, MA Duration: Long term contract Pay Rate: $51 to 57/hr. on w2 with voluntary employee paid benefits No# of openings: 2 Required We are seeking a senior software engineer with background in… https://t.co/4LDUCCWzzJ https://t.co/PG5qXY4GWl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Programmer Analyst, Data Informatics: The successful candidate will be an experienced, highly motivated self-starter with the ability to solve data analysis problems. They will have experience using programming languages to manipulate large… https://t.co/pXxtwEvTsA https://t.co/tcK7ShDEt2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Quality Engineer Testing: Software Quality Engineer Testing Lenexa, KS Salary: OPEN Prestigious Organization is seeking a Software Engineer who focuses on testing, building automated test cases to analyze functionality. RESPONSIBILITIES: The… https://t.co/D8H12V22m9 https://t.co/2vtN23V5X0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer- Hillsboro,OR: Python Automation Engineer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C#/C++/Python Familiar… https://t.co/Dr7PmamjpV https://t.co/Ssxs9q62zu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Science (Python) Consultant: Data Science (Python) Consulting Consultant Deloitte Consulting’s Human Capital practice is a leading global advisor and implementation partner working with companies, governments, and organizations around the world. Our… https://t.co/GQn90QvVJ5 https://t.co/tpqcUUI8gx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead IT Systems Engineer: CenturyLink (NYSE: CTL) is a global communications and IT services company focused on connecting its customers to the power of the digital world. CenturyLink offers network and data systems management, big data analytics,… https://t.co/AGuDvtnpMi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[python/c++ Automation developer: Python/c++ Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python Familiar with any… https://t.co/Vps2ke2zSz https://t.co/x6KFjZot5Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Django / Python DevOps: If working with a sophisticated cloud environment spanning multiple service providers and using a range of technologies such as Python, Django, Docker and many others is what youre aiming for, then wed be happy to welcome you to… https://t.co/qlAMVpvW6g https://t.co/XdFwBcPDAV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Web Developer – https://t.co/xPBHAdVeaN: ********** has an opening for an experienced Web Developer to lead and grow a 3 developer team. ********** is a leading online service provider to Lawyers and Consumers. Our LAMP servers handle over a million… https://t.co/1Seu0KktnU https://t.co/LCUC6GMUcK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Performance Engineer with GOLANG – Python scripting: Performance Engineer with GOLANG – Python scripting jobs in 08057 | ******** Toggle navigation – Tech Careers – Job Search – Skills Center – Dice Careers Mobile – Career Explorer – Salary Predictor –… https://t.co/MI8a0Yv2xo https://t.co/Dk0sQa4me3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer (Python/Django): Software Developer (Python/Django) Skip Navigation Raytheon – Cyber – News – What We Do – Who We Are – Global – Investors – Careers – Visit:Cyber – Who We Are – Leaders – Businesses – Corporate Responsibility – Culture… https://t.co/w8TknJBW3q https://t.co/WsvcxR1x0g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Python Application Developer 4 – Top Secret Clearance Required:   Job Description – Sr. Python Application Developer 4 – Top Secret Clearance Required (18002106) Sr. Python Application Developer 4 – Top Secret Clearance Required Requisition ID :… https://t.co/UlD3sW6Vr2 https://t.co/fUM1zvzFlP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Bellevue, WA: Software Engineer Bellevue, WA Full Time Position Job Description: In this position, the candidate will be integrating and validating different machine learning frameworks also developing POCs in the augmented/Virtual… https://t.co/Qf8m8UTMFo https://t.co/0zIHHZeDY9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Engineer Client: CMMi Level 5 Company Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Programming Skills – Python (mandatory), Shell Scripting ,OOPS Concepts (Mandatory). Development of Test… https://t.co/SrG6ueknSH https://t.co/A6HYqRBVbm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Security Engineer 4: Cyber Threat Engineering: Job Description Since 1852, customers have trusted that Wells Fargo would keep their assets secure from theft and always available. Today, maintaining customer trust remains our underlying operating… https://t.co/h76AG9fbA6 https://t.co/bkDzgoToM9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Security Engineer 4: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the center of everything we do. Join… https://t.co/IbgMvzNmdI https://t.co/349hnf6j6I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Python/JavaScript Developer: Muster is a cloud based web platform that enables customers to create online advocacy campaings with analytics. We are seeking an experienced developer to help build and maintain our web application, written primarily… https://t.co/LHXfN0BOOA https://t.co/bViWIlYeKy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer: Python Automation Engineer Bellevue, WA Full Time Position Job Description: Understanding of PC Platform and mother board architecture Good understanding of different power states of system and devices (ACPI S-states,… https://t.co/ZRu5yykvIb https://t.co/2YeQVQ6zhW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer (Python/Django): 106428BR Software Developer (Python/Django) VA – Herndon 106428BR Raytheon Intelligence and Information Services (IIS) – Raytheon Cyber Solutions(RCS) is looking for an experienced Software Developer to advance several… https://t.co/AHztehxW0O https://t.co/XiZGGc1hdn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back End Developer – Python: San Francisco, CA Full-time $100k – $120k Posted Today Are you a Back-End Developer? Do you have experience with Python? Do you have awesome communication skills? If so, then please read on! Based in San Francisco, CA, we are… https://t.co/8qzZdmcUFH https://t.co/pcXJOhUQNh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Security Engineer 4: Cyber Threat Engineering: Job Description Since 1852, customers have trusted that Wells Fargo would keep their assets secure from theft and always available. Today, maintaining customer trust remains our underlying operating… https://t.co/9YN32VbBZL https://t.co/a9QilePQJO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal – Analytics Delivery: Role Principal – Analytics Delivery Auto req ID 29889BR Domain Analytics Skillset PYTHON , Country USA State / Region / Province Washington Work Location Redmond, WA Company ITL USA Job Description Infosys– DNA– Principal… https://t.co/Vn7lulpjvx https://t.co/nMPRh1eFvt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Software Engineer Python: Web Software Engineer $75-140K +bonus Lenexa, KS Prestigious Financial Firm is seeking a Web Software Engineer with strong Python skills or a desire to learn Python. We build websites that handle millions of requests per… https://t.co/TSBvDVh997 https://t.co/HTSpDxT7FU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java/Python development: Java/Python development Malvern, Pennsylvania – United States Job Start Date – 03/21/18, Posted Date – 03/21/18 Primary SkillsAWS,Java/Python development,implementing REST API’s with Java for integration to 3rd party… https://t.co/wHjBPUh4xg https://t.co/YIcAOgN02h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Security Engineer 5 – Continuous Monitoring Compliance Analysis and Reporting Team: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented… https://t.co/JzXvgeanvT https://t.co/PAfszET5Ms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Incident Response Experienced Associate: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more about… https://t.co/T3zyi5JbVu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer: Python /Linux Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++. Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python. Familiar with any… https://t.co/M0X7pSR6B3 https://t.co/9M602IcOeR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AWS Big Data Developer: To provide intermediate level system analysis, design, development, and implementation of applications and databases for mainframe-, client/server-, Web-, and/or PC-based systems, under supervision of a more senior developer.… https://t.co/QCpFGYb3id https://t.co/zAgGAQwhC1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Security Engineer 5 – Continuous Monitoring Compliance Analysis and Reporting Team: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented… https://t.co/Qzc1Ekuiy3 https://t.co/Xup1WNvPvb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: PYTHON DEVELOPER TYSONS CORNER, VA OPPORTUNITY DETAILS: Our client, located in the northern Virginia area, has an immediate need for a Python Developer. This position will work with other member of the engineering team to support the… https://t.co/Os92jPYj0o https://t.co/U6QMNmBwfd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embedded SW Engineer (Embedded C/C++, Python): Embedded SW Engineer (Embedded C/C++, Python) Ref No.: 18-16627 Location: san diego, California Hi, This is Shipra from Enterprise Solution Inc. I have a urgent requirement for the position mentioned below.… https://t.co/6Jd8OeYm1n https://t.co/f7f8hHmMvI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Python Application Developer 4 – Top Secret Clearance Required:   Job Description – Sr. Python Application Developer 4 – Top Secret Clearance Required (18002106) Sr. Python Application Developer 4 – Top Secret Clearance Required Requisition ID :… https://t.co/ShbIFss8Ma https://t.co/ZTshjW31al]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Python Developer downtown Chicago, Illinois – United States Job Start Date – 03/21/18, Posted Date – 03/21/18 Primary SkillsPython DeveloperTax TermsC2COverview EAD from IT Serve Phone – Skype 5 month project in downtown Chicago. Please… https://t.co/Yu8gGqqnyD https://t.co/r7chpnyWos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer Sr: Req ID : 423850BR Job Code/Title : E1073:Software Engineer Sr Job Description : Responsibilities will span all aspects of support equipment life cycle, including requirements generation, system and software design and implementation… https://t.co/akg3p5cQWv https://t.co/TrFtjZimMf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Developer Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: Python programming experience is a must. Should have atleast 2+ Years of experience in Python Application Development Able to understand OOPS concepts… https://t.co/nPdGoPk3uC https://t.co/W11PO9uujZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: You should possess at least a Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science, Computer Engineering or related field. A Master’s degree is preferred.… https://t.co/bTy3BBTRzX https://t.co/ygxCznbNGy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Security Engineer 5 – Continuous Monitoring Compliance Analysis and Reporting Team: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented… https://t.co/R04OLyQSQO https://t.co/ODKyJmndsV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AI/Machine Learning Senior Engineer (Java &amp; Python): AI/Machine Learning Senior Engineer (Java &amp; Python) at Twilio (View all jobs) San Francisco, CA Twilio Understand is the brain of Twilio’s natural language understanding (NLU). Twilio Understand,… https://t.co/L1bq8oojGp https://t.co/LGY2YUklyj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer: Python Automation Engineer $110-130K +Bonus *Can be located in Hagerstown, MD; Marietta, GA or Wilmington, DE* Prestigious Fortune 500 Company is seeking an Automation Engineer. Our ideal candidate is highly autonomous, very… https://t.co/BhkYmPGv3W https://t.co/dNYq0hCq0Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Application Developer: CenturyLink (NYSE: CTL) is a global communications and IT services company focused on connecting its customers to the power of the digital world. CenturyLink offers network and data systems management, big data analytics,… https://t.co/DLjoelV6lg https://t.co/5BO3jP3SbV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer: Automation Engineer (C++/Python) Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Responsibilities: Implement automation solution for BIOS validation test cases through Python programming Debug the test failures in automation… https://t.co/BHJIfGJWMR https://t.co/08GX5Bs4c8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Security Engineer 5 – Continuous Monitoring Compliance Analysis and Reporting Team: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented… https://t.co/osDCUnC9Y8 https://t.co/8koojEtzKA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer: Python Automation Engineer San Jose, CA Full time Position Job Description: * Should have Bachelors degree in Computer Science or equivalent stream * Should have 7-9 years of Experience in PowerShell or Python * Should Have… https://t.co/0qWrYmm4B5 https://t.co/aRGnVpDBdR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Science Software Engineer: We believe in the power of people. We are a network strategy and technology company that is motivated by making a difference in people’s lives – their productivity, their creativity, their health and comfort. That’s why… https://t.co/fBla1HzURD https://t.co/eCCQ2QVIS5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior DevOps Engineer: At Fitbit, our mission is to help people lead healthier, more active lives by empowering them with data, inspiration and guidance to reach their goals. We started our journey in 2007as a team of two with one big idea. Since then,… https://t.co/sGsgVL9deE https://t.co/OuDSPeGjua]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Applications Engineer III (Cyber Software Engineer): ALL CANDIDATES MUST HAVE AN ACTIVE TS/SCI WITH POLYGRAPH CLEARANCE! Description: The candidate will: Design, develop, document, test and debug applications software and systems that contain logical and… https://t.co/bU5by7t8Z1 https://t.co/QO3m7yrFUv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flight Software Engineer: Flight Software Engineer Skip Navigation Raytheon – Cyber – News – What We Do – Who We Are – Global – Investors – Careers – Visit:Cyber – Who We Are – Leaders – Businesses – Corporate Responsibility – Culture – History –… https://t.co/T60aGOdcmX https://t.co/RQ35zPqU2Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Data Python Software Engineer: We’re looking for a Senior Data Python Software Engineer to help us build internal tools for our data team to allow us to better scale our growing suite of products. Our stack includes — but is certainly not limited… https://t.co/An0Joa9NfA https://t.co/NBmEGbFUjb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: Description As a DevOps Engineer, you’ll be part of a small operations team responsible for engineering and maintaining the production infrastructure for Tivo’s Advanced Search and Recommendations platform in the cloud and on-premises.… https://t.co/oMuZ2Pdjiv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist: Company Introduction OneinaMil is a talent matchmaking firm, we specialize in culture driven recruiting. Our mission is to change the way traditional recruiting is done by putting human connection and culture back into the talent… https://t.co/0XEUzb3hhq https://t.co/biLpC2F18Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Video: Description Video is becoming a key workload in Datacenters. Existing architectures are performing sub-optimally for highly complex video workloads like h.264, HEVC and VP9 encoding. FPGAs are programmable, low power and offer… https://t.co/aXRaMIpbwd https://t.co/Fc2Zi1IXkh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer – Python: Job Description We are looking for a full stack Web Framework developer to work on upstream R &amp; D projects closely with a data science team, performing functional prototyping and facilitating the transfer of successful… https://t.co/icgGyPQBPo https://t.co/R8CiBlHqlt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C++/Python Automation Engineer – OR: C++/Python Automation Engineer Hillsboro OR Full time position Responsibilities: Implement automation solution for BIOS validation test cases through Gherkin/Python programming Debug the test failures in automation… https://t.co/M6Y39Q3kUN https://t.co/Sbsh36FV2c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Real-time Control / Power Systems: Open Systems International, Inc. (OSI) ************ [******************************************************* is a fast-paced, growing, high technology company, headquartered in Medina, Minnesota. As… https://t.co/mDs4gwkp6f https://t.co/VXhYyYrymF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Network Engineer: The Hut Group aims to be the Worlds leading Online Health &amp; Beauty Destination. We are currently the UKs leading multi-website online retailer with rapidly growing global operations and a unique proprietary technology platform.… https://t.co/Kz5VvDvxwM https://t.co/kLt4n7Ex8Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer – Java: Thermo Fisher Scientific – Software Developer Job in Java – Home – Discover Our Stories – Career Areas – Engineering – Field Service – Finance – General Management – Human Resources – Operations &amp; Supply Chain – Quality –… https://t.co/gLBtk7svlf https://t.co/vNvRM3kL91]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Full Stack JavaScript Developer: Looking to join a team where you’ll make an immediate impact? Tire Discounters is searching for a Senior Full Stack JavaScript Developer to join the family in Sharonville, Ohio. If you’re a detail-oriented,… https://t.co/5dzHTIwsGt https://t.co/OVzw6Os24S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Full Stack Engineer: Eagle Eye Networks Engineering has a truly unique opportunity for well-rounded engineers. Sure, call it a Full Stack position, however the Eagle Eye Networks technology stack extends beyond the usual frontend/backend developer… https://t.co/CP57CXZgrT https://t.co/3ASgoR0ioV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Staff / Principal Engineer – Complex System Optimization: Huawei is a leading global information and communications technology (ICT) solutions provider. Through our dedication to customer-centric innovation and strong partnerships, we have… https://t.co/Sf8pFL1ALq https://t.co/ZZZtDeUE0b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer-Python: Phantom is the only purpose-built Security Automation &amp; Orchestration platform, and the first to provide an open community for sharing Playbooks and Apps. It makes security smarter, faster, and stronger. We are an early-stage… https://t.co/22KSmnI7Rd https://t.co/Zdud9FreG3]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>