<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome running t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the running lovers in your life!  http://t.co/3AVX81GpzW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know who invented high heels, but all women owe him a lot! - Marilyn Monroe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mr. Bentley - He builds fast trucks. - Ettore Bugatti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Corona Beer  http://t.co/D7TPSN8NVX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to War  http://t.co/Y05s0RVxgA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And now, I'm just trying to change the world, one sequin at a time. Lady Gaga]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its Real - You Can Print Shoes with a 3D Printer!  http://t.co/qeZalEK4VY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The absolute fundamental aim is to make money out of satisfying customers. - John Egan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best thing to save for your old age is yourself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 2 - Road Trip!!!  http://t.co/w1OMUZPtzR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool just found these 25 Original Unopened Packs of Vintage Baseball Cards (80s-90s) - can find some value in there!  http://t.co/4tZ2hb9p2a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Top 10 Asian Beers  http://t.co/5VRzzirvQq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sex and the City changed New York - New York's become a big shoe store now, unfortunately. -  Chris Noth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The two-party political parties in the US consists of the appointed and the disappointed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To win without risk is to triumph without glory. - Pierre Corneille]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Popcorn Ceiling Removal - A Complex Job  http://t.co/aRWecOgkvu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1,000 Incredible Costume and Cosplay Ideas http://t.co/bgrEyKgRiJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need to tie some kerosene rags around his ankles so the ants don't eat his candy #$@ - Dale Earnhardt speaking of Mark Martin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In difficult times, fashion is always outrageous. - Elsa Schiaparelli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is the mark of an educated mind to be able to entertain a thought without accepting it. - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hiring Strategy Consulting Firms: The Importance of Competitive Analysis  http://t.co/oMvQpDr7aT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It costs a lot of money to look this cheap --&gt; Dolly Parton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anthony “Tony” Harris, CSECO President and CEO, receives an Honorary Doctorate in Engineering from Purdue University  http://t.co/dh0Lur6w6Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You see things; and you say "Why?" But I dream things that never were; and I say "Why not?" - George Bernard Shaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Assisted Living in Your Own Home  http://t.co/nMyk9sVmXV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of Stargate Universe  http://t.co/T4PRb8ULxr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't realize how strong a person really is until you see them at their weakest moment. - Unknown Author]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone has a right to a university degree in America, even if it's in Hamburger Technology. - Clive James]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you go to buy, don't show your silver - Chinese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sam Cooke was the king of soul - read his history - http://t.co/S7zc82zhIb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a stuffed toy! It's a sleeping bag. IT'S A SHARK! - Its COOL! http://t.co/07eeelroAu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Celiac Disease And Gluten Free Foods  http://t.co/ITPx135uBW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most beautiful thing in the world is a ballpark filled with people. - Bill Veeck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Ketchup  http://t.co/E7OV1loIZF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the Romans had been obliged to learn Latin, they would never have found time to conquer the world. - Heinrich Heine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, no, he didn't slam you, he didn't bump you, he didn't nudge you - he rubbed you. And rubbin, son, is racin' Harry Hogge, Days of Thunder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Help with Picking Garage Cabinets  http://t.co/Huv5nxcpe2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is an admirable thing, but it is well to remember from time to time that nothing that is worth knowing can be taught - Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A baseball game is simply a nervous breakdown divided into nine innings. - Earl Wilson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tornado Automatic Cocktail Shaker - VERY COOL http://t.co/w2YjTDoitl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The opera always loses money. That's as it should be. Opera has no business making money. Rudolf Bing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes I can't figure designers out. It's as if they flunked human anatomy. --&gt; Erma Bombeck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman's dress should be a like a barbed-wire fence: serving its purpose without obstructing the view. - Sophia Loren]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Tips from Web Building Experts  http://t.co/pWiLKkTS0U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the dressing room, I always put on my right shoe first. Same thing for my right wristband. -  Mary Lou Retton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You teach best what you most need to learn. - Richard David Bach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to J.R.R. Tolkien  http://t.co/b01SlCEUEH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make Your House More Attractive With Fall Flowers  http://t.co/0ci1g69W2O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prometheus is reaching out for the stars with an empty grin on his face. - Arthur Koestler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wal-mart --  do they like make walls there?  Paris Hilton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Eric Clapton  http://t.co/D42WW5Ycad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I started out writing much more science fictiony stuff and writing about science fiction. - Neil Gaiman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In order to break the ice --  crack a smile]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is tool cool a LED Kitchen Sink Faucet Sprayer Nozzle - make the water turn blue!  http://t.co/ZVWlbtrnYV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever hear of instant credit? You just add money]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Assisted Living - Some Things to Consider  http://t.co/fhpGbLjdfu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who wish to sing, always find a song. - Swedish Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Elvis Presley    http://t.co/ablHs8mGyb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about the History of San Francisco, California http://t.co/X61bujMzDO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is a progressive discovery of our own ignorance. - Will Durant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gin and Titonic Ice Cube Tray - Add the Titanic To Your Drinks http://t.co/4etmgaSdRf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one can make you feel inferior without your permission. - Eleanor Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then there was the crooked crematory operator who sold the ashes to cannibals as instant people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Invest in Penny Stocks And Earn Huge Profits  http://t.co/jPwqbeTM8G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret of success is constancy to purpose. - Benjamin Disraeli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Foreigner  http://t.co/kJpSkUHQDK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Politicians should read science fiction, not westerns and detective stories. - Arthur C. Clarke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science fiction is not predictive; it is descriptive. - Ursula K. LeGuin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the largest life insurance companies in the US!  http://t.co/8kUvPea99O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Publishing Management with HootSuite  http://t.co/RLKdxXU0Dt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The probable reason some people get lost in thought is because it is unfamiliar territory to them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who can believe that there is no soul behind those luminous doggie eyes! - Theophile Gautier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Modern Glo Night Light - Night Light Fashion!  http://t.co/mslQL0OZgh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The internet has turned what used to be a controlled, one-way message into a real-time dialogue with millions - Danniel Sacks, Fast Company]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Beach Boys  http://t.co/m1eiN1tpun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to be the Cecil B. DeMille of science fiction. - Steven Spielberg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn The Importance of a Good Pitching Repertoire for Young Pitchers  http://t.co/649lprlaiJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Fitness Apps – Is There One That Is the Best?  http://t.co/MWbJyXuho7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Deep Purple  http://t.co/Oi4T53Reuc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Introduction to Steak 'n Shake  http://t.co/xnJ4CwhMSk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The blunt people make the most pointed remarks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Very Interesting History of Shoe Sizes  http://t.co/YvYsdJaw8S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even on the most solemn occasions I got away without wearing socks and hid that lack of civilization in high boots --&gt; Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think education is expensive, try ignorance - Derek Bok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who likes not his business, his business likes not him. - William Hazlitt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hops Holster 12 Can Ammo Pack - Beer Anywhere!  http://t.co/qRhrwmL3zQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every instructor assumes that you have nothing else to do except study for that instructor's course.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That guitar is okay but you'll never make a living with it - John Lennon's Aunt Mimi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About eCommerce E-Tips  http://t.co/7OZWvYAeA9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Future generations will be born free, equal and in debt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not anorexic. I'm from Texas. Are there people from Texas that are anorexic? I've never heard of one. And that includes me. Jessica S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heredity:  what makes the father and mother of a teen-ager wonder about each other]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome basketball t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the basketball lovers in your life!   http://t.co/QbMG4N4jN0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is A Hedge Fund?  http://t.co/BvEv7vKpxT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mr. Bentley - He builds fast trucks. - Ettore Bugatti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give a girl the correct footwear and she can conquer the world. - Bette Midler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Amazing Nappy Brown  http://t.co/bsuV0pWBfj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Battleship Memorial Park – Mobile Alabama – A Great Historical Experience  http://t.co/lUv0EjbGeS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who are the Three Degrees oldies group?  http://t.co/jXgAWh3syk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like this ship! You know, it's exciting! - Scotty]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>