<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Golden slumbers fill your eyes, smiles awake you when you rise. - Golden Slumbers by The Beatles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The glass is neither half-full nor half-empty: it's twice as big as it needs to be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read an Introduction to Sonic Drive-In  http://t.co/DWZm6PbSJT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As far as I'm concerned, there won't be a Beatles reunion as long as John Lennon remains dead. - George Harrison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the Lava Lamp - so retro and so cool --&gt; http://t.co/8A6bebLQD5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picking Earphones for Fitness Activities  http://t.co/Xkfwoaztqh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Daddy: Mommy just backed the car over my bicycle! "I told you not to leave it in the living room!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CONSCIENCE: The thing that hurts when everything  else feels good…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many a man doesn't start living until he's married. And then he's finished.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make the Most of Twitter for Your Business  http://t.co/e78zum9k1g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome camping t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the camping lovers in your life!  http://t.co/KLRcsPDGy1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bring out your dead. - Monty Python and the Holy Grail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You cannot dream yourself into a character: you must hammer and forge yourself into one. - Henry D. Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about the Bay Area city of Pleasanton, California http://t.co/rHogTg9pzp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last word of the Emperor Montezuma, "Someone tell those Marines to stop singing in the halls."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't see pitches down the middle anymore - not even in batting practice. -  Hank Aaron]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to Douglas Adams  http://t.co/Q2Xg4wkcMm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Green Acres is an American sitcom classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/L9tuoqpxBQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's no need for a piece of sculpture in a home that has a cat. - Wesley Bates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think education is expensive, try ignorance - Derek Bok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Planning Beach Camping Tips  http://t.co/X1dyhljs2q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one gets very far unless he accomplishes the impossible at least once a day. - Elbert Hubbard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To succeed --  You need to find something to hold on to, something to motivate you, something to inspire you. - Tony Dorsett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is the key to unlock the golden door of freedom. - George Washington Carver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A mosquito is just like a child, when it stops making noise, you know it's getting into something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the Lava Lamp - so retro and so cool --&gt; http://t.co/8A6bebLQD5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are seven winners of the Monaco Grand Prix on the starting line today, and four of them are Michael Schumacher. - Murray Walker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of Artemis Fowl By Eoin Colfer  http://t.co/Ie6gIZCejI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've learned that when things seem to go wrong, stay calm and wait till you see the bigger picture!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is more than a game to me, it's a religion. - Bill Klem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Scientific Explorer's Mind Blowing Science Kit! http://t.co/fmLUQbl5My]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Foxy  http://t.co/InpqDbRsKy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[High heels are pride and privilege, the passkey to decadence. - Karen Heller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hiring Strategy Consulting Firms: The Importance of Competitive Analysis  http://t.co/kJ5r4KhEZg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is A Derivative?  http://t.co/fKDuSxUW1N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The client is not always right. - Enzo Ferrari]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Five Guys Burgers and Fries  http://t.co/3aKwryXuii]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man with a lot of money may be a bad egg, but folks seldom take offense until he is broke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Scientific Explorer's Mind Blowing Science Kit! http://t.co/fmLUQbl5My]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You will never change your life until you change something you do daily. - Mike Murdock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The dog was created especially for children. He is the God of frolic. - Henry Ward Beecher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You think dogs will not be in heaven? I tell you, they will be there long before any of us - Robert Louis Stevenson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It isn't the age, it's the mileage that counts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go Big, or Go Home - Eliza Dushku]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You may delay, but time will not. - Benjamin Franklin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of the hilarious "I Love Lucy" episode - The Kleptomaniac  http://t.co/kZ7e7MIZKF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kneel before Zod. - Zod, Superman II]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we're growing, we're always going to be out of our comfort zone. - John Maxwell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turbochargers are for people who cant build engines. - Keith Duckworth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nobody remembers the guy who finished second but the guy who finished second. - Bobby Unser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whenever you are asked if you can do a job, tell "˜em, "˜Certainly I can!' Then get busy and find out how to do it. - Theodore Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My name is Inigo Montoya. You killed my father. Prepare to die! - Inigo, The Princess Bride]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never look back unless you are planning to go that way. - Henry David Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can You Imagine Melting Clock - Very Cool - Jazz Up Your Office Space! http://t.co/Qljdsh1SMC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of American Hamburgers  http://t.co/CsVQHGUeKo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about the History of San Francisco, California http://t.co/wdkQqXV6A8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The difference between a mountain and a molehill is your perspective. - Al Neuharth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His timing is perfect, so is his two-timing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you haven't got it, fake it! Too short? Wear big high heels, but do practice walking! - Victoria Beckham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating Introduction to Marmalade Insurance: How to Select an Insurance Agency  http://t.co/LJ5KnDmKV9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By working faithfully eight hours a day you may eventually get to be a boss and work twelve hours a day. - Robert Frost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Out the Top Football Teams of the 2011-2012 Season  http://t.co/Z0ODYY1VsG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Gardening Fall Flowers  http://t.co/jS9q8Veuhu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Cooking – An Effortless Way to Bond with Kids  http://t.co/nhx6vjym0O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The King of ‘Rhythm’ and ‘Blues’: Johnny Ace  http://t.co/emjzNPgKwK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Al Green  http://t.co/gXpMJ7zXoY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A university is what a college becomes when the faculty loses interest in students. - John Ciardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money was never a big motivation for me, except as a way to keep score. The real excitement is playing the game. - Donald Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome baseball t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the baseball lovers in your life!   http://t.co/dIz5tNp1pG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His head is getting too big for his toupee...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Emmylou Harris  http://t.co/F2PCDzjQnO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dream house is one that cost twice as much as you ever dreamed it would…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think the last 4 words of the national anthem are gentlemen, start your engines, you might be a redneck. - Jeff Foxworthy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret of toe cleavage, a very important part of the sexuality of the shoe; you must only show the first two cracks. - Manolo Blahnik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To win without risk is to triumph without glory. - Pierre Corneille]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't speak ill of your predecessors or successors. You didn't walk in their shoes. - Donald Rumsfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fish Hotel Aquarium - Jazz Up Your Office! http://t.co/MzBfKpTri9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can lead a boy to college but you can't make him think. - Elbert Hubbard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A business has to be involving, it has to be fun, and it has to exercise your creative instincts. - Richard Branson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get a Hunger Games Mockingjay Pin - http://t.co/IsNbuPjYHk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Arthur Alexander – Country and R&amp;B Pioneer  http://t.co/CekGNKflHQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Youth is when we want to set the world on fire... Middle age is when we hope our children won't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They just couldn't live without each other --  so they got married and discovered they could]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The opera always loses money. That's as it should be. Opera has no business making money. Rudolf Bing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So exactly what is an atomic clock?  http://t.co/dS9Nh6iHk4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Platform Shoes  http://t.co/ceYYfEBnDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If man is a little lower than angels, then angels should reform.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You may have to fight a battle more than once to win it. - Margaret Thatcher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome cooking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the cooking lovers in your life!   http://t.co/0oz6H0O0Hl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money was never a big motivation for me, except as a way to keep score. The real excitement is playing the game. - Donald Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peace Through Superior Firepower "We endanger species"  - Mottos of the marines in Aliens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Modern Homesteading  http://t.co/797OvMbzuC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can lead a boy to college but you can't make him think. - Elbert Hubbard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your chances of winning, I've got to believe are really, really small when you score one run in 18 innings. - Clint Hurdle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The dog was created especially for children. He is the God of frolic. - Henry Ward Beecher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the Little House on the Prairie Episode The Nephews  http://t.co/EpbO6lJQ7Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Best Camping Destinations  http://t.co/lhiqaCSBaG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thats the way Baseball go - Ron Washington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Christian Louboutin  http://t.co/MTzAcmEzGI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the business world, everyone is paid in two coins: cash &amp; experience. Take the experience first; the cash will come later - Harold Geneen]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>