<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TimHarford: Has economics failed? Tom @prospect_clark debates @ChrisGiles_ https://t.co/OmhCqPYn0u I think Tom's being unfair. Let me e…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ChrisGiles_: Time for economists to stop mumbling into their shoes and tell the Queen she was asking a stupid question https://t.co/6iS…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @prospect_clark: Picking up from EconoWars w @HowardRReed @DianeCoyle1859 and many others in @prospect_uk, @ChrisGiles_ &amp; I debate @ft w…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has economics failed? @prospect_clark and @ChrisGiles_ go head to head  https://t.co/WlyYsyoaGG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@toby_n @just_shelter Agreed. Reviewed it for @FinancialTimes https://t.co/CrkejkeRos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@georgeeaton @MazzucatoM See also Colin Crouch and Wolfgang Streeck https://t.co/e3ZfCCVnFo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OiPolloi: Samuel Beckett - novelist... playwright... jacket wearer. https://t.co/Mh9hiXWQ9W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apologies for banging on, but @sarahoconnor_'s contribution to FT Big Picture on work and the gig economy is superb https://t.co/RqSoKEYqY4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent: @amiasrinivasan on Waldron on equality  https://t.co/W3gsECbdYY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilariously over the top, and thoroughly enjoyable, piece about Jan Wenner by James Wolcott https://t.co/5bI7DyHIIu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GavinJKelly1: Enjoyed talking to @sarahoconnor_ for her ace new @FT 'Big Picture' podcast on the future of work: covering insecurity, g…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@gideonrachman on Brexit, the customs union and a tsarist-era joke about a horse https://t.co/A8wdfCkO9P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sarahoconnor_: "Sometimes you have good days, a lot of times you have bad days. It's just a wild west." 

What's it like on the coalfac…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SebastianEPayne: The second instalment of @FinancialTimes Big Picture podcast is out 🎉

Listen to @sarahoconnor_ on the changing world…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Episode 2 of FT Big Picture: @sarahoconnor_  on the changing world of work https://t.co/RqSoKEYqY4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hoganem And episode 2 - @sarahoconnor_ on the changing world of work - is out tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hoganem Might I recommend this, too? https://t.co/85WrG2KFax]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think this is a metaphor for something #SPD #Berlin https://t.co/PwvdjbA5pw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeyyLowe Naturally, I'm sympathetic to that view, though Berlin is giving Paris a run for its money this week https://t.co/yvMMm5hLsb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Neukölln, Berlin doing a passable impression of the Mediterranean https://t.co/OlgnGrhG3q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's Julian Jackson's gloss on those 24 hours - from his forthcoming book on de Gaulle, A Certain Idea of France https://t.co/l7zjeqYvhr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fifty years ago today, de Gaulle abruptly left France - it turns out for the HQ of French forces in Germany. Exactly what happened in the 24 hours he was away remains obscure  https://t.co/JhLyP8Gevp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonderful footage from last year's memorial service at All Souls for Derek Parfit. Edward Mortimer's recollections of the young Parfit are particularly moving https://t.co/AXesLPE4XH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This 2008 encounter between Philips Dodd and Roth is very entertaining indeed  https://t.co/WLPWJ6N2yJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone has put the whole of Tristram Powell's 1983 adaptation of the first of Philip Roth's Zuckerman novels, The Ghost Writer, on You Tube https://t.co/RCfNDLRPyQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonderful: Emmanuel Dongala on what he owed to Philip Roth https://t.co/zXPDQPKhkk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Robert Paxton on Serge and Beate Klarsfeld https://t.co/obaU6U0QNu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["How can there be Jews without baseball." Echt Roth. https://t.co/kusB3UwmnC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dsquareddigest @kamaalwilliams I like it. Not ambient so much as fusion - I do like the analogue keyboard textures.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally, at the end of a busy week, I get to reacquaint myself with this https://t.co/Lrp2DpEkBp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @djmgaffneyw4: J'en Ai Marre was such a perfect name for the guitarist in the Smiths. https://t.co/4vEsrpPip8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NaomiOhReally: Memorial in central Dublin for Savita Halappanavar, whose death after she was denied an abortion in 2012 galvanised the…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @gavreilly: IRISH TIMES EXIT POLL: YES 68% #8thRef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JacobHeilbrunn @kamaalwilliams Much less exalted! Pro-Ject Essential III.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's nice to come home to: the new @kamaalwilliams record https://t.co/1PimnEcBtN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @galbeckerman: I'm particularly fond of @DMendelsohn1960's response to the question of his favorite Roth book. "Operation Shylock" is up…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At last! An appreciation of Roth that gives The Counterlife and Operation Shylock their due https://t.co/36aZpWHjAz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the @FinancialTimes' commentary this week on Italy's populist experiment in one place https://t.co/YpKSn99HSl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SaraRFerguson @martin_oneill It is a hill I and my colleagues on the FT opinion desk will die on too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ireland votes tomorrow. Here's Clair Wills on what this referendum means https://t.co/AJ7Bayhiwb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This by Zadie Smith on Philip Roth is particularly fine - especially on the distinctively critical quality of his patriotism https://t.co/iYxUXChGye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great @libe front page https://t.co/aZaTi8fsGU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating piece by @JamilAnderlini on the history wars between India and China https://t.co/Xr4pr6C9j7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Philp Roth: iconoclast and chronicler of the American condition | FT News on acast https://t.co/WJqUng0ahd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I talked to Jan Dalley about Philip Roth https://t.co/DF226928va]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joshspero In the Library of America edition https://t.co/CQa6GQBnDN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hermione Lee's Paris Review interview with Philip Roth https://t.co/fImGEywk50]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DenisMacShane There is no one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I didn't have other things to do, I'd be hunkering down with this lot today https://t.co/ZUbXep5bjE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BlakeBaileyOn: Philip Roth died tonight, surrounded by lifelong friends who loved him dearly. A darling man and our greatest living wri…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wake up to news of death of Philip Roth. Hard to say what is pinnacle. For me, The Counterlife, Operatiom Shylock or Sabbath's Theater.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As @RanaForoohar was saying ... https://t.co/XGsKltxo3Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@martinwolf_ on what Italy's new government could mean for the eurozone  https://t.co/vNn6HxzDIg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very good piece by Clair Wills on the Irish abortion referendum https://t.co/AJ7Bayhiwb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kategobell: This is v good, and makes the case nicely for our call for joint and several liability for breaches of employment rights th…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@sarahoconnor_ argues that supply chains can have a big effect on workers' bargaining power https://t.co/BSFjcq7lCX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We've now completed the first series of the FT Big Picture podcast. Listen to all five episodes here https://t.co/ntXqKWkt3U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Jderbyshire: I've reviewed @michaelkenny_ and @IPR_NickP's Shadows of Empire https://t.co/DP9mcWFjmv https://t.co/qws1HtVlPH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really looking forward to the @TheCookersMusic show @Church_of_Sound on Thursday https://t.co/lE7uSKkl0a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ftcomment: Podcast:John Thornhill: Artificial intelligence - the new frontier John Thornhill: AI, the new frontier https://t.co/VtlIQkq…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FTLifeArts: Is the dream of the Anglosphere dead? https://t.co/xDhUk20wnR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaelkenny_ @IPR_NickP Link seems to be broken, Mike https://t.co/DP9mcWFjmv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've reviewed @michaelkenny_ and @IPR_NickP's Shadows of Empire https://t.co/DP9mcWFjmv https://t.co/qws1HtVlPH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DenisMacShane And see @GavinJKelly1's op-ed https://t.co/BquyLMW7Se]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DenisMacShane Listen to Sarah's FT Big Picture podcast https://t.co/7eXCSOw7RE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These boys came so close today. Fabulous effort by everyone. Forza Dulwich! https://t.co/RBCUD4TLjI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DenisMacShane @sarahoconnor_ As it happens, Sarah has written extensively about how to unionise the precariously employed. E.g. here https://t.co/C9v3fCAOxT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lessons from Weimar for italy - @EuroBriefing in characteristically sunny mood https://t.co/Cx016XszRx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@harikunzru Tune!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @harikunzru: I just stumbled upon this amazing 1980 doc about the jazz funk scene. A few years before my time - by about 1985 I was goin…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good piece by @EswarSPrasad on the future of the US dollar's "exorbitant privilege" as global reserve currency https://t.co/a1H9kzZHFH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@medlar_ @WasimWozAhmed @onthecornerteam Love the Collocutor Black Satin EP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WasimWozAhmed @medlar_ Great isn't it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @medlar_  remix of DJ Khalab's 'Zaire' is an Afro-electro jewel https://t.co/6yBwAs5BIF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @alanbeattie: Possibly the best rejoinder ever seen on Twitter, or anywhere. https://t.co/WuKkqdyqsh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Matteo Salvini, a populist on the verge of power - nice profile of the League's leader by @JamesPoliti https://t.co/9GR6k6rYJR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @podknife: On @podknife now: FT Big Picture - Stay on top of fundamental changes taking place around us in the early 21st century w/ hos…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ingram Pinn's illustration of the week: bursting Bolton's bubble https://t.co/eVit8ggtt9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @McKinsey_MGI: Listen: @johnthornhillft — #Artificialintelligence, the new frontier https://t.co/zrneUzBO4r via @FT @RichardWaters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@martinwolf_ argues that intergenerational fairness is the wrong lens through which to look at the UK economy https://t.co/VUcpwBVjdX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Five Star MP accuses @FinancialTimes of causing an "offence to professional journalism" - on the FT's letters page https://t.co/wMu08mhigm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EdwardGLuce: “Even George W Bush showed some sensitivity for the Arab street. Mr Trump cares only about the Arab penthouse — particular…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to reading this https://t.co/ecIfS0Utm1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Catching up with Saturday's @lemondefr and I see they've devoted space to the semiotics of the Tory "power stance". https://t.co/q2XYatxK2p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You're denying minerality?" I loved this Gopnik piece on the winemaker Randall Grahm https://t.co/Y98OHAbpL0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peter_watts Wonderful record.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peter_watts Sounds great. Recently made belated acquaintance with Wobble's collaboration with Holger Czukay and Jaki Liebezeit https://t.co/PHKZSk1Hhl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great piece by @ChassNews on the 'cheminots' in her family https://t.co/tP7qN887j3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Episode 5 of FT Big Picture - @johnthornhillft: AI, the new frontier https://t.co/JTi9WBiKJt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GroomB: In an age of poisonous political dialogue, Tessa Jowell was a model for what can be achieved by human warmth and civility. My o…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnharris1969 @NewStatesman Super review.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@grimes_ce Picked these Japano-modal beauties at the Independent Label Fair today. https://t.co/Q5VysxwV0N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DebFriedell My pleasure. Wonderful (and maddening) piece.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This @DebFriedell piece on the Republican governor of Missouri is superb  https://t.co/n8MIB79QCg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great to have @alexandrascaggs moonlighting for @ftcomment from @FTAlphaville on incels &amp; 'redistribution of sex' https://t.co/aVaX68g1Ab]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staying on the 80s hip hop tip https://t.co/wbS1N69bDD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Old skool https://t.co/Xs32kjqMo3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah, mais non ... https://t.co/1vn1LniLPw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DuncanWeldon Mark Steyn was doing the "Eurabia" stuff in 2002-3.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alanbeattie Alan Biley, surely https://t.co/H6DVTEr1Pf:]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>