<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Yesterday was yesterday, focus on today

#quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Raise your words, not your voice. It is rain that grows flowers, not thunder."
#Quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't Promise when You are Happy,

Don't reply when You are Angry
&amp;
Don't Decide when You are Sad...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hard work doesn’t guarantee success, but improves its chances. – B. J. Gupta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't promise when you're happy. Don't reply when you're angry. Don't decide when you're sad. #Life #Tip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The problem is not the problem. The problem is your attitude about the problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never give up. Great things take time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Work hard in silence; let success make the noise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never let the things you want make you forget the things you have. #gratitude]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A leader is one who knows the way, goes the way and shows the way. – John Maxwell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Repetition does not transform a lie into a truth. – Franklin D. Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't waste your time with explanations: people only hear what they want to hear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Work hard in silence; let success make the noise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I choose a lazy person to do a hard
job. Because a lazy person will find an easy way to do it.
#Bill Gates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are essentially two things that make us wiser:

The books we read
and
The people we meet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happiness is in the heart, not in the circumstances. - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The important thing is to learn a lesson every time you lose." - John McEnroe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find someone who will change your life, not just your status.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listen to your enemy's speech...
Because your mistakes are well known by your enemies only.."
-shakespeare-]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cover your heart with sincerity just like you cover your body with clothes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winning is a must for success. – Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Believe in yourself and create your own destiny. Don't fear failure!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't need a lot of people who ready 2 cry when i die
I just only need a 1 parson who ready 2 die when i cry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes the person who tries to keep everyone happy is the most lonely person.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @UseFuL_Study: "Iғ Yoυ Cαɴ, Help Oтнerѕ; Iғ Yoυ Cαɴ'т Do Tнαт, Aт Leαѕт Do Noт Hαrм Tнeм.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not judge me by my successes, judge me by how many times I fell down and got back up again. – Nelson Mandela]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A negative mind will never give you a positive life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes the person who tries to keep everyone happy is the most lonely person.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s hard to beat a person who never gives up. – Babe Ruth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest weapon against stress is our ability to choose one thought over another.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The richest man is not he who has the most, but he who needs the least.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let your smile change the world but never let the world change your smile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do small things with great love.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone you meet has something to teach you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[-
Q527: Education Is The Most Powerful Weapon Which You Can Use To Change The World.
+
#Nelson Mandela]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'll never find the RIGHT person if you never let go of the WRONG one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't be afraid to give up the good and go for the great.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is only one rule for being a good talker -- learn to listen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Only_NTS: How Many Hockey World Cup Won Pakistan?
A. 4
B. 5
C. 2
D. 3
Answer Is   A - 4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mistakes are proof that you're trying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The problem is not the problem. The problem is your attitude about the problem.
#Quote #Quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The richest man is not he who has the most, but he who needs the least.
#Quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good things come to those who wait. But better things come to those who work for it.
#quoteoftheday  #quotestoliveby  #aqwal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[-
"We learn by doing." - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[-
Don't look back - you're not going that way.
#Quote #Aqwal #Quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[-
Never get so busy making a living that you forget to make a life.
#Quotes
#Quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Count your blessings, not your problems.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone you meet has something to teach you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You cannot find peace by avoiding life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Use your eyes to see the needs, and use your talents to meet them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most of the richest people in the world do not have higher education. They have the ability to think independently :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your child will follow your example, not your advice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[-
Everyone you meet has something to teach you.
-
#Facts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life does not have to be perfect to be wonderful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smiling is the best way to face any problem, to crush every fear and to hide every pain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only you can change your life. No one can do it for you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Raise your words, not your voice. It is rain that grows flowers, not thunder.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If we do not plant knowledge when young, it will give us no shade when we are old." - Lord Chesterfield]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you do something out of love, you don't count the cost.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fall seven times, stand up eight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stars can't shine without darkness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every minute you are angry you lose 60 seconds of happiness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The happiness of your life depends upon the quality of your thoughts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone will be famous for 15 minutes. – Andy Warhol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is only one rule for being a good talker -- learn to listen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I walk slowly, but I never walk backwards.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/ZWoVC2r5TI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't be afraid to make mistakes, learn from them and become great

#quote #quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hardwork beats talent when talent doesn't work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stay positive. Good things will happen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[-
Old habits won't open new doors. Create new habits if you want to see new results.
#Quote #quotes  #quotesforlife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good Start is Half Done.

#quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[-
Difficult things take a long time, impossible things a little longer.

#quote #quotes #quotesforlife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fake friends are easy to find and easy to lose but real friends are the hardest to find and hardest to lose.

#quotes  #FriendQuote  #loyal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“A poem begins in delight and ends in wisdom.” Robert Frost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One small positive thought in the morning can change your whole day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“A thing of beauty is a joy forever.” John Keats

#Quotes #Quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[-
Love all, trust a few, do wrong to none.

Shakespeare
#quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“You’re never a loser until you quit trying.” – Mike Ditka #sports #quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[-
A Day without a Laughter is a day Wasted.
#Life #Love #Quotes #Quote https://t.co/SujgQ5jux2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[-
The future holds wonders for those who work hard.
#Quote #Quotes #HardwWork #Life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Life is one time offer, do it #WELL.

#Life #Quote #QuotesForLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[-
"Love has reasons which reason cannot understand." Blaise Pascal
#Quote #CulturesWays #Pakistan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[-
Intelligence without ambition is a bird without wings.
#quote #quotes #quoteoftheday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[-
Without the dark, we'd never see the stars.
#quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[-
Failure is not fatal, but failure to change might be...

#quote
#quotes
#QuotesForLife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great minds discuss ideas; average minds discuss events; small minds discuss people.
#quotes
#quotesandsayings 
#quotestoliveby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The richest man is not he who has the most, but he who needs the least.
#rich
#quote 
#quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Knowledge speaks, but wisdom listens."

#knowledge 
#wisdom 
#quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't hate what you don't understand.

#quote 
#quoteoftheday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We don't see things as they are, we see them as we are." - Anais Nin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember, the greatest failure is not to try.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weak people revenge. Strong people forgive. Intelligent people ignore.
#Albert #Einstein #Quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[-
“Intelligence without ambition is a bird without wings.”

#Quote #Quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[-
Success doesn't come to you; you go to it.

#Quote #quotes #quotesforlife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[-
Hard times teach us valuable lessons.

#quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More than 90% of people are no longer friends with someone that they once called their best friend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[-
True friends never count things they count memories.

#Quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[-
Don't hate what you don't understand.

#Quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[-
Never give up. Great things take time.

#Quote]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>