<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Why spend ur time trying to be someone else in order to get his attention? If he doesn't like u for who u are, he's not worth ur time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes we just have to SMILE. Not because we're HAPPY, but because we need to find an escape from the PAIN we're in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There will always be those days when the sky just isn't blue enough or when the clouds are too gray. Not everyday is gonna be happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you have choices, choose the best. If you have no choice, do the best.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you really love someone, I believe that there is nothing in the world that you can not overcome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't feel sad over someone who gave up on you, feel sorry for them because they gave up on someone who would have never given up on them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A friend is one of the nicest things you can have, and one of the best things you can be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let go of those who bring you down and surround yourself with those who bring out the best in you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We can only live in TODAY: eat, love, pray, work, relax, and above all enjoy today. (´▽`)/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes there are many things that will make u give up on ur way on achieving ur dreams, but u gotta keep focus n never give up hope.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear God.. Thanks for this beautiful life and forgive me if I don't love it enough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They ask me what I see in you and I smile, look down, and say nothing because I don't want them to fall in love with you too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter how good of a person you are, there will always be someone criticizing you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Long distance relationships will only work if you both trust one another and love one another. It won't be easy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If they took you for granted, let them go, walk away and find someone better, someone you deserve, someone who treats you right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's amazing what prayer can do. It comforts you, makes you feel whole inside, and gives you hope.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one will make a lock without a key. Similarly, God won't give problems without solutions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God made you, then He made me, and then He whispered... "Meant to be".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To the world you could be one person, but to one person you could mean the world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't count how many new friends you can make. Count how many old ones you can keep.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mencintai bukanlah tentang memberikan yang terbaik dalam segala kelebihan, tetapi memberikan yang terbaik meski dalam kekurangan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't be with someone because it's easy. Be with someone because you love them, even if it's difficult.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't find a reason why I like you, I just do. I can't find a reason why you should like me, it's up to you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#note2boys A girl is in love with you when she realizes she's willing to do things for you she wouldn't do for anyone else.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving God when everything is easy, that's great. Still loving Him when nothing is easy, that's faith.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the best feelings ever in the world is when you're hugging someone you love really tight and he hugs you back even tighter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The ultimate lesson all of us have to learn is unconditional love, which includes not only others but ourselves as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A love like ours isn't common. We treat each other with respect and we remain loyal because we only want to be with each other.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I'm down, I remember that there is someone who will ALWAYS love me, and that is God.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love you, I love you, I love you. Even if I say it a thousand times, it's not enough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am not a mind reader, but I can feel it when you are lying to me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear God, thank you for all my blessings, my wonderful family, my healthy life, and thank you for what You have in store for my future.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Missing someone is a part of loving them. If you're never apart, you'll never really know how strong your love is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes God pushes us to our limits, it's because He has greater faith in us than we have in ourselves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love you because you're the only one who fought for me and made me believe that I was worth it. Thank you for that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GOD, MOM, DAD = People who will always support and love you no matter what.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do you choose to be sad when you can be happy? Remember, it's not what happens to you that matters, it's how you take it. Be positive!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A smile on your face is the best thing to see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A person who truly loves you, will never let you go, no matter how hard the situation is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A real boyfriend: Calls you for nothing, texts you all the time, wants to see you, cries, gets jealous, overprotective, and loves you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Each time I miss u, a star falls down from the sky. So if u look up and find it dark, it is all ur fault. U made me miss u too much!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True love is about being with the person that makes you happy in a way that nobody else can.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tall boy + Short Girl = Cute couple ^^]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You should know that you are the only one who makes me laugh when I don't even want to smile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys who kiss girls on the forehead are the sweetest and the most gentleman you can ever have.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God always has His best way for us, but sometimes we're too stubborn, we just want our own ways.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The past is where you learned the lesson. The future is where you apply the lesson. So don't give up in the middle, which is the present.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When some things go wrong, take a moment to be thankful for the things that still going right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes the person who made you stronger, is also your greatest weakness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes no girl believes she's truly beautiful until one guys comes along and make her feel like she is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once you find laughter, no matter how painful your situation might be, you can survive it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Girls always find things out, they might not say anything right away, but they know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Girls want a guy who say I love you every night and proves it every day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need someone who won't give up on me, no matter how many times I mess up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Self confidence is the most attractive quality a person can have. How can anyone see how awesome you are if you can't see it yourself?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The happiest couples never have the same character. They just have the best understanding of their differences.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't care how we met, I'm just happy we did.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You control your actions, God controls the results. Always put your best effort forward and God will reward you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter who you are or what problems you face in your life, your life is worth living, not just surviving.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one can ever understand love. It has its own reasons, its own answer, its own explanations. Maybe it was never meant to be understood.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't need a perfect person, I just need someone that can make me happy and complete my life perfectly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God knows who belongs in your life and who doesn't. Trust and let go. Whoever is meant to be there, will still be there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't lead someone on. If you like someone, then tell them. If you just want to be friends, then don't make them think they have a chance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When yesterday is a disappointment &amp; today isn't better.. Remember there's always a tomorrow, make it something to look forward to. Smile!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't force anyone to love you, but you can show them what they're missing out on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're always special and precious. Don't let anyone say you're not, because you are always precious in God's eyes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are over 7 billion people in this world. Don't let a single person to make you cry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes I wish I had never met you because then I could go to bed at night not knowing there was someone like you out there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DESTINY... it's when both are brought to the right place, at the same time, and for a perfect reason. That's Love!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In this world that full of peoples, why should we meet and fall in love with each other? Don't you think it is destiny?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Confusing shows up, when your head doesn't wanna know what your heart says.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apapun yang akan kamu lakukan, sertakan Tuhan dalam hatimu. Karena Tuhan selalu ada di sisimu, ketika tak seorang pun ada untukmu.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes your heart sees what’s invisible to the eye.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't say "Why, God?" when He takes something from ur life, if u never say "Thank God" when He gives everything in ur life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People say it's better to hear the truth than to hear lies. But once they know the truth, they wish they never knew. Funny.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tak perlu kesempurnaan untuk bisa berbahagia. Karena bahagia sesungguhnya adalah ketika kamu melihat apapun secara sempurna.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's easy to say "Have Faith" when you're fine. But when you're having a bunch of problems, you can't even can encourage yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you are brave enough to love, then you are strong enough to let go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I make mistakes, I know I'm not perfect. That's why I'm thankful for the true friends who stick by me knowing how I am.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most touching line said by a best friend: "When I die, don't come near my body, because my hand may not be able to wipe your tears anymore."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My prince doesn't ride on white horse. He isn't tall, dark, and handsome, but he is the best thing that has ever happened to me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember the good times, be strong during the difficult times, love always, laugh often, and thank God every day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's easy to get discouraged and give up, but God wants us to be so full of hope that we just can't help but believe for the best.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smile. It will make him so jealous to see you're happy without him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are loved for the way you are. Don't try to be different.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you love someone, showing them is better than just telling. If you don't love them anymore, telling is better than showing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love... What is love? Love is to love someone for who they are, who they were, and who they will be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I truly respect the people who stay strong, even when they have every right to break down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are many things in this world you may run out of, but God's love is not one of them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's hard to explain something to a person who doesn't want to understand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you truly want to be with a person, listen to your heart and not all the voices from all the people around you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If God gives me one more chance to love/forget you, I will choose to forget you, because once I love you, I can't forget you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the bravest things ever are teardrops. Wanna know why? Cause tears are not afraid to fall even for the wrong reason.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one comes with a "clear history" button, so you have to accept their past.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making someone smile is probably one of the best feelings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some days you don't need words of wisdom or inspiration. Some days you just know you have to do what you have to do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't complain and ask why it happened to you; just get over it and do your best to make sure it doesn't happen to you again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life may not always be as good as it should be, but it's never as bad as it could be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best things in life aren't material "things", they're moments, feelings, lessons, faith, emotions, discoveries, and truths.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being hurt is something you can't stop from happening, but being miserable is always your choice.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>