<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Jill Stein Has Raised More Than $1.5 Million To Fund Recounts In 3 States https://t.co/XnPqJ7v4fM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's Why Trump Probably Won't Be Able To Repeal Common Core Nationally https://t.co/8ornBumyF3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Florida Supreme Court Signals Possible Upheaval For State's Death Row https://t.co/b3hrmdFq4i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[19 Photos Show What Life Is Like In Newly-Red Michigan https://t.co/VNQH8pl4xL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ben Carson Signals He'll Be Named Housing And Urban Development Secretary https://t.co/BUG8ASMZgc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Acknowledges, Disavows White Nationalist Alt-Right Movement https://t.co/wdNimypVUH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alabama Probably Won't Be Trying A Never-Before-Used Single-Drug Lethal Injection https://t.co/u1ALlitwgB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conservative Lawyers Take Up The Unexpected Opportunity Of Trump's Win https://t.co/8swNMjY9t1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You Are Amazing!" Donald Trump Wrote To Harry Reid In 2010 https://t.co/CIKB940k9l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After Trump Win, The Alt-Right Prepares For An Unexpected Future https://t.co/MQK7U7jf43]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Non-Muslims Are Saying They Would Add Their Names To A Muslim Registry In Solidarity https://t.co/mlKMapMMLt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ivanka Trump, Expected To Run Father's Business, Also Met With Japanese Prime Minister https://t.co/xLby3W9Z6A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House: We Don't Have The Authority To Pardon DREAMers https://t.co/SSYLSswV7r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FBI Director Of National Intelligence Jim Clapper Resigns https://t.co/sSscTEfOTj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anti-Trump Protesters Post Personal Information Of Electoral College Members https://t.co/iaW5bD0RVf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bernie Sanders Is Demanding Trump Fire "Racist" Steve Bannon https://t.co/I92Eygpwsn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Georgia Set To Execute Man For Killing His Ex-Girlfriend https://t.co/cIWuKNC30e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Black And Latino Democrats: It’s Time For New Leadership https://t.co/WlfxJVjPwD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats Focus On Their Trouble With White, Working-Class Voters https://t.co/q6DhPAZv8m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harry Reid Blames Trump For Climate Of Fear And Racism https://t.co/ACF9TZVAxi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Steve Bannon Who? Washington Republicans Say They "Don't Know" Trump Strategist https://t.co/c6D7K6jnJI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Picks Reince Priebus As Chief Of Staff, Steve Bannon As Chief Strategist https://t.co/HjfV9zZcEr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With Faith In Omarosa, Black Republicans Gear For Place In 'Most Diverse' White House https://t.co/NsKlfRpfIr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reports: Clinton Places Some Of The Blame For Her Loss On FBI Director Comey https://t.co/wKUieoG6Zf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chimamanda Adichie Brilliantly Shut Down A Man Who Said Trump Isn’t Racist https://t.co/Eo0dJ3wEDj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women Are Going To March On Washington The Day After Trump Takes Office https://t.co/kgBKXk4Ci2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Calls Clinton "Very Strong And Very Smart" In "60 Minutes" Interview https://t.co/YivfSNPKeQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Despite Promises, Trump May Not Repeal Obamacare After All https://t.co/rNvfdt1637]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's Revenge https://t.co/jDMqO2Gb06]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harry Reid: Trump’s Election “Emboldened The Forces Of Hate And Bigotry In America” https://t.co/qH6v3fL8Ys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Latinos Say Kids Are Already Being Bullied At School In The Two Days Since Trump Won https://t.co/Mear9W80Q0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Carrasquillo: Immigration activists have been plunged into uncertainty, but the first priority is trying to somehow save DACA https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Carrasquillo: Latino leaders are resigned to working with President Trump in the name of a fearful and anxious community. https://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Undocumented Immigrants Fear Mass Deportation Under President Trump https://t.co/qsZsA4thzU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former GOP Rep. Aaron Schock Indicted On Spending Allegations https://t.co/MJHqfSJD1P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alabama Offers To Execute Inmate With Never-Before-Used, Single-Drug Injection https://t.co/FecIvDbc7H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democratic Congressman: "It's Not A Race Issue. It's A Class Issue." https://t.co/UBE9dRXclO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Donald Trump Could Revitalize The Death Penalty https://t.co/9Y1Stso13H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These Latino Voters Explain Why They Voted For Trump https://t.co/uyXXrcH5pK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Secretary Of Education Ben Carson? Here's A List Of Potential Trump Cabinet Picks https://t.co/o43qxz2Dyd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After Trump Election, Immigrants Fret Over Deportation Protections https://t.co/GNR1Nhp0TM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Election Changed The Politics Of The Supreme Court https://t.co/yDAAeYYiSF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instead Of Voting To Abolish The Death Penalty, Californians Decide To Speed It Up https://t.co/vICrxdNW1B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Leads A Global Nationalist Wave https://t.co/njamMdXbl5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People Are Fuming Trump Won The Election, Declaring “He’s Not My President” https://t.co/COzRom0doD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Middle America Trump Supporters: This Is Our Night https://t.co/sg4z4G6nTd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Wins https://t.co/9vDk9stpuR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People With Disabilities Are Expressing Disbelief That Trump Might Be President https://t.co/1SYiAVrO9U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Faced With A Trump Presidency, Could A State Actually Secede? https://t.co/dXYLGRrB32]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republicans Hold On To Their Senate Majority https://t.co/qG7kjE0nLH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nebraska Votes To Bring Back The Death Penalty https://t.co/fHRPHI5pRa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fox Anchors Were So Bored On Election Day They Spent A Minute Talking About Chapstick https://t.co/aj8O4LW9P0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Decision Desk HQ Results Map https://t.co/ig1SE7calF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People Are Sharing This Video Of A Broken Voting Machine Which Is Already Fixed https://t.co/0MLJv156KL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Campaign Alleges Late Voters Allowed Into Nevada Early Vote Lines https://t.co/4jx08QIg4i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Peeked At Melania's Ballot And People Think It's Hilarious https://t.co/kRN5seLf9S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clinton Ends With A Marathon Sprint And A Sense “Of Joy” https://t.co/Iv4OmbtbYj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Sagebrush Candidate: McMullin Wants The Feds Out Of The West https://t.co/tH1StVuq0h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In North Carolina, A Final Effort To Turn Out Black Voters https://t.co/K2YRn3iQIW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Two Days, The Politics Of The Supreme Court Will Change https://t.co/xQfntkKYEg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[43 Iconic Pictures From The 2016 US Presidential Election https://t.co/a1J4mmLWCB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Black Republicans Are Planning To Be At Trump Tower If He Wins https://t.co/y4mQq5zzi7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Choice In Clinton’s Last Ad: “Dark And Divisive,” Or “Hopeful And Inclusive”? https://t.co/2v4rh9foSu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[15 Revealing Stories About Donald Trump, His Businesseses, And His Movement https://t.co/yDICpKnfF9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[15 Crucial Stories About Hillary Clinton And Her Campaign https://t.co/UyASTJKLBO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many Minnesotans Are Angry At Trump Saying Their State Suffered Because Of Somali Refugees https://t.co/55jXuRL80U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First Woman Attorney General Janet Reno Dies At Age 78 https://t.co/S8TGv7lnyn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Final Trump Campaign Ad Criticized As Having Anti-Semitic Tones https://t.co/7gqmNQ7QMu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[14 Crucial Stories About The Latino Vote In 2016 https://t.co/2jeTprlnId]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Appeals Court: No New Anti-Voter Intimidation Rules In Place In Ohio For This Election https://t.co/2zTqgi8VAh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge Denies Dems' Request To Hold RNC In Contempt For Trump Voter Fraud Efforts https://t.co/eOceDvokfn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ZekeJMiller: Good time to re-up this @rubycramer piece: USSS Agents Protecting Candidates Aren’t Getting Paid For All Their Work
https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beyoncé And Jay Z Campaign Where Some People Just Don't Think Voting Matters https://t.co/qFTIoSFQvv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @samarkaukab: Follow @chrisgeidner for the min to min latest on election litigation taking place this weekend. Per usual, such on point…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supreme Court Attempts To Slow Flood Of Last-Minute Election Litigation https://t.co/zDkz9hGcst]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Win Or Lose, Trump Supporters Say They've Been Transformed https://t.co/XaUMvvaosE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama Chides Clinton Crowd For Booing Trump Supporter: "Hold Up! Hold Up!" https://t.co/Yzy8Bjwjvk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democratic Electoral College Voter Says He Won't Cast Ballot For Clinton https://t.co/CM8JL2JCEg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federal Court Backs Protections For Gay Worker Under Existing Law https://t.co/G9BxKqhRT8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rulings In Three Election-Related Challenges Favor Democrats In Key States https://t.co/6R6Bw0unim]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Planned Parenthood, Gloria Steinem, And Harry Belafonte Join Women's March On Washington Leadership https://t.co/KjaeFkk1bL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carl Paladino Makes Racist Comments Targeting President And First Lady In 2017 “Wishlist" https://t.co/wBa4uRb1eb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @alexis_levinson: Drama inside the effort to get Ben Carson ready to be HUD Secretary, per @darrensands https://t.co/BGrtETAmyc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Internal Politics Already An Issue In Ben Carson’s Confirmation Prep https://t.co/dNCsXwKjMt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Merrick Garland Will Be On The Bench — But Not The Supreme Court — In January https://t.co/O9sAA20Cdc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Anti-Trump Electoral College Effort Is Only The Beginning https://t.co/LgeXqtfz4L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's One Guy Who Is Taking The Electoral College Fight Seriously https://t.co/SnsFNjEGVM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Pizzagate” Suspect Pleads Not Guilty To Gun Charges https://t.co/P2ATGvGD1O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Transgender Student Can Continue To Use Girls' Bathroom, Federal Appeals Court Rules https://t.co/ogfU8q8eCe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democratic Group, Clinton Aides Team Up To Sink Trump Nominees https://t.co/e75PEW2lXO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will My Brother's Keeper Continue In The Trump Administration? https://t.co/G8sNiP8jEx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delaware's Current Death Row Inmates Will Now Get Life Sentences, State High Court Rules https://t.co/XNudAAxYS2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clinton Staffer Enters The Race For DNC Vice Chair https://t.co/zNkWaIo9ft]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harry Reid Says Electors Should Have Intelligence Briefing https://t.co/YL08SI4bGy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federal Judge Criticizes Death Penalty — But Concludes Only Supreme Court Can End It https://t.co/l90RX7rLkr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top Candidates For DNC Chair Pitched CBC For Their Support https://t.co/PtKzGRLEwL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's Secretary Of State Nominee Already Has Republican Opposition https://t.co/Tp1CPtF1qc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Election Recount Is Over And Trump Is Still Going To Be President https://t.co/RNa7nUa9M6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clinton Campaign Backs Electors' Request For Intelligence Briefing On Russia's Influencing Election https://t.co/0PaliK1ezi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Bolton Says Election Hacking Could Have Been A "False Flag" https://t.co/cxJST8xXQT]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>