<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't think I'd be up for that going away for Christmas business it's all about being at home with all the family for me ðŸŽ…ðŸ½]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/1RFdgkZEue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gaymore11 hahahahah just when you think this couldn't get any better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ be disappointed in this fella if he didn't say  "what you on about you dope that's me cousins house" https://t.co/vl6hSDLUfV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GannonAaron ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ have a good pic for you here mate check your dm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give the city players a break can't be easy for them to go out and try play a match after the devastating news about Gundogan #RIPGundogan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunday getting spent watching the chicken connoisseur videos ðŸ‘ŒðŸ½]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 people followed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/1RFdgkZEue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fucking cringey bastard https://t.co/qZQ52YhDTn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some reception from crowd fuck me #Bellator169 https://t.co/EoLtusUqdI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@calgreen123 you are a legend bro appreciate that x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KerrWils0n: fucking sick of it. get rid of it. https://t.co/dlSOQHYMDW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People have a few thousands followers on Insta and think they're successful ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ Instagram ruined Dublin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rowemance96 @KirstyTaaffe oh my god ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/1RFdgkZEue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DylanCoombes11 they don't exist anymore bro every man for himself these days]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ffs_OMG @SeanyLawson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No messing around with the arctic stone ice cream out in dundrum ðŸ˜³ðŸ‘ŒðŸ½]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DylanCoombes11 @PhillyG_ Ronnie from jersey shore he's like https://t.co/zmAw0volLl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanyLawson pigeons getting swallowed ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ see at the end there the monkeys pulling the pigs tails ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanyLawson fuming when they start showing pigeons, waited all week to see a leopard eat a kid and he's showing me pigeons ðŸ™‰]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 people followed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/1RFdgkZEue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GannonAaron the lads not happy your man tried to charge them into the mosque ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Didn't know they had a south circular road in Bradford https://t.co/9RM853Z7Yb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatieTaylor @LaurenSlattery7 congrats]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Lar11_ Cuala/Ballyea final im telling you Cuala gona do it ðŸ˜‚ but sure look we'll just have to wait and see]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do people go the gym on a Sunday I can hardly get off the sofa here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Lar11_ very true like they did Leinster final last year but Con O'Callaghan big difference this year for them!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wanyama should of got a yellow card for how bad that header was]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Lar11_ wouldn't know about the football but think it's a step too far for ballyea they done well to win Munster]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Lar11_ would of said varley myself tbh! Vincent's/Cuala double for the all Ireland?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Lar11_ I didn't see the first half did he deserve MOTM? Cause at one stage I thought he was after going off in the second]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Lar11_ some things he does deserves the applause, but can't take it when he does basic things and all the 'experts' on here lose it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Lar11_ absolute wankfest on that page every time he plays ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing worse than playing bad in a match feel like just going to bed ðŸ˜´]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one person followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/1RFdgkZEue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanyLawson @ROUNDTHEBEND__ ahahahahahahahaha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@samcaswell33 ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ sorry bro that pic was too good not to post]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When your out with the boys and remember your ma told you to take the chicken out of the freezer 2 hours ago https://t.co/Rnykc1p1XM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Major craving for a big load of pancakes ðŸ˜©]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AaronMateAaron @GannonAaron @SeanyLawson @adammcnamara34 @louisefl8 ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jamie__Dunne ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ the people on here don't know that ðŸ¤‘]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/1RFdgkZEue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeighG_97 @PhillyG_ "hot dust" fucking cracker ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's 2016 and people are still sharing this shite thinking there gona win a voucher fucking hell https://t.co/FWLaSeNLr0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every morning ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/Rzb7X7bsWg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine being one of them blokes that just doesn't stop texting a bird when they get the seen hahahaha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanyLawson @LFCFansCorner @vine ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 people unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/1RFdgkI35E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanyLawson @PhillyG_ click on the link https://t.co/n5mn2UCdZc for 10% off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KirstyTaaffe absolute scenes in the Carlisle ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big culchies in the gym drinking protein shakes from Volvic bottles would wanna take a day off ðŸ˜·]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 people followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/1RFdgkZEue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EvoFields20 can't believe I'm seeing horse racing "fans" say this wasn't blatant fella sits back down inal ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeeColeman3 @DylanCoombes11 you'll like this one x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/En1FWX8vvo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 people followed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/1RFdgkZEue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhillyG_ don't get this bro only one black lad on the team ðŸ¤”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Jeremy Kyle is next level stuff cannot believe what I'm seeing here ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@taylynskey unreal isn't she ðŸ‘ŒðŸ½ solid 10]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jamie__Dunne how can you even argue this one]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rowemance96 @DylanCoombes11 any time someone rings the doorbell all you hear is Martin Tyler "Pogbaaaaaaa"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine the amount of people that would of said jake hall would never get anyone better than Chloe Lewis. Alright https://t.co/R4dhnrPwcn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DylanCoombes11 @Rowemance96 has 38 Old Trafford outside his door fact]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone won't be getting a game this year after letting this pic out ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/Mgw7A0m1Bm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GannonAaron ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ make you run faster with them chasing ye ðŸƒðŸ½]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pretending it's summer this morning in the pheno ðŸƒðŸ½ðŸƒðŸ½ðŸƒðŸ½ https://t.co/0Ueneu57AW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanyLawson @Owen85Weston2 @_Lar11_ @GZambra_92 @Paul_Wilson16 ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ #JustJewIt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gaymore11 couldn't agree more, wish he was on this to give him serious abuse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RoyHughess ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ only buzzing bro I'll be starting soon give you a shout during the week]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RoyHughess one week in and he can't hack it ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ali_leech thanks very much ðŸ˜†]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can you deactivate Instagram or do you just have to delete it does anyone know?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jamie__Dunne always said he was my favourite baseball player bro #Baller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adamryanboom some people thinking into it too much ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 people followed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/1RFdgkZEue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Owen85Weston2 @SeanyLawson never forget ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SeanyLawson "the reason you come out crying is because your remember everything from your past life" ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people wanna give their heads a shake ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/iSrlZ7giJ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How good is Harry winks for spurs like a young Scott Parker. Baller ðŸ‘ŒðŸ½]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Absolutely no need for them blokes rocking around the jacuzzi in the gym in them little poxy speedos ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheNotoriousMMA: Brick top https://t.co/woaVXuTwLR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing better than a good 13 hour shift on a Saturday ðŸ‘ŒðŸ½ðŸ‘ŒðŸ½ðŸ‘ŒðŸ½]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the best on the album ðŸ‘ðŸ½ https://t.co/sh3URnKmWy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What sort of wifi you got up there mate https://t.co/eIn3wEW33Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DeniseRyan3 @PhillyG_ @BobCourtney3 this isn't the first time he's been told Denise don't worry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DeniseRyan3 @PhillyG_ @BobCourtney3 will you's go somewhere nice please so Philly can propose and we can have a stags thanks ðŸ‘ŒðŸ½ðŸ˜†]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know everyone's going on about being sick but me nose is blocked about 2 weeks now fucking joke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ROUNDTHEBEND__  @SeanyLawson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 people followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/1RFdgkZEue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ https://t.co/06dMZgqywq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GannonAaron no I didn't bud the place would fall apart without me ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itsDanielle_x3 ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ‘ðŸ½ðŸ‘ðŸ½ hook me up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New job needed big time ðŸ˜´]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PhillyG_ when's it out lad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dallas buyers club on tg4 ðŸ‘ŒðŸ½ and no it's not in Irish you's mongos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Done for about 6 months after the last few weeks was good while it lasted ðŸ˜´ https://t.co/rHcDCwDGVH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feeling rough today can the hurling season just start back already so I can't go out anymore ðŸ˜´]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 people followed me and one person unfollowed me // automatically checked by https://t.co/1RFdgkZEue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Iamcalledjacob: How can buses charge so much money? Mate you're driving that way anyway give us a lift]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>