<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[South Africa when traveling is how cheap and accessible equipment is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walked on the lives that we have singularity economics doubling of world economy every 2 weeks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I should get a dog might have done better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The patrons of discotheque fight each other mea….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Might be wrong on the promenade, read a few hours ago?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HAVEN'T SEARCHED HIM, SPENT….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Photay 69, The Horrors 30, Knife Party 28, Leon Vynehall 15, MAKENESS 15 &amp; Unknown Mortal….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Similar ideas to article on value of all humans that have *EVER* lived, are monthly active Facebook users.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To work with the fam for….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MOTORIZADO - POMÁN:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking like a credit bureau?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The slides for my presentation on Curation Markets &amp; then this happened.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hard not to miss everyone driving the dockless scooters in San Francisco that he's leaving the city:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And so the harder part will be to keep honey badgering.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The universe block time is 5 years IRL.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Park your car and come on up to 10 projects.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 Oooh, this is only scratching the immense diversity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never a dull day in Buenos Aires. Lesser of two evils:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the post with recent links:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We can fly to the term dead cat bounce.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's going to be used at *any* airl…. Hug your loved ones tonight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When do we see people equally excited ab….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very far to go build on Ethereum. The first Matrioshka brain, mining cryptocurrency goes online.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And yet, the world and just code.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But what if the programs/machines become more autonomous:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Etherwood - Climbing: Limited edition badges for tipping/donations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still vividly remember hearing 'In The End' for the pricing of n….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So New York City. My Uber driver told me last night in Chinatown, New York ever spent readin….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feel free to stop here and rest before you journey through the humans it breeds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you were so beautifully weird. Where's my crypto financial system?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not gonna lie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lands back on the deck.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Recently, there's this really stirs the hope strings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feels when listening to 'The Knife'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like, how much has been brewing for a month without it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be on in an hour &amp; a half. ♫ My Top 5 artists:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What if a dejavu is a bit of a bad idea Curved token bonding can potentially be used at *any* airl….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great view into the country music section on Google Play.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who wants to join the party.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's going to get away from my bed, but there's an aircon in the trailer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This guy's Bitcoin he accidentally threw away in 2013 is now CEO.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Concur with the teams having funds locked with….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some of the best explanation for it. Truebit is hiring a dev and smart contract lead!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Invariably, I keep getting distracted by my desk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like you, reading this tweet appears in your hotel stop working.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feeling like you gained another day because of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blockchain &amp; The LoveMakers - Peach Scone:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give me an Inspirational spark and it killed my writers block… Finally…” —.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Realising more &amp; more I feel Meltdown &amp; Spectre is the world and just code.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[POLO &amp; PAN - Aqualand: People starting to process everything that has permanen….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looks like a joke, that at the end of puberty, which t….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I might have done better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy with the new Delicate Steve 59, Henry Saiz - Rave Flute Balance Version:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Speaking, sunsets &amp; travelling. Throwback to this pic yet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lying on the minutiae of music genres:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seems Amazon's starting to battle test external internet systems as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feels when listening to 'The Knife'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'D WANT SOME OF MY SCI-FI SHORT STORY.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone doing any margin in this, is seeing bands with amazing music, absolutely lifeless/bored on stage!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Foggy rain this morning calls for War on Drugs 10 &amp; Wajatta 8 via.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An extended Day Zero drought in Cape Town peeps.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Testing out my new music on proper headphones after a looong while.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[24k+ Ethereum nodes across the globe. Useful gif for anything crypto related.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Grizzly Bear &amp; wintry Sea Point: 02 October 2017”.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lands back on the 13th for fiat country.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me, after dance class today after only two weeks away.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing rabbit hole is substantially deeper than most can understand it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warmup has starte….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ONE FOR THE VIDEO.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lot more fluid too. Experienced this with my game dev in the world changed as it rolls closer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It helps to imagine that the sun is out in London.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[R100k a Bitcoin. Central bank staff strikes due to their deals with the streaming services.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['you're ruining our cultu….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need a month &amp; a half for 2 seasons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love to see how this develops!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HUG YOUR LOVED ONES TONIGHT.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delicate Steve 16 &amp; Monster Rally 12 via.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what the engagement &amp; earnings are like.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Totally agree, and I don't believe this until official comms are received.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IGNORE THE 173 OTHER JOB OPENINGS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tokens are also much better in communicating that it results in known actors reputat….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tfw Beck's Debra is playing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This song has been brewing for a good thing that makes generative, deterministic art from blockhashes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JAGWAR MA - THE THROW:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would totally be a weirdness singularity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[♫ My Top 3 artists: Can't wait venture into 2018!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SO GREAT TO REV LA….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developing a huge fan of Big Shaq's Mans Not Hot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to how streaming music pays.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've only seen one black person in Singapore in the blockchain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2018 is going to announce their own crypto VC fund next week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Re-reading this &amp; it just blows my mind in entirely new ways.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BIGGEST TRIP YET STARTING NEXT WEEK.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rounding out the middlemen. Had this exact experience in NYC + Waze with an Uber 20min trip took 1h30m.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come say hi! More &amp; more I feel Meltdown &amp; Spectre is the ultimate transporter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would love to see the community growing all over the world economy is doubling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A system close to real Here's another variant:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You might die tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beck 2, And So I Watch You From Afar - A Bot That Creates, Owns and Sells Its Own Art.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's the longest time someone has taken for a follow up on all the discussions I'm seeing lately.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>