<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @markaci: "@CNDLND: update on #AmandaLang &amp; RBC http://t.co/Qs3oHyJY2c" Romantic rel'ship w/ RBC Board Member W. Geoffrey Beattie since …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good news for Canadian journalism. The good guys didn't back down from #RBC scandal or #amandalang the shill with her hand in the till.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amanda Lang, financial correspondent, paid to sabotage her colleagues in another CBC scandal. https://t.co/EWNEdih8EO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amanda Lang tried to sabotage a CBC story that scandalized RBC, who paid her http://t.co/Mkd6AoQbsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amanda Lange,  financial correspondent, caught in selling good news for cash in another CBC scandal. http://t.co/Mkd6AoQbsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of France braces for war against terrorism.

More than 3 million march in protest on Sunday in Paris and... http://t.co/ZOChcOTDSO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It will be hard for the Republicans to find a GOP candidate as good as Obama. http://t.co/Bavo2DuYYv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ArleneArgento A quip and a smile is your sword and shield.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The tale of La Demoiselle was first told as a favorite story among French fishermen, seeking new sources of fish... http://t.co/eNRrUSAynM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Blame for the Charlie Hebdo Murders http://t.co/VSEu10ljpi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The truth is the soul of wit. http://t.co/XVjyqFPty0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C'est vrai. Si triste. http://t.co/hQ54U4Atjd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RtKd7 C'est vrai.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RtKd7 Merci.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RtKd7: #JeSuisCharlie http://t.co/AzVnxtX7ow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RLOppenheimer @RtKd7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Ordinary people, Hollywood by Von Wong https://t.co/xcFngi2S2l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canadians are facing the darkest hour in the country's history.

Prime Minister Harper's Conservatives pledge to... http://t.co/nQ4eoCbrCo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rio de Janeiro is 450 years old this year. Looming challenges, but always puts on a brave face and a smile. http://t.co/VAzm5vjTaF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those Bat-shit crazy people in Colorado are at it again. Trying to regulate personal inquiry and deep reflection.... http://t.co/t4CNMLZKlw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyS_Thompson I go there often, without a dog on a leash.  You staying in Vancouver?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My grandfather Michael had a mining claim on Cheyenne Mountain. 12 tribes of native people shared these sacred... http://t.co/NewBeLLYbD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what progress looks like. 

Belo-Monte was created without public approval. Opponents have been murdered... http://t.co/uST8CaJSAz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama veto cripples right-wing oil barons and their lackey Prime Minister Harper. http://t.co/t3ydKyxUle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy cow! 1 in 4 Americans didn't know the earth orbits the sun. http://t.co/vKuNgyvw0i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/hZpXSIAMMq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have a friend who always smiles away a problem. Love is the answer. http://t.co/vP17dWpYTV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harper refuses to disclose secret police actions that will put Canadian citizens in prison http://t.co/7S4zOd3JTC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 ways Prime Minister Stephen Harper can put Canadian citizens in prison for protests http://t.co/XyzVRFOSzx via @pressprogress]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This lusty trio is guiding our sex appeal for the next six months. http://t.co/yKhgrwZY8Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mars and Venus now bring a vigorous energy to Aries &amp; Pisces. http://t.co/9vVfHceiqh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/E7Yth4Llt5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[George's verses give our decisive voices pause &amp; peace. "While My Guitar Gently Weeps" consoles now 44 years later. http://t.co/sWgZXuW2mS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/5PHp9QhUHY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My writing technique for creating space around creativity. "I interview myself” https://t.co/iWsNGMZJYP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing the power of music. http://t.co/SEooQIzs6D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Owls on a limb. http://t.co/UmHvT9bBVG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After several weeks of rain, it was crowded at the gym today. Taking exercise with the Canadian geese. http://t.co/bY3AvgCtFL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pubslush The same rules apply to books as before when using #crowdfunding. Films thought they could bend the rules and fail miserably.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A tragic musical about of wanting to be beautiful in America http://t.co/T5KuRrElHI via @nytvideo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just published “I interview myself” https://t.co/amCABEWNfJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/Yg5WtviEbI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The GOP at work. http://t.co/HoITea5yHV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Soon to be America. http://t.co/ftjo6cUG1L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Duke of Abruzzi biography is now available to readers on Kindle and iBooks this week, (Winter 2015).  http://t.co/Avdd83Im43]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Day in the life of Rio http://t.co/ISNlWZAEMi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My biography about the Duke of the Abruzzi is now available in Kindle and iBooks this week. http://t.co/Avdd83qLcv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This week my biography #theDukeoftheAbruzzi biography now available for #Kindle and #ibooks http://t.co/OFxk71ua1R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My biography about #theDukeoftheAbruzzi is out in #Kindle and #iBooks this week.Tale about the most famous adventurer of his generation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just published “The Life and Death of a Somalian Village” https://t.co/QA6qpOGanS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now available on Kindle and iBooks this week. http://t.co/pYXwtTtLVH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now available this week on Kindle  and iBooks, The Duke of the Abruzzi, Mountaineers Legends and Lore Series.... http://t.co/F4GqapaisQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Defection of Tory to Liberals a sign that Harper losing his grip@globeandmail http://t.co/f9Go7jYvPm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I grew up thinking all dames were like those in movies. Hardbitten, desperate, sulky and complicated. Imagine my... http://t.co/I5EMEGwct5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunrise on the Ganges. 1977. http://t.co/Q8PYExfeFM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Alma mater at the foot of the Flat Iron mountains, Boulder, Colorado. http://t.co/2bOFr7ZGtF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The ‘Give A Shit’ Life Lessons Manifesto — Love Madly Now. http://t.co/v4LpNSdbwJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I taught Maslow's theory for many years. I would add coffee. http://t.co/YftGPvhX3s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you abuse Novocaine? In Performance | ‘Everybody Gets Cake!’ http://t.co/4sYuS9qRhI via @nytvideo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MyDatingRx Not in my neighborhood. Guys are heading for the man cave. Something in the horoscope perhaps.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HARBORSmusic many influences and you are still fresh and original with room to grow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woman finds the perfect man. http://t.co/4JZb45w7u6 via @TheOnion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful Minds: Stephen Wiltshire: https://t.co/TkGmQiTAIY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maggietranquila Nice to meet you Maggie. You look very chill.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woman's Beautiful Lullaby To Her Sick Pig Will Make You Feel Better, Too http://t.co/bdRnMA651E via @HuffPostGreen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @wrong_kraut: There are tweets so intense, rich and full of meaning, they possess the power to change lives all around the globe. This i…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlicePoet Thank you, Alice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DeHarrisOnline Thanks, Digital Mom. I appreciate the follow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ElizabethMay  Canada will be going into Syria airstrikes with aging fighters because the F-35 is not fit to fly. Another Harper debacle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PM Harper's smear campaign against women now includes a member of Parliament via @globeandmail http://t.co/NuFxMU88Iw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only the Green Party standing up against PM Harper's bullying tactics@globeandmail http://t.co/NuFxMTQxjW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only the Green Party standing up against PM Harper's bullying tactics@globeandmail http://t.co/NuFxMU88Iw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MyDatingRx Good luck.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MyDatingRx Hang out with the mom and you get an even better stranger later on. A family with benefits.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GermanyKent I'm there, and you showed up, a positive voice. Law of attraction.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyS_Thompson  where to in states?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CatVescovi I think you are doing very well for a beginner. I love your photo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Americans are so in love with their guns explained by an Australian comedian who sums it up http://t.co/TGTfIjz5FJ via @amandataub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Married Vancouver mayor Gregor Robertson swept away by 25-year-old Chinese pop star Wanting Qu in karaoke love fest. http://t.co/9GRtHEqurw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada going to war in Syria with aging warplanes. Harper's F-35 debacle worsens as new fighter is grounded again. http://t.co/loE08WY15J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada going to war in Syria with aging fleet of warplanes, while the new F-35 is being grounded again. #ISIL http://t.co/loE08WY15J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyS_Thompson when? How can I reach you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@okchico807 thank you, I like!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JustinTrudeau @Elizabeth May once again Harper calls his mommie the #CPC so he doesn't have to take on that mean old bully May. .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vancouver mayor Gregor Robertson has been swept away by a 25-year-old Chinese pop star in love with the sound of her own music. #WantingQu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vancouver mayor Gregor Robertson, 50s, and his 25-year-old Chinese pop star girlfriend are making music together. http://t.co/2a5071bTEy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever at a loss to have something to say to a Brazilian ? http://t.co/UU3DNw3ewJ via @MatadorNetwork]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thomas Mulcair mobbed in Vancouver by thousands of adoring fans...the next Trudeau ! Mulcair Mania! http://t.co/v7d60z4Pb2 via @SyrupTrap]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Oliver takes on racist billionaires ripping off NCAA players in March Madness: https://t.co/dmuMGmWhBb via @YouTube #SOYBEANWIND]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CTV QP: No voice on terror http://t.co/Ae6DqgdBSL via @CTVNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just published “What’s Troubling About Rio’s Water?” https://t.co/ob62a1R8sY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just published “What’s Troubling About Rio’s Water?” https://t.co/mL7RXmFi2w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iran Offers to Mediate Talks Between Republicans and Obama - The New Yorker http://t.co/iUq9vYjKYJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iran Offers to Mediate Talks Between Republicans and Obama http://t.co/Is4rgp2HCR via @BorowitzReport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arriving In Rio! http://t.co/OBtqJ6N0wd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The last vestige of this magic city hold on as long as there is poetry, fog and City Lights. http://t.co/FAhogbFj9r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/NFo1mZBAM0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/PqLWdPiBek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 http://t.co/gDm5atSCb4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/8b6zXI0vs3]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>