<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I am the legal guardian over a massive shoe collection. - Linda Dominique Grosvenor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Choosing To Use Solar Power  http://t.co/6Om28XoWzz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bad habits are like chains that are too light to feel until they are too heavy to carry. - Warren Buffet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any pitcher who throws at a batter and deliberately tries to hit him is a communist. - Alvin Dark]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Learning Tool for Kids - Snap Circuits Jr - Hands On Learning All About Circuits http://t.co/9KWzbkfiZ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The groundwork of all happiness is health. - Leigh Hunt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is the key to unlock the golden door of freedom. - George Washington Carver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good pitching will beat good hitting any time, and vice versa. - Bob Veale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aerodynamics are for people who can't build engines. - Enzo Ferrari]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How To Find Best Supplies For Gardening  http://t.co/YQ84CeeKNM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love my crazy girlfriend - hilarious t-shirt - http://t.co/OKSQoTt1ff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get up to Speed on Baseball with this Summary of Baseball Positions  http://t.co/rcMd3vy2LN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame Turf Wars: Them Hackers Though  http://t.co/00UvfqiQNb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Genesis  http://t.co/Ibv2OlCjtO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great History of the Rolling Stones  http://t.co/HeExfy7CR8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poets are like baseball pitchers. Both have their moments. The intervals are the tough things. - Robert Frost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're either making money or you're not. If you're not making money get out of the business. Meredith Whitney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space or science fiction has become a dialect for our time. - Doris Lessing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Foxy  http://t.co/i4fhQs1OKP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The designated hitter rule is like letting someone else take Wilt Chamberlain's free throws. - Rick Wise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WOW - Very Cool A Sticky Note Wrist Watch! http://t.co/ny1id246fT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Coors Beer  http://t.co/XdqeVPQOZr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bring out your dead. - Monty Python and the Holy Grail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the top science fiction movies of all time!  http://t.co/EQrK5FMdKw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you have six dates with a man who never even tries to kiss you -- Lie about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these top auto insurance companies!  http://t.co/RnCrYtcfoy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Love Unlimited  http://t.co/xWZAmudSB5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball's future? Bigger and bigger, better and better! No question about it, it's the greatest game there is! - Ted Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was never interested in being a rock star. I always wanted to be Boris Karloff. - Gene Simmons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The truest test of moral courage is the ability to ignore an insult]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, I'm from Iowa. I only work in outer space. - Kirk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the Romans had been obliged to learn Latin, they would never have found time to conquer the world. - Heinrich Heine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The human body is the best work of art. --&gt; Jess C. Scott]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About The St. Augustine Alligator Farm – Zip Lines and Lots of Gators!  http://t.co/yy9xmxlICv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first and the best victory is to conquer self. - Plato]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Fitness Apps – Is There One That Is the Best?  http://t.co/5g4H1r7wJQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You cannot dream yourself into a character: you must hammer and forge yourself into one. - Henry D. Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet Stay Thirsty My Friends Dos Equis T-Shirt - Most Interesting Main In the World - http://t.co/osyb54qgV1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NERD?  I prefer the term intellectual Bad ASS!  http://t.co/TsqciB8fwu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The chains of habit are generally too small to be felt until they are too strong to be broken. - Samuel Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helpful Tips for Web Marketing  http://t.co/4Z3xB2UVf3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Famous Canadian Places to Visit  http://t.co/6DlU5RDxfk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to look young and thin, hang around old fat people. - Jim Eason]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the hot new Minecraft video channel Crimson Mine - http://t.co/og1UV1HfGt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instead of giving myself reasons why I can't, I give myself reasons why I can. - Unknown Author]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even on the most solemn occasions I got away without wearing socks and hid that lack of civilization in high boots --&gt; Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 2 - Road Trip!!!  http://t.co/TDRJbP6u4j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I didn't grow up thinking, 'Oh, maybe someday I'm going to have a shoe named after me.' -  Sheryl Swoopes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I raced a car last it was at a time when sex was safe and racing was dangerous. Now, it's the other way round. - Hans Stuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Grapevine, Texas  http://t.co/Mr2lzimvK3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love making money, but you can't live your life waiting to get rich in a job that no longer feeds you artistically. Julianna Margulies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So say we all. - Battlestar Galactica]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome gardening t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the gardening lovers in your life!   http://t.co/Vpbpl8LkfV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only place where success comes before work is in the dictionary. - Vidal Sassoon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Far Out and Super Cool Watches  http://t.co/1iJACEYXjH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here I Am T-Shirt What Are Your Other Two Wishes http://t.co/zDA5tqWj7q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need to tie some kerosene rags around his ankles so the ants don't eat his candy #$@ - Dale Earnhardt speaking of Mark Martin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give a girl the right shoes, and she can conquer the world. - Marilyn Monroe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the shoe fits... buy it in every color.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Who is The Grass Roots Classic Rock Group?  http://t.co/kPZUmMJKHT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before you judge a man, walk a mile in his shoes. After that who cares? He's a mile away and you've got his shoes - Billy Connolly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Eagles   http://t.co/JXxPyRCBjz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just started my INSANITY: 60-Day Total Body Conditioning Workout DVD Program - wish me luck!  http://t.co/MesMSvrk95]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More die in the United States of too much food than too little. - John Kenneth Galbraith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marvel's The Avengers - ALL FOUR Movies in one Collection - including The Avengers - VERY COOL!!!! http://t.co/oYSwdXyM2G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not anorexic. I'm from Texas. Are there people from Texas that are anorexic? I've never heard of one. And that includes me. Jessica S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every boy should have two things: a dog, and a mother willing to let him have one - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All our dreams can come true -- if we have the courage to pursue them. - Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of the first book in the Left Behind Series by Tim LaHaye and Jerry Jenkins  http://t.co/SotrRugWIb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Questions to Ask a Lawyer Prior to Hiring Them  http://t.co/my62d6foGq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Kiss  http://t.co/1t1wdmcPWv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What is Eating Paleo?  http://t.co/vq4O23Dzkj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of the animals except for man know that the principle business of life is to enjoy it. - Samuel Butler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Foreigner  http://t.co/S7xErHRMZM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must do the thing you think you cannot do. - Eleanor Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[History of Blogging  http://t.co/CsyQABk4KZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we can't live together, then we're going to die alone. - Jack Shephard, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Lynyrd Skynyrd  http://t.co/gsFAqlCyrC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you can leave two black stripes from the exit of one corner to the braking zone of the next, you have enough horsepower. - Mark Donohue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is the world flat? I never thought about it. Sherri Shepherd, The View, after Whoopi Goldberg asked her if she thought the world was flat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only way to prove that you're a good sport is to lose. - Ernie Banks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suitor: A guy who thinks he's throwing a girl a line when all the time he's being roped in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft MiniGame QuakeCraft: Victory was in Sight!!!!! http://t.co/zfnpDyCMUz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Early History of Marvel Comics  http://t.co/UsbcFKYwtc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would give a million bucks to have seen my mother say "cute shoes" to a naked Ashley Judd. --&gt; Brian Fies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't care half so much about making money as I do about making my point, and coming out ahead. Cornelius Vanderbilt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to make the donuts (love that commercial!!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Cool Pixie Espresso Maker - Compact and Cute! http://t.co/S4yuIgfKe0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Electric Light Orchestra  http://t.co/9o2YDgGxjy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Barbara Acklin - The Popular Singer  http://t.co/EGFVZMO1uC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you know of the Klingon proverb that tells us revenge is a dish that is best served cold? It is very cold in space. - Khan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I live in heels. Give me a pair of flip-flops and I'll trip all over myself. - Brenda Song]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn from yesterday, live for today, hope for tomorrow. - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Experience is not what happens to a man. It is what a man does with what happens to him. - Aldous Huxley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Star Trek Enterprise Pizza Cutter! http://t.co/ohB4nGJyTV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our Review of Amazon’s Popular Kindle Reader  http://t.co/Dtni6sy5de]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To finish first, you must first finish. - Juan Manuel Fangio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Renowned Tuba  http://t.co/MCSvS46DVS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you blame others, you give up your power to change. - Dr. Robert Anthony]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 13 - Covering the costs of treatment – is it worth it all?  http://t.co/hl4Bm9NL90]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>