<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @StillGameQuote: WANTED: DEID OR DEID. STEVIE THE BOOKIE #StillGameQuote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @max_ski: Ante Kostelic replaced as course setter, ''unskiable' set RT @skionline_ch: Kostelic steckte "unfahrbaren" Kitz-Kurs: http: ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nile Ranger spelled his name in money before getting arrested on suspicion of rape http://t.co/AfQ8weYL @rossmcnairn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dominik Paris? Wow. #fisalpine #streif]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @hahnenkammrace: Dominik Paris (ITA) wins the downhill @hahnenkammrace! 2nd is @eguay (CAN) followed by Hannes Reichelt (AUT) congrat ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RollingStone: Happy birthday, Questlove! Celebrate by checking out his top 50 hip-hop songs of all time: http://t.co/xqmNKDsO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ThisisMannah: Wilfried Zaha arrives for his Man United medical wearing Imogen Thomas tshirt #mufc http://t.co/D8ImSikh "Hi Ryan, I'm ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ThisisMannah: That Rab Burns eh... He's sexy and a poet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#sandwichvan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThisisMannah kiss ass]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @salomonfreeski: #Skiing in China? Yes. Vincent Gagnier and Freeski TV have proof. Photo by leoahrens @ China http://t.co/P2lr16u9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@efox1986 @rory_g_macrae it's okay. I've got the m&amp;ms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TeamBSS: The men's racers are topping the 100mph mark at the WC DH on the Lauberhorn......simply amazing....mind blowing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @gdunbarap: Still racing at Wengen downhill, but looks like Johan Clarey of France has the all-time World Cup speed record of 161.9 k ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conditions in #Wengen look phenomenal. Think we're going to see 100mph! #fisalpine #worldcup #skiracing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tedligety: Skipping DH to prep for SL. If someone nails this turn they could go 100mph. #fromthecore @shredopt @ Wengen http://t.co/ ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ChrissyMac7: Delighted to stop off at the No.1 @FootballAid feeding point... Zest in Biggar. Incredible baguettes!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @stevenwyeth: When Nigel Adkins took charge at #saintsfc 28 months ago they were 22nd in League 1. Now 15th in PL, lost just 2 of 12  ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JLLUK: SWIP today announces that it has awarded the property management of its £8.5bn UK portfolio to Jones Lang LaSalle #JLL: http: ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JojoRobertson1: Who's this random getting in on our photo?! #loljks #itsonlyRoryMcilroy #NBD http://t.co/9iy1WFpF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AP_Mobile: A sampling of Lance Armstrong's choicest doping denials: http://t.co/BjiBNJuC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes @JamesWoodsy !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Newschoolers: .@usfreeskiing Grand Prix Men's Slopestyle Finals top 3: 1) @JamesWoodsy, 2) @RussHenshaw, 3) Alex Beaulieu-Marchand.  ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pamthorburn: Britain have a World Cup winner!!! @JamesWoodsy slayed. Unreal!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @frankieboyle: #Splash is on, and the viewers at home are cheering on their favourite. The concept of paralysis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @guskenworthy: Woken up at 6AM by USADA looking for a drug test... Wish someone had told me you're not supposed to poo in the cup. Yikes!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rustyboy2310 #lolzy ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @iainmacintosh: What a turnaround! Yilmaz lobs the keeper and Schalke are deep in the Schit! 1-2.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David Villa looks like Rino Gattuso]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#spl reconstruction. How long before they just give up trying and do nothing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @daveryding: An unreal day today, still can't quite believe I managed to win the Europa Cup Slalom title, but somehow I did! https:// ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Kenny_Millar: Similar case for recent derby when group of 30 English businessmen knocked back as they weren't on database. Went to M ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Kenny_Millar: Disappointing to see so many empty seats at Easter Road, especially after seeing tourists trying to buy tickets turned ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My get up and go has fucked off and left me #hangover]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @skigrahambell: #Competition #Win NEW Tracker 13 Binding Ski’s &amp; bag courtesy of @AtomicSnowUK To enter RT, follow me &amp; @Atom ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHIT!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @frankieboyle: After watching Scottish football, this match is like Crouching Tiger, Hidden Dragon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fergies team selection is madness...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HibernianFCClub trying to buy tickets for derby on Sunday and created account but I 'don't have correct privileges' -can I not buy tickets?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BBCAnnaT: Top effort by @jamienichollsuk in the Burton US Open, 5th place in slopestyle. Meanwhile @GBFreeski training in Oslo ahead ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @iainmacintosh: I am one of the first to arrive at Stamford Bridge. I claim the right of Prima Nocta with the buffet!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @frankieboyle: A billion Catholics are now temporarily leaderless, unsure exactly why they should hate themselves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheRealKirstyG: I am very proud to be named Patron of @HibsLadies! My Dad is over the moon... http://t.co/aRO65GA15k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FRabbits awesome version of 'my backwards walk' tonight guys. Cheers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RahlvesBanzai: Classic bathroom wall.  Shane McConkey at the Pearly Gates http://t.co/neB1d9WAAx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @iainmacintosh: Imagine what it's like to be a Bradford fan now. Imagine the joy. Imagine the excitement. Imagine the ferocious stiff ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is pish]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BBCAnnaT: Ex GB ski coach Mark Tilston now coaches Spain's Carolina Ruiz Castillo. She's won Meribel World Cup downhill, 13 years af ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really, really shite sunburn. #ouch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AgentScotland: Kudos to @OnlyAnExcuse for highlighting this, hilarious meltdown from a girl Celtic fan after the juve game http://t. ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ted ligety. One of the best ever? #fisalpine #gsmaestro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @martinobeat: @iainmacintosh They're petitioning to have an electro rendition of the CL anthem played before the return leg at Westfa ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Varane is going to star tonight. Future word class centre half]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @StupidFootball: Bayern Munich's president on the club's season ticket prices. This is exactly how football fans should be treated: http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can they?....  #ucl #rmcf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With no English teams left, the #itvfootball commentary team are keen to see Howard Webb lift the champions league trophy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coutinho is amazing. The new silva #motd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Beathhigh: Thanks to @AdaptSki for letting me know. Brilliant people who take disabled people to the slopes - in most weathers!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new daft punk tune is sweet audio chocolate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alicrawley  The crawlmeister, can you please DM me your email address?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mspfilms: Exclusive debut of the official poster for McConkey goes LIVE! http://t.co/JlIGMeIFop http://t.co/g71YWUEyeH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @usasoccerguy: WESTSIDE HAMMERS GOALSHOT! it's Vaz Tea who kicks the ball past Richard De Gere with his head! #prideofwestlondon #epl ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kevinbridges86: I'm supporting whoever's playing for Chubbs here. Dam alligator bit his hand off.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rustyrockets: Congratulations Hibernian. Great team, cool fans.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CarolineCheese: Coulthard to Alonso: "We can see your girlfriend down there, I'm sure you'll be having a nice private celebration" # ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wishing I had stuck more than a quid on Snedeker or Scott to win the masters!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aspy87 in Glasgow for the football so will give it a miss. Could be tempted for Sunday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My visit to t'pub seems to have cost me some ridiculous #football tonight. Unbelievable scenes. #ucl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SimcoeBrewDog: "I love the taste of ice cold beer with a wedge of lime" Said no clever human. Ever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I Knew it!

 http://t.co/hrK33F6tSi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GilesBarrie: Today programme says @Ed_Miliband will launch 'Save the high street' campaign today - a bit late, five years after intr ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dani Alves #bytheway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome! -"If you've ever wondered about Chelsea's famous press lounge buffet, wonder no more. RT @PhilippeAuclair:  http://t.co/9rCWI1cHGN”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Stepto: Does anyone else refer to the anticipation of Game of Thrones as “getting a throner”?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paolo di Canio is an unhinged, racist nutjob. Obviously still a place for him in the #epl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DMiliband: Statement on Sunderland AFC role: http://t.co/L0n26tKdQY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching 'how TV ruined your life' and want to kill myself. How did we come to this? It's hilarious and horrifying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rustyboy2310 http://t.co/wU12kLGomj …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cbrookmyre: Glory glory to thon Hibee.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Scroobiuspipyo: If you can't reach your books then you only have your shelves to blame.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamiefox1 I like think Aksel maybe doesn't drink so much red bull for his usual sessions...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @millarmind: Yeah, 4th in the bunch sprint, whateves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rory_g_macrae the life and times of a mushroom trooper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rory_g_macrae  http://t.co/B8my57cHcc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listen: Deltron 3030: "City Rising From the Ashes" http://t.co/dxyNdPyfiN  Aaah!! New Deltron album!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jimmy Fallon's Video Game Week Suggestion Box: Tariq's Mario Rap - YouTube http://t.co/B8my57cHcc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@iainmacintosh: Oh, you sexy, sexy, sexy bearded God, you.”  @rory_g_macrae]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent article - The Bad Habits of Good Negotiators | LinkedIn http://t.co/DGvDI4uNCR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JLLUK: Good luck to Andy Irvine (JLL's Scottish Chairman &amp; British &amp; Irish Lions 2013 Tour Manager) &amp; squad for tomorrow’s game vs. the…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the capital! #hibees]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThisisMannah a great day!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @templebuilders: Someone has stolen Seamus Heaney our wee Border Terrier outside Sports Direct in Perth - please RT &amp; nut the thief]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Mad Billionaire Behind GoPro: The World's Hottest Camera Company http://t.co/L5Yq84xzTY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @fredmacaulay: Anyone else watching this new tv sport called 'tyre strategy'. It's like a shite version of F1.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BonnieGull: And in the blue corner... http://t.co/8SWurWmDeU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tmccord88: @tmccord88: 4 hungover model citizens #throwbackthursday #tbt @brober87 @wiggasaparis @domdunnett #deathwish09 http://t.co/M…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The chuck Norris cameo in #expendables2 is absolutely appalling. No effort not to do a 'chuck Norris so so tough...' Joke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tmccord88: Muckle toon high street. #skyporn @ Langholm http://t.co/TARx6ELLwk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CammyM_: @usasoccerguy When I saw my Scottish EPL Soccer Franchise team's jersey I knew I had to buy it. Awesome! http://t.co/iyqt7ArfSi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GlennWool: with time to kill yesterday i inadvertently saw "sunshine over leith" followed by "filth". i really wish i'd done that the o…]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>