<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Why worry? If you’ve done the very best you can, worrying won’t make it any better. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a world of laughter, a world of tears. It's a world of hopes, and a world of fears. –It’s A Small World]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m still learning myself. –Mulan (Mulan II)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All my troubles and obstacles have strengthened me. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you are in love with someone, you want to be near him all the time. –Miss Piggy (The Muppets)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't worry, Minnie. You're all the music I'll ever need. –Mickey Mouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most important thing is the family. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you focus on what you have left behind, you will never be able to see what lies ahead. –Gusteau (Ratatouille)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s a mistake not to give people a chance to learn to depend on themselves while they are young. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be a Princess, you don't need a crown and dresses. All you need is a kind and pure heart. I am a Princess.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes we only see how people are different from us, but if you look hard enough, you can see how much we're all alike. –Jasmine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you don't know where you are going, any road will get you there. –Cheshire Cat (Alice in Wonderland)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are never too old for a Disney movie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dreams do come true, and maybe something wonderful will happen. –Giselle (Enchanted)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just because you haven’t found your talent yet, doesn’t mean you don’t have one. –Kermit (The Muppets)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/W9vv5m3BdL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You’ll always be part of my favorite story. –Belle (Enchanted Tales)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s kind of fun to do the impossible. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once you’re grown up, you can’t come back. –Peter Pan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You try. You fail. You try. You fail. But the only true failure is when you stop trying. –Madame Leota (Haunted Mansion)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When we work together, things are always better. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Open your eyes now before you get hurt. –Tiana (Princess and the Frog)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We own ourselves. We’re masters of our own fate. We control our own destiny. –Lotso (Toy Story 3)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope your hair never looks like this: http://t.co/34SjEv07T5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I shall call him squishy and he shall be mine and he shall be me squishy. –Dory (Finding Nemo)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go and chase your dreams, you won't regret it. Anything can happen if you let it. –Mary Poppins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snow White :) http://t.co/tyl6od9Ypc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still wish on the stars as they fall from above ‘cause I still believe in love. –Cinderella 3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lilo: “Don’t leave me, okay?” | Stitch: “Okay.” –Lilo and Stitch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I knew who I was this morning, but I've changed a few times since then. –Alice (Alice in Wonderland)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Katy Perry as Snow White! Angelina Jolie as Pocahontas! Anne Hathaway as Belle! Here's the pic: http://t.co/2jYdbZtQoX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even when I'm upset, I still love you more than anything in the whole world. –Mrs. Potts (Enchanted Tales)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Childishness? I think it's the equivalent of never losing your sense of humor. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No sweeter harmony than the sound of laughter. –Sebastian (Little Mermaid Series)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Retweet if you want a Disney Tattoo like this: http://t.co/Vpd2uCrzXK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wendy: “You won't forget me, will you?” | Peter Pan: “Me? Forget? Never.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing's impossible if you believe you can do it. –Phineas (Phineas and Ferb)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yesterday is history, tomorrow is a mystery, but today is a gift, that’s why its called the present. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pirates 5, Finding Dory, Maleficent,Toy Story 4...Here's the list of next Disney movies: http://t.co/PCTuopjyzZ - sp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once you love someone, they stay in your heart forever. –Nita (Brother Bear 2)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm only brave when I have to be. Being brave doesn't mean you go looking for trouble. –Mufasa (The Lion King)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christopher: “Forever and ever is a very long time.” | Pooh: “Forever isn’t long at all when I’m with you.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That awkward moment when you realize these once child Disney stars are now sexy: http://t.co/GAmHCQY2iK - sp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I tried to fit in. I really do. I just can’t. Sometimes I feel like I really don’t belong here. –Hercules]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just because you wish for something, doesn't make it true. –Tiana (Princess and the Frog)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are never too old for a Disney movie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes the less you say, the more that people understand. Keep it simple. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just trust your friends to do their best. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leave the world behind. I will be alright if you stay by my side. –Disney Fairies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I make wishes, I have dreams, and I still want to believe anything can happen in this world for an ordinary girl. –Hannah Montana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know what else to do except to try to dream of you and wonder if you are dreaming too, wherever you are. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes it’s better to be alone. Nobody can hurt you. –Megara (Hercules)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listen to me. The human world is a mess. –Sebastian (Little Mermaid)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Retweet if you love these Disney Pictures!: http://t.co/9gIzwZZeLT - sp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I won't stop. For every minute of the rest of my life, I will fight. –Rapunzel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you do the things that you can do, you will find a way. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who are clever, who have a brain, never understand anything. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Promise me you won't forget about me, ever, not even when I am a hundred. –Christopher Robin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What I really wanted was to prove that I could do things right, so that when I looked in the mirror, I'd see someone worthwhile. –Mulan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're never too old to be young. –Snow White]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cheer up, child. It'll turn out all right in the end. You'll see. –Mrs.Pott (Beauty and the Beast)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life's full of tough choices, isn't it? –Ursula (The Little Mermaid)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think of the happiest things. It's the same as having wings. –Peter Pan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m sorry I bit you. And pulled your hair. And punched you in the face. –Lilo (Lilo and Stitch)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That’s the real trouble with the world, too many people grow up. They forget. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Miracles are real but they need someone to believe, so they can happen. –Disney Fairies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world's still the same. There's just less in it. –Jack Sparrow (Pirates of the Caribbean)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You've got a friend in me. If you got troubles, then I got them too. There isn't anything I wouldn't do for you. –Toy Story]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I realized that I miss you and I need you. –Kermit (The Muppets)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You just focused on the bad stuff when all you had to do was, let go of the past and keep moving forward. –Lewis (Meet the Robinsons)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You’ll always be part of my favorite story. –Belle (Enchanted Tales)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don’t let the most important person in your world slip away. –Gary (The Muppets)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rafiki: “Change is good.” | Simba: “Yeah, but it's not easy.” –The Lion King]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll do anything to make things right again. I just have to be brave. –Merida (Brave)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing's impossible if you believe you can do it. –Phineas (Phineas and Ferb)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What you give is what you get. –Tiana (Princess and the Frog)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rafiki: “It doesn't matter. It's in the past.” | Simba: “But it still hurts.” –The Lion King]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most important thing is, even if we're apart, I'll always be with you. –Christopher Robin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you have a little problem, I could try to lend a hand. If you're feeling sad, just tell me and I'll try to understand. –Piglet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For every laugh, there should be a tear. –Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good friends are more important than anything else. –Snow White]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wanna call your name forever, and you will always answer forever. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wendy: “I should like to give you a kiss. Don't you know what a kiss is?” | Peter Pan: “I shall know when you give me one.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't pick someone I'm not in love with. –Minnie Mouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well that's strange... http://t.co/zcZq7RUpEK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yesterday is history, tomorrow is a mystery, but today is a gift, that’s why its called the present. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rafiki: “It doesn't matter. It's in the past.” | Simba: “But it still hurts.” –The Lion King]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Believe you can, then you will. –Mulan (Princess Stories)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People always do crazy things when they're in love. –Megara (Hercules)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So True... http://t.co/5B408XzseN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m feeling happy, which is a big deal for me. –Marlin (Finding Nemo)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes we only see how people are different from us, but if you look hard enough, you can see how much we're all alike. –Jasmine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think of the happiest things. It's the same as having wings. –Peter Pan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I shouldn't ask for more. I've got so many things I should be thankful for. –Rapunzel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When You See It... http://t.co/AWF5Uc2J5Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If good you give, hope for better, and when better is achieved, hope for extraordinary. –Mickey Mouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A smile means friendship to everyone. –It’s A Small World]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things have a way of coming together whenever friends are around. –Pooh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're weird, but I like you. –Dot (A Bug’s Life)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look at me. You may think you see who I really am, but you'll never know me. –Mulan]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>