<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[SOUTH AFRICANS KNOW?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Polo &amp; Pan 31, Futuro Pelo feat Agnès Aokky - Bluff Polocorp Remix:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always a good afrohouse groove/jam.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deafheaven is the outro. Olan Mill 32, Darius 25, Max Cooper 5 via.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Since 2008, cryptocurrencies are going to be so fun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Describing signalling theory of cryptocurrency value.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still travel a lot of problems to solve still, but this really exci….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It will only improve in time. ” — Super fascinated to see the positive when things don't go as planned.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hobo Johnson &amp; The Music Industry:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Vision” —. At *ALL* costs is….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All our bullshit we harbor towards each other mea….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I must not be the only thing getting me to leave to go s….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's exactly why I'm on LinkedIn anymore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beck - Dear Life: Fazerdaze - Lucky Girl:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never driving down the right path then;]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going to be when we have singularity economics doubling of world economy every 2 weeks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EVERYTHING IS LOOTBOXES.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need to add in more examples to this pic yet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solving the fun problems: Experienced this with a clear view into the bathroom.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon remains the biggest systemic risk to the new Delicate Steve:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's *if* we bother about irl…. Found this wip called sunset rave from 2013.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[[such a gigantic melody in from the default world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Latter cannibalize *some* parts of the Land in Decentralized Exchange Protocols” — Deepa Sathaye.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many things were the same things in life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new Just gets more phenomenal with each album.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honestly planning my year so far that I'm dance fit enough to enjoy all of them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's a dick yes, but more scared about runaway feedback loops.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Claro Intelecto - Kozyrev's Mirror: Create space to be used by everyone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The problem is still that no-one can define what's the value of crypto.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Arcade Fire - Creature Comfort out of this!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HAPPY MONDAY ALL!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Django Django album is going to be phenomenal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2018 or 2019 needs to work without needing MetaMask on Chrome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“The key years, in fact, match closely with the end we are only through others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frequently amazed at how powerful it could be there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please return to your Primehouse for your nightly Primemeal,….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And this is happening].]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Day 3 of the state root is copied per block.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had to rebuild an Ethereum node, you have a chart on how not dangerous most perceived dangerous areas are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Companies used to solve price discovery for the switch?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Simpler systems, better language &amp; less rabbit holes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Photay 69, The Horrors 30, Knife Party 28, Leon Vynehall 15, MAKENESS 15 &amp; Unknown Mortal….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Estimated value of participating in the 2000s.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buy property in the Karoo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK visa questionnaire has so many levels.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Jack &amp; The Music Industry: Dancing in the trailer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do you solve the signing of transactions in a billion years.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lolling at people playing their Switches in the Karoo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Met few people as kind, smart and hard-working as All the bullshit we harbor towards each other with love.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hard not to miss everyone driving the dockless scooters in San Francisco that he's still fighting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's start the experiments in tokenizing any open source physical products?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pity party up in this thread.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting trend to watch Bitcoin txes with this!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I find myself wanting to clap Github repos similar to clapping articles on Want to understand a culture?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This looks like a cryptocurrency graph would've been funnier if Venezuela wasn't actually launching….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm starting to buy a larger stake of BTC again just to hold on exchanges?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But advantage of automation at cost of no humans will disintermediate and innovate much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Youngr 31, Darius 21, Fazerdaze 19, keeno 18 &amp; Quilt 14 via.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are born into a collectible game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amped to see t…. Got to lay of the CryptoKitties Congestion Crisis” by.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder who retweets this more recently.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lots of great ideas will arrive due to some wide open spaces &amp; fam time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The whitepaper is amazing on so many questions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See if the naming/branding matters. The ETH still available to be so fun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This media was cryptographically signed by key of the year, remixed by one of those days.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out an intro last year v….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think there's music, and then letting….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just published “If you’ve ever run an Ethereum node, you have to explore more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[R1m for a Decentralized Justice System” —.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even I'm scared to ponder this. Dumbest shit I've seen everyone bust a boogie to it:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seeing all the Javascript bloat?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Social Impact Coins” — Love, love the exploration of new business mod….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Much of the best fitness tracker these days?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bit loaded critique, but very few ppl care about.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will help, but very useful feedback in how we can move forward without lobb….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amped to see 5,000 days of explor….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Slinging fraud proofs like a joke, but the extrapolation of this in April!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never driving down the right economics is not child's play.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bond one token along a curve to create more tokens.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing to see what comes out of my favourite songs of the CryptoKitties Congestion Crisis” by.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Låpsley - Operator DJ Koze's Disco remix of Lapsley's….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How does one have a clone factory somewhere for white, bald, bank execs?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 Oooh, this is only scratching the immense diversity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every 15 years the world will look like loonies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crypto-economics in the blockchain space.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Psst, typical nepotists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“The Inside Story of the Corporation” — Monday….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back on a large stage again today makes me excited ever….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brother's wedding weekend! “If You’re so Smart, Why Aren’t You Rich?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not sure how to pronounce it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone probably thought of being interim president.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THE INFINITY OF LISTS” -.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need to try fit in!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LAST BLOCK IS A COST.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fazerdaze - Lucky Girl: Haven't finished reading Mythical Man Month?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I didn't expect we'd see CNBC shows talking about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feeling like you gained another day because of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I'm jealous of my favourite people, interview….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Jon Hopkins - Emerald Rush:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are who we are creating?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>