<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer – Mbed Data Services: Job ID #: 12915 – Job Category: Information Technology – Employment Type: Experienced Professionals – Division: Internet of Things – Department: ISG Web Services – Primary Country: USA – Primary Location:… https://t.co/qzwGQYOMn8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GOP nominee: Voting for black rival would 'monkey this up': • Analysis: 5 lessons from Andrew Gillum's shocking win in Florida https://t.co/M8tQzcpYOy https://t.co/eldBYMZmIx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Administrator: A health services organization is seeking a Systems Administrator to join their team in Fort Worth, TX. Essential Functions Installing new software releases, system upgrades, evaluates and installs patches and resolves software… https://t.co/UByjcLHmwf https://t.co/z7Li0SiITg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Papa John's scorches Papa John https://t.co/u8bOI3Rq1D https://t.co/IMrZCxOizr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Quality Specialist: COMPUTER/IT Senior Quality Specialist for Ariba, Inc. (Palo Alto, CA) to work in a product, cross functional, or testing team with a special focus to quality assurance and test related tasks within the product creation process.… https://t.co/DNXWmBBBf4 https://t.co/VdCon4hU3r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer: SENIOR SOFTWARE DEVELOPER Wanted for our Blueprint Project. Will be responsible for software development along with team of developers and architect by understanding problem statement and provide solutions with C#.NET Core.… https://t.co/TOzZz6MIkw https://t.co/vXvZMLLJGn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mom charged after drugs in breast milk killed baby, prosecutors say: In Bucks County, Pennsylvania, prosecutors are arguing that 30-year-old Samantha Jones killed her 11-week-old son, R.J., by breastfeeding while using drugs. https://t.co/ayeVFxM45B https://t.co/auHF4lgyRL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior SQL Server DBA: As a Senior SQL Server DBA at DaVita, you will design, create, manage and tune production databases on DaVita servers, and participate in database-related initiatives in alignment with DaVita s Mission and Core Values. The ideal… https://t.co/gmnB1UCTK8 https://t.co/dTpf0TBWrw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Specialist Developer (T-SQL, PL/SQL, Database design, objects, tuning): Sr. Specialist Developer (T-SQL, PL/SQL, Database design, objects, tuning) ‘ Developer, Application Development and Tools:’ Responsible for designing custom applications and… https://t.co/WqzJFTGltM https://t.co/03JUrk8PEv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch senator's tearful tribute to McCain: Sen. Lindsey Graham (R-SC) remembers his friend Sen. John McCain on the floor of the Senate. https://t.co/ajLMYQRuk7 https://t.co/jGNqkpNQEM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst with Wholesale Banking Experience: Job Ref: ********* Employer: NTT DATA Country: United States County/State: New Jersey Address: Post Date: 31/07/2018 00:30 Req ID: 23179 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board,… https://t.co/0yawR8zB6V https://t.co/fKdOTskp3l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Serena Williams is being policed for her blackness: In the 21st century, black people are still subjected to forms of racial discrimination that feel -- and should be -- things of the past. White standards of beauty still dictate that the features of… https://t.co/AhB8eaSsnD https://t.co/7dBbUVhSDs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior SQL Developer- DC: Senior SQL Developer- DC – (12839) This details all the information about the job posting. Job Title Senior SQL Developer- DC Organizational Unit Ashley Furniture Industries , Corporate , Information Technology Location… https://t.co/pxczABS3mV https://t.co/t5cv14TY6C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst (SQL): Job Description – Data Analyst (SQL) Job LocationUS-VA-Reston Job ID10301 Job LocationUnited States CategoryInformation Technology/Software Overview American Institutes for Research (AIR) is a leading professional services firm with a… https://t.co/E51Du4NY38]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server DBA/Architect: Job TitleSQL Server DBA/Architect – ID:28818 Duration9 – 12 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsSQL, SQL Server LocationEl Segundo, CA &amp; Las Vegas, NV Date Posted07/18/2018 SQL Database Administrator/Architect As a Sr. Database… https://t.co/VCrEVA4ooq https://t.co/DRE3lgRQ33]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL/SQL- COBOL Developer: Date: Aug 14, 2018 Location: Miami, FL, US Company: NTT DATA Services Req ID: 28123 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The quality, integrity, and commitment of our employees… https://t.co/qwzhgMEV7s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MySQL DBA: MYSQL DBA LOCATIONS: PITTSBURGH, PA/CLEVELAND, OH LOOKING FOR EXPERIENCED MYSQL DBA TO ASSIST WITH ENTERPRISE MYSQL DESIGN AND IMPLEMENTATION PROJECT. * The candidate must have experience with the following technologies: * MySQL Architecture,… https://t.co/uPzAigbCx9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Business Systems Analyst — GRS — Strong SQL: Technical Business Systems Analyst’ ‘ GRS ‘ Strong SQL Formulates and defines system’s scope and objectives based on both user needs and a good understanding of the application, business, operational… https://t.co/MdEVgeVL8z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: Make your mark in Broadcasting and Digital Media. Sinclair Broadcast Group and Sinclair Digital Solutions are dedicated to making Sinclair a communications powerhouse! We are the largest and most diversified television broadcasting company… https://t.co/WwrcV8Yp1B https://t.co/snmQ25bMz3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cops: Boy confronts bullies, gets attacked: Police in Olympia, Washington, are investigating an assault on a 6-year-old boy who says he stood up to bullies and was brutally attacked. https://t.co/wjjHElUEGI https://t.co/ulmw2rPOcb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Administrator – SQL: TRAX International Careers – Home – Our Services – Our People – Our Leaders – Careers – About Us Returning Applicant? Login Now New Job Search Database Administrator – SQL Job Code:2018:0303-002 Location:Lynchburg, VA FT/PT… https://t.co/KL0rd0gviY https://t.co/W7MKfoR83u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET / SQL Developer: .NET / SQL Developer – CareWorks TechCareWorks Tech CareWorks Tech Menu – Services – IT Consulting – Enterprise Service Management – Infrastructure – Events – Careers – Training – Contact Careers – Careers – Current Opportunities… https://t.co/Nv2Um6pTrb https://t.co/hE36SZnzO5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook bans a military official for the first time https://t.co/XY9iwvWaSm https://t.co/JSu3BkPVRt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer SME: SQL Developer SME – 18-02550 Ref No.: 18-02550 Location: Greenwood Village, Colorado Akraya is looking for a SQL Developer SME for one of our clients. If the job description below is a fit, please apply directly or call Ajay at… https://t.co/uhiO0X8qXf https://t.co/JPLA8wzVzK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst (SQL): Job Location US-VA-Reston Job ID 10301 Job Location United States Category Information Technology/Software Overview American Institutes for Research (AIR) is a leading professional services firm with a growing software engineering and… https://t.co/zXZ23JnSnO https://t.co/7MIanLlkpw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Administrator – SQL: TRAX International Careers – Home – Our Services – Our People – Our Leaders – Careers – About Us Returning Applicant? Login Now New Job Search Database Administrator – SQL Job Code:2018:0303-002 Location:Lynchburg, VA FT/PT… https://t.co/YEQ0Jy5fFq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lawmaker: Anyone who smears McCain deserves a whipping: Sen. Johnny Isakson (R-GA) pays tribute to John McCain on the Senate floor, saying anyone who tries to "tarnishes the reputation of John McCain deserves a whipping." https://t.co/I0o58PSm5y https://t.co/rF3aY8Vw8U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Java Developer JavaScript, Angular, Kafka, SQL: Principal Java Developer ‘ JavaScript, Angular, Kafka, SQL ‘ The Principal Developer position in the AST Performance, Monitoring &amp; Availability Engineering Team will be responsible for developing… https://t.co/Q6ePwchzAK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 50-year lessons America still hasn't learned https://t.co/g9xX2ZXlia https://t.co/KvC1xxnU5E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Analyst with C#: Job Locations US-WA-Redmond Job ID 2018-5457 # of Openings 1 Overview Beyondsoft Consulting, Inc., is a leading, technical solutions and consulting partner. We combine emerging technologies and proven methodologies to tailor elegant… https://t.co/afqkhcDjPg https://t.co/Hm0ZfhQDGe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL/SQL Developer: PL/SQL Developer Ref No.: 18-33612 Location: tempe, Arizona Hello, Greetings for the day ! We have an urgent requirement for PL/SQL Developer in Tempe , AZ. Please let me know if you are looking for a new project. You can reach me at… https://t.co/jsWIGhwDaK https://t.co/sXDTrEImU6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[North Carolina federal court throws out congressional map: A panel of three federal judges in North Carolina ruled Monday the state's congressional map is an unconstitutional partisan gerrymander that favors Republicans, and said it may require districts… https://t.co/U8hecqnTFg https://t.co/UIRmSxpAtM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Database Administrator: Requisition ID 2018-43302 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level None Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description General Dynamics is looking for an experienced MS SQL Server Database… https://t.co/NBHTBl7se2 https://t.co/MI2uwyIJbC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Windows/SQL Server Systems Administrator: Senior Windows/SQL Server Systems Administrator Job Locations US-DC-Washington Job ID 10591 Minimum Clearance Required Public Trust Responsibilities Functional Responsibilities:  ISYS Technologies is… https://t.co/O9ZedFBIAB https://t.co/TCvp7njeOv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US and Mexico reach a preliminary trade deal that could replace NAFTA: The United States and Mexico are on track to announce details of a new trade agreement Monday as part of ongoing discussions over the future of NAFTA, a senior US official said. https://t.co/wLjDtHqe1S https://t.co/AzGS15eL3Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server Database Administrator: Requisition ID 2018-40213 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Secret Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description Responsible for the installation, configuration, administration and… https://t.co/lrRunuWk2t https://t.co/aT8NeDSDHk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See man rush stage at Beyoncé concert: A man ran on stage during the closing of Beyonce and Jay-Z's "OTRII" concert in Atlanta. https://t.co/jWIMOt2szL https://t.co/r5RElSqf4i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Support Specialist: Network Support Specialist Department: Information Technology Classification Professional/ Managerial, Exempt Employment Employment Status: Regular, full-time, 12-month Deadline: Until Filled Type: Full Time Function:… https://t.co/zvuMgemQp4 https://t.co/4Nj1TJDEZr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shooting suspect interviewed in 2017: Two people are dead and nine others shot after a mass shooting at a Madden video game tournament in Jacksonville, Florida. https://t.co/c09I6gklM0 https://t.co/mEgPNxUjko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering Senior Developer: Senior Developer for Ariba, Inc. (Palo Alto, CA) responsible for development focusing on design, coding, testing, quality assurance of complex product features in a development team. Bachelor’s degree in Comp Sci,… https://t.co/0mxjGJNPcb https://t.co/km1SY044kq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Specialist Appl Support Analyst, UNIX/LINUX/Windows, SQL (Sunday – Thursday): Job Description Sr. Specialist Appl Support Analyst, UNIX/LINUX/Windows, SQL (Sunday – Thursday) Overview Of BNY Mellon: BNY Mellon is a global financial services company… https://t.co/0zixzEBtWu https://t.co/1aYbRPIjO7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server Database Developer: SQL Server Database Developer home About Us – News – Blog – Careers – Resources – Leadership Products – TruCare – Integrations Demo Careers Contact Customer Log In Careers Home Career SQL Server Databa… Careers SQL Server… https://t.co/rzqP09DjEu https://t.co/m7hF7hA5HM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Database Administrator: Job Description 41927BR Enterprise Database Administrator Entry Level/ Junior Professional Job Description We are hiring for an Enterprise Database Administrator’s to maintain and support databases to provide… https://t.co/DGeHXm4Txp https://t.co/XqcvvFQgAD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advanced Data Scientist Intern: Job/Internship Description Advanced Data Scientist Intern ABB Inc., in Cary, NC is seeking for an Advanced Data Scientist Intern to join our Corporate Function Finance team. The positions are as Advanced Analytics interns… https://t.co/4Ypuf1yHX8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. SQL Server DBA: Markit Digital is looking for an experienced Database Administrator to provide support for our diverse SQL Server estate and contribute to new deployments and projects. A challenging role that provides exposure to the finance… https://t.co/ckNDdrTcJ2 https://t.co/E74WAyybvl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Java Agile XP Developer: Prestigious Fortune 500 Company is currently seeking a Lead Java Agile XP Developer with TDD experience. Candidate will lead Agile XP development teams in building digital products. Your team will develop code all day, every… https://t.co/PYZGTgh9xj https://t.co/D5b9BFy6md]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Witness says victim ran into a nearby restaurant https://t.co/WX3vgonJsX https://t.co/XLzXmZqZE2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Java Developer JavaScript, Angular, Kafka, SQL: Job Description Principal Java Developer – JavaScript, Angular, Kafka, SQL The Principal Developer position in the AST Performance, Monitoring &amp; Availability Engineering Team will be responsible… https://t.co/hRWMvNJZOe https://t.co/J6z6UfNFi5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL/Oracle Analyst: SQL/Oracle Analyst job | Cognizant job in Richardson, Texas, United StatesJob Details | Cognizant – ************* – Industries – – – Services – – – Latest Thinking – – – About Cognizant – – Careers Home – Get To Know Us – Our Core… https://t.co/LuC4iV2Ne8 https://t.co/5rlbdpSonQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Analyst, Resource Planning: Job Description Job Description The Customer Service organization is looking for an energetic, self-directed, detail oriented candidate for the position of Sr. Analyst, Resource Planning. This person will evaluate T-Mobile… https://t.co/cIPFvvxiJh https://t.co/b81IJc3DIr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pope Francis speaks to thousands at Mass in Dublin amid sex abuse scandal: As Pope Francis prepares to celebrate Mass with half a million faithful in Dublin on Sunday afternoon, thousands are expected to take to the streets in protest over clerical… https://t.co/m46LoWF4AL https://t.co/NaTSt0GfCg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Engineer Java, API, SQL/No SQL exp. required: American Express is in the midst of an exciting Product and Digital enterprise evolution driven by an energetic team of high performers. If you have the talent and desire to deliver innovative payment… https://t.co/WUbxdZ4Ig3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MySQL DBA: MYSQL DBA LOCATIONS: PITTSBURGH, PA/CLEVELAND, OH LOOKING FOR EXPERIENCED MYSQL DBA TO ASSIST WITH ENTERPRISE MYSQL DESIGN AND IMPLEMENTATION PROJECT. * The candidate must have experience with the following technologies: * MySQL Architecture,… https://t.co/toGE9S1BBE https://t.co/dmn6pjHOAT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MySQL Database and Systems Administrator: Requisition ID 2018-44503 # of Openings 0 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Secret Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description MySQL Database and Systems Administrator General Dynamics is… https://t.co/rqLPY1JGQ9 https://t.co/SF2nQF1D0d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: ******/SQL Developer Ref No.: 18-31506 Location: Englewood – Colorado, Colorado Description : Develop, implement Stored procedures, Functions, and Triggers using Microsoft SQL Server Review and interpret ongoing business report… https://t.co/lc6qu3rRnl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PHP / MySQL Developer: PHP / MySQL Developer Ref No.: 18-35571 Location: RTP, North Carolina Position: PHP / MySQL Developer Location: RTP-NC Duration: 6 Months Job Details: Total Experience Required 6-10 Years Core Development Understands APIs… https://t.co/98mHRVuyke https://t.co/BceNSfUkvO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle PL/SQL Developer: Oracle PL/SQL Developer job | Cognizant job in Dallas, Texas, United StatesJob Details | Cognizant – ************* – Industries – – – Services – – – Latest Thinking – – – About Cognizant – – Careers Home – Get To Know Us – Our… https://t.co/l1rloJJrxH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full stack Developer: PySpark developer Ref No.: 18-36987 Location: NYC, New York Position: PySpark developer Location: Tampa, FL and NYC, NY Duration: Full-Time (Onsite Position) No C2C/C2H, No Sponsorship, No Remote/Telecommute. Job Responsibilities 1.… https://t.co/GQuXGwGsIE https://t.co/fWZhEbsN66]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Project Lead (Microservices): Job Ref: ********** Employer: NTT DATA Country: United States County/State: California Address: Post Date: 27/07/2018 00:25 At NTT DATA we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The quality,… https://t.co/gXUCPe0HeH https://t.co/TBkov0QgkI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Senior Developer with strong DB experience (NoSQL/Mongo): Job Ref: ********** Employer: NTT DATA Country: United States County/State: New Jersey Address: Post Date: 31/07/2018 00:10 Req ID: 16819 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right… https://t.co/O9fhuPJBWI https://t.co/x5yiew7zHC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Servicenow Developer: Servicenow Developer Ref No.: 18-32798 Location: Reston, Virginia Position: Servicenow Developer Location: Reston VA Duration: 12 Months – B.S. degree in Computer Science, MIS or equivalent preferred – Ideal candidate must be… https://t.co/EAKb9dpyv7 https://t.co/c0DSW5iOGN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sports gambling isn't a win for casinos https://t.co/EUNIF8xrFo https://t.co/S7xH9WNFhT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Intelligence Analyst: JOB SUMMARY Responsible for supporting and managing a program of business unit-focused initiatives designed to help business partners drive value from information. Contributes to Broad River Retail’s success by ensuring… https://t.co/xBsz1yOtoX https://t.co/uEnOaPSDco]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL/SQL Developer: Date: Aug 14, 2018 Location: Miami, FL, US Company: NTT DATA Services Req ID: 28125 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The quality, integrity, and commitment of our employees are key… https://t.co/duerYzqgtH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elon Musk won't take Tesla private https://t.co/jzFpV31U83 https://t.co/6r8wItyMNJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Specialist Appl Support Analyst, UNIX/LINUX/Windows, SQL: Sr. Specialist Appl Support Analyst, UNIX/LINUX/Windows, SQL (Sunday ‘ Thursday) ‘ Overview Of BNY Mellon: BNY Mellon is a global financial services company focused on helping clients manage… https://t.co/79hmjzuUMt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer I (SQL Server DBA): GENERAL PURPOSE: The SQL Server DBA Engineer provides the technical design and delivery role in the Engineering and Infrastructure Delivery lifecycles from installation, integration, maintenance, currency and upgrades of… https://t.co/oPA3D422nL https://t.co/I9nugMvpBp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here are the world's 100 greatest places to visit: Sometimes the world can seem like a giant Netflix watch list: Your to-do list gets longer and longer, and there's still new stuff to check out. https://t.co/BYkI6dpaQX https://t.co/U7ks7QhQ99]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Software Support Specialist, Infinite Visions: Associate Software Support Specialist, Infinite Visions ======================================================= Infinite Visions is a software solution designed to meet the financial needs payroll,… https://t.co/cDw5Xv80cS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: What Trump gets right (and wrong) about 'flipping': We've become accustomed to President Trump criticizing Special Counsel Robert Mueller's investigation, his own Justice Department and even Jeff Sessions, the man he personally selected to be… https://t.co/AA0LuWujcR https://t.co/TGNM9sA8PN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top executives here keep disappearing: Several of China and Hong Kong's most powerful businessmen have mysteriously vanished and reappeared months later. Is the Chinese government the culprit? https://t.co/h1H1gWeHwA https://t.co/D2r85JUmey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL/Share Point Developer: Career Opportunities at New Horizons St. Louis Student Login Search Site search – – – – Cart St. Louis &amp; Southern Illinois ************ – Home – Training and Certifications – Microsoft Office – Office 365 – Access – Excel –… https://t.co/7ebsU4L5az https://t.co/4FbVPoOPso]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As Pope Francis arrives, anger in Ireland is palpable: In Dublin's Phoenix Park, one of the largest city parks in Europe, final preparations are underway for the arrival of Pope Francis this Sunday. https://t.co/PUi8TccgRD https://t.co/5s9ukl9kUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ledbetter: Brett Kavanaugh would be bad for women https://t.co/oXjFdpOgUi https://t.co/eIPY5Wq6rQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mysql Admin: ******/Mysql Admin Ref No.: 18-33427 Location: Mc Lean – New York, New York LEAD-ADMINISTRATOR-L1 Job Description(As per hiring manager) Key skills required for the job are: MySQL Admin-L3 (Mandatory) As a Lead Administrator, you should be… https://t.co/NngNx7fB8L https://t.co/S2Hrk1bnIB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jr. SQL Database Administrator: Greensboro, NC 27408 #2018-26522 DescriptionOverview The Fresh Market currently has an opening for a Jr. SQL Database Administrator at our Corporate Offices in Greensboro, North Carolina.Responsibilities – Provide support… https://t.co/HXZKX0hos4 https://t.co/ZZDfvPUjyL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Internet calls out Trump's tweet at 1 a.m.: President Trump tweets "rigged witch hunt" and "no collusion" at 1 a.m. CNN's Jeanne Moos reports. https://t.co/Ye2B1i5Vpb https://t.co/t7s7wYWmeP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Automation Engineer: Senior Automation Engineer – Hamilton MT 59840 Skip Navigation Toggle navigation Account – Refine search – View my account – Sign in Job details Senior Automation Engineer – Requisition ID: WD****** – Position: Full time –… https://t.co/sfKmGZofQ8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hurricane unleashes flooding and landslides as it nears Hawaii: Hurricane Lane weakened as it marched toward Hawaii, but it's list of life-threatening calamities is still going strong. https://t.co/sOPK7XdDpy https://t.co/XqF6CW8vF2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Developer, Mid: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Annapolis Junction, MD Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 8/8/2018 About Us About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’… https://t.co/3wJ1PMlthe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL/Share Point Developer: Career Opportunities at New Horizons St. Louis Student Login Search Site search – – – – Cart St. Louis &amp; Southern Illinois ************ – Home – Training and Certifications – Microsoft Office – Office 365 – Access – Excel –… https://t.co/Itk8aLhDWH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MicroSoft SQL Developer: MicroSoft SQL Developer Ref No.: 18-34558 Location: Sunnyvale, California SQL Server Developer Sunnyvale,CA 12,Months SQL Server 2012 Development, SQL Server 2012 Integration Services (SSIS) Strong Exp designing and developing… https://t.co/6xKDHtmTZb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Irish abuse survivors say Pope must face up to Church's past: The last time a Pope came to Ireland was 1979, and Colm O'Gorman remembers tuning into live television coverage of the visit from his family's home in County Wexford. https://t.co/MOGqduQDQL https://t.co/QYYZH28tFy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SSIS/SQL ETL Developer-Charlotte,NC-Hagerstown,MD: SSIS/SQL ETL Developer-Charlotte,NC-Hagerstown,MD Sign in – Home – Locations – Not finding a job? – Join Our Talent Community – View All Jobs Search by Keyword Email similar jobs to me – Log in with… https://t.co/REtuAYK7I3 https://t.co/uQA4qhj1Z3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: What allegations against Argento tell us: On Sunday, The New York Times reported that Italian actress Asia Argento, whose allegations that she was sexually assaulted by Harvey Weinstein helped launch the #MeToo movement, has been accused of… https://t.co/nnIleJbf29 https://t.co/odxQ8Ix1VZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Engineer SQL/Hadoop/Java or Scala-Vice President: Job Title: Senior Engineer SQL/Hadoop/Java or Scala-Vice President Job ID: ******* Location: Cary Full/Part Time: Full-time Regular/Temporary: Permanent Return to Previous Page Technology Our… https://t.co/rgBy3WPwKb https://t.co/5s8vykIef8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: Title: SQL Developer Organization Name: Energy Exemplar Division: Market Research &amp; Analysis Openings: One Work Schedule: 8:00 am to 5:00 pm Hours per Week: 40 Salary: Based on qualifications Employment Start Date: As early as August 10th,… https://t.co/pA82e5YKxg https://t.co/N0GIj2rkWR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL DevOps Engineer: SQL DevOps Engineer – Clinicient – Login / Support – ************ – Toggle Menu Skip to content – Products &amp; Services – INSIGHT Platform – EMR – Billing &amp; Collection Services – About – About Us – Careers – Contact Us – Resources –… https://t.co/hHvjYqwam7 https://t.co/Zh40nsfbGU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flipping should almost 'be outlawed,' Trump says: President Donald Trump decried those who testify against former confidants to ease legal troubles, bemoaning the practice in an interview aired Thursday. https://t.co/RVBQ5gRMMa https://t.co/ltEYenGLIs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Massive 5,000-year-old burial monument unearthed: Kenya's arid, gullied Lothagam Valley is a throwback to a very distant past. Now, the region is the site of a discovery that has the potential to change how the world views ancient societies and the way… https://t.co/GqiZLDcOJI https://t.co/i1Xd661Ffk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer – Adobe Stock: Job Description The Challenge We’re looking for a senior engineer who loves building services for the creative professional and implementing features across the full Web Solution Stack for Adobe Stock. Adobe Stock is… https://t.co/SqdqAg69qT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GOP lawmaker rips DOJ after indictment: The first two members of Congress to support then-candidate Donald Trump, Rep. Duncan Hunter (R-CA) and Rep. Chris Collins (R-NY), have both been indicted on federal charges. CNN's Sara Sidner reports. https://t.co/21GQSPL8qI https://t.co/WgU7IK1WH9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle PL/SQL Developer: Job Ref: ********** Employer: NTT DATA Country: United States County/State: Pennsylvania Address: Post Date: 16/08/2018 00:10 Req ID: 28294 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible.… https://t.co/CM56FfxnLn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Software Programmer # JN: – Like us on Facebook – Follow us on Twitter – Connect with us on LinkedIn – Instagram – Watch us on YouTube – Visit our page on Glassdoor – Our Blog RSS Feed – Home – Employers – Overview – IT – Engineering –… https://t.co/RQWwCO4fFR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: SQL Developer Ref No.: 18-00584 Location: Cockeysville, Maryland We collaborate. We create. We innovate. Intrigued? You’re a business professional with an innate curiosity that thrives in a dynamic and Agile environment. You appreciate… https://t.co/LzjV0IFrQM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Data Warehouse Architect / SQL Developer: Job Snapshot Employee Type: Contractor Location: Rosslyn, VA Job Type: Information Technology Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 8/16/2018 Job Description SQL Data Warehouse Architect / SQL Developer… https://t.co/Yh2Y8NjPL4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C++/PL/SQL Developer: C++/PL/SQL Developer Ref No.: 18-34939 Location: Charlotte, North Carolina C++, PL/SQL Developer Charlotte, NC Job description 1. Should possess strong technical skills to develop software using C++, Oracle PL/SQL and Unix Shell… https://t.co/4n0uEdaZtd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Support Representative, eSolutions (Temporary): Software Support Representative, eSolutions (Temporary) ======================================================= The Software Support Representative on the Application Support Team is responsible… https://t.co/lMSAdCPLs1 https://t.co/hmvZJg24gP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAS/SQL Developer: SAS/SQL Developer SAS/SQL Developer – Interacting with Clients to understand Business Requirements (Analytics &amp; Insight process) — Create/ modify SAS/ SQL codes using SAS enterprise guide — Create VBA routines to match the system… https://t.co/Z9oxjGpFGL https://t.co/Z37ePfXji2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Video shows man set SUV on fire in driveway: Authorities hope surveillance video showing a suspected arsonist setting an SUV on fire in someone's driveway will help lead to an arrest. https://t.co/p0iXOaIy6o https://t.co/EZzRfswxlt]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>