<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Google and the Rise of 'Digital Wellbeing': Google wants to unglue people from their phones. But like other wellness trends, "digital wellbeing" promises more than it can deliver. https://t.co/zhyGVMPO4W https://t.co/xRzk4IiXSu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Channel Center of Excellence (CoE) Global Manager- Hybrid Cloud: Job Description As the leader of the IBM Cloud Channel Center of Excellence (CoE), this manager will have the following primary responsibilities Lead a team of IBM Cloud WW channel and… https://t.co/YbSrV9k3Y5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ebola outbreak in Democratic Republic of Congo: The government of the Democratic Republic of Congo declared an outbreak of Ebola hemorrhagic fever, a rare and deadly disease, on Tuesday, the World Health Organization reported. The declaration came after… https://t.co/1N0G7QGCLb https://t.co/vpx4bnH2Xy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Favor Delivery Driver (No Experience Needed &amp; Flexible): Are you looking for a flexible way to earn extra cash daily, make your own schedule, and provide a great experience to customers, all while having fun? You are in luck, Favor’s personal delivery… https://t.co/INND627MCL https://t.co/LWIIKkEkdD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Consultant 4 – Enterprise PM Tools and Automation Business Analyst: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we want to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them succeed financially. We’re looking for talented people who will put our… https://t.co/VrGf2JeZHo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The President has a ravenous desire to eradicate Obama's legacy and a propensity for global TV drama: Donald Trump's exit from the Iran nuclear deal was one of the most significant moments of his presidency -- and cemented a sharp turn in decades of US… https://t.co/oeJKcyKYAL https://t.co/py3BUJEKVR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer – Application Programmer Analyst 3: Job Description This position is available for a Java Developer and System Analyst in the Consumer Lending area within the Enterprise Information Technology (EIT). In this role, the selected team member… https://t.co/j1nCSiHO63]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer – Application Programmer Analyst 3: Job Description This position is available for a Java Developer and System Analyst in the Consumer Lending area within the Enterprise Information Technology (EIT). In this role, the selected team member… https://t.co/vDQVyLUxIl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Program Manager Core Measures (Register Nurse) / Quality Management / NYC: Job Description As a Core Measures Program Manager you will provide leadership and coordination in the execution of daily program activities, assist in development and design of… https://t.co/hroiK9wnSW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Direct Support Professional-Fulltime-Fargo: Core CHI Behaviors:  The following behaviors have been identified as critical to all leadership roles at CHI. Integrity &amp; Character – exhibits high standards of personal conduct by engaging in ethical… https://t.co/Eyl9llKncL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Favor Delivery Driver (No Experience Needed &amp; Flexible): Are you looking for a flexible way to earn extra cash daily, make your own schedule, and provide a great experience to customers, all while having fun? You are in luck, Favor’s personal delivery… https://t.co/2tJPaZkNMl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Favor Delivery Driver (No Experience Needed &amp; Flexible): Are you looking for a flexible way to earn extra cash daily, make your own schedule, and provide a great experience to customers, all while having fun? You are in luck, Favor’s personal delivery… https://t.co/k1LUoFzU5h https://t.co/epD6Z1NCnd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's all about accessories at the Met Gala: See what celebrities are wearing at this year's Met Gala in New York. https://t.co/bgURxnRy9O https://t.co/UFxrYSNd8W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analytics Software Developer: Are you ready to be part of a leading global engineering design house specializing in the design and development of embedded software, electronics, and electro-mechanics? What we’re looking for · Highly motivated software… https://t.co/H5p3vEF7wI https://t.co/z62OrGyGBx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electrical Instrument Technician: CalPortland – “EXPECT MORE… WE DELIVER!”This is us…– Best-in-Class, industry leader with a rich 126-year history– Largest building materials contributor to some of the West’s biggest construction projects including:•… https://t.co/eV688bvNEi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lens, Google's Visual Search Tool, Gets Its Most Significant Update Yet: Google Lens now works in more than 10 native Android cameras, bringing it one step closer to dominating visual search. https://t.co/9Dz9mrMHHk https://t.co/CpGecDLtpQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 Best Wireless Gaming Headsets of 2018 (PS4, Xbox One, PC, Switch): No matter how you game, these are the best wireless gaming headsets out there. https://t.co/SVPwMeP1R7 https://t.co/MoWgrKQMMu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst – IT: Requirements: * Bachelor’s degree required. * Strong business analyst skills required. * Project Management/Coordination skills highly desirable. * Supports Vehicle Safety and Regulatory Compliance suite of applications *… https://t.co/IP5EXXd0t4 https://t.co/EmCa4nKECy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quantitative Risk Analyst Lead – MIS Risk Analytics: Purpose of Job We are currently seeking a Lead Quantitative Risk Analyst-MIS Risk Analytics for our San Antonio, TX facility. The Lead Quantitative Risk Analyst is responsible for designing and… https://t.co/Hs62TWeJEq https://t.co/U8ZALnzOF1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back-End Engineer – Stealth – Cyber Security – Healthcare: New York City, NY Full-time $120k – $140k Posted Today If you are a Back-End Engineer – Stealth – Cyber Security – Healthcare with experience, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us… https://t.co/5AMbOkPhRS https://t.co/4M17W3s7hK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meditech Senior Analyst: Job ID: 245792 Meditech Senior Analyst Amsterdam, New York Regular / Day Additional Job Information Title: Solutions Develop Senior Analyst City, State:  Amsterdam, NY Location:  NYAMS 427 St Marys Hospital Department:   Meditech… https://t.co/kAPNzU5kcN https://t.co/dFHoRqihzQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google I/O 2018 Liveblog: News From Google's Big Show: Follow along as WIRED's staff covers Google's biggest event of the year. https://t.co/QBPirhZ2kd https://t.co/MSKgNQcIfW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Burnett: Why would Trump take the Fifth?: CNN's Erin Burnett breaks down Rudy Giuliani's comments that President Trump may assert his Fifth Amendment Rights in an interview with special counsel Robert Mueller, even though Trump has stated in the past… https://t.co/q3tYOKYzS3 https://t.co/Li03woSLUz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Service Desk Technician: Service Desk Technician Job Category: Information Technology Requisition Code: 2018-IND-008 Location: Indianapolis, IN FT / PT / Temp Full Time Hours Per Week 40 hours Summary: GAI is undergoing exciting growth! Put your skills… https://t.co/EMaPYJK5j1 https://t.co/VneKZHqFio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Software Engineer – Systems: Job ID: 33495 Lead Software Engineer – Systems Our client is seeking a Lead Software Engineer with specialization in Linux embedded systems device programming. A successful candidate will manage a portion of the team… https://t.co/uCpmlfltdr https://t.co/395p6fT20d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The cruelty of the Trump administration strikes again https://t.co/577Y8hw9iI https://t.co/Ht2efWwmxg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch Microsoft Build 2018 Right Here: Microsoft's developer conference kicks off with a keynote address at 8:30 am PST on Monday May 7. Watch it here. https://t.co/4iPALMhIAb https://t.co/I5ncYugHmg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Melania Trump to announce formal platform today: Melania Trump will announce her eagerly awaited formal platform Monday during a Rose Garden event, nearly 16 months into her tenure as first lady. https://t.co/dJ2rTlioK3 https://t.co/6OpntvWlGH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Risk Quant Developer – Capital Markets Application Systems Engineer 1: Job Description Enterprise Finance &amp; Information Technology offers technology and services that exceed Wells Fargo customers’ expectations and directly enable them to succeed… https://t.co/OjJ2ZRsa20]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Network Engineer: We are currently seeking a motivated, career and customer oriented Sr. Network Engineer to join our team in Arlington, VA to begin an exciting and challenging career with Unisys Federal Systems. Experience in network infrastructure… https://t.co/KhCaIOVszc https://t.co/t78pHDqf64]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Assurance Project Manager: SUNDIAL SOFTWARE IS CURRENTLY RECRUITING FOR A PROJECT MANAGER FOR A CONTRACT OPPORTUNITY. QUALITY ASSURANCE PROJECT MANAGER DESCRIPTION The Quality Assurance Project Manager will work with a talented team to develop… https://t.co/9OBNYeIm8r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ServiceNow-Developer—Norcross–GA: ServiceNow Developer – Norcross, GA 3169 Holcomb Bridge Rd, Jefferson Plaza Norcross, Georgia, 30071 United States ServiceNow Developer – Norcross, GA The opportunity: – Actively participate in the complete software… https://t.co/BjiF2WmzRa https://t.co/b1nuvas7Wv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Company Description Dropbox is a leading global collaboration platform that’s transforming the way people work together, from the smallest business to the largest enterprise. With more than 500 million registered users across more than… https://t.co/aNO9RNNy9m https://t.co/DMnX3NAM9X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[House Intel chair threatens Sessions with contempt over Russia materials: House Intelligence Committee Chairman Devin Nunes warned Sunday that he plans to urge lawmakers "this week" to hold Attorney General Jeff Sessions in contempt of Congress for… https://t.co/qkElAR5Hig https://t.co/G8BI1ugN2L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce Consultant: As we are primarily a remote organization, we are open to candidates located anywhere in the US. Who we are: Mavens works to elevate healthcare worldwide. We connect people to cures using best-in-class cloud technology solutions.… https://t.co/jmzM89QgEj https://t.co/8DU6vreGCf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer/Lead: Description: Leidos ranks in the top 40 on LinkedIn’s 2017 "Top Companies" list. We offer challenging and meaningful problems, a collaborative culture, and support for your career goals and growth. We are seeking a talented… https://t.co/DCjkJXB2rT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer, Ceribell EEG Cloud Platform: Who We Are: Ceribell is a fast growing venture-backed medical device start-up company founded by two faculty members at Stanford University. We have developed a highly innovative… https://t.co/hpLqxysyzQ https://t.co/WkHfCyT5th]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Services Manager: Description:The Health Products and Solutions Group is seeking an experienced Network Services Manager to lead a Telecommunications team consisting of Data Communications, Voice Communications, Audio/Visual, and… https://t.co/4tt4jYK8jY https://t.co/KkIIWggxIa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: Senior Java Developer Toggle navigation – About Us – Inside Luxoft – Benefits – Automotive – Excelian – Training &amp; Communities – Relocation Program – Social Responsibility – Discover Us – Events – Referral Program – Recruitment… https://t.co/QRmmQqOmz5 https://t.co/eObtljh7ne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hardware Engineer/Systems Integrator: DESCRIPTION: The Hardware Engineer/Systems Integrator will be a key member of a Software Engineering Services team sustaining and deploying the Biometrics Automated Toolset-Army (BAT-A) which is finding increased use… https://t.co/Mv0c5Oztop https://t.co/xHky0AfqlM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Crimes Unit Technology Senior Associate: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities. Learn more… https://t.co/AfOuU7UJDl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Assurance Innovation &amp; Technology – Software Architect Manager: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities.… https://t.co/7Dk9zwQn6c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man who killed Indian engineer in Kansas bar gets life in prison: A Kansas man who killed an Indian engineer at a sports bar in Olathe was sentenced to life in prison for the shooting that injured two others and drew international attention. https://t.co/tbrhXYQyaj https://t.co/weNSIL9HBC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Site Operations Manager: Description: Leidos has a career opening for a Site Operations Manager located in Alexandria, VA. POSITION SUMMARY: The job of the Site Operations Manager is to be responsible for managing daily CONUS &amp; OCONUS site operations… https://t.co/JEDxtbMSKZ https://t.co/5qPGFuWZZf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Linux Systems Administrator: Description:The Defense and Intelligence group at Leidos currently has an immediate opening for a Senior Linux Systems Administrator at San Antonio, Texas.   This position is dedicated to the support of the Defense… https://t.co/DDxPJIXCAW https://t.co/Ai83qwvA9F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Engineer of Data Science: Amgen is seeking a Principal Engineer of Data Science to be based out of our Thousand Oaks, CA global headquarters or our office in Cambridge, MA, and who will report to the Executive Director of Process Development… https://t.co/t8XV4vbxco https://t.co/bIb3e0Kspc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Assurance Innovation &amp; Technology – Senior DevOps Engineer: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for our clients and identify opportunities.… https://t.co/DCHe6WjxEy https://t.co/uqRJNiud4K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple Beats Headphone Sale: Studio3, Solo3, PowerBeats (and Other Tech Deals): The new Beats Studio3 Wireless and other headphones are on sale, along with other great deals this weekend. https://t.co/6gNKQUZAOd https://t.co/tN2uyFEjCK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RN – Forensics: Overview At WellStar we all share common goals. That’s what makes us so successful – and such an integral part of our communities. We want the same things, for our organization, for our patients, and for our colleagues. As the largest… https://t.co/xX1xpwdF0D https://t.co/JhgnO2SZmi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce (SFDC) Administrator / Contract / PA: Position Title: SFDC Admin Location: Radnor, PA Type: Contract Required Skills: We would need a SFDC admin resource for one of our clients soon. Here is the job description which we are looking for this… https://t.co/J9kXrAPcsd https://t.co/PdzBT4urBq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MPS IT Developer: MPS IT Developer at HP Inc. Skip Navigation Careers Search for jobsWorking at HPFaqs Sign in &amp; apply Blog Search jobs Keyword CategorySelectAdministrationBusiness PlanningCorporate AdministrationEngineeringEngineering… https://t.co/fl2aKSXT3L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Brokerage Transformation Manager: Cloud Brokerage Transformation Manager 126196BR As a Brokerage Transformation Manager with IBM GTS Cloud Brokerage Services team, you will be responsible to collaborate with the Brokerage Delivery and account teams… https://t.co/tDckvC1BnI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge tosses Kennedy nephew's murder conviction: The Connecticut Supreme Court has vacated Michael Skakel's conviction in a decades-old murder case and ordered a new trial. https://t.co/h0yYfPBS37 https://t.co/7tz6khDSlH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pence swears in openly gay ambassador: Vice President Mike Pence swears in Richard Grenell, who is openly gay, as US ambassador to Germany. https://t.co/hdj9t5reRG https://t.co/3Gts6JBXrK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer/Developer: Software Engineer/Developer Expedent Corp Irving, TX. Develop Design, implement, review, repair &amp; improve Existing Code Required Java, C++, VB, Oracle, Linux .NET. C#, https://t.co/GUAVEoxYxU, MVC, MS SQL Server, Can work… https://t.co/FmoR9LO2n3 https://t.co/XZiSAGpA4h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Europe's Kentucky Derby drought could come to an end: He's tall, dark and handsome and named after a German composer. https://t.co/DkOBfZgkzK https://t.co/QsVl71Odcd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manager 3, Program Planning &amp; Scheduling:   Job Description – Manager 3, Program Planning &amp; Scheduling (17027036) Manager 3, Program Planning &amp; Scheduling Requisition ID : 17027036 Location : United States-California-Redondo Beach US Citizenship Required… https://t.co/xHt0xudyua https://t.co/SGX6ohHgNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democratic rep.: Yes, that's me in the complaint. No, I did not assault teen: Democratic Rep. Tony Cardenas of California is vehemently denying accusations that he sexually assaulted a 16-year-old girl in 2007. https://t.co/Mw0BrOZyzS https://t.co/ug20rtZeWJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RF Electronics Engineer 5:   Job Description – RF Electronics Engineer 5 (18008732) RF Electronics Engineer 5 Requisition ID : 18008732 Location : United States-California-Point Mugu US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation Assistance:… https://t.co/HqlEuIjbxw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer 1: Performs services to enable all aspects of the network to include maintenance, sustainment of existing networks, and identification/correction of complex internetwork issues. ALL SHIFTS AVAILABLE:6am -2:30pm;2pm -10:30pm;10pm-6:30am.… https://t.co/DaHT0gaVxi https://t.co/ix9UJRSaMF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[35,000 pounds of ground beef being recalled: A North Carolina food processing company that supplies meat to Kroger is recalling more than 35,000 pounds of ground beef because it might be contaminated with bits of hard plastic. https://t.co/vK5bMujiXJ https://t.co/Y88FJPVwAy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Transportation Lead: Job Summary With over 300 locations across the US, Apria Healthcare’s mission is to improve the quality of life for our 1.8 million patients at home by providing home respiratory services and select medical equipment to help them… https://t.co/fMxqIZLrNy https://t.co/qsf2imQRhs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Land Development Engineer – Roads/Highways: Walnut Creek, CA Full-time $80k – $130k Posted Today If you are a Senior Civil Engineer with Land Development experience, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us – Competitive base salary OPEN DOE –… https://t.co/l01S3Ibkgg https://t.co/xrR1GF8FiS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VP, Operations / Data, Finance and Headcount Management:   Job Description – VP, Operations / Data, Finance and Headcount Management (00018850) Job Description  VP, Operations / Data, Finance and Headcount Management – (00018850) Description   Improve… https://t.co/8cSuYDMviY https://t.co/3ON0ctAmtO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Program Manager: IT Program Manager – MOJA Job Openings &gt;&gt; IT Program Manager IT Program Manager Summary Title:IT Program Manager ID:A26640 Job Category:N/A Location:Chantilly, VA. Description ***An active Top Secret/SCI Full Scope/Poly security… https://t.co/d7SEVtUhdd https://t.co/wDRToGEQUz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Security Engineer: Fivesky is looking for a highly passionate DevOps Security Engineer to join a team of talented/smart cloud vulnerability experts in a challenging and innovative environment. The ideal candidate must possess knowledge of cloud… https://t.co/I4ZbjQfg0D https://t.co/WQ9jCzY2Gi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embedded Software Engineer San Jose CA: Embedded Software Engineer San Jose, CA Fulltime Position Job Description – Experience on ARM or Intel based architecture &amp; thorough understanding of development &amp; debugging on ARM or Intel based systems. –… https://t.co/a7YeQrSR2z https://t.co/q3HEp1D2co]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bystanders rush to man trapped in crash: Witnesses worked together to pull a victim from a burning vehicle after a big rig crashed into a car in Los Angeles. https://t.co/L46kgu9wxM https://t.co/ISJYbaAxZz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Master Automation Test Engineer #R44491: Master Automation Test Engineer Requisition ID R44491 Capital One Services, LLC in Richmond, VA; Multiple positions available: -Lead overall engineering, design, development and execution of complex automated… https://t.co/EO1H39SE40]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Clinical Data Manager (Epping): *** No one with less than 2 years industry experience will be considered. *** *** No third party candidates will be considered. *** Candidates MUST have a minimum of specific domain experience and no resumes will be… https://t.co/AX8hwEVDUy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eaton Leadership Development Program: Global (MBA):   Job Description – Eaton Leadership Development Program: Global (MBA) (044120) Job Description  Eaton Leadership Development Program: Global (MBA) – (044120)  Description   We make what matters work.… https://t.co/cAi1kFtVyB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AWS Solutions Architect: GreenZone Solutions, Inc. is currently seeking an AWS Solutions Architect to support a federal client by leveraging an expertise in cloud solutions to provide strategic direction and technical oversight for the changing… https://t.co/qzHTlPIqog https://t.co/nAFUhL8gS4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supplier Quality Engineer / Manassas, VA: Req ID : 428945BR Job Code/Title : E1582:QA Engineer Job Description : At Lockheed Martin Rotary and Mission Systems (RMS), we are driven by innovation and integrity. We believe that by applying the highest… https://t.co/IH9mzdmDQ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Program System Architect: Global Research &amp; DevelopmentOur Global Commitment to DeliverAround 3 million individuals worldwide suffer from renal failure. With innovative products and therapies we define highest standards for the dialysis… https://t.co/TQ7z0YUm7c https://t.co/wmkzkMXm9G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interface Developer (Mid-Level): Careers | BizFlow BPM Software and Business Process Transformation Solutions – Contact – Blog – News – Products Products – BPM – Case Management – Cloud/PaaS – Tasking Frameworks – New Business and Underwriting – Claims… https://t.co/uu5trcWu87 https://t.co/VT6UbrIqqW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst II: Job ID 11221 Type Regular Full-Time Company Fred Hutchinson Cancer Research Center Location US-WA-Seattle Category Information Technology More information about this job Overview Cures Start Here. At Fred Hutchinson Cancer Research… https://t.co/1HBI8BViue https://t.co/1jBi7UCI6k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coke and Hershey's costs are going up. Will you pay more? https://t.co/c2efqZTlQc https://t.co/EKHPT1Uq6R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staff Engineer: Staff Engineer Job location is Seattle, WA Use knowledge of cloud computing, information security, &amp; advanced data mining to develop &amp; implement technical engineering solutions to complex video streaming issues. Design, develop, unit test… https://t.co/8HkGn1Gi6P https://t.co/M5yFB7dbYP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: https://t.co/1lLRyVf69V, Inc. has the following opportunities available in Salt Lake City, UT: · Senior Java Developer (Req#: 16-3241): Assist with continuous development of cloud platform w/ focus on improved features &amp; functionality for… https://t.co/gsxXWzAmxM https://t.co/u6N09nRjz7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carmakers and big tech struggle to keep batteries free from child labor https://t.co/Jg5osdRppc https://t.co/YLH6ucgWGR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Developer (Liferay/Java) #6855: Senior Developer (Liferay/Java), Portal Services.  Analyze business requirements and design, code, test and develop applications using Liferay and Java.  Test applications and identify and resolve issues.  Modify… https://t.co/7cSBHhCoVT https://t.co/1QTt9k5RTV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chinese video app targets 'subversive' Peppa Pig in online clean-up: A children's cartoon character has become an unlikely victim of China's ongoing push to clean up cyberspace. https://t.co/Ex2t9Sg6PP https://t.co/F6svzqnvmq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Structural Engineer:     Come join the Farnsworth Group team and find out why our employees earned us the Great Place to Work certification!   Farnsworth Group is a full-service engineering and architecture firm with offices and employment opportunities… https://t.co/OAXrqtdFM6 https://t.co/IaKQyju3rM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook F8 2018 Liveblog: Follow along with WIRED's staff as Mark Zuckerberg takes the stage after a scandal-filled year. https://t.co/yqgtiYHvAj https://t.co/9C6mffynBe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Web Designer: Interested in working for a growing, fast-paced company with diverse projects and technologies? COLAB is looking for talented team members to help shape the companys future. At COLAB, we have a close-knit team with no office… https://t.co/tW188Sa0r8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Customer Operations Manager: Customer Operations Manager 10-4, a Trimble Company, is redefining the future of freight execution with intelligent Supply Chain Visibility that delivers real-time visibility and streamlined communication. Our software… https://t.co/pRoq5nsAES https://t.co/oYcU4ZNRV8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal DEVOPS Software Engineer:   Job Description – Principal DEVOPS Software Engineer (18002749) Principal DEVOPS Software Engineer Requisition ID : 18002749 Location : United States-Maryland-Annapolis Junction US Citizenship Required for this… https://t.co/H8VSj9Ttk8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Program Manager – Consumer Technology: Overview Other companies make products. We make a difference! Click Here! Contribute to a Safer, More Secure, and More Sustainable World. At UL, we know why we come to work. Thousands of us around the world wake… https://t.co/chGefvsPZ7 https://t.co/QTQd3sbafI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cooper: Trump building a wall of untruth: CNN's Anderson Cooper breaks down the Trump administration's repeated claims that construction on a new border wall has begun. https://t.co/Kn63UtX0xS https://t.co/Eh1Zuk8PTy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook F8 2018: How to Watch Live: Did your invitation get lost in the mail? That's OK. You can watch the whole thing online. https://t.co/pVk25n3RdS https://t.co/jCJbC8t9Q9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Business Analyst: Sr. Business Analyst DHS77558611*Des Moines, IA*The Senior Business Analyst will participate in all phases of the systems development lifecycle from Requirements, Design, Development, Testing, and Implementation to meet business… https://t.co/f42hxScunO https://t.co/h7oYPkc5mW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple Flash Sale (2018): Apple Watch, Mac, iPad, Beats: If you're hunting for a MacBook, iMac, iPad, Apple Watch, or Beats earbuds, you may want to give Best Buy a gander. https://t.co/Vrp3oPotbD https://t.co/6IZcB7Am2x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Release Management: Release Management Analysts, Irvine, CA: Work on Atlassian JIRA to automate internal &amp; external demands. Create analytical matrices reports, dash boards for release services based on JIRA tickets. Develop &amp; maintained UNIX/Perl/Ant… https://t.co/bRUW9Wzkw3 https://t.co/PxWmjsaXV4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Subject Matter Expert (Congressional): Experienced in conferring with senior management using industry expertise to define the client’s strategic information technology business goals and advising in the re-engineering of business processes to meet these… https://t.co/2x6yvdKaBu https://t.co/eiJgqxT0Ma]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Journalists among dozens killed in Afghanistan blasts: At least 21 people, including five journalists, have died in two explosions on Monday morning in the Afghan capital Kabul, according to government officials. https://t.co/gckD2y0uJK https://t.co/fP6ZEgZX2w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: 113762BR Software Developer CA – San Diego 113762BR This is a temporary position of undetermined length. Real time software development including requirements, design, code, test and integration. Required Skills: Realtime Linux, C++… https://t.co/SfdbF8hZW9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Non Destructive Test Tech 3:   Job Description – Non Destructive Test Tech 3 (18007805) Non Destructive Test Tech 3 Requisition ID : 18007805 Location : United States-California-El Segundo US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation… https://t.co/ux6vce1Zc1 https://t.co/OjF75ScqVj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mechanical Project Manager: Job Description Mechanical Project Manager – 1717 S Boulder Ave, Tulsa, OK 74119, USA – Full-time Company Description Imagine a place where responsibility is shared equally among all employees. Where leaders are approachable,… https://t.co/PClq8JeBnZ https://t.co/bg30QE81mU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Administrator: Search Display Loading Close Your account has successfully been deleted. Close Message deleted. Job has been emailed. Job(s) has been emailed. Send email is not working. Please try again. Close Notifications and Messages… https://t.co/r6RGS33cOD https://t.co/yiEQ4M5tsW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[eCommerce Data Analyst: ECOMMERCE DATA ANALYST (REPORTING) This is an exciting opportunity for a Data Analyst or Reporting guru to join a fast growing company in the Smyrna area! You will be responsible for monitoring and reporting of the day-to-day… https://t.co/V2U8GIwjbX https://t.co/95vK1wwsyd]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>