<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Be still. He is God. You may be overwhelmed. But He isn’t. And He is for you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best part of working from a coffeeshop? Random conversations with strangers about Jesus! #BeIntentional]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RCChurchDC: Absent a relationship with the Word of God, you will chronically underestimate the power of God. https://t.co/OS75w9vMlp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't remember the dentist being this fun when I was a kid! https://t.co/pIkNfJeNIj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The door to lead rarely opens for those who don’t have the character to serve!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes!!! https://t.co/neXd6N6Icj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you to every single volunteer who sacrificed to make this morning so powerful @RCChurchDC!  I love you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Newest band member! https://t.co/UD2DGyjQHU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hearts astonished by the gospel lead to lives shaped by the gospel. Pray for astonishment has you gather with the church today!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fifteen months into Restoration City and I still get so excited for Sunday mornings.  Don't ever want to get over it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Distraction is one of the greatest joy killers in our lives. Be present. Be focused. Be purposeful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not what we HAVE time for that defines us.  It's what we MAKE time for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A prayerless life will be a powerless life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love everything about this!! https://t.co/8xCuyM4j3t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's no place for slavery in our world! Joining the chorus raising our voices against the… https://t.co/xeJWZTFDuC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Use your voice for the good of others, not the glory of self.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's the day. Join enditmovement in shining a light on slavery. All it takes is a ❌ on your… https://t.co/hITHW5czAk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Secrecy builds suspicion. Transparency builds trust.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love @JohnPiper and his thoughts on life after 70. https://t.co/VVsemFFlT6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't miss this! https://t.co/7G8ViHAm0A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The shifting sands of our world offer little hope.  The limitless power of God offers unlimited hope!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The gospel compels us to live with unhurried urgency.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God prunes deeply so we can bear fruit abundantly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teaching the boys the finer points of fort building! https://t.co/pt9Pk6wnO7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Restoration City, this is what we're all about! Just some of the people at our Nicaragua… https://t.co/fuWv3jW4X9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just spent the morning with our Community Group Leaders - so excited for everything that’s ahead!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you’re trying to hide it, you already know you’re headed in the wrong direction.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We always want the miracle shortcut. Frequently, God gives sustaining grace for the long haul!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leaders make clear what others prefer to leave ambiguous. Clarity requires courage!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[College students, this summer could be life changing! Join us in DC &amp; Nicaragua for 8 weeks: https://t.co/E77traCVwf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The rays of God's faithfulness will burn off the fog of our doubts. [Today's Blog: https://t.co/I2YL8iwF1w]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The power of God is found in the presence of God.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New to Restoration City? Come have lunch with Laura and I this Sunday! https://t.co/tX1GTGJULs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamesmarshallg don’t even point to the current weather as proof!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A God who gives us what we need is infinitely better than a God who gives us what we want. His ways are higher!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grace destroys self-importance. - @timkellernyc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey, remember that time complaining about the weather made it better? Me neither.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Something so powerfully uniting about celebrating Jesus around the communion table!  Loved this morning!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brr...it's cold!  But our gathering is going to be so worth it!  Remember, we're in the Crystal City Marriott this morning!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RCChurchDC: To be like Christ is to empty yourself for God's glory. Philippians 2:5-11]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday, Mr. Lincoln. Leadership leaves a legacy! https://t.co/CGYVoFArZt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The trials of today are not too much for "the God of endurance and encouragement"(Rm.15:5)!!  He lifts and strengthens!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Praying for @louiegiglio, @shelleygiglio &amp; the @passion268 team in South Africa. Amazing nights unfolding on the other side of the globe!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our first ever College Community Group meets tonight at 8pm in the Marvin Center on GW’s campus!! Pray God moves powerfully!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A leader's response to failure: own it, learn from it, move on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Outdo one another in showing honor."(Rm.12:10) Imagine if we competed to give, rather than receive, honor!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're sending a team to Nicaragua with @NewHopeProjects this July!  Interested?  Find out more: https://t.co/fwUO3ZL15D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jamesmarshallg @jdgreear That's a little thing we like to call contextualization!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really special days at Restoration City - so much of what we've prayed for is coming to life!  Thank You, Jesus!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This morning’s big headline: Jesus is alive! He’s building His church and we get to be a part of it! Incredible!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fasting doesn't prove our strength.  It reminds us of our weakness and need for grace.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best part of yesterday? ServeDC is more than halfway full after one day of sign-ups! Don’t miss out: https://t.co/Hk7TG9t8cF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you @spotswoodnews for your prayers tonight. So grateful for your partnership in the gospel! https://t.co/P5bdN5fIwI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So happy for my friends Dan and Twila! Congrats Mr. &amp; Mrs. Iten! #danandtwila2016 https://t.co/agvbo21RNQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Restoration City, we're fasting as a church next week.  Here's why: https://t.co/zMNIaO9q2Y https://t.co/zGXwJ82gZi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s hard to live a joyful life with your face buried in a phone. Ironic tweet, I know. But true!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm asking everyone at Restoration City to join me in 3 things between now &amp; Easter. You in? [New Blog:https://t.co/z7cpk1lutE]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only the gospel motivates sustained sacrifice for the good of others intent on doing you harm.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The church isn't an irrelevant escape from the world.  It's a powerful source of transformation in the world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cultural decay amplifies the need for gospel renewal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LIVE on #Periscope: Q&amp;A: The Gospel and Politics  https://t.co/ZW6fSyTcYZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going live on Periscope in 5 min. Q&amp;A. The Gospel &amp; Politics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sermon Q&amp;A tonight at 8.30 on Periscope. Main Topic: The Gospel and Politics. Get your questions ready!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love #SpringForward - first time my kids haven’t gotten up early in months!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spring Forward. Change your clocks and get ready for a great morning wth Restoration City!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The boys travel in style! https://t.co/koP1YsICYE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spent the day in Philly celebrating Laura’s grandmother. Sorrow that she’s gone. Joy that she’s with Jesus!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to be baptized on Easter Sunday?  Click here to let us know: https://t.co/qJXIUDxzW9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently he's skipping walking and going straight to a scooter! https://t.co/dK8wSKfYv8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only Jesus can hold up under the weight of our greatest desires!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, God doesn’t follow our script. He’s writing a better, harder, more beautiful one!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prayer is a joyful wrestling to align our hearts with God’s, not His with ours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just got home from Community Group - love those people so much! Joy is found in community!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loved grabbing lunch and seeing so many Restoration City friends hanging out today!… https://t.co/e5GpLaMXFN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Praying we come ready to meet with Jesus this morning - expectations can’t ever be too high when He’s in the house!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So excited for tomorrow at Restoration City...can't come fast enough!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The more you guard your heart, the less you need to guard your words.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best thing about the beach? Walks with this girl! #latergram https://t.co/TO8UwxsgkB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saddened by the passing of Laura's grandmother but grateful for her legacy of joy, humor and faith.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most exciting Presidential news of 2016! Trusting God’s leadership through you @jdgreear: https://t.co/zf6GQkHEci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back in DC after some incredible days with family! Loved the time with Laura, Jack, Aidan &amp; my… https://t.co/9jSqh9olVl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starting Point is one of my favorite things we do as a church! Love meeting so many new friends. https://t.co/gCxvTHFnri]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you're coming to Restoration City tomorrow, don't forget the Diaper and Supply Drive for… https://t.co/2IShv4RAKA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True - but I'm not sure I'm helping the cause very much! https://t.co/cqyDa6xYOJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leaders live in the land of uncertainty and risk.  Nothing new is born out of certainty and safety.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deep bonds require both shared sacrifice and shared celebration. Can’t skip either!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hard to find a greater joy killer than comparison.  It's a one way ticket to pride or despair.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus is constantly leading.  Especially when we can’t see the path for ourselves!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BethMooreLPM: The promises of God haven't disappeared from the page. They've disappeared from our prayers. We've traded private prayer…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[15 more minutes of thinking per day would result in an hour’s less doing. Focus on what matters!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great advice for preachers as well! https://t.co/Ss6hJgg8Ti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Among genuine Christians the contention is for the lowest place;among sham Christians the controversy is for the higher positions. -Spurgeon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before she moved back to NC, Beth Ridgill wrote a letter to our church. Read it here: https://t.co/2XEUKEW6lB https://t.co/YktBTn4vox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let’s gather with the same excitement and anticipation this Sunday as last. The tomb is still empty!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stalled out in your relationship with God? Looking to grow? This next series is for you! Can't… https://t.co/1YRdUalaib]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We talk much about working, but working is better than talking about working." - CH Spurgeon. Less talking, more doing!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People may not agree with our theology but they shouldn't be able to argue with our lives.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait to spend the next 8 weeks letting this letter soak into our hearts at Restoration… https://t.co/6Y9z7uiQ6q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My heroes are the people in the game, not the critics on the sidelines.  Get out of the cheap seats and onto the field!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest freedom comes when we are completely controlled by the love of Christ.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>