<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[South Korea's taxi drivers protest against plans for carpool service: Tens of thousands of South Korean taxi-drivers held a massive rally on Thursday in Seoul, the capital, saying a carpooling service planned by the operator of the country's top chat app… https://t.co/6QUBnthJMR https://t.co/0Kl5FhmEfp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweden's Ericsson third-quarter sales, profits surge as savings kick in: Mobile telecom equipment maker Ericsson on Thursday posted operating profits well above forecasts, boosted by rising sales for next-generation 5G gear in North America, and said it… https://t.co/ATDIiGkyxg https://t.co/TrtYmdP3d6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TSMC third-quarter profit slips 0.9 percent amid trade war uncertainty: Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co Ltd (TSMC) , the world's largest contract chipmaker, reported a 0.9 percent fall in third-quarter net profit, amid worries over trade tensions… https://t.co/z2g4LtNatt https://t.co/zFogZ9RyW2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tax byte: Africans fear trend towards levies on data, services: The brisk business Julius Kirya did from his cash transfer kiosk in the Ugandan capital has slowed right down with a new tax on mobile money. Many of his customers have returned to sending… https://t.co/dA2DdqwCdi https://t.co/nxjGqGp6yS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TSMC third-quarter profit down 0.9 percent, in line with market forecasts: Taiwan Semiconductor Manufacturing Co Ltd (TSMC) , the world's largest contract chipmaker, said on Thursday third-quarter net profit fell 0.9 percent. https://t.co/Xv7p9sHLvL https://t.co/kJvq2PbPlP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Robot market growth slows as trade war hits industrial spending: robot industry chief: An escalating trade war between the United States and China has dampened manufacturers' appetite for investment in equipment, causing growth in the industrial robot… https://t.co/DKwOn8kh59 https://t.co/AOoUBeC8gx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ericsson posts third-quarter operating profit above expectations: Mobile telecom equipment maker Ericsson reported on Thursday a substantially higher third-quarter operating profit than expected and said it was tracking well towards its long-term targets. https://t.co/rEdBUZ9syO https://t.co/C68CoPTraE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager/Senior Project Manager, Internal Medicine – GI (including UC, Crohn-s, Idiopathic Gastro paresis, IBD an: ICON named by Forbes as one of the best employers in America! ICON was the highest ranked CRO in the best large employers listing,… https://t.co/5UlD0K1gtm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mideast ride-hailing app Careem raises $200 million to expand, expects more funds: Middle East ride-hailing company Careem said on Thursday it had secured $200 million in fresh funding from existing investors and that it expects to raise more to finance… https://t.co/MEFMIms2YJ https://t.co/PdZ7AvZ6kx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/bwYJSm2bUN spies profits in China's giant parcel delivery market: Chinese e-commerce firm https://t.co/bwYJSm2bUN Inc said on Thursday it was launching a parcel delivery business, a move which could help the firm leverage its network of… https://t.co/Po819H090s https://t.co/GtovPrIiMW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP raises guidance as cloud transformation gathers pace: Germany's SAP said that its cloud revenues grew by 41 percent in the third quarter as its business transformation gathers pace, enabling management to raise guidance for revenues and profits this… https://t.co/m1bZgSwl4E https://t.co/L0l0UxnYZN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hacked, scammed and on your own: navigating cryptocurrency 'wild west': When Peggy and Marco Lachmann-Anke learned in January that hackers cracked a 40-character password and cleaned out their cryptocurrency wallet, they did not go to the police or alert… https://t.co/cwsh3NMuSR https://t.co/ibF0IOUOY6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Freedom Consulting Group ************ ************* – Home – Company – Services – Training – Courses – Professional Training – Career – Registration – Contact Us Resources Product/Development Plan Supporting Utilities Courses Our… https://t.co/XLOsFeAlWS https://t.co/78fCpGvEko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook tentatively concludes that spammers were behind recent data breach: WSJ: Facebook Inc has tentatively concluded that a recent hack that affected millions of accounts was perpetrated by spammers, and not a nation-state, the Wall Street Journal… https://t.co/Wb6jOvmyVa https://t.co/QArubjV1CQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Facebook, public funds join push to remove Zuckerberg as chairman: Four major U.S. public funds that hold shares in Facebook Inc on Wednesday proposed removing Chief Executive Officer Mark Zuckerberg as chairman following several high-profile scandals… https://t.co/2ZyxzTWw6I https://t.co/76hq6N9o20]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seven international banks agree to launch digital trade finance network: Seven banks, including HSBC and Banco Santander , have signed a Memorandum of Understanding (MoU) to create a global digital network in trade finance aiming at allowing cheaper and… https://t.co/RPR7LrV7Al https://t.co/LIF91JtM9h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wooing investors, Rwanda hosts first tantalum-tracking blockchain: Rwanda's mining boss announced on Tuesday the world's first blockchain project to track tantalum from the pit-face to the refinery, part of a push to woo investors seeking a conflict-free… https://t.co/8jHqLfm7b8 https://t.co/USq7Q3WEvf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spec’st Appl Support Analyst: As a Senior Application Support Analyst for Corporate Treasury and Finance, you will have a production services support role for a suite of applications and services.’ A support analyst will be primarily involved with… https://t.co/EWNGPhYPng https://t.co/VatWMAmboL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Job Information: Senior Software Engineer – ******* Job Email Opening Title Senior Software Engineer – ******* EOE StatementCarnegie Mellon University is an Equal Opportunity Employer/Disability/Veteran. Description What We Do:… https://t.co/LbwtZyZIlG https://t.co/ds0MVMbBED]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exclusive: Amazon zooms in on central Mexico for large new warehouse: https://t.co/XCGE1TBbK6 Inc is scouting for land in central Mexico for a fourth distribution center in the country, sources said, aiming at a bigger slice of the burgeoning e-commerce… https://t.co/qpXuDf1nlG https://t.co/RMTMTlS4Ct]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook shareholders back proposal to remove Zuckerberg as chairman: Several public funds that hold shares in Facebook Inc on Wednesday backed a proposal to remove Chief Executive Officer Mark Zuckerberg as chairman, saying the social media giant… https://t.co/ErdIfoUdRx https://t.co/lKSMdD5pI6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber enters trailer leasing business: Uber Technologies Inc [UBER.UL] said on Wednesday it is entering the trailer leasing business. https://t.co/hczGjgvbKL https://t.co/9tIrjiEVLv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT repairman seeks home for Apple collection, possibly world's largest: An Austrian computer repairman has amassed what he believes could be the world's biggest collection of old Apple computers, but it might all soon be destroyed unless someone can take… https://t.co/GmWl5kaOy0 https://t.co/mdGV5s4ErS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple gives U.S. users tool to see what data it has collected: Apple Inc on Wednesday rolled out an online tool to users in the United States and several other countries to download, change or delete all the data that the iPhone maker has collected on… https://t.co/KYH7U9vKma https://t.co/gavj595FGC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Developer: Job Description DUTIES: Develop, support and manage business initiatives and technical projects relating to the AMPS application. Lead java code development efforts across the team utilizing expertise in J-Boss development… https://t.co/QWQ8Vr1nLg https://t.co/R342fB2pxK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP vows to ease cloud transition; German customers less keen: Software company SAP SE said it plans to offer more support to help reluctant clients shift to its latest cloud-based business suite, a transition crucial for its future profitability. https://t.co/pcUuM71yCc https://t.co/EchcqMQ3OE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exclusive: Russian high tech project flounders after U.S. sanctions: U.S. sanctions targeting Russia's nascent high tech industry have caused a Russian microchip company significant financial woes and delayed the launch of an initiative meant to produce… https://t.co/x3Ja8Ag1LD https://t.co/ZSQ9FLimUM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hackers accused of ties to Russia hit three East European companies: cybersecurity firm: Hackers have infected three energy and transport companies in Ukraine and Poland with sophisticated new malware and may be planning destructive cyber attacks, a… https://t.co/m9oaYnq7UB https://t.co/2f6CD9XxM5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla secures Shanghai site for $2 billion China Gigafactory: Tesla Inc has signed an agreement with the Shanghai government for an 860,000 square meter plot of land to build its first overseas Gigafactory, the electric carmaker said in a Chinese social… https://t.co/6XiHRA4CNb https://t.co/wfYEnZl8Qi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hackers accused of ties to Russia hit 3 East European companies: cybersecurity firm: Hackers have infected three energy and transport companies in Ukraine and Poland with sophisticated new malware and may be planning destructive cyber attacks, a software… https://t.co/lKOVRK9yXb https://t.co/ZiJrEkqdfD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla secures Shanghai site for China Gigafactory: Tesla Inc has signed an agreement with the Shanghai government for an 860,000 square meter plot of land to build its first overseas Gigafactory, the electric carmaker said in a Chinese social media post… https://t.co/pxV4aG536V https://t.co/81jfViWzuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla signs agreement in Shanghai for gigafactory site: Tesla Inc has signed an agreement with the Shanghai government for an 860,000 square meter plot of land to build its first overseas Gigafactory, the electric carmaker said in a Chinese social media… https://t.co/5fgrCfAX2J https://t.co/WeWc3BEcyv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Philippine watchdog fines Grab, Uber for rushed merger, drop in service quality: The Philippines' competition watchdog fined ride-hailing firms Grab and Uber Technologies on Wednesday, saying they consummated their merger too soon and that the quality of… https://t.co/J0b7gt5PDG https://t.co/o4a7L2uv8h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ASML's bullish outlook pulls computer chip stocks higher: Semiconductor industry bellwether ASML Holding NV's better-than-expected third quarter results and bullish outlook gave sector stocks a boost on Wednesday after fears of slackening demand had… https://t.co/J8tej9yAhV https://t.co/vQdnfsYeO8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fintech making inroads, but U.S. bank revenues little changed: report: Financial technology startups and other new entrants are making inroads in the U.S. banking market, but have yet to capture a threatening share of bank revenues, according to research… https://t.co/DinqUq9P3z https://t.co/QfEi55VeiO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Technician: Researches, troubleshoots, monitors and maintains systems that affect critical system components for the business and/or stakeholders. May perform duties in one or more of the following disciplines: Print/Document, Telecommunications,… https://t.co/TXz32HIhnh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Summary: The Software Engineer engages in a variety of analytical and programming assignments that facilitate the development, enhancement, and maintenance of software applications and operating systems, as related to Heartland ECSIs… https://t.co/aafNRb4ZeB https://t.co/xJqeGlqEit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Search engine Baidu becomes first China firm to join U.S. AI ethics group: Chinese search engine Baidu Inc has become the first Chinese company to join an artificial intelligence (AI) ethics group led by top U.S. tech firms, amid wider political clashes… https://t.co/ECpnyo7pVu https://t.co/6neKqCZiT4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Company Description With a workforce of over 25,000 people, and opportunities in more than 1,000 different job categories, the City of Philadelphia is the fifth largest city in the United States and one of the largest employers in… https://t.co/AWSD3y3zHL https://t.co/tseOQ6vP4W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber considers minority investors for self-driving car unit: FT: Uber Technologies Inc [UBER.UL] is considering selling minority stakes in its costly self-driving car unit as the ride-hailing firm tries to address rising cost pressures ahead of its… https://t.co/BJeDKjES8d https://t.co/LsHra4u3wi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YouTube back up after widespread outage: Google-owned YouTube said https://t.co/GpBdm1gm5h on Tuesday a widespread issue with some of its services has been resolved, almost two hours after several people took to social media to complain about… https://t.co/hq1iFt6gX9 https://t.co/EgM2ojie0i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/hyVEKumQGu with Azure cloud: ******* with Azure cloud Ref No.:18-16711 Location: Chesterbrook, Pennsylvania Position Type:Contract Start Date: 09/14/2018 Job Title: ******* with Azure cloud Location: Chesterbrook, PA Duration: Longterm… https://t.co/mFgUBI840U https://t.co/LGIGfbJscZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Samsung Electronics buys AI tech firm Zhilabs to boost 5G capabilities: Samsung Electronics Co Ltd said on Wednesday it had acquired artificial intelligence technology firm Zhilabs to enhance its 5G capabilities, marking a major push into the 5G market. https://t.co/SFGsiGzOQR https://t.co/Rqg6jCgSBS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Specialist – Technical Analyst, Global Drug Safety: Job Title: Specialist – Technical Analyst, Global Drug Safety – BUS****** Description Merck &amp; Co., Inc. Kenilworth, N.J., U.S.A. known as Merck in the United States and Canada, is a global health care… https://t.co/7zsUxDGJOJ https://t.co/JOcnoIDOtg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YouTube says looking into reports of user access issues: YouTube, the Google-owned streaming service, said it was looking into reports of issues with its services after several people took to Twitter to complain about broadcasting issues. https://t.co/mZAGQYpL1o https://t.co/MOtQsfR7kd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Full-Stack Developer: To provide senior level system analysis, design, development, and implementation of applications and databases for mainframe-, client/server-, Web-, and/or PC-based systems. Looking for a highly motivated and engagednet-centric… https://t.co/qBqEoeWutj https://t.co/rScouOr9jD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Netflix record subscriber growth dispels Wall Street worries: Netflix Inc hooked 7 million new streaming subscribers from July to September, a third more than Wall Street had expected, reassuring investors who had worried the company was facing a… https://t.co/th666vrGp0 https://t.co/0CdNFMVd6x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Principal Developer- Spring, REST, JavaScript: Java Principal Developer- Spring, REST, JavaScript Consults with internal business groups to provide high-level application software development services or technical support. Provides comprehensive… https://t.co/pU49ZgJF56 https://t.co/hrK4VK1UHN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chinese electric car makers, nurtured by state, now look for way out of glut: Humming away in an industrial estate in the eastern Chinese resort city of Hangzhou, electric vehicle designer Automagic is one of hundreds of companies looking to ride the… https://t.co/WytMGz3P8b https://t.co/etAlmLPnOd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waive wireless bills for some Hurricane Michael victims: U.S. FCC chief: U.S. Federal Communications Commission Chairman Ajit Pai on Tuesday called for wireless carriers to waive October bills for people hardest hit by Hurricane Michael after some… https://t.co/0EDg0WYjXl https://t.co/tvdD7SYtMO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Developer: Careers Center | Application Developer Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome page… https://t.co/BEtiXqqv7g https://t.co/NMDqUkmaXp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Netflix eases Wall Street worries with record quarter: Netflix Inc hooked 7 million new streaming subscribers from July to September, a third more than Wall Street had expected, reassuring investors who had worried the company was facing a slowdown in… https://t.co/67Sb0fTwEL https://t.co/rBPQH0zITV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber boosts bond offering to $2 billion: Bloomberg: Ride-hailing firm Uber Technologies Inc increased the size of its debut bond offering to $2 billion as orders for the private placement swelled, Bloomberg reported on Tuesday, citing people with… https://t.co/dgV3y2m96C https://t.co/KNXDHoDUkk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mexican top court rejects ban on cash fares for ride-hailing firms: The Mexican Supreme Court on Tuesday struck down a ban on cash fares for ride-hailing firms, setting a key precedent for Uber and other industry players seeking to reach millions of… https://t.co/HEemUrNoix https://t.co/5xt5Zr1Iir]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HR Talent Acquisition Project Manager (Investment Management) – Part Time: As a member of the BNY Mellon Investment Management’ Human Resources Project Management team,’ the’ Talent Acquisition Project Manager, in partnership with Global Head of Talent… https://t.co/Uu1Q5Cu23y https://t.co/upK7WTFxja]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber extends safety features to passengers, drivers in Europe, Middle East: Uber Technologies Inc [UBER.UL] is to connect passengers and drivers directly to emergency services in Europe, the Middle East, and Africa as part of a wider rollout of largely… https://t.co/JSI7tTmbwI https://t.co/3RKL4Qnqxw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waive wireless bills for some Hurricane Michael victims: FCC chief: U.S. Federal Communications Commission Chairman Ajit Pai on Tuesday called for wireless carriers to waive October bills for people hardest hit by Hurricane Michael after some Florida… https://t.co/ZjfR08Ray2 https://t.co/M42IfiAjCU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IBM misses revenue estimates as server, software sales slow: International Business Machines Corp missed Wall Street estimates for third-quarter revenue as software sales slow down and a boost from the launch of new server products begins to dry up,… https://t.co/hYpONTEVqB https://t.co/UAoZP964rF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IBM misses revenue estimates as server sales slow: International Business Machines Corp missed Wall Street estimates for third-quarter revenue on Tuesday, weighed down by slowing demand for its mainframe servers. https://t.co/vr7zm4T9oZ https://t.co/Q9OV2JqWVk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Netflix subscriber growth beats estimates, shares surge: Netflix Inc added more subscribers than expected in the third quarter, as new seasons of original shows such as "Orange is The New Black" and "BoJack Horseman" pulled in users. https://t.co/zIxlYBiCaV https://t.co/fKG1k8AWme]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Netflix subscriber growth beats estimates: Netflix Inc added more subscribers than expected in the third quarter, as new seasons of original shows such as "Orange is The New Black" and "BoJack Horseman" pulled in users. https://t.co/tV7nqWa79Z https://t.co/sIevncBoQI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. Senate bill could give Tesla, GM electric car tax credit boost: Tesla Inc and General Motors Co, which have lobbied Congress to lift a cap on electric vehicles eligible for a $7,500 tax credit, could get their way for up to four years under a new… https://t.co/2JTkRHBrPa https://t.co/yY54I3BFa9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FCC to probe Florida wireless outages, urges carriers to waive bills: Federal Communications Commission Chairman Ajit Pai on Tuesday called for wireless carriers to waive bills for October and allow consumers to switch carriers without penalties after… https://t.co/85iX1vqMEj https://t.co/uYc155Ix11]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SEC warns corporate cyber weakness could violate federal law: Public companies that fail to tighten their cyber security controls could be violating federal law, the U.S. Securities and Exchange Commission (SEC) said on Tuesday. https://t.co/LtMZOS3ORW https://t.co/Oi97EKmCqc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Realpage settles U.S. charges over tenant screening reports: Realpage Inc, which provides technology to the real estate industry, agreed to pay $3 million to settle charges that its tenant screening reports violated federal credit reporting law, the U.S.… https://t.co/MS0EPlGl7O https://t.co/R1YMYxpmlT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dell maintains plans to go public despite Icahn opposition: Dell Technologies Inc said on Tuesday it was sticking to its plans to go public by buying back its tracking stock , a day after activist investor Carl Icahn opposed the move. https://t.co/frksjRBUGS https://t.co/OXOhclP5jZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EU regulators ask Sony's rivals and users how it might use power after EMI deal: EU antitrust regulators reviewing Sony Corp's $2.3 billion bid for EMI are asking rivals and users whether they think the Japanese group would use its greater market power… https://t.co/Y7bDG64123 https://t.co/CURGsJpfjJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lyft selects JPMorgan, Credit Suisse for IPO in 2019: source: Ride-hailing company Lyft Inc has chosen JPMorgan Chase &amp; Co, Credit Suisse and Jefferies as underwriters for its initial public offering, slated for the first half of 2019, according to a… https://t.co/IqbzbHmgnX https://t.co/99IqbaDEc7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google to charge smartphone makers for Google Play in Europe: U.S. tech giant Google will charge smartphone makers a licensing fee for using its popular Google Play app store and also allow them to use rival versions of its Android mobile operating… https://t.co/srDTDWvmlf https://t.co/uM1sXSuwrs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Telefonica Brasil rolls out Netflix partnership in paid TV push: Telefonica Brasil SA has begun integrating its pay TV service with Netflix Inc's streaming platforms, Brazil's largest telecoms company said on Tuesday, in another step in its focus on… https://t.co/7mfSV9nuYD https://t.co/3IzHtFoEwF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber IPO proposals value company at $120 billion - WSJ: Ride-hailing giant Uber Technologies Inc [UBER.UL] could be valued at $120 billion, when it finally goes public next year according to proposals made by U.S. banks bidding to run the offering, the… https://t.co/8Q52QPbo1t https://t.co/x2l3BWXOeF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TomTom shares slide 13 percent after Volvo contract loss: Shares in navigation firm TomTom slid 13 percent on Tuesday on news it had lost a contract with carmaker Volvo, renewing worries that Google's entry into in-dashboard software may hurt the Dutch… https://t.co/TwLkrLuedR https://t.co/6gMltFbq2H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huawei launches new flagship phones in bid to keep No. 2 spot: Huawei [HWT.UL] unveiled new flagship smartphones with novel smart camera and video features on Tuesday, as it seeks to sustain momentum among price-conscious consumers. https://t.co/dtIiGyX9eB https://t.co/CgYVIvT24l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate QA Automation Engineer: Associate QA Automation Developer Position Summary CEI’s Custom Applications division is seeking an Associate QA Automation Developer whose passion is helping customers build and improve their testing frameworks using… https://t.co/NZNsBxQDiB https://t.co/29P5l5OfNw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VW targets online sales, over-the-air updates in new contract with European dealers: Volkswagen will overhaul its dealership and sales organization by April 2020 to enable online sales and over-the-air software updates for its new electric cars, the… https://t.co/tvjETZPXuC https://t.co/l8Rd5VCIp6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer – Referral Partnership: Are you an independent web developer with a large network of clients who process e-commerce transactions? Do you design web pages that require an e-commerce solution? Are you looking for proven opportunities to… https://t.co/tpmlzNT0Ha https://t.co/5V8dSneJHV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber proposals value company at $120 billion in a possible IPO - WSJ: Uber Technologies Inc [UBER.UL] recently received proposals from Wall Street banks valuing the company at as much as $120 billion in an initial public offering that could take place… https://t.co/lQWuSc3dwB https://t.co/smbOcQlLRV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Musk says new autopilot chip to be available in six months: Tesla Inc Chief Executive Officer Elon Musk said a new chip that improves autopilot features would be available in about six months in all of the company's new production electric cars. https://t.co/kyEqHpMSg5 https://t.co/62D29SfS4w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dutch battery company to build 1.6 billion euro plant in China: Lithium Werks BV, a startup founded by Dutch entrepreneur Kees Koolen, said on Tuesday it had signed a 1.6 billion euro ($1.85 billion) deal to build a new storage battery plant in China. https://t.co/Y6QmNvW5Jr https://t.co/lY7XlwRxn4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TomTom earnings beat expectations on digital mapping sales: TomTom , the Dutch navigation company, said third-quarter earnings beat expectations, helped by sales of higher margin digital mapping products. https://t.co/w4ne8SAFv3 https://t.co/KoLHoMXLB9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TomTom reports better-than-expected third-quarter core earnings: TomTom , the Dutch maker of digital mapping software, on Tuesday reported better-than-expected third-quarter core earnings of 62.4 million euros ($72.2 million), compared with 35.5 million… https://t.co/BPL1oFqHt7 https://t.co/CLrQcuXO5Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL DBA: SQL DATABASE ADMINISTRATOR LOCATION: PITTSBURGH, PA/MONROEVILLE, PA (SOME REMOTE WORK IS AN OPTION) REQUIRED SKILLS: * Serve as DBA for operational and strategic planning and projects. Coordinate production releases and changes including… https://t.co/xkHiI1AQWV https://t.co/zQkow4BQ7M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OnDeck launches new subsidiary to partner with banks: OnDeck Capital Inc has set up a subsidiary that will provide technology and other services to banks looking to lend to small businesses online, it said on Tuesday. https://t.co/XVnlIS5bQd https://t.co/IigrpTOiDH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Field Engineer Civil/Rail: Job Ref: ****** Employer: Bechtel Address: Post Date: 28/08/2018 18:01 Requisition ID: Project Overview: The Pennsylvania Chemicals Project is a world scale petrochemicals facility to be constructed in Monaca, Pennsylvania, USA… https://t.co/Zghuwpf3v6 https://t.co/Oc1Pom7GUO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Qualcomm, FTC ask judge to delay ruling to pursue settlement: Qualcomm Inc and the U.S. Federal Trade Commission on Monday asked a federal judge to delay a preliminary ruling in an antitrust case U.S. regulators brought against the mobile chip firm in… https://t.co/gJkjfbG2S5 https://t.co/Ozf9MCmsYG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google latest to withdraw from Saudi conference: Alphabet Inc's Google on Monday became the latest company to drop out of a business conference in Saudi Arabia. https://t.co/HlSIrolNPs https://t.co/mv0vR4eQjx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crypto exchange Coinbase opens Dublin office as Brexit looms: Cryptocurrency exchange Coinbase has opened an office in Dublin, it said on Tuesday, joining the growing ranks of banks and financial firms with major British businesses developing European… https://t.co/XSMNZJJpzs https://t.co/K2l3DTC5r5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook to say who pays for UK political adverts: Facebook said on Tuesday that it would require British political adverts posted on its pages to carry disclaimers and identity flags, in an attempt to crack down on the spread of misinformation. https://t.co/HvIMtqBQuo https://t.co/g1HCMCUKrc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud software firm Twilio to buy SendGrid in $2 billion deal: Cloud communications provider Twilio Inc said on Monday it would buy email technology firm SendGrid Inc in an all-stock deal valued at about $2 billion. https://t.co/apVkFBHPuk https://t.co/tXWzzVbRnE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft co-founder Paul Allen dies of cancer complications at 65: Microsoft Corp co-founder Paul Allen, the man who persuaded school-friend Bill Gates to drop out of Harvard to start what became the world's biggest software company, died on Monday at… https://t.co/Pre0iU2DGd https://t.co/Z3ujdCoaEC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft co-founder Paul Allen dies of cancer at 65: Microsoft Corp co-founder Paul Allen, the man who persuaded school-friend Bill Gates to drop out of Harvard to start what became the world's biggest software company, died on Monday at the age of 65,… https://t.co/muebwsn9ji https://t.co/jnG7PVRfKF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft co-founder Paul Allen dies at 65: Microsoft Corp co-founder Paul Allen, who had been suffering from non-Hodgkin's lymphoma, passed away at the age of 65 on Monday, his investment firm said. https://t.co/DHdhLhzToh https://t.co/swCEggn3fe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. consumers need more control over social media data: lawmaker: U.S. consumers should be able to easily move data like photographs and contacts from one social media application to another, potentially opening up a path for new tech entrants to… https://t.co/W9fEzb9vNH https://t.co/17Bm0TI9Kq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Renault-Brilliance plans electric vans to buck China slowdown: Renault and Chinese partner Brilliance plan to launch three electric delivery vans in two years, seeking to capitalize on robust growth in China's commercial vehicle market and city center… https://t.co/dbHW3KUyUc https://t.co/EMuQfjEVxk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud communications provider Twilio to buy SendGrid in $2 billion deal: Cloud communications provider Twilio Inc said on Monday it would buy bulk email sender SendGrid Inc in an all-stock deal valued at about $2 billion. https://t.co/LxipFSl5qv https://t.co/vq0KMmBkTr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exclusive: Facebook to ban misinformation on voting in upcoming U.S. elections: Facebook Inc will ban false information about voting requirements and fake reports of violence or long lines at polling stations in the run-up to and during next month's U.S.… https://t.co/dnJvdx0om9 https://t.co/Zh2FQZX5ba]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Airbnb bill may limit short-term rentals in U.S. capital: Short-term rentals of Jackie Howard's two-bedroom home near major tourist attractions in Washington, D.C. have helped her family pay for everything from plumbing emergencies to braces for her… https://t.co/1tH4B0Jr7Q https://t.co/OMirjnK6MW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon India say services boosting large appliance sales: Amazon's investment in an extensive delivery network, and offering installation services and monthly payment plans, helped make large appliances a major category during its annual festive sale,… https://t.co/AqWkWEmU89 https://t.co/SJSBResLnu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Intelligence QA Analyst: Job TitleBusiness Intelligence QA Analyst – ID:30894 Duration6 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsExperience working with development team from the initial development of business requirements, through all the Agile/Scrum… https://t.co/3nLJKlPxPp https://t.co/YhkcfneyN1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fidelity launches new company for trading and storing cryptocurrencies: Fidelity Investments has launched a new company for its institutional clients that will trade and store digital assets such as bitcoin, the asset manager said on Monday. https://t.co/LhoRp1KRF5 https://t.co/VjK6C3HnDU]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>