<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi ck this out, are U looking for a done for U home business website, become an affiliate with us. PAYS CRAZY Commission. http://is.gd/5fhp0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi you might want to ck out this new marketing site, getting bigger by the day, 
dont wait till its to late  -http://bit.ly/26Klp, Join me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi all, havent been here for a while Ive been working on new site & getting great 
returns of money, will go live in NOV http://bit.ly/26Klp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IF You are a winner & Money is attracted to you. YOU WILL SUCCEED 
HERE! This is your chance for real success. http://bit.ly/26Klp  join now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starting new business. Long-term residual income potential. Generous 
rewards program, w/CAR award program ,
 JOIN NOW - http://ow.ly/kwsX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You need to act NOW if you want to stake your position in what is going to rock the industry! Great Health program also -http://bit.ly/26Klp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Marketing Company. Work from home. Earn a fantastic income. http://bit.ly/26Klp,  We are independent marketers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for following, I wish you would ck this out, its BIG!!! It is changing my LIFE!! IT might change yours. - http://bit.ly/82Oar -]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We all have dreams of being successful; why not make yours a reality. ACT NOW JOIN NOW - http://ow.ly/kwsX Don't wait its happening now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future depends on what we do in the present. Join here now & your FUTURE WILL BE SECURE - http://ow.ly/kwsX -- DON'T PASS THIS UP!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi , Thought you might ck this out, it is going to be big in the 
new future, not everyone knows about it! join us - http://bit.ly/26Klp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Small monthly fee, great monthly return, great natural vitamins and more to 
help U with your daily PROBLEMS, stress, memory, weight & more]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the bell tolls, I will answer. Where will you be? 
This is  my  gift in life, where will you be in your life? http://ow.ly/kwsX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This man wants to help those in America become secure with their 
future. JOIN NOW it happening NOW -http://ow.ly/kwsX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We all have dreams of being successful; why not make yours a reality.  ACT NOW 
JOIN NOW - http://ow.ly/kwsX Don't wait its happening now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Try this out, its big, Health & Wealth.. Don’t miss out on a once in a lifetime 
opportunity..http://bit.ly/26Klp  -Join today, Don't wait.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You need to act NOW if you want to stake your position in what is going to 
rock the MLM industry! DON'T MISS IT!!!  http://bit.ly/26Klp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starting new business. Long-term residual income potential. Generous 
rewards program, GREAT HEALTH PROGRAM,
http://bit.ly/26Klp -Join today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The time is now... Don’t miss out on a once in a lifetime opportunity..http://ow.ly/kwtl 
DON'T PASS THIS UP, IT IS GREAT 4 WEALTH & HEALTH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember that time is money. Let this time be your money.  Its Here 
JOIN NOW: http://ow.ly/kwsX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life Is Not Measured By The Number Of Breaths You Take, But The Number 
Of Moments That Take Your Breathe Away...http://ow.ly/kwtl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly paychecks, monthly bonuses, & residual income, WHAT MORE COULD YOU 
ASK FOR?  http://ow.ly/kwtl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi,  this is going to be the biggest thing next to Microsoft, ck it out,  http://ow.ly/kwtl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Trump Network - Discover the difference between opportunity and success | http://ow.ly/kwsX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Join me, Take the leap of faith that's necessary in any worthwhile endeavor"  Donald Trump  -Its Here - Its NOW join: http://ow.ly/kwtl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Expand yourself here, its great, dont wait to long.  It doesn't 
get any better than that  Launching soon ITS HERE- http://bit.ly/26Klp JOIN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump starts a Network Marketing Company. 
Work from home Earn a fantastic income. http://bit.ly/26Klp, We are independent marketers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They call him "The DON" NOW HE IS BRINGING THIS TO YOU -Weekly paychecks, monthly bonuses, & residual income,   http://bit.ly/82Oar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what made a difference in our lives, Donald Trump knows what he is doing, check it out,  http://bit.ly/26Klp  DONT pass this by!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JOIN us to make a great financial difference in your lifestyle - http://bit.ly/26Klp 
Make More $$ Than You've Ever Dreamed Of.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what has made a difference in our lives, 
Donald Trump knew what he was doing, check it out,  http://bit.ly/26Klp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Expand yourself here, its great, dont wait to long.  It doesn't 
get any better than that  Launching soon ITS HERE- http://bit.ly/26Klp JOIN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi all, havent been here for a while Ive been working on new site & getting great returns of money, will go live in NOV. http://bit.ly/26Klp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Insanity is doing the same things over & over and expecting a different result.
Get something different & expect results http://bit.ly/26Klp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New company new program new product lines-vitamins, 
energy drinks, weight loss. Weekly paychecks with Monthly bonuses. 
http://bit.ly/26Klp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IF YOU HAVE FOLLOWERS THEN BRING THEM IN WITH YOU & MAKE MORE 
THAN YOU CAN IMAGE-JOIN US-SUCCESS IS HERE -DON'T WAIT  http://bit.ly/26Klp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to increase your Success rate, dont stop now,
Obstacles don't have to stop you. Success is here-http://bit.ly/26Klp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Earning six figures is easy when you know how to get there. Its right here, 
go there now TO JOIN THE WEBINARS--http://bit.ly/26Klp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YOU need to join NOW, so that you too can get in the fast start program IT WILL BE GREAT daily training Unlimited income http://bit.ly/26Klp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Moving to the greater Tulsa area, ck out these houses at www.billysharp.net ,you wont be sorry, cant get any better prices, beautiful homes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow us to the future, It is happening NOW, DON'T MISS OUT. 
Will launch in Nov. be in the start of it all. Join NOW http://bit.ly/26Klp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are entering our newest fall launch.Our team is expanding & we are 
needing people to work from home.  JOIN NOW -http://bit.ly/26Klp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IF You are a winner & Money is attracted to you. YOU WILL SUCCEED 
HERE! This is your chance for real success. http://bit.ly/26Klp  join]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Billionaire is about to launch the largest health & weight loss MLM 
Network the world has ever seen,  JOIN NOW HERE - http://bit.ly/26Klp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Days to launch - join now & be on the top, don't mess around with others. 
WE WILL be on TOP of it all,  JOIN US NOW  http://bit.ly/26Klp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They always say TIME changes things but you actually have to change them 
yourself MAKE the TIME 2 change yours -http://bit.ly/26Klp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only thing money gives you is the freedom of not worrying about Money. 
Here is the MONEY FOR FREEDOM JOIN US NOW-   http://bit.ly/26Klp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi , Thought you might ck this out, it is going to be big in the 
new future, not everyone knows about it! join us - http://bit.ly/26Klp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey ALL,If U want something better than affiliate marketing 
CK THIS OUT-THIS IS the biggest thing on the market http://bit.ly/26Klp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you miss this, its not my fault, I tried to get you in, Join now, I can't say more, 
Its great! JOIN NOW! Don't wait  http://bit.ly/26Klp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starting new business. Long-term residual income potential. Generous 
rewards program, GREAT HEALTH PROGRAM,
http://bit.ly/26Klp -Join today]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future depends on what we do in the present.  Join here now & your FUTURE WILL BE SECURE - http://ow.ly/kwsX  -DON'T PASS THIS UP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The time is now... Don’t miss out on a once in a lifetime opportunity..http://bit.ly/26Klp
DON'T PASS THIS UP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you willing to make a fortune? You will here, from one who knows about natural supplements needed for todays health, you wont be sorry!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Alone we can do so little. Together we can do so much."- HELEN KELLER , 
LETS GET TOGETHER AND MAKE REAL MONEY
http://bit.ly/26Klp join now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FEEL TIRED ALL THE TIME? DEPRESSED? Need help losing weight? www.idealhealth.com  Use Sponsor ID#6229173,  Bill Sharp   for discounts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JUST GOT THE BLUES? GET ENERGIZED with natural vitamins, www.idealhealth.com  Use Sponsor ID#6229173,  Bill Sharp   for discounts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you know about all natural vitamins and nutrients, go here and see 4 yourself  www.idealhealth.com Use sponsor ID#6229173  Bill Sharp.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A home based biz, plus extreme health in 1 package - don't miss this.   
http://ow.ly/kwsX  Launching in NOV. start now to earn big!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join With The Biggest Name In Business While Still In Pre-launch With The Most 
Successful Networking Team Possible.  http://bit.ly/26Klp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NEED MORE MONEY? WOULD MONEY HELP? JOIN THE MOST SUCCESSFUL 
TEAM IN THE NETWORK!! GO TO AND JOIN NOW-- http://bit.ly/26Klp  
HELP IS HERE!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is not good enough to have a good mind, the main thing is to use it well & wisely. See what ONE BILLIONAIRE is doing http://ow.ly/kwsX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only thing money gives you is the freedom of not worrying about Money. 
Here is the MONEY FOR FREEDOM JOIN US NOW-   http://ow.ly/kwsX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is something that's real, most people take vitamins, are U taking the right ones to help U with the problems you face every day?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Small fee, great monthly return, great natural vitamins & more to help U 
with your daily PROBLEMS, stress, weight & more http://ow.ly/kwsX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This man wants to help those in America become secure with their 
future. JOIN NOW it happening NOW -http://ow.ly/kwsX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starting new business. Long-term residual income potential. Generous 
rewards program, GREAT HEALTH PROGRAM,
 http://ow.ly/kwsX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starting new business. Long-term residual income potential. Generous 
rewards program, w/CAR award program ,
 JOIN NOW - http://ow.ly/kwsX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We all have dreams of being successful; why not make yours a reality.  ACT NOW 
JOIN NOW - http://ow.ly/kwsX Don't wait its happening now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You need to act NOW if you want to stake your position in what is going to rock the 
MLM industry! DON'T MISS IT!!! JOIN
http://ow.ly/kwsX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Wise men talk because they have something to say; fools talk because they have to say something." Plato - be wise join
http://ow.ly/kwsX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for vitamins & other nutrients, IdealHealth.com, sign up & use my sponsor ID# 6229173,  Bill Sharp, get in better health today!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you saying to yourself “If others have been successful, why not me too?” You can  here with us: http://ow.ly/kwsX  join now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This man wants to help those in America become secure with their 
future. JOIN NOW it happening NOW -http://ow.ly/kwsX join now to get rich]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you have a weight problem, this can help you lose weight & you can earn money at the same time. Follow this link:   http://bit.ly/82Oar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join Me at The Bar - http://bit.ly/16CWP5 - its free to join & U can make money also. DON'T WAIT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey, we just found a great place, its the front door to a back office, for FREE & IT 
PAYS in 15 DAYS We joined, http://134.powerbarclub.com]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life Is Not Measured By The Number Of Breaths You Take, But The Number 
Of Moments That Take Your Breathe Away...http://ow.ly/kwsX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember that time is money. Let this time be your money.  Its Here JOIN 
NOW: http://ow.ly/kwsX   Weekly paychecks, monthly bonuses & more]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future depends on what we do in the present.  Join here now & your FUTURE
WILL BE SECURE - http://ow.ly/kwsX ]
DON'T PASS THIS UP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you willing to make a fortune? You will here, from one who knows about natural supplements needed for todays health, you wont be sorry!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Discover The Difference Between Opportunity And True Success! GREAT 
WEALTH & GREAT HEALTH IN 1 PACKAGE: http://bit.ly/26Klp JOIN 
NOW!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow us to the future, It is happening NOW, DON'T MISS OUT. 
Will launch in Nov. be in the start of it all. Join NOW http://bit.ly/26Klp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't know what you will be missing out on, join now and be 1 of the best, 
JOIN US NOW IN THE BEST that's here,  -http://bit.ly/26Klp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are entering our newest fall launch.Our team is expanding & we are 
needing people to work from home.  JOIN NOW -http://bit.ly/26Klp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stressed Of Your Low Income? Unsure Of Your Future? The Solution Is Within 
Each & Everyone Of Us, CHANGE YOUR LIFE NOW http://bit.ly/26Klp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ANYONE LOOKING TO MOVE TO THE TULSA OK, AREA?   WE HAVE GREAT HOMES AVAILABLE, CK OUT www.billysharp.net, your home awaits their great homes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do You Have Extreme Financial Pressure Right Now? I DID It's paralyzing.  
I'm getting out of it FAST, WITH THIS..  http://bit.ly/26Klp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IF You are a winner.IF Money is attracted to you. YOU WILL SUCCEED 
HERE! This is your chance for real success. http://bit.ly/26Klp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join With The Biggest Name In Business While Still In Pre-launch With The 
Most Successful Networking Team Possible.  http://bit.ly/26Klp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Wonderful Magic Of The Internet Has Connected US!  So Let Me Share 
This Gift…http://bit.ly/26Klp  GREAT MONTHLY INCOME JOIN NOW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America In A Recession?? Not For Long Thanks To This Man, Check Out How 
He Is Changing It..http://bit.ly/26Klp   IT HAS CHANGED MY LIFE!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is not good enough to have a good mind, the main thing is to use it well & 
wisely. See what ONE BILLIONAIRE is doing http://ow.ly/kwsX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Billionaire is about to launch the largest health & weight loss MLM 
Network the world has ever seen,  JOIN NOW HERE - http://ow.ly/kwsX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If U are looking to make money online join someone that knows what they are 
doing, D.T. knows how to make money JOIN US  http://ow.ly/kwsX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Days to launch - join now & be on the top, don't mess around with others. 
we will be on top of it all,  JOIN US NOW  http://ow.ly/kwsX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They always say TIME changes things but you actually have to change them 
yourself MAKE the TIME 2 change yours -  http://ow.ly/kwsX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only thing money gives you is the freedom of not worrying about Money. 
Here is the MONEY FOR FREEDOM JOIN US NOW-   http://ow.ly/kwsX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi , Thought you might ck this out, it is going to be big in the 
new future, not everyone knows about it! join us - http://bit.ly/26Klp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is something that's real, most people take vitamins, are U taking the right ones to help U with the problems you face every day?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>