<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[When a girl cries for a guy, it means she really misses him. But when a guy cries for a girl, nobody can love that girl more than him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The truth is you don't know what is going to happen tomorrow. Life is a crazy ride, and nothing is guaranteed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be with people who know your worth. You don't need too many friends to be happy, just a real ones who appreciate you for who you are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listen carefully to how a person speaks about other people to you. This is how they will speak about you to other people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes you have to put on a fake smile on and just pretend it never happened. It's not giving up, it's growing up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter what you may be going through in your life, never forget to smile because the smile is what makes us all happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beauty isn't about having a pretty face. It's about having a pretty mind, a pretty heart, and a pretty soul.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I see you have time to update your status, but you don't have time to text me back.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want that relationship where people know of us, but know nothing about us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't regret my past at all. I just regret some of the time I've wasted with wrong people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It doesn't matter how you look, what your weight is, or how much make up you put on. The right guy will love you for what's on the inside.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ketika bertemu seseorang yang mencintaimu dengan tulus, balas dengan cintamu yang tulus juga, karena cinta yang tulus jarang ada.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are hundreds of languages in this world, but a smile speaks them all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People come and go all the time. All you can do is hope the right one stays around.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not all guys want sex, some want a relationship. They all won't hurt you, because some are decent and would rather see you smile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If she can make you smile, hold on to her and give her the most you can.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes life becomes too complicated and all you need is just to let it flow, because God still controls everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most romantic words by a boy: Will you allow me to see your face everyday when I wake up?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you love someone tell them... because hearts are often broken by words left unspoken.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't promise you a perfect relationship without arguments &amp; differences. However I can promise you as long as you're trying, I'm staying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While you're ignoring her, another guy is giving her attention, and while you're giving her problems, another guy is listening.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is like flute. It may have many holes and emptiness, but if you work on it carefully, it can play magical melodies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HOPE is the little voice whispering "maybe" when it seem like the whole world shouting "NO".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dear God, I don't know Your plan for me and at times it can be scary, but I know You have a purpose for everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not the type to give up easily, but once you give up, I no longer feel the need to beg for your attention]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are everything I never knew I always wanted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's no such thing as being too busy. If you really love something, you'll make time for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WhatILove MOM. No matter what we go through, no matter how much we argue, at the end, she'll always be there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#WhatILove God! He's the reason why even in pain, I smile; in confusion, I understand; in betrayal, I trust; &amp; in fear, I continue to fight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A morning text doesn't only mean "good morning". It also means "I think about you when I wake up".]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're the only person I want to fall asleep next to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To me, no other girl is as beautiful as you are. You're the only one I always think about. I can't imagine me without you for a second.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever since we've been together, it seems like you're the only girl who exists in the entire world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’ve seen you at your worst and I still think you’re the best. ♥]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being someone's first love may be great, but to be their last is priceless.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One day you will meet someone, who worth all your laugh and tears, who will treat you the best, who will make you his/her priority.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I continue to smile each day because life is simply way too short to cry over anything that's worthless.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When guys lie, they say they love you. When girls lie, they say they don't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are the one of those people that I need in my life. I can't stand not talking to you, I think about you all the time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's unbelievable how fast people can change. One day, you mean everything. The next day, you dont exist anymore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's the worst part: Liking someone so much and knowing he'll never feel the same way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep 3 words in the pocket: TRY - TRUE - TRUST. TRY for better future, TRUE with your work, and TRUST in God.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A good boyfriend loves his girl with all his heart. He isn't afraid to point to his girl in front of his friends and say, "That's my baby."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is when I see you smile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Try to be a RAINBOW in someone's CLOUD everyday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter who you are or what happens in your life, you deserve to be happy and live your life to the fullest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I have to chase and fight for your attention, eventually I wouldn't want it anymore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every love story is beautiful, but ours is my favorite.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your smile, your hugs, your laugh, your texts, I truly miss everything that makes my day perfect, it's you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have the power to make your life happy or miserable, no one else. So do not give anyone the chance to try and make you unhappy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hold your head up high, and know God is in control he has a perfect plan for your life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes I feel like I’m never going to be good enough for anyone or anything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why should I care what people think of me? I am who I am, and who I want to be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be nice to everyone, always smile and appreciate things because it could all be gone by tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friends know how to make you look beautiful. Best friends know how to make you feel beautiful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Open your mind before you open your mouth. Don’t mix bad words with a bad mood. Just be calm and deal with your emotions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I prefer that you tell me the truth even if it hurts rather than lie to me just to make me happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smiling for no reason is a sign of craziness, then you made me smile for no reason and I must be crazy in love with you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many people turn to God when life has them down but forget to keep in touch with Him when He turns it all around.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A thousand people could tell me they think I'm beautiful, but it doesn't mean anything unless it's coming from you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not scared to tell you I love you, I'm just scared of what you'll say after.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If someone wants to be part of your life, they'll be there. So don't bother saving a spot for someone who won't make an effort to stay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They say you don't know what you got until it's gone. Truth is, you knew exactly what you had, you just never thought you'd lose it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He wasn't looking for perfection, just someone who made him feel secure enough to be insecure around her.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tell him that days go by and I don't even notice. I don't lose sleep over him anymore and I already forgot about what happened between us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you see him, tell him that I'm doing better and there's someone by my side who has made me fall in love again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I really think I should thank you for letting me go at the first place. If not, I wouldn't have found him.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The PAST is where you learned the lesson. The FUTURE is where you apply the lesson. Don't GIVE up in the middle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The hardest moment is not when tears flow from your eyes, it's when you have to hide the tears in your eyes with a smile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you are unsure about your future just keep doing what you know is right. What is meant to be will find you. God will make sure of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a MALE inside fe(male), MR in every (Mr)s, HE in each s(he). Which prove that MAN can't live without wo(man).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people smile because something good has happened; other people smile because they've learned that when they smile, good things happen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to meet someone who is afraid to lose me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every girl deserves a guy that can make her forget her heart was ever broken.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love, Trust, Respect, Loyalty, and Communication are 5 essential parts of a successful relationship.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['I love you' means thinking of you, dreaming of you, wanting, needing you constantly, and hoping you feel the same way for me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['I love you' means that I care enough to fight for what we have and that I love you enough not to let go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometime in life our good fortunes come early, sometimes they come late, but they always come. And they’re always right on time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['I love you' means loving you when you're down, not just when you're fun to be with.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['I love you' means that I will love you and stand by you even through the worst of times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women are sensitive, they overthink every little thing and they care way more than they should, but that's what makes their love so strong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If he loves you, he'll care for you, stay up with you, kiss you passionately, make you happy, not break your heart, he will respect you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ketika kita berdoa, Tuhan mendengar lebih dari apa yg kita katakan, Dia menjawab lebih dari apa yg kita tanyakan dgn caraNya &amp; waktuNya.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you know why we should be thankful? Because we may not have everything, but at least we never had nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A broken heart is like getting shampoo in your eyes. It feels for a while like you'll never see again but after a few tears you get over it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You make me smile... For now that's more than enough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I say I miss you, I wish you are by my side. And when I say I love you, I wish we are together, till we grow old.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nobody is perfect, so accept who you are and don't be so hard on yourself, just be grateful for this life that has been given to you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are a lot of ways you can start and end your day, but the most important way is with prayer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to be the reason for your smile, the reason your world is a little bit brighter, and the reason you know what true love is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd rather have hard times together, than to have it easy apart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing is more beautiful and powerful than a smile that has struggled through the tears.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When two people really care about each other. They will always look for a way to make it work, no matter how hard it is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is not how you listen, but how you understand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a lot of things science can not explain... like why tears fall from our eyes when we know we can't be with that person.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a lot of things science can not explain... like why our hearts beat faster when we're near with someone we like.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The person who really loves you will never leave your side no matter how hard things, get through better or worse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything is going to be alright, maybe not today, but eventually.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't count the number of friends you have, but the number of friends you can count on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your life is like a puzzle. God has all the pieces &amp; He knows what the outside of the box looks like. He sees the BIG picture. Trust Him.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>