<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Trini Lopez    http://t.co/R2DsTmn5d8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who are the Three Degrees oldies group?  http://t.co/8qzw269xGL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Glowing "Moon In My Room" Wall Decal - Glows! http://t.co/IwgjIwL2I5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He didn't believe in flying saucers until he tickled the waitress]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Kiss  http://t.co/fbNtMN5Xs7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge a man by how much he does when he doesn't need to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dr. Who Blue Tardis Min-Fridge - so “COOL”! - http://t.co/6iM1pCArMR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Do Parents Pick Favorite Things for their Kids?  http://t.co/ZmbP4ofnET]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Marvin Gaye  http://t.co/Uv9q2SRf6L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A waist is a terrible thing to mind. - Tom Wilson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most serious mistakes are not being made as a result of wrong answers. The truly dangerous thing is asking the wrong question P Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lie travels around the earth while the truth is putting on its shoes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Christians Making a Profession of their Religion  http://t.co/cf0yanLtm9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Julie London  http://t.co/ElAdMhp4q1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only undertake what you can do in an excellent fashion. There are no prizes for average performance.- Brian Tracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You've got to say, I think that if I keep working at this and want it badly enough I can have it. It's called perseverance. - Lee Iacocca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Habit is second nature, or rather, ten times nature. - William James]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Very Unusual Hamburgers  http://t.co/kvLUFFx2rn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Customer:  "Could I try on that suit in the window?"  Clerk:  "We'd rather you do that in the dressing room."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these lovely Dos XX Most Interesting Main the World Commercials!  http://t.co/a9woVHURy6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women should look like women. A piece of cardboard has no sexuality. - Alexander McQueen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't go into details, I've already told you  more than I overheard myself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have the end in mind and every day make sure your working towards it - Ryan Allis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of a sudden, you're like the Bin Laden of America. Osama Bin Laden is the only one who knows exactly what I'm going through.  R. Kelly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aerodynamics are for people who can't build engines. - Enzo Ferrari]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Popular Places and Activities in Europe  http://t.co/azXVUEyA0Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Budget: A domestic quarrel!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I get to go to a lot of overseas places, like Canada.  Britney Spears]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live daringly, boldly, fearlessly. Taste the relish to be found in competition - in having put forth the best within you. - Henry J. Kaiser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketing is what you do when your product is no good. - Edwin Land]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn Marketing Secrets for eCommerce Business  http://t.co/eC1EMtIm0R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space is the stature of God. - Joseph Joubert]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome gardening t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the gardening lovers in your life!   http://t.co/ByX51NoMGO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life begins when we first realize how soon it ends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You cannot dream yourself into a character: you must hammer and forge yourself into one. - Henry D. Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A computer lets you make more mistakes faster than any invention in human history - with the possible exceptions of handguns and tequila.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding the Right Fitness Gadgets for Better Health http://t.co/yKzPXGFjAq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Al Green  http://t.co/QAHRH6iY1d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Queen  http://t.co/8osFTLMsTX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Temptations  http://t.co/gCpt5FI9QK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nobody remembers the guy who finished second but the guy who finished second. - Bobby Unser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Foghat  http://t.co/HBq54Ou9rC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you know of the Klingon proverb that tells us revenge is a dish that is best served cold? It is very cold in space. - Khan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the goodness of a good egg cannot make up for the badness of a bad egg...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL A Toilet Mug for your Coffee!  http://t.co/4xQzG2ZhW7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't preach a boy about his problems. Just remind him that you, too , were a Nincompoop at his age.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fool and his money are never without friends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just started my INSANITY: 60-Day Total Body Conditioning Workout DVD Program - wish me luck!  http://t.co/ijbpOB0yaz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Staple Singers  http://t.co/2V2hd5NDtQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is better than poverty, if only for financial reasons. - Woody Allen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Overview of Domestic Adoption  http://t.co/MNY654DVCP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Cy Young: The Greatest Pitcher Baseball has Ever Seen  http://t.co/as4xAKewUM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the business world, everyone is paid in two coins: cash &amp; experience. Take the experience first; the cash will come later - Harold Geneen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The Music of L.T.D.  http://t.co/GCdSVF0e9P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion Note: Little change in men's clothes this year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The quickest way to get a doctor today is to turn on your television set. . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love This Nerds Candy Juniors Tunic Tank Dress with Nerd Glasses - Dig It! http://t.co/qpwL4nM592]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got hit in the head pretty hard. My clock ran backwards for two years. - Buddy Baker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About why Kids Love to Read and Review  http://t.co/idSiap4fVA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of James Brown  http://t.co/KkwOT6ze69]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is the ability to listen to almost anything without losing your temper or your self-confidence. - Robert Frost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ELVIS - The King - One Person's Thoughts  http://t.co/1O5C9eFV6c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Led Zeppelin  http://t.co/nzKvyi2BDe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'll forgive me, Madam President, if I don't wish to be executed based solely on your... gut feeling. - Doctor Gaius Baltar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to find somebody and you want to be married and you want to have children, don't make it a rock star. - Stevie Nicks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Three Styles of BMX Bikes and their Uses  http://t.co/BF76QpI1cn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stay Ahead in eCommerce With Marketing Tips  http://t.co/awVWTlMpK4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guns Don't Kill People, Dads With Pretty Daughters Kill People http://t.co/ilwh7S7czz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a very easy way to return from a casino with a small fortune: go there with a large one. - Jack Yelton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Top Secrets for Using Facebook Pages for Your Business  http://t.co/DuhQF29viL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you know how hard it is to maintain cover while dancing the salsa in three-inch heels? - Syndey, Alias]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The reality of science is that it takes 40 years to get to Jupiter, and that's a dull show. - Glen Morgan, "Space: Above and Beyond"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch wearing isn’t dead - check out these very cool trendy watches - http://t.co/9eOUzpFjeW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dogs come when they're called; cats take a message and get back to you later. - Mary Bly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hello again, everybody. It's a bee-yooo-tiful day for baseball. -  Harry Caray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Foxy  http://t.co/D7w7G7r5Nc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wait a minute, Doc. Ah --  Are you telling me you built a time machine --  out of a DeLorean? - Marty McFly, Back to the Future]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about Oakland, California  http://t.co/4jkuhNovW0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Top Science and Tech Websites  http://t.co/PaOPREtZJ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Joe Simon  http://t.co/jtyO7miXAN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introducing to the SEO Power Suite  http://t.co/NI7fXddQ5G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can a guy win a game if you don't give him any runs? - Robert Bo Belinsky after Losing 15 - 0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Ohio Players    http://t.co/XILepdSo0C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Great Music of Bill Justis  http://t.co/qqrIL9nond]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Peregrine Falcons: Lords of the Sky  http://t.co/AFfJpgMDTT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It costs a lot of money to look this cheap --&gt; Dolly Parton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool iPhone 4 Review  http://t.co/WmOEpcU3ST]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest thing in this world is not so much where we stand, as in what direction we are moving. - Oliver Wendall Holmes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have enemies? Good. That means you've stood up for something, sometime in your life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A tax collector has what it takes to take what you got]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing shocks me - I am a scientist. - Indiana Jones, Indiana Jones and the Temple of Doom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Maxine Brown  http://t.co/cOJZfbTZZ7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can I build a high quality free website?  http://t.co/gu8mOEtT4O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lot of rock bands are truly a legend in their own minds. - David Lee Roth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education ... has produced a vast population able to read but unable to distinguish what is worth reading. - G. M. Trevelyan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bring out your dead. - Monty Python and the Holy Grail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Heart  http://t.co/ybHdnPdhlJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't preach a boy about his problems. Just remind him that you, too , were a Nincompoop at his age.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Very Cool Hand Juicer http://t.co/K0cLIQMlbU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Don Henley  http://t.co/7eiIwptDQF]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>