<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The main part of intellectual education is not the acquisition of facts but learning how to make facts live." - Oliver Wendell Holmes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I look at modeling as something I'm doing for black people in general. Naomi Campbell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your body is the baggage you must carry through life. The more excess the baggage, the shorter the trip. - Arnold H. Glasgow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read How to Use LinkedIn for Your Company   http://t.co/ssXoV0OhzR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pop culture is not about depth. It's about marketing, supply and demand, consumerism. - Trevor Dunn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Johnny Ace: A Life of Unfulfilled Dreams  http://t.co/Dg2ONZDicG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The worst examples of snap judgment are usually found in the old family album]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only point in making money is, you can tell some big shot where to go. Humphrey Bogart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these lovely Dos XX Most Interesting Main the World Commercials!  http://t.co/XXza5GzpFm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So very many cool types of mens shoes - learn about men’s shoe styles... http://t.co/RGrnyjdp6t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can You Really Make Things Invisible?  http://t.co/KiQqVMR8pa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conceit is a strange disease, it makes everyone sick but the one who has it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is not a rock opera. This is not Tommy. I can write songs that emote, and that's it. - John Mellencamp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The groundwork of all happiness is health. - Leigh Hunt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live daringly, boldly, fearlessly. Taste the relish to be found in competition - in having put forth the best within you. - Henry J. Kaiser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interested in Solar Power?  Find out about all the different ways to pay for adding solar to your home - http://t.co/Zu86xn3Qmd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lifetime of training for just ten seconds. - Jesse Owens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A horse gallops with his lungs, Perseveres with his heart, And wins with his character. - Tesio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 7 ages of a woman are the right one and 6 wild guesses!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Allstate Insurance  http://t.co/v9jMlilZcL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Horse! A Horse! my kingdom for a horse! - Shakespeare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For Real!?!? - this is AWESOME - a Redneck Beer and Soda Can Holster! http://t.co/4HvgaImHkc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometime the best thing to get off your chest is your chin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 6 - Follow-up Appointment  http://t.co/72l2oP2Fhz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Christian Louboutin  http://t.co/Xb2tQOivpr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overwhelming underdogs. - Yogi Berra While Referring to the 1969 New York Mets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotta Love It - 12 Nerd Rubber Duckies!  Makes Bath Time Fun!  http://t.co/XnyJmR7CG0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would be more frightened as a writer if people thought my movies were like science fiction. - Neil LaBute]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Ride - La Vibora at Six Flags Over Texas in Arlington  http://t.co/JA9ZZVjsbB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Race cars are neither beautiful nor ugly. They become beautiful when they win. - Enzo Ferrari]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The earth is the cradle of humankind, but one cannot live in the cradle forever. - Konstantin Tsiolkovsky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Golden slumbers fill your eyes, smiles awake you when you rise. - Golden Slumbers by The Beatles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you know how hard it is to maintain cover while dancing the salsa in three-inch heels? - Syndey, Alias]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I pretty much try to stay in a constant state of confusion just because of the expression it leaves on my face.  Johnny Depp quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you wish to grow thinner, diminish your dinner. - Henry Sambrooke Leigh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Parliament  http://t.co/75A2ItyI6H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drill sarge to recruit:  "wipe that opinion off your face!”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Air Supply  http://t.co/tkU4aetN2H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a great day to play two!  - Ernie Banks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for great resources on Beer?  Check out our top 10... http://t.co/eAakBmEgTN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Locate Your Garage Space Before Installation Of Cabinets  http://t.co/UAfMPXIXLq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Bobby Darin    http://t.co/j8z252BrRk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Real education must ultimately be limited to men who insist on knowing, the rest is mere sheep-herding. - Ezra Pound]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of Little House on The Prairie Episode - "In the Big Inning"  http://t.co/uQ6JtY1KcH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips To Draw More Traffic With Quality Link Building  http://t.co/qPKsm0pY78]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Rose Royce  http://t.co/CM4RUbru5C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be successful, you have to have your heart in your business, and your business in your heart. - Thomas Watson, Sr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep NFL Football Is Here To Stay!  http://t.co/dwgbpjx7WV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As far as cheating goes, they'll never stop it. The only way it can be done successfully, only one person can know about it. - Smokey Yunick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People share read &amp; generally engage more with any type of content when its surfaced through friends &amp; people they know and trust - Facebook]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Awesome Nintendo Wall Graphics! http://t.co/5FOoW74oEF]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Jackson Five  http://t.co/DzJXsArKUR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is nothing permanent except change. - Heraclitus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn from yesterday, live for today, hope for tomorrow. - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Ankle Watches – Is This the New Place to Wear a Watch?  http://t.co/SfbHmTD5hq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Air Supply  http://t.co/tkU4aetN2H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Biking Guide BMX Review  http://t.co/ZCO0SddYLn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the The Early History of Beer  http://t.co/CuMp3kWe4n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before the marriage, he talks &amp; she listens.  During honeymoon, she talks &amp; he listens.  Later, they both talk &amp; the neighbors listen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Popcorn Ceiling Removal - A Complex Job  http://t.co/xRoBHV4AEI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need to be able to rock out.  - Bryan Adams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Ben E. King - his story and music  http://t.co/LTS4x5qV3Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His pockets always outlast his suits...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We live in a dark and romantic and quite tragic world. --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get A Life? Cool! Where can I download one of those?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nolan Ryan is pitching much better now that he has his curve ball straightened out. - Joe Garagiola]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Power of Solar Power - Get Plugged In!  http://t.co/RomFnwjwie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Build your own propeller racer and watch as it blazes a path over a smooth surface!  Fun and educational for kids! http://t.co/5fJuMNKW6z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The trouble these days is there's no arrest for the wicked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can You Really Make Things Invisible?  http://t.co/KiQqVMR8pa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gluttony is an emotional escape, a sign something is eating us. - Peter De Vries]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space or science fiction has become a dialect for our time. - Doris Lessing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Seniors and Social Networking  http://t.co/l2CrNIUWEj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Earth, Wind and Fire  http://t.co/E6LR56UjuA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Joni Mitchell  http://t.co/et9HxSlxeU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Clash  http://t.co/0xkYva0m5z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Ral Donner  http://t.co/2V4RGbPJkT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overview of Social Bookmarking Sites  http://t.co/7YuBriAKbi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Creative Writing Degree - Why You Should Consider One  http://t.co/Svcs7ofGsU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can accept failure, but I can't accept not trying. - Michael Jordan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, I'm from Iowa. I only work in outer space. - Kirk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A mind once stretched by a new idea never regains its original dimensions. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'll be back - The Terminator]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the hot new Minecraft video channel Crimson Mine - http://t.co/0g5AR6Y9QV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One thought driven home is better than three left to die on base. . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Grateful Dead  http://t.co/Xt9RKCjY1u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Fleetwood Mac  http://t.co/5Qao5JkNXG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought Europe was a country? Kellie Pickler, on "Are You Smarter Than A Fifth Grader"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very cool 23 mile range walkie talkies!  Stay connected!  http://t.co/VgBbOhQ01x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's easier to ask forgiveness than it is to get permission - Grace Hopper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today’s Top Women’s Shoe Designers  http://t.co/B9fKiMRo5N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Parliament  http://t.co/EjuiiSkGuh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Setup an iPad Speaker System  http://t.co/h92L7KdByR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make Money by Tweeting, Blogging and Photo Sharing with Izea  http://t.co/DTAVm7MQnD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Guide to Mountain Biking  http://t.co/hZqF86A121]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You may delay, but time will not. - Benjamin Franklin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[History of Mojang - The makers of Minecraft - http://t.co/AIqfOyHr5R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cheap Divorce Lawyers: Avoiding Exorbitant Legal Costs  http://t.co/xFHTIucgRb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't preach a boy about his problems. Just remind him that you, too , were a Nincompoop at his age.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the The Recent History of Beer  http://t.co/FTQLxkHpjs]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>