<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing black spoken word artist,says it all. https://t.co/8fWYFKTpby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why liberals are so wrong about Islam. https://t.co/YaN7HpZr9r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/qmedr34SMx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/v5HC13cfl5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/MJNqfX7JFa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is memory? https://t.co/4bwT79kD9m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow ! https://t.co/Zl3sE52cSG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/2AJB99BFmo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a boy I often explored this rock with friends at the Garden of the Gods. It was our getaway. This place was... https://t.co/t5hhIXv3S7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/lp0Jeit6un]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/6hNoOfTq9t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/9JiW4cH0Dy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shanakassa I wish you the very best Christmas and an amazing year ahead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is the head of the country in good shape? https://t.co/A9t6bOFbJC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/aW0jd6FbUr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Felice Natal on the lagoa Freitas Rio de Janeiro. https://t.co/tcsbkNRrrb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/mhr2sm0v9L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada's Miss Universe controversial outfit robbed her of the title. https://t.co/14GLsCgUAN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Beaver is a national symbol in Canada &amp; Miss Canada's was a hit. https://t.co/hUtBrWW3a4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/fl3IHpvLP1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes the pagans rule, folks. https://t.co/vWx43Ha7Au]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These vets have taken their oath seriously. We are humbled by their service in the field and at home. https://t.co/IOBbJXrMer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/LnirlDaXh6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Austin Healy 3000. Still dream of Jessica. https://t.co/yJq0oa4JGB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before Reagan's wars, America had a space program. And now it's back. https://t.co/vRRWFbXFs7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/ka8xxGjiAW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/ST2BPUBSVz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/uKI05scWZd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/QlGddPkB59]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Z4M32xfg9Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Nazi dumps on Jimmy Carter and no Christian calls out Trump. https://t.co/4atguroJ8F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hahaha! https://t.co/3Qcilo8cwg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In these dark days of Nazism in America causing fear and hatred by Republicans, consider this... https://t.co/BbPwTxBoU3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/qKDfAJBT73]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cruz and Trump are both bed wetters who just want to feel safe. https://t.co/kdBWqRG69t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A holiday greeting you didn't expect. https://t.co/4NzcvtSWrO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A white christmas with no malls or shopping traffic. https://t.co/lXEx932zmo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Believe in a love that is being stored up for you like an inheritance, and have faith that in this love there is... https://t.co/2rVUYuwujr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/f30aa6OaNq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Betcha you dog lovers will be touched. https://t.co/hUyvIWRTl5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyMitchell @LittleCookingT Any tips for a vegan?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shanakassa let's forget the seminar :) and I'll come up with a better option.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KellyMitchell @LittleCookingT thanks for the follow I'd love to get in your kitchen for the holidays.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/HDz657hezt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@joelcomm Hi Joel, a CU grad, I was in Greely once and got a ticket for no other reason I was driving a sports car. Thanks for following.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch How This Dog Cries Tears of Joy In His Soldier Daddy’s Lap https://t.co/lgJWNArCWG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/2M2Mj1x1eb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shanakassa Looking forward to getting together on 28 or 29. Lots to catch up on. My treat. M.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Call me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I went over my tweet limit...how about we talk over wine &amp; snacks..somewhere we can hear ourselves talks. Tell me what you prefer. Call m...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[of the deep polarization. A good topic for our next meeting? I sent off my script to LA two days ago and am happy to have finished in tac...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[our plans? M.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Ucv9JOamcG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump has a problem with his great Canadian wall idea. https://t.co/f4BeNid9lC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[North Carolina Republican Calls It Quits With GOP, Joins Democratic Party https://t.co/3H3k39oOqL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To Those Fleeing President Trump: Welcome to Canada! https://t.co/r7KnE1jgTT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/77TrmCKR3q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/miCk30FB34]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Took this photo one year ago and now look back to this day and wondering if I had the choice would I relive it.... https://t.co/J11GKbkrnj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump has an anthem written in his honor. https://t.co/oYcuacyjcI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[W. is throwing his hat into the GOP race. He's already proven he's reliable to just make a few major screw-ups is... https://t.co/suHGyIsjtk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada's PM welcomes Syrian refugees to their new homeland.u https://t.co/oQ9YFoRl44]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deeply inspiring. https://t.co/LcZtAllGKq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/73v0ZBRkFW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What did the people of Paris do on December 13th - one month after the terrorist attack?- they marched to... https://t.co/9xwW6AqIuZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look what the Pope cooked up on behalf of endangered species. https://t.co/qtnCYiCTZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The faces of soldiers from three perspectives; before, during and after tours of Afghanistan. https://t.co/5BrJGHi0vs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And a wicked pharoh wants them put in chains. https://t.co/pMe36GO3pc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NFL quarterback calls out Trump. https://t.co/eccQYSNU4f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need these guys today! Real class. https://t.co/UaVPxv5gMk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/PdTPEu9Brg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/pzQuZfp0Tl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/3X4K3eV0OW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/bQS74FZsbZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Model comes to life. https://t.co/lKJIqJz3QP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love Greece, especially the islands in the Adriatic. https://t.co/lUWanTDLLs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harrison Ford's  rebuke of Trump who is unaware of movie and reality. https://t.co/ScIjgo2I70]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's pretty well known that you are a coward,  George Takei is now  calling you out to come and see for yourself... https://t.co/zBqDNIQf5F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uh oh!  Now Trump will have Anonymous to deal with. We get to see his dirty laundry. https://t.co/xj6w8gQ02Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yo, dude. You are trippin. These babes play in whole nuther league. One we ain't invited to. https://t.co/2KHhQQLvxM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have lots of Muslim friends and have taught to many more. Now  I am purging myself of any friend who likes Dumb... https://t.co/OLsWrlXSK7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile in Canada... https://t.co/SYPum7uZbo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool rock anthem re: dumping the trump:" I don't want to be associated with you" https://t.co/bGZvjB5Gny via @YouTube]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A new rock anthem video dedicated to dumping the trump. "I don't want to be associated with you...."  Rock on! https://t.co/eTyQNF4je0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe Justice Scalia could tutor at a nearby junior college and find a janitor job at night. https://t.co/fCkIve7LgW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reservations required if you want a room for baby Jesus. https://t.co/Oc3stfFE0i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christmas in Rio. The famous tree on the historic Lagoa Freitas https://t.co/DRAFlKHupS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kurt von Hammerstein-Equord - Wikipedia, the free encyclopedia https://t.co/6RUL6Bvs3v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/MdIA0ixMW9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/VgjdLnV6U5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This song got me through my high school years at a pub where I could drink beer with a fake I.D. and feel I could... https://t.co/L2j5HGULks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/G2Qr3WW6y4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Muslim haters please read a post on how wrong you are. https://t.co/NIWtBlEucl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been drawn to do abstract paintings and sketches and now know why. https://t.co/O4F6uUfNbr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/3HZK21gkbt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/33pYTQeFwF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A tough book to write in any case. https://t.co/smZCclaYTe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@delmagodoy hi delma. It's Michael. I think of you this time of year. I hope you are well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amariebergman are you available? M.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Massively grand! David Bowie &amp; Pink Floyd. https://t.co/Zoi6nLUSSS]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>