<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[To finish first, you must first finish. - Juan Manuel Fangio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Humble Pie  http://t.co/aR5nPAMn6r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[London Weight Loss Salon sign: "We value the pound."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Three Dog Night  http://t.co/mZS0EtDb0W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Neil Young  http://t.co/gn87G45I2M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have a very striking face. How many times were you struck there?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Successfully Use Other Websites for Link Building  http://t.co/0GjV0qvhxu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Evolution of the Wooden Clog  http://t.co/Q5rSWzUuI2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can tell whether a man is clever by his answers. You can tell whether a man is wise by his questions —&gt; Naguib Mahfouz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read How to Use LinkedIn for Your Company   http://t.co/b5VogTPWJa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The reality of science is that it takes 40 years to get to Jupiter, and that's a dull show. - Glen Morgan, "Space: Above and Beyond"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I did not have three thousand pairs of shoes, I had one thousand and sixty. - Imelda Marcos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His timing is perfect, so is his two-timing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's 106 miles to Chicago, we've got a full tank of gas, half a pack of cigarettes, it's dark &amp; we're wearing sunglasses. Hit it! - Elwood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The roots of education are bitter, but the fruit is sweet. - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Bob Dylan -- His Biography    http://t.co/McnDkl9sld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You gotta love that - an aquarium coffee table!  Drink with the fishes! http://t.co/rVJoPCUTcp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Face it tiger, you just hit the jackpot! - Mary Jane, Spider-Man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Mod Showcase: Secret Rooms Mod  http://t.co/KWEBsEH9Jb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good pitching will beat good hitting any time, and vice versa. - Bob Veale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People all over the world recognize me as a spiritual leader.  Steven Seagal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The great difficulty in education is to get experience out of ideas. - George Santayana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Emmylou Harris  http://t.co/F86vqJKmWT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thats the way Baseball go - Ron Washington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes many a tumble to keep us humble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You may delay, but time will not. - Benjamin Franklin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret of toe cleavage, a very important part of the sexuality of the shoe; you must only show the first two cracks. - Manolo Blahnik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By working faithfully eight hours a day you may eventually get to be a boss and work twelve hours a day. - Robert Frost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no psychiatrist in the world like a puppy licking your face. - Ben Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Mod Showcase: Secret Rooms Mod  http://t.co/UPbiC1RpdC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Cool Types of Garage Flooring  http://t.co/4GLfUtQdWe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alcohol and gas do mix but they taste terrible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Trouble with a kitten is that eventually it becomes a Cat - Ogden Nash]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're never beaten until you admit it. - George S. Patton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Guide to Mountain Biking  http://t.co/p17W9m3wbj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Style is knowing who you are, what you want to say, and not giving a damn --&gt; Orson Welles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The needs of the many outweigh ... the needs of the few... Or the one. - Kirk and Spock - Star Trek II: The Wrath of Khan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you know of the Klingon proverb that tells us revenge is a dish that is best served cold? It is very cold in space. - Khan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is a skilled game. It's America's game - it, and high taxes. - Will Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Star Trek Uniform Onesies - Dress Up Your Little Geek! http://t.co/2fLLokgHJ4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 1 - What the heck do I have????  http://t.co/JKZjnYJfXK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stevie Wonder  http://t.co/fMjEfygxkU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to that hilarious sit-com Three’s Company - http://t.co/KRBbpx6A62]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never go to a movie in Poland, you'll end up setting behind a Pole.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have always felt I was more accurately a Hard Rock musician.  - Geddy Lee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People who enjoy what they are doing invariably do it well. - Joe Gibbs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The dog represents all that is best in man. - Etienne Charlet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Options for Using Slimmers and Trimmers for Weight Loss  http://t.co/TFQycOoxFU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I went to college for four years. - Kim Kardashian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 11 - Waiting  http://t.co/jeS429GiBR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Platform Shoes  http://t.co/3VwtRdTejw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome fine wine t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the fine wine lovers in your life!   http://t.co/PcqtScQaC4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cocaine is God's way of saying you're making too much money. - Robin Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the shoe fits, it's too expensive. - Adrienne Gusoff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome gardening t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the gardening lovers in your life!   http://t.co/Gl4H0TRWCT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Who Is SpaceX?  http://t.co/1BAa2tB4fA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of State Farm Insurance  http://t.co/3xdkrJWAnz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I didn't grow up thinking, 'Oh, maybe someday I'm going to have a shoe named after me.' -  Sheryl Swoopes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good-bye, Broadcast.  Hello, Conversation.  Shel Israel - Co-Author Naked Conversations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Second marriage --  triumph of hope over experience]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Courtship is the period during which a girl decides whether or not she can do better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In youth we learn in age, we understand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Rufus  http://t.co/RvnyH2pLz6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't do fashion. I am fashion. - Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Molly Hatchet  http://t.co/p9h2tg82sK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About James Taylor - his biography  http://t.co/9HAVqPCCg8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The Top 10 European Beers  http://t.co/F2tP88rrCr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spock, where the hell's the power you promised?" - Kirk  "One damn minute, admiral" - Spock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the Hillbilly 10 Commandments ROFL - http://t.co/JMBilYO64b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exciting History of Baseball  http://t.co/CHhXUNCbPF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame Turf Wars: Such Rage; Much Death  http://t.co/TWVLpBzkwz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome running t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the running lovers in your life!  http://t.co/MnSjVyqFmW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Some Very Interesting and Unusual Beers  http://t.co/NQzNtuapwf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When money talks these days, it's probably asking what happened]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never go in against a Sicilian when death is on the line! - Vizzini, The Princess Bride]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is a better safeguard of liberty than a standing army. - Edward Everett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A tax collector has what it takes to take what you got]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Hire a Strategy Consulting Firm?  http://t.co/RI5dPc3SXu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read a Short Introduction to ABBA  http://t.co/5Bz76sj3c4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of Little House on The Prairie Episode - "In the Big Inning"  http://t.co/PePsG8OJfA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Kitty Kallen  http://t.co/BoW3p8FzAg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Ohio Players    http://t.co/JV7jhiC80s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I knew the words to 25 rock songs, so I got in the group. Long Tall Sally &amp; Tutti-Frutti, that got me in. - Paul McCartney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About eCommerce E-Tips  http://t.co/OhSC51h2HH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very cool Star Wars windshield sun reflector - may the force be with you!   http://t.co/6B2Co3KLed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome - Hopside Down Glass - Upside Down Beer Bottle Glass - Cool! http://t.co/kH1dtcxapl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Star Trek Uniform Onesies - Dress Up Your Little Geek! http://t.co/2fLLokgHJ4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Hallmarks of a Quality Insurance Company  http://t.co/ibF6A482sy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flattery, like perfume, should be smelled, not swallowed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awe cool - A Lock N' load target alarm clock/Gun alarm clock - shoot the dang thing! http://t.co/FGLFgswu0k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The kindness planned for tomorrow doesn't count for today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually, I majored in marketing and I have a bachelor of science. - Wanda Sykes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes I can't figure designers out. It's as if they flunked human anatomy. --&gt; Erma Bombeck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great History of Johnny Ace: A ‘One of his Kind’ Musical Legend  http://t.co/nkfosqR1XM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotta love this Minecraft wall torch - http://t.co/6gj4L8Q5aY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret of success is constancy to purpose. - Benjamin Disraeli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Meat Loaf  http://t.co/iNgW5Y7omd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not whether you get knocked down; it's whether you get up. - Vince Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Little by little does the trick. - Aesop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What people forget is that every movie that gets made keeps making money for somebody FOREVER. Dave Thomas]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>