<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About How Technology Has Helped Seniors to Make Great Strides in their Lifestyle  http://t.co/rGG81xCOev]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I could turn and live with animals, they are "¨so placid and self-contained,"¨I stand and look at them long and long. - Walt Whitman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Use Twitter in Business  http://t.co/3rudC8MX4q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He who laughs last, didn't get it!!  :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I die, I'm leaving my body to science fiction. - Steven Wright]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My advice if you insist on slimming: Eat as much as you like - just don't swallow it. - Harry Secombe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's an edge to real rock 'n' roll. It's all that matters. - Neil Young]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beauty shop: where woman go to save face.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goonies never say die. - Mike, The Goonies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Resources for Home Brewing  http://t.co/SZWPu4Q1fN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are seven winners of the Monaco Grand Prix on the starting line today, and four of them are Michael Schumacher. - Murray Walker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Blue Origin - A Profile of This Emerging Space Company  http://t.co/dMDbLC2j6Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How Small Business Can Grow with Social Media Sites  http://t.co/x0obQGp2Fi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thats the way Baseball go - Ron Washington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Out the Top Football Teams of the 2011-2012 Season  http://t.co/lxE8bNtJUu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Totally cool LEGO Star Wars R2D2 Awesome --&gt; http://t.co/fs6FZOwVsS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Tools for Finding Good Keywords  http://t.co/ezWF5grFHp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is amazing how may drivers, even at the Formula One Level, think that the brakes are for slowing the car down. - Mario Andretti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is Horology?  http://t.co/pZ9edBouEF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You Have Never Seen Knives Like These - They Interlock with in each other - stylish and modern! http://t.co/A2X3wFUW7Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A tax collector has what it takes to take what you got]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The crashes people remember, but drivers remember the near misses. - Mario Andretti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give a girl the right shoes, and she can conquer the world. - Marilyn Monroe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Design is a constant challenge to balance comfort with luxe, the practical with the desirable. - Donna Karan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ways to Earn a Living with a Creative Writing Degree  http://t.co/8dIZGe1Y7i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Strategy Consulting Firms to Avoid  http://t.co/85nlwAE19G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To climb steep hills requires slow pace at first. - William Shakespeare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making money is not gonna change anything about what I am, except I won't answer the door. Abel Ferrara]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 7 - No Luck!  http://t.co/5FqTflnS1W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The reality of science is that it takes 40 years to get to Jupiter, and that's a dull show. - Glen Morgan, "Space: Above and Beyond"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rule your mind or it will rule you. - Horace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So exactly how did the modern Garage evolve into its current form?  Very interesting... http://t.co/6mGQ9Ph1MC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome camping t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the camping lovers in your life!  http://t.co/sqHhD7NCxr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its not so much about the shoes, but the person wearing them --&gt; Adriana Trigiani, Viola in Real Life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attitude: It is our best friend or our worst enemy. - John C. Maxwell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Kim Carnes  http://t.co/ZORVJjHqJV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History Of Samuel Adams Beer  http://t.co/5qyVZ6p9FC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overheard when the boss returned from his safari in Africa: "He's the first man the head shrinkers ever failed with."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fool and his money are soon accepted into the highest social circles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is the ability to listen to almost anything without losing your temper or your self-confidence. - Robert Frost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money, if it does not bring you happiness, will at least help you be miserable in comfort. - Helen Gurley Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blow off some steam, or rather, shoot some smoke rings. The Zero Fog Blaster is a ray gun - totally cool!  http://t.co/kMothSEGv0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can a leopard change his spots?  "By going from one spot to another"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Badfinger - The Godfathers of Power Pop  http://t.co/wQ6GvxqiaX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Big-Dog Pet Fountain - Keeps Fresh and Tasty Water for Your Big Dog! http://t.co/Gx5Ec04I0V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trust people and they will be true to you; Treat them greatly, and they will show themselves great. - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweatpants are a sign of defeat. You lost control of your life so you bought some sweatpants. --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[End Of Line - The MCP, TRON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How Small Business Can Grow with Social Media Sites  http://t.co/x0obQGp2Fi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Adoption Part II - the Bulgaria Phase  http://t.co/EE4nvLb2qc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We thought you was a toad! - Delmar, O Brother Where Art Thou?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bird does not sing because it has an answer...  It sings because it has a song. - Chinese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Neil Diamond  http://t.co/JhSfY6eLtp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting Overview of Top 10 International Beers  http://t.co/NQUqh23LBe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Mod Showcase: Secret Rooms Mod  http://t.co/SzPHoll7S6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things could be worse. Suppose your errors were counted and published everyday, like those of a baseball player. - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Little Feat  http://t.co/d4yPmqiuvo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...Spinal Tap rocked my world. Its for rock what The Sound of Music was for hills. They really nailed how dumb rock can be. Jack Black]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Great Tours of Europe  http://t.co/vjOKZyLFbQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sorry, Dave. I'm afraid I can't do that. - HAL - 2001: A Space Odyssey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eat, drink and be merry, for tomorrow ye diet. - William Gilmore Beymer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here Kitty Kitty Kitty! - Tony Stewart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's recording techniques would have been regarded as science fiction forty years ago. - Tony Visconti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Few people SUFFER from egotism. With most of them it's a PLEASURE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The process of growing old is a question of mind over matter. If you don't mind, it doesn't matter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cowboys, Mavs, Rangers and more read about the Sports teams of the Dallas Fort-Worth Metroplex - http://t.co/8oaRFc3wgD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Yanjing Beer  http://t.co/8imnmoaFRF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So very many cool types of mens shoes - learn about men’s shoe styles... http://t.co/vSgm7daJ5U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was a pretty good coach and working with marketing was like coaching. - Bernard Ebbers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advertising is the life of trade. - Calvin Coolidge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did You Know this About Blackbeard in Pirates of the Caribbean 4  http://t.co/IFBYfUbSYr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Clarence Carter  http://t.co/7lM8zWR9dH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See you in another life, brother. - Desmond Hume, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Son, a father told his growing boy, "just remember on thing:  I know a lot more about being young than you do about being old."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mama always said you could tell an awful lot about a person by the kind of shoes they wear. - Forrest Gump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana’s Lyme Journey – Part 17 – More on Supplements  http://t.co/rZ7grhzXo3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Golden slumbers fill your eyes, smiles awake you when you rise. - Golden Slumbers by The Beatles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great overview on using Redstone in Minecraft - http://t.co/VAsmSl7529]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make the Most of Twitter for Your Business  http://t.co/MEG3Yd7hgo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahh Read About Loving Fine Wine  http://t.co/4ttPZelnjn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Supertramp  http://t.co/Lg3zgvMZ4e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Jose Feliciano  http://t.co/4TAsLQIIwe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these different types of beer - lots of options including ales, lagers, hocks and more!  http://t.co/mC0W9DgDW4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picking Earphones for Fitness Activities  http://t.co/Imk6yjt0eN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teenagers do everything we did…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Increase Space in Your Garage with Suitable Garage Floors  http://t.co/I8tQsUn7zn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting Your Creative Writing Degree Online  http://t.co/dY907HCHgI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The earth? Oh the earth will be gone in a few seconds...I'm going to blow it up. It's obstructing my view of Venus. - Marvin the Martian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Guide – Business to Business Internet Marketing Tips  http://t.co/uhlTxSHOMC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1f u c4n r34d th1s u r34lly n33d t0 g37 l41d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes a man to admit he's wrong but it takes a woman to prove it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wait a minute, Doc. Ah --  Are you telling me you built a time machine --  out of a DeLorean? - Marty McFly, Back to the Future]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once burned a lesson is learned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The scenery was very beautiful. But I did not see the Great Wall. - Yang Liwei, China's first astronaut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tantrums, Sick Days, and Being a Patient Mommy  http://t.co/djwsUpbf4d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rock and roll is here to stay. - Neil Young]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sovereign invigorator of the body is exercise, and of all the exercises walking is the best. - Thomas Jefferson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your chances of winning, I've got to believe are really, really small when you score one run in 18 innings. - Clint Hurdle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thats the way Baseball go - Ron Washington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NASA Unveils a Very Cool New Space Suit  http://t.co/V3AAJ6DnBw]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>