<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RepEBJ: My intern Audra Jackson led Democratic Interns in their own selfie 2day showing #DemInternDiversity #DemInternSelfie https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ddale8: Here is a list of some of the things that happened at the first day of the Republican convention: https://t.co/97H81oP8i6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm in the District so I am complicit in / Congress just taking our vote and dismissing it https://t.co/frA5LdzoIf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just digging in, but @Grist's election guide is v cool - tip of the hat to @scottdodd @rebleber and the whole crew! https://t.co/z6vJ8Yw711]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Activists looking to build a wall around Trump and the whole RNC. https://t.co/x2DFxkW07S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bluefin Tuna have been fished down to 2.6% of their historic population. Tell NOAA to do something about it:  https://t.co/yS5KbejdfO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If anyone's asking, clean cars aren't *just* good for the environment, as @ConsumersUnion points out. #ActonClimate https://t.co/5rTnTA5ooE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BGAlliance: With #FuelEconomy standards @EPA @NHTSAgov are successfully addressing #climatechange and building #jobs. https://t.co/fR3a…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New gov't report shows progress on huge part of @POTUS' legacy on climate: clean car standards.  https://t.co/PLKkRqHSLO… #ActOnClimate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @aaronhuertas: Only modest gains in EVs needed to meet #fueleconomy standards, agencies say. https://t.co/2adGpMTbe4 https://t.co/bH0m1u…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ggreeneva: When the Speaker takes a photo w/ House interns, and maybe three people of color are in it: https://t.co/etj6oRreLo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vive la France.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apparently coal is clean. And hey you can sequester your CO2 pollution with this bag of magic beans I have for sale. https://t.co/C7he06pyoC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Agent350: Watching a bunch of climate deniers pretend to defend science is pretty rich: https://t.co/us0MgKLDky #ExxonKnew]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rezdreams: The joint statement from DOJ halting DAPL construction near Lake Oahe and recognizing #NoDAPL as peaceful https://t.co/aUREM…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[love that so many people are using @bikeshare but can't use it even to get home anymore in @BloomingdaleDC due to full docks miles around]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RheaSuh: California's @JerryBrownGov is about to sign historic climate legislation. Watch here:  https://t.co/lwfbTPNYr8 #ActOnClimate…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC: HAPPENING NOW: California Governor @JerryBrownGov signs historic climate legislation https://t.co/oPaM9UuQ4e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Booyah. #ActOnClimate https://t.co/qzmDvkXHGJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From @POTUS en route to China: maybe R's will give him credence on climate once he's not president. https://t.co/zDZV62ulzD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NOAA: DEADLINE 9/9: Help identify #WHChampions assisting ongoing recovery of America’s #fishing industry &amp; communities https://t.co/e8m…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smog from oil and gas operations causes 750,000 asthma attacks a year in the U.S. Here's where they're happening: https://t.co/mbBg4eN0a4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RheaSuh: Good news. The #IUCNCongress just passed a motion denouncing the killing of whales under the guise of science. https://t.co/gW…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How oil &amp; gas exploration tortures marine life and damages ecosystems: https://t.co/Hoia0nzHMF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @guardianeco: Nasa: Earth is warming at a pace 'unprecedented in 1,000 years' https://t.co/qZ8OiFjugB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CapJohnMcMurray I thought it was well said!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NatGeo: President Obama just quadrupled the size of a national marine monument off northwestern Hawaii. https://t.co/rlmF5ZC7Ze]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I want to go hike Old Rag. And write to some gov't officials. Great column, @BucciVA! https://t.co/fkNg0MrAeA @EnvironmentVA #NPS100]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think i see an @adambduffy down there. Happy birthday, both to our national parks and to Duffy! https://t.co/9XdvfmdIh1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations to CA on the most aggressive emissions targets in the country! Lead on. #ActOnClimate  https://t.co/NVLl3uOExs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saw @iamjohnoliver tonight! He says he's staying in the U.S. no matter what after the election, "like the string quartet on the Titanic."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sens. Tim Kaine and Mark Warner are both now opposing offshore drilling. #ActonClimate #ProtectOurCoast https://t.co/Mjc6ghClUd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Oceana: Animated maps show dolphins and whales threatened by seismic airgun blasting in Atlantic https://t.co/zhclwjiLIV https://t.co/L…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great explainer of breakthrough #fisheries policies in the mid-Atlantic. Color commentary from @CapJohnMcMurray https://t.co/oA0t9oLRW0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AaronCouch @THR sure man, whatever you need to tell your Heat Vision buddies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice work from @AaronCouch on  the anniversary of the SNES. If only he were as good at Street Fighter as at writing. https://t.co/ptNfKGqCRv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JasonK350 @joshfoxfilm @350  I have a planning meeting on some other greenhouse gases booked sadly, but if it's canceled I'll be there!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1 pm tomorrow at the DC District Court, @JasonK350, @joshfoxfilm and @350 are rallying in solidarity. https://t.co/f43lY2CNDV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoyed this Stranger Things talk w/ the Duffers; still think @Energy's "we aren't evil" response was hilarious. https://t.co/Nh4Z9vwfJD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When someone says "we don't want to tell you how much we're polluting" that's a decent sign it should be required. https://t.co/MlLsh2u38V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great piece! @SenatorBoxer on how/why we need to account for carbon pollution in transportation planning. https://t.co/vfxm4kAMaI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good 101 from @EEPublishing on the historically bad flooding: https://t.co/fc4HCveD2P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most disastrous weather event in the U.S. since Sandy is happening, if you didn't know. https://t.co/awKi9TvwDE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlexBWall Scrooge would have been a better choice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SenJeffMerkley: .@POTUS' new truck fuel efficiency rules are critical to fight #climatechange. We must keep pushing strategies to get t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AaronCouch Speaking of fan trailers, did you see the Rogue One trailer setup used for Empire? https://t.co/WFd696Iy4Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WhiteHouse: Big news: We just took new steps to cut carbon pollution and save consumers money →
 https://t.co/WoV945mztb https://t.co/1…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On a more hopeful note, carbon pollution standards for heavy duty trucks (e.g. 18-wheelers) were finalized today.  https://t.co/GE6uAdopMz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC: It's official: July was the Earth's hottest month since at least 1880, acc. to @NASA. https://t.co/egQAuqtq9M via @mashable #ActO…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hottest July ever. "We’re going through these records like nothing this year." #ActOnClimate https://t.co/P0kky3cgAx https://t.co/LOL81xccxk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ICYMI: @POTUS' wkly address is all about climate change: Paris, power plants, cars, and more. #actonclimate https://t.co/zt4firgnMV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kansas has seen fewer and weaker quakes since reducing fracking. #AdAstraPerAspera https://t.co/hk1UKLp9Yl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just for the record,  @AaronCouch and all of geekdom, I called this over a year ago. https://t.co/du1U6NaDeQ https://t.co/kQ9Bg2BDuy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AaronCouch Same here, but the older I get, the more I lean Fellowship.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AaronCouch All these years, I thought you were a Return of the King kind of guy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @paulkrugman: Climate change never comes up unless HRC brings it up. Debate moderators have completely failed on the most important issu…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @paulkrugman: So, four debates; four shout-outs by moderators to deficit scolds; not one question about climate change. It's really disg…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MikeGrunwald: Wallace says the debt hasn't been discussed at the debates. That is really really not true. #coughclimatecough]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JasonK350: Three debates
Zero climate questions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right, about that. The only reason #climate has come up in any of them is that @HillaryClinton and @TimKaine have mentioned it. https://t.co/NyTV2elRZO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Final topic is the debt?  You forgot one that effects billions and has made major int'l news in recent days. #ActOnClimate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You should deregulate. Also, you should have stopped me. https://t.co/IsaBf2H1nM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You won't find a quote from me" on reckless nuclear policy, says remarkably incorrect @realDonaldTrump   https://t.co/bfJdw0X0go via @WIRED]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RTing for the climate, staying for the Riker https://t.co/tLoGVTPXVr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jonfavs: He's gone full Baldwin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New #EUbioenergy policy MUST protect our climate, crops &amp; forests - Make it right #Šefčovič &amp; #Cañete! #SOSforests https://t.co/TjvyWajOqB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EliseHiggins Not a viewer, so I'm actually envisioning this with Adam West's Batman and it checks out. https://t.co/CrdnFwycoy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fivefifths making the primary villains less relatable by association]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations, planet! World leaders take another critical step toward avoiding disastrous warming: https://t.co/31km8cGjQM  #HFCphasedown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EU policy affects US forests, and we need action to make sure our forests aren't used as fuel worldwide. Join the Thunderclap! #SOSforests https://t.co/pS45EamehS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @adriannaq: We are ready to #ActOnClimate @VocesVerdes https://t.co/0N8aX6W2hK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @aaronhuertas: .@POTUS cementing his status as the biggest science nerd president since Teddy Roosevelt. https://t.co/410SA0yswn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Takeaways from the new report: Latinos' support for climate action, vulnerability to impacts, and growing numbers in the U.S. https://t.co/IILpr66V0q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Latinos support efforts to #actonclimate, and get hit hard by climate impacts. @NRDC and @VocesVerdes's new report: https://t.co/IO09zyJgae]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm pretty sure I saw this Renault in a 90's Batman movie. EV's totally steal the (auto) show: https://t.co/6f22KFmz7x #cleanercars https://t.co/bT9XvINd9R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CrossisBoss touché.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LFFriedman: "I have a comprehensive energy policy but it really does include fighting climate change because I think that is a serious…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent fact check. https://t.co/4gHVnhQnWH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There is a thing called clean coal." Can we get a fact check on this?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You spoke gleefully about engaging in sexual assault. Get off this stage and the national stage. https://t.co/xhOQcE0ZtD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's response on the recording, basically: there are much bigger problems in the world than how terrible a person I am]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RheaSuh: Alright, time for the #debate Let's hope we finally get a question about #ClimateChange.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's official: the Paris Agreement has gone from blueprint to reality in record time. #actonclimate  https://t.co/Mad1JUxX2L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LFFriedman: Once again #climatechange gets name-checked within the opening minutes of a debate. Will there be an actual substantive que…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@timkaine just followed @HillaryClinton's lead by addressing need to #actonclimate at the opening of his debate. #VPDebate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RheaSuh: Good news. The European Union will formally approve the Paris climate agreement. Here's my statement for @NRDC_AF https://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@POTUS @LeoDiCaprio and @KHayhoe are wrapping up. Here's the trailer for the new documentary from Leo. https://t.co/X1CB4ZuiD7 #ActOnClimate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WhiteHouse: "We're in a race against time." —@POTUS talking about why we need to #ActOnClimate with @LeoDiCaprio &amp; @KHayhoe at #SXSL ht…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We shouldn't be debating whether we're causing climate change but how we address it. @KHayhoe just did a great job of laying that out. #sxsl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live: President Obama is hosting @LeoDiCaprio and @KHayhoe on the South Lawn to screen a new doc on #climate:  https://t.co/A672rDJPpc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The most important thing to do is to connect this issue to what is already in our hearts." Dr. Hayhoe on talking #climate change. #SXSL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reflections on the #CleanPowerPlan's day in court: “I feel like we’ve all been through a marathon today." https://t.co/98rD3MZZfy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC: "The Clean Power Plan had a very good day. But we aren’t taking that to the bank just yet." – @ddonigernrdc on today's hearing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ddonigernrdc: #CleanPowerPlan had a very good day in court. https://t.co/5nsUrgOE7N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jillianhmurphy The third term is the incentive to go find another planet already.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're going to deny climate science, or deny denying it, at least keep your falsehoods straight. #actonclimate https://t.co/v9scPhWgNg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SenMarkey: 200+ former House &amp; Senate members filed a bipartisan amicus brief in support of the #CleanPowerPlan. Read more here
https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC: The #CleanPowerPlan will save lives and money, says @drkimknowlton. Here’s why:  https://t.co/ue5Xo9pW2Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, 1) it was the most tweeted debate ever. https://t.co/kYvupZzxtW  2) the most RT'd tweet was from 2012. https://t.co/iF7xo2LNh1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dfirgs: A @BloombergDotOrg poll found that voters support the #CleanPowerPlan in states where AGs are suing to block it https://t.co/wI…]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>