<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[1st Line Support HelpDesk: 1st Line Support Help Desk Technician This is a great opportunity for you if you are looking to progress your career within IT Support, you will be supporting the current IT Manager working on a range of tasks and day to day… https://t.co/wGJQ3U4eQ1 https://t.co/Fy9eHhp7AG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Consultant: Senior Pre-Sales Technical Consultant | South East England | Salary Negotiable Jonothan Bosworth Recruitment Specialists are working with a global provider of security solutions and IT services. With a worldwide client base, our… https://t.co/X92SkLoOTS https://t.co/OgZj4HwLJJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google’s Waze has expanded its carpooling app to every US state: Waze Carpool, the app designed to connect drivers and commuters, is now available throughout the U.S. with a special focus on connecting Amazon employees. As part of the nationwide rollout… https://t.co/mMoXG8v9fd https://t.co/NVh8gLv0XW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NetSuite Functional Consultant – London: I am currently working with a customer based in Central London, with a strong foundation within the Finance Industry. The mentioned customer has an urgent requirement for a NetSuite Functional Consultant, starting… https://t.co/4be0v7Y7zO https://t.co/LQgosZAlxn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PART TIME Project Manager: Business Project Manager Initial 9 Month Contract Reading PART TIME – 18.75 hours per week. I am partnering with a global technology company who are looking for a Project Manager to join their team supporting delivery across… https://t.co/24KY3Ob0Ox https://t.co/6HRQIHAj8p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sears shares falter on bankruptcy fears https://t.co/VaFlXjdLDk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Designer: Senior Designer – Manchester An exciting opportunity has arisen in a busy retailer based in Manchester. This position will contribute to the continued success of their already established Design team, in which as a Senior Designer you… https://t.co/Ry8iydIuVt https://t.co/NNunQjSi5h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shujinko brings in $2.8M for its cloud security compliance platform: Shujinko is emerging from stealth today with $2.8 million in seed funding from Unusual Ventures, Defy, Vulcan Capital, PSL Ventures and Vas Ventures. https://t.co/PTgVg8FSCP https://t.co/CJtxy282rj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Automation Engineer: I have an excellent opportunity for an experienced QA Automation Engineer to join an exciting start-up based in Dublin. They have recently received some major investment due to the high demand for the unique and innovative product… https://t.co/Xoa32oUxkN https://t.co/UqQfWg67IB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dev Ops Engineer – .Net- SQL- 55K: Working for a Global company with multiple options of exposure to new technologies. Working in a research and development team compiled of 10 people. Opportunity of international travel and to be involved in some… https://t.co/VkAQBI4z0B https://t.co/zVMj42PXPg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst: Capita IT Resourcing is currently recruiting for a Business Analyst to join our FTSE250 client on a permanent basis. The successful candidate will join a shared resource team working across multiple programmes, projects and clients. Key… https://t.co/NGVOdfaOha https://t.co/IO3UUoDt6U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Robinhood cuts trading fees, grows profits with in-house clearing: As zero-commission stock trading app Robinhood starts preparing to IPO, an engineering investment two years in the making could accelerate its quest for profitability. Most stock broker… https://t.co/zA69v8tiDP https://t.co/QQSoKt6MTg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lessons from Jersey's full-fibre internet https://t.co/mZOxgqZ0n9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agile Coach/Delivery Manager: An exciting opportunity for an Agile Coach to be part of shaping the cultural transformation and improving/introducing agile ways of working within a fast-growing organisation has become available. Based in the South of… https://t.co/Ox9wIvLvxz https://t.co/fW1qoZml2z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior IT Support: Salary: £16,000 – £18,000 plus excellent pension scheme and generous company benefits, plus free on-site parking. Location: Shipley, West Yorkshire Working Hours: Mon – Thurs 8.30am – 5pm, Fri – 8.30am – 1.30pm OVERVIEW Our client are… https://t.co/lXeon7xrAO https://t.co/HgbnT4i6Fu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[University 'dual nationality' plan for Brexit https://t.co/1IFknsF87X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Cloud: Project Manager – Cloud London A leading Cloud Service Provider is looking to add a talented Project Manager to here London based teams to work with their client's during the integration and migration of their systems to Cloud… https://t.co/ynGqvo5GTr https://t.co/QxUFPJZ8kn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hot summer gives boost to UK economy https://t.co/b6IZZJeCfI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nasty Gal ad banned over underweight model https://t.co/RTSMTYXzvq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Office 365 Solutions Architect: aspire cambridge are currently recruiting for an Office 365 Solutions Architect on behalf of our client in Swavesey, Cambridge. We are looking for a creative Solutions Architect focused on the Office 365, SharePoint… https://t.co/hLTU30Bw4r https://t.co/Jr1w2ixnQS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Divvy, an interesting new fractional home ownership startup, just raised a Series A round led by Andreessen Horowitz: Tech startups have found all kinds of ways to lend money to those hampered by either too little or not very good credit. The approach of… https://t.co/V7DvCTc5xA https://t.co/yAZ9gCqFej]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network and Security Consultant: Network and Security Consultant – Full Time – Wimbledon We are seeking an office based Experienced Network &amp; Security Consultant to support and administer our 780+ UK sites. The candidate will be involved in BAU as well… https://t.co/IJZoxIZOGm https://t.co/oS4R8twvPu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Patisserie Valerie warns of potential fraud https://t.co/RM2BavH2EQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst: My client, one of the UK’s leading providers of technology enabled business services, are looking for a proactive Business Analyst to join their Edinburgh based team. Working within a Business Support function, this role is responsible for… https://t.co/nbmIHueWXW https://t.co/ot6ColTlu8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infrastructure Automation Engineers – Powershell: Infrastructure Automation Engineers x 2 + NSOIT Project at Corsham + Roles are INSIDE IR35 + Equivalent Ltd company rate would be £(Apply online only) per day + PAYE – £(Apply online only) + Holiday pay +… https://t.co/RAvM5gVg95 https://t.co/R2pT34FYM3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Partner Marketing Manager: Partner Marketing Manager London Marketing – Marketing Full-time Permanent Our Purpose Improbable is dedicated to building powerful technology designed to help solve previously impossible problems and enable the creation of new… https://t.co/DI8nswbUiK https://t.co/P0FotCLLJj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solution Architect: Role Solution Architect Auto req ID 34387BR Domain Telecom Skillset Cable Technology , Country United Kingdom State / Region / Province London Work Location London Company ITL UK Job Description Role – Solutions Architect  Location –… https://t.co/SOKhhOZADK https://t.co/VPSTSWudrU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Autonomous Driving/ADAS – Senior/Principal Analyst, Europe: Autonomous Driving/ADAS – Senior/Principal Analyst, Europe IHS Markit Automotive Supply Chain and Technology Solutions team is looking for a qualified candidate to lead its North American… https://t.co/4SdaJMtTvZ https://t.co/6JbUUEvXj1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Skincare brand Deciem shuts stores following online post by founder https://t.co/wztggeZ7Nx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South Africa's finance minister Nhlanhla Nene quits over Gupta scandal https://t.co/UfwDPnpacd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Pixel 3 phones launch during privacy storm https://t.co/Fx2LjhTfag]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[North Sea Rhum gas field deal moves closer amid Iran sanctions https://t.co/wLY4cibLYE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Security Architect – London: Security Architect – London or Guildford – IDAM, Encryption, Cloud Security, Network Security, Application Security, CISSP, TOGAF, MODAF Outsource UK’s Cyber Team are looking to hire a number of Security Architects to work as… https://t.co/VViNlKW84b https://t.co/5EXIrvMAuG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Final Draft screenwriting software goes to 11: Of all the fascinating apps to be found out in the wild I’m especially enamored of Final Draft. It’s an app dedicated to writing and developing screenplays and it has stood the test of time, going through 11… https://t.co/8Tssl0BOhe https://t.co/VMOXjVVUyH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Pixel’s product directors on single cameras and notches: Google hardware launches are never spec-fests. The search giant would rather just sit on the sideline while companies like Apple and Samsung battle it out on that front. In fact, numbers… https://t.co/N3usDEHNrH https://t.co/QiMCHSC75C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kafka Developer: Kafka Developer Location: Split between Ipswich (25%) and Saudi Arabia (75%) All expenses including travel and accomodation covered in Saudi Arabia Visa and travel covered by client Rate: £500 – £580 per day Duration: 5 Months –… https://t.co/FyHQbWuTbg https://t.co/o6ajpyV85y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce CPQ Consultant: A leading Platinum Salesforce partner, based in Central London are seeking an experienced Consultant with hands of Salesforce CPQ / Steelbrick implementation experience, to drive forward their expanding CPQ offering. As a… https://t.co/Pqa3qKc0Xh https://t.co/N0464kbwiv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Government watchdog says US weapons systems are vulnerable to hacks, but the Pentagon is slow to act: A government watchdog has said the Department of Defense has not done enough to protect critical weapons systems from cyberattacks. The new report out… https://t.co/9yz927TXqd https://t.co/m4drIvHt2Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Engineer – Python/Javascript: I am currently working with a thriving company based in Newbury who are seeking a QA Engineer to join their team. They have grown from a team of 10 to 40 in the last year and have projections to continue growing at a… https://t.co/eRALLzfZ1P https://t.co/DsxLwiUTOo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Netlify just got $30 million to change the way developers build websites: Netlify wants to revolutionize the way developers build websites, abstracting away the web server and breaking web sites into microservices, making the process more like building a… https://t.co/Z4tiVmM0iT https://t.co/bzzrD2wIQW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back End Engineer: Back End Engineer London We are currently recruiting for a new position of Back End Engineer to join a team of a very successful Tech start up working with the Artificial Intelligence market based in London. Responsibilities: * To have… https://t.co/bDmrnunNZk https://t.co/GILRzVLamT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SEO Manager: SEO Manager – Farringdon, London – Up to £35k We are currently looking for an experienced SEO Manager for a huge digital agency based in Farringdon, Central London. This company are working with a number of large and well recognised… https://t.co/kJ566FgCH8 https://t.co/TwgKYm3bP0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Windows 10 Migration Engineer: Windows 10 Migration Engineer – 6 Month Contract – Motherwell – £140 – £150 Per Day I am currently on the hunt for an Windows 10 Migration Engineer for a leading client of mine based in Motherwell to join a small Team, My… https://t.co/nrfC9yZjg8 https://t.co/LIYj0c5UNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Binance will disclose listing fees and donate them to its own charity: The biggest cryptocurrency exchange wants to make its coin listing process a bit less sketchy. In a Medium post on Monday, the company said that moving forward it would disclose fees… https://t.co/qVINB7TA2R https://t.co/G1rrYVlmp8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gwyneth Paltrow on Goop: We disagree with pseudoscience claims https://t.co/B32hUBfIJy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps/WebOps Engineer – London – Up to £52,000: DevOps/WebOps Engineer – London – Up to £52,000 + Amazing Benefits (DevOps, WebOps, Cloud, Linux, Windows, Bash, Go, Terraform, Ansible, Kubernetes, GCP, AWS, Azure, Rackspace, Varnish, Nginx, Apache,… https://t.co/GrzAntvhrA https://t.co/nKB5bB666K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst (SAAS): I am currently recruiting for a Business Analyst to join my clients software delivery team in Central Brighton. My client specialises in the implementation of bespoke software packages to a range of different industries and… https://t.co/XzSumskjBC https://t.co/amKS2fhA5l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bank of England in unusual warning about risky business debt https://t.co/bnJrysYkm9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer – Cyber Security Java Developer – Cyber Security  A Java Developer for a cyber security company. The Java Developer will be involved in the building of an API detection systems. The Java Developer will be designing… https://t.co/84NpDZz46b https://t.co/RVmbKkf1lr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Implementation Manager: Our client, a software company who specialise in global mobility management solutions are looking to add a Global Mobility Software Implementation Manager to their growing operations in London. The Implementation Manager… https://t.co/qeTtgqi0oa https://t.co/qsuUUAr4KE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Symfony Developer: Senior PHP Symfony Developer – £50k – £65k – Central London Senior PHP Symfony Developer £50k-£65k Central London Pearson Frank are currently recruiting for a Senior PHP Developer with good experience of the Symfony framework to… https://t.co/i4Osinib5s https://t.co/Ym1v7ec1Zg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aviva chief executive Mark Wilson in surprise departure https://t.co/HzjzLNIpfK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fortnite maker buys anti-cheat software company: Epic’s gotta do something with the money it’s printing through Fortnite purchases. Acquisitions appear to be at the top of that list, starting with Kamu, the Finnish startup behind Easy Anti-Cheat. Epic… https://t.co/zBVtfMlk4S https://t.co/5X9YXftaTp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Courier – Newcastle: Job: Technical Courier Overall Job Purpose: To assist with the deliver and collection of IT equipment and to support the Distributed and System engineering teams in the various activities which reside within these areas of… https://t.co/B2OYuenfcH https://t.co/GCVZWa4rh7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Product Manager: Senior Product Manager Are you a Senior Product Manager who has been there and done that what seems like ten times over? Are you desperate to find a challenge where you can build from scratch? Then this unique opportunity is your… https://t.co/wmLD801GGJ https://t.co/3JPTOHxKm2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Jonny 5 is a ‘Alive’… struck by lightning Johnny gained the power of independent thought and is on the run to develop and build his own army of Software Developers and Engineers. Number Five has realised the meaning of being ‘alive’… https://t.co/8DaUrSpIUT https://t.co/khoZEgZuEH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Morrisons appealing over staff data leak compensation https://t.co/L2UemAk5v5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Sales Executive/Business Development: Sr Sales Executive/Business Development Sales Executive IHS Markit (Nasdaq: INFO) is a world leader in critical information, analytics and solutions for the major industries and markets that drive economies… https://t.co/oBnvhicqSv https://t.co/2QkMRppukP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump tariffs make world 'poorer and more dangerous' https://t.co/knkkf3aRkX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YouTuber creates concept video showing Fortnite in first-person mode: Fortnite Battle Royale was undoubtedly the big game of 2017, and 2018 is shaping up to be very similar. And with such popularity inevitably comes a swath of critics. Take, for example,… https://t.co/jEXNLkWWYx https://t.co/qdgHLi3lMM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Business Technology Analyst (Business intelligence / Data warehousing): Senior Business Technology Analyst (Business intelligence / Data warehousing) ZS is the world’s largest consulting firm focused exclusively on improving business performance… https://t.co/nf71oasqhM https://t.co/yALewZ8juK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amsterdam's canal boats go electric https://t.co/naYNHXPAKN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coding for life https://t.co/A85k7HzXcd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jaguar Land Rover plans two-week closure as demand falls https://t.co/ePt6s2OhBA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-Tesco directors on trial over fraud and false accounting https://t.co/1mHjFMOPbn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heathrow fined for USB stick data breach https://t.co/cffCXrPIzs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Software Developer (Java focus – trading systems). Fantastic career opportunity for a junior-to-mid-level software developer, with core Java skills, to join the technology team at this global financial systems vendor. The company is… https://t.co/fTHukAsaWF https://t.co/AK2QCuUtIl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LinkedIn acquires employee engagement platform Glint: LinkedIn, the social network for the working world with close to 600 million users and now under the wing of Microsoft, has announced an acquisition as it continues to work on expanding the ways that… https://t.co/t4YB6ojLfI https://t.co/B6xnxiN8QP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test Development Engineer (Hardware &amp; Software) – Germany: My client is a world leading manufacturer of power tools for the professional industry. Offering specialist products for a wide variety of industrial settings, the client is renowned for the… https://t.co/5yCzBOCQQc https://t.co/E7ByF1uLPB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The top smartphone trends to watch in 2019: This was a bad year for the smartphone. For the first time, its seemingly unstoppable growth began to slow. Things started off on a bad note in February, when Gartner recorded its first year-over-year decline… https://t.co/JyopsLeJO7 https://t.co/vi73HJKnkk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C# Developer: An opportunity for an experienced C# developer to join a city centre development team working on cutting edge business applications. You'll need to be confident working with C#.NET, MVC and React. Knowledge of MS SQL Server and Entity… https://t.co/THFc2RB0l1 https://t.co/DX6LPXpHc6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here comes the downturn: It’s remarkable how fast the tenor of the times has changed. Only a few months ago we were in a boom that seemed like it might never end. Now the yield curve has inverted; the markets have gone bear; and Google Trends has the… https://t.co/Ae8FCgHAev https://t.co/agpFYcefc9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer – Leeds – £45k: Full Stack Developer – Leeds £30,000 – £45,000 The company: A creative agency based in Leeds who really push the boundary on all their projects. Having worked with a variety of global brands on various creative… https://t.co/J7utLKK75r https://t.co/pkZwQKFbOn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Technical Infrastructure Analyst: As our IT Technical Infrastructure Analyst you'll troubleshooting and resolving issues with Unix servers, Oracle/SQL Server databases and performing software installation and upgrades – no two weeks will ever be the… https://t.co/rpVvsVxaJT https://t.co/4Ykkf7ug1L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Super Saturday' fails to boost retailers https://t.co/9mXgi3ubHO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CISO, Information Security Officer: The role will be responsible for a wide range of information security controls and processes to maintain confidentiality, integrity, availability, and accountability, to ultimately protect company assets from the… https://t.co/SdAsHuJujE https://t.co/y7jh40XI3S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Quality Assurance in County Cork: CK Group are recruiting for an IT Quality Assurance Engineer to join a company in the Pharmaceutical industry at their site based in Innishannon, County Cork on a contract basis for 12 months. The Company: Our client… https://t.co/6XG949rJLD https://t.co/zlYSWTdLz4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Engineer – London – Blockchain: Lead Engineer – London – Blockchain Lead Engineer A great opportunity to work with the disruptive technology Blockchain – creating applications which are aimed to solve cross-industry challenges such as automating… https://t.co/lehrnjOi82 https://t.co/hdURXHJuUX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Support Engineer: Application Support Engineer – Chief Information Office Peterborough Who we are An award-winning bank here to help Britain’s go-getters. More about us In 2009, Aldermore set out to be the bank helping those with ideas, big… https://t.co/pB7MwSjJgb https://t.co/Lsgjq8L57R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[E-Commerce Content Manager: E-Commerce Manager Elstree, Herts c£35,000 Role purpose is to Manage the E-Commerce Platform Reporting to the Global Head of IT, this role requires an experienced Content Manager with Magento 2.0 Administration experience in a… https://t.co/1lJxq4599V https://t.co/tmDDJwSG3P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trainee Internal Sales: Overview Excellent trainee sales opportunity in a large prestigious technology company, ideal for someone looking for a great company in which to build a fast-track career. Based in Abingdon. You will be creating leads through new… https://t.co/JyWscth1v4 https://t.co/n0pFFGypjE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack PHP Developer – Sheffield – Up To £45,000: Full Stack PHP Developer – Sheffield – Up To £45,000 If you’re technically gifted, creative and have that entrepreneurial drive then this position will definitely be of interest. The company works in… https://t.co/QSaIOeLbdr https://t.co/vXjAapN8eM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Manager: Technical Manager: Beyond is looking for an experienced Technical Manager to join the team in London. The successful candidate will partner with the Delivery Lead and client Technical Lead on the smooth running and delivery of the… https://t.co/BzJm0vd3Qa https://t.co/qwVlScOOD9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Service Desk Engineer: Are you a Service Desk Engineer looking for a chance to grow and build on your career with a forward thinking company? Look no further as my client are well established, well known in the market and a big player within the… https://t.co/x5DTPeXlNS https://t.co/WyJ4vrXBX2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Web Developer: Our client are looking for a Full Stack Web Developer to join their team. You must be able to work well in a team and be able to adapt to various different technologies, from the latest frontend frameworks and tools, to working… https://t.co/vmMiTpU1C6 https://t.co/6KuAEBjZi0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Controller: Financial Controller, Financial Controller, Financial Controller Job Title: Financial Controller Location: Bodmin Salary: £18,000 (FTE £30,000) 16-24 hours a week 15% with a 50/50 split Acorn is currently working with a leading IT… https://t.co/EYDICt4rAK https://t.co/qMqWCkmq8c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Apple event, but with Bad Lip Reading: Bad Lip Reading has held a special place in my heart longer than just about any other YouTube channel. The formula is just too perfect: take a thing we know, blend it up in a stew of uncanny absurdity, and… https://t.co/XXwjVyFcbt https://t.co/yQG8Liqq0E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Support Engineer: Application Support Engineer required by a successful high-tech company located in Basingstoke. Due to the continued growth of the company is need of an experienced engineer to help support multiple applications and… https://t.co/EukUsbrt0h https://t.co/4fwsAjuDoI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer – PHP: We have an exciting opportunity to join a well established and rapidly growing company. Our client provides a world-leading consultancy service to some of the world’s leading brands and they are looking for an experienced… https://t.co/qc5gsDSjcH https://t.co/xXRJe6MSxV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Coordinator: Project Coordinator required to join a large IT Services company who are delivering a global Windows 10 deployment for a tier 1 bank. The Project Coordinator is required to work closely with the customer to develop, schedule and… https://t.co/j5HSz2RJKH https://t.co/lkOzs3mCAE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Administrator: System Administrator Northampton – New offices Temp to Perm Full Time (9-5) £11.28 per hour Are you an expert in Excel and enjoy producing reports and manipulating data? Would you like to join an ever expanding business and provide… https://t.co/DYm3lqtKMp https://t.co/yxGHekacmT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AT&amp;T says it’s getting that 5G Samsung phone, too: Samsung announced yesterday that it’s set to bring a 5G phone to market in the first half of next year, name-checking Verizon in the promise. This morning, however, AT&amp;T was quick to note that it will… https://t.co/xUokIH5QaL https://t.co/szx9L9NUdo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Service Desk Technician – Huddersfield: Our Client a facilities management organisation are looking to recruit an IT Service Desk Technician to be based at their new HQ in Huddersfield. For over ten years our Client have provided comprehensive waste… https://t.co/BBf1FkWdTK https://t.co/cXomkSW3ED]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Network Consultant – Cisco – North West: A Senior Cisco Technical Engineer or Consultant with a good understanding of server and virtualisation technologies is required by an extremely well established and expanding Managed Service Provider based… https://t.co/EpahTGrKtj https://t.co/WO9rvTUCng]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C# .Net Developer – Dublin: C# .Net Developer – Dublin One of the most exciting companies to set up in Dublin over the past few years have recently kicked off development for a new product they hope to launch into the European market at the end of next… https://t.co/qFi7Ix8JjW https://t.co/nnNOZnh8jF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bose is dabbling in ‘audio AR’ with a pair of sunglasses: Back in March we first caught wind that Bose is dabbling in augmented reality, with the launch of a new wearable SDK. Seems the headphone maker is ready to bring that technology to market,… https://t.co/QpAVMsKdqV https://t.co/cStQgNj8K7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Network Engineer: Lead Network Engineer – Harlow – Circa £50k + Benefits We are looking to join a market leader of innovative solutions for the defence and aerospace industry at their Harlow location in Essex. This individual will be responsible for… https://t.co/xBzWOwthIR https://t.co/QCknV8Ksh6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior Web Applications Developer: JUNIOR WEB APPLICATIONS DEVELOPER (Home based permanent contract) This is a fantastic opportunity to join the largest privately-owned HR and Payroll provider in the UK. With offices in Nottingham, Dublin, Washington and… https://t.co/2HvN40ZUiC https://t.co/B4AnsddexD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tencent Music moving ahead with its $1.2B U.S. stock market debut: Tencent Music Entertainment’s initial public offering is back in motion, two months after the company reportedly postponed it amid a global selloff. In a regulatory filing today, the… https://t.co/XsLXteP67Y https://t.co/MaZSxqqYUX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Graduate Consultant: Job Title: Graduate Consultant Salary: £23,000 plus £26K+ OTE Sector: Financial services Our client: A market leading client of ours are on the lookout for an ambitious graduate to join their team as a Graduate Consultant. This… https://t.co/DXPWeWvPMU https://t.co/GcVMKJfAjK]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>