<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Arson Suspect Arrested as Cranston Fire Rages in California https://t.co/wbmNp9QiqF https://t.co/hFefYC2KYZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woman and 2 of Her Great-Grandchildren Die in Carr Fire, Family Says https://t.co/6tXi57fffY https://t.co/NZZBDNg5eA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Officer’s Bullet Killed Trader Joe’s Employee in Los Angeles Standoff, Police Say https://t.co/xXUVPECL5Y https://t.co/wASAPnrR6N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two Trump Allies, Seeing Unlimited Opportunity, Instead Drew Scrutiny https://t.co/2HekCioqzw https://t.co/xquCRspdxB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police May Seek Hate-Crime Charge in Attack on Latino Mayor https://t.co/bvKlckFaB7 https://t.co/oERMumpQ0q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still Standing, Jared Kushner and Ivanka Trump Step Back in the Spotlight https://t.co/EWJRVDIg9E https://t.co/133GBYv9qx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Civil War Portrayals’ Glaring Omission https://t.co/lxj09nFn9T https://t.co/VYultancKy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DealBook Briefing: A Favorite Trump Bank Questioned Over Kushner Credit https://t.co/xbAzwqunZI https://t.co/SWasUp4LZM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump’s Twitter Threat vs. Iran: Loud but Hardly Clear https://t.co/JwFD3lE3y3 https://t.co/G0pgBdYoy0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BART Stabbing Suspect Is Arrested in ‘Vicious’ Attack That Killed Woman https://t.co/uV44TMYWIy https://t.co/yUxBcHIRxi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pruitt’s Successor Wants Rollbacks, Too. And He Wants Them to Stick. https://t.co/ZbsJJOBlh1 https://t.co/2o7BUzo3id]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian Hackers Appear to Shift Focus to U.S. Power Grid https://t.co/xISZFM0EVg https://t.co/inU4r6ChSg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As Affordable Housing Crisis Grows, HUD Sits on the Sidelines https://t.co/tNmL5qyfdI https://t.co/Qsf34o8uRK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sex Scandal Toppled a Silicon Valley Chief. Investors Say, So What? https://t.co/B0mCfCRAD4 https://t.co/EDyk9ofoFZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iran, Toronto, Subway: Your Monday Evening Briefing https://t.co/09zg9WauUt https://t.co/XGACteAGoL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook and YouTube Give Alex Jones a Wrist Slap https://t.co/DnEYaGG1N4 https://t.co/cTfcmzf22A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How a Small Bank Became a Go-To Lender to the Trump Family https://t.co/Ze1P5Xdy4i https://t.co/T45utbbW7P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will the Trump Tax Bill Drive Down Ticket Sales? https://t.co/z1R9AeJxe7 https://t.co/tCUYBRZAdF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dirk Nowitzki Signs One-Year Deal With the Dallas Mavericks https://t.co/950x6877nJ https://t.co/mKGGfGLsy4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carmelo Anthony Is Set to Sign With the Rockets https://t.co/noVFR6Efw6 https://t.co/qt35UhesgW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Robert Mueller, North Korea, ‘Mission: Impossible’: Your Friday Briefing https://t.co/SV51MBPnuv https://t.co/EMhTa51b5f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top Trump Officials Clash Over Plan to Let Cars Pollute More https://t.co/Js4tjDT989 https://t.co/SH4MxQ6s89]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toronto ‘Shocked’ by Shooting That Left 2 Dead and 13 Injured https://t.co/UYKt0J7msZ https://t.co/d5C9TdfTuV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Nigerian Scam, With a Royal Twist https://t.co/e7PgNObG2m https://t.co/gXGRMjCCJN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft Employees Question C.E.O. Over Company’s Contract With ICE https://t.co/Y0mjh3FhbY https://t.co/F5N02frXXz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prosecutors Seek to Question Trump Organization’s Finance Chief https://t.co/a088dF2hG1 https://t.co/k6AqfiEPOk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Threatens Sanctions Against Turkey Over Detained Pastor https://t.co/oQ7MYlOgOK https://t.co/FnoRKFs2fy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A #MeToo Reckoning in China’s Workplace Amid Wave of Accusations https://t.co/dlE4W4vBt2 https://t.co/WMmHb2FsBb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hundreds of Migrants Storm Fences to Enter Spanish Enclave in Africa https://t.co/Ghf4CfCyis https://t.co/0nC5VMoYhf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mueller Examining Trump’s Tweets in Wide-Ranging Obstruction Inquiry https://t.co/82qLLiIw4K https://t.co/jgdkgJeXls]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With Deadline Hours Away, Authorities Scramble to Reunite Migrant Families https://t.co/RCuTzZzSVO https://t.co/xIuHCfbhQX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Kushner Ally Was Up for a Federal Post. Then the F.B.I. Began Digging. https://t.co/wtSHE47SqC https://t.co/TdU5DWHBke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Billionaire Yogi Behind Modi’s Rise https://t.co/fyoSFcHtik https://t.co/xh2zT5yVog]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blast Rocks Area Outside United States Embassy in Beijing https://t.co/ulp6Y8o5Vz https://t.co/k9q5KfPypO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trader Joe’s Employee Killed During Hostage Standoff in Los Angeles https://t.co/5vcgKGA2Um https://t.co/dl2adLSu6F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When ISIS’ Call to Arms Falls on the Ears of the Mentally Ill https://t.co/powKzznGxH https://t.co/bUksPJ7Uvu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Stand Your Ground’ Cited by Florida Sheriff Who Declined to Arrest Suspect in Killing https://t.co/SdsO0GICnx https://t.co/3cEQhoARR9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[California Today: L.A.’s Plan to Harness Hoover Dam’s Energy Reserves https://t.co/5QwmjcmcWU https://t.co/2O4fnJrJSN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Demi Lovato Is Said to Be Hospitalized for Drug Overdose https://t.co/O6rnSEEmUh https://t.co/ISNve2ErQR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Greed Came Over Me’: $8 Million in Rarities Stolen From Pittsburgh Library https://t.co/jpHl1IaPun https://t.co/AUcbeXKHxK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nia Wilson Had Big Plans. Then She Was Killed in a BART Station. https://t.co/OUBUL4IwWA https://t.co/DIsE4gqq7a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DeVos Proposes to Curtail Debt Relief for Defrauded Students https://t.co/keHd2K0G6d https://t.co/LF2SbENcG1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Michael Cohen’s Audio Clip Unraveled Trump’s False Statements https://t.co/vXNptoOvDE https://t.co/M2CRKO8ngg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Murdoch and Iger to Skip Fox and Disney Shareholder Votes https://t.co/eVAmBIs7UY https://t.co/Qc6WsZBVsE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Swede Blocks Afghan Man’s Deportation by Refusing to Sit Down on Flight https://t.co/HNG4WnK47g https://t.co/dcjP9iFyN5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vandal Shatters Trump’s Star on Hollywood Walk of Fame https://t.co/FLAD9SFso6 https://t.co/7NeIJuv8fJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China Said to Quickly Pull Approval for New Facebook Venture https://t.co/hwiU5aNbCp https://t.co/duxdXF9mBM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Big Business of Being Gwyneth Paltrow https://t.co/UXedNo4HT1 https://t.co/htWIgQkXeL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Doubles Down on Russia. The Spies Shake Their Heads in Disbelief. https://t.co/FMva4x4w3u https://t.co/WQMmZZxwnG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Missouri Duck Boat Accident Kills 17, Including 9 From Same Family https://t.co/6VQrNnYEbo https://t.co/kSAI0kPMXj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump’s Sense of Timing on Nuclear Threats Confounds Experts https://t.co/q5r9lXjWb8 https://t.co/OLQPjGpwzo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Blasts Fed, China and Europe for Putting U.S. Economy at a Disadvantage https://t.co/04EWPOXFBx https://t.co/3xspAZqiyp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From New York to the Heartland: Ocasio-Cortez Debuts on National Campaign Stage https://t.co/Ke08HyaE9G https://t.co/WTgiFqbOj9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seduced by Hate, Indian Politician Embraces a Lynch Mob https://t.co/wOfRk0HOKr https://t.co/bw9vsKpqGX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Endorsement in Georgia Race Surprised, and Frustrated, Some Republicans https://t.co/izzpE0DL4S https://t.co/kgrxFS7qXb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disney Fires ‘Guardians of the Galaxy’ Director Over Offensive Tweets https://t.co/LoVCcpaQlZ https://t.co/iKCPOL8uRE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Insider Attack in Afghanistan Exposes Risks for Advisers at Center of Trump Strategy https://t.co/MCLYNvxZ5f https://t.co/JOZyMBskya]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glass Bottle Inside a Box Carried Poison, British Victim Says https://t.co/se9x7Dj9o8 https://t.co/mSPgj14fDM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump, Missouri, ‘Mamma Mia’: Your Friday Briefing https://t.co/iJCY4KbVsH https://t.co/DZaPJZbxnk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two Trump Allies, Seeing Unlimited Opportunity, Instead Drew Scrutiny https://t.co/2HekCioqzw https://t.co/XC8nn4KzP5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Officer’s Bullet Killed Trader Joe’s Employee in Los Angeles Standoff, Police Say https://t.co/xXUVPECL5Y https://t.co/3se1dShXvt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michael Cohen Secretly Taped Trump Discussing Payment to Playboy Model https://t.co/TqVQIhpHs0 https://t.co/rY1VEUDoUi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police May Seek Hate-Crime Charge in Attack on Latino Mayor https://t.co/bvKlckFaB7 https://t.co/3qscvC8qNw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Farmers to Receive Up to $12 Billion to Ease Pain From Trump’s Trade War https://t.co/jkBbWrQnbt https://t.co/Bo8ISVQLqH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DealBook Briefing: A Favorite Trump Bank Questioned Over Kushner Credit https://t.co/xbAzwqunZI https://t.co/zZg0BRqmp7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bill Shine, Trump’s Top Communicator, Was Questioned by Federal Prosecutors https://t.co/R5WEHS4JRP https://t.co/mzGhm11YJ5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As Migrant Families Reunite, Texas Border Cities Scramble to Help https://t.co/q0ge4gpjp5 https://t.co/RckOHfyKgz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dolphins Policy Says Players Could Be Suspended for Anthem Protests https://t.co/MOldjABdOX https://t.co/jIMgZiqU6D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump’s All-Caps Threat Against Iran: Loud but Hardly Clear https://t.co/JwFD3lE3y3 https://t.co/CQaKRGhLD0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fatal BART Stabbing Is Third Killing in Bay Area Transit System in a Week https://t.co/uV44TMYWIy https://t.co/JwfyfK6ZSa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the Start, Trump Has Muddied a Clear Message: Putin Interfered https://t.co/USCs5cLjsj https://t.co/mlTvfIhEAo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who Heard What Trump Said to Putin? Only One Other American https://t.co/UTP78Cyz60 https://t.co/rQ5hp3IGdG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tabloid Company, Aiding Trump Campaign, May Have Crossed Line Into Politics https://t.co/JAvQQSC5m3 https://t.co/smL2gWomHq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kimberly Guilfoyle, Co-Host of ‘The Five,’ Is Leaving Fox News https://t.co/k3kAmJL4bn https://t.co/qWaECZmc0e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amid Worker Shortage, Trump Signs Job Training Order https://t.co/hwfB1W1yOw https://t.co/UOJR8IFXRi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House Withdraws Appeals Court Nominee Who Deplored Multiculturalism https://t.co/4xMuudU5VL https://t.co/06BpU4o6C0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[American Accused of Being ISIS Fighter in Syria Faces Prosecution in U.S. https://t.co/is9goIB8uc https://t.co/6bG81m8jAG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iran, Toronto, Subway: Your Monday Evening Briefing https://t.co/09zg9WauUt https://t.co/JMit1OnABI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Weighs Stripping Security Clearances From Officials Who Criticized Him https://t.co/5wNAiyd5sk https://t.co/CIVPkyBNui]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brooklyn Man Convicted in Slaying of Cuomo Aide in 2015 https://t.co/L7fe5z0VEz https://t.co/yHRQk0khUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police Move to Discipline Officer Involved in Eric Garner’s Death https://t.co/OKG1MXKPRA https://t.co/JQd9sZGAZy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How 2 Media Moguls’ Once-Warm Friendship Turned Frigid https://t.co/EhKx7ktzjV https://t.co/VwpxZzZo6m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Comcast Pulls Offer for Fox Assets, Ending Bidding War With Disney https://t.co/y1rSz64gpP https://t.co/OTfLmIg3EM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dirk Nowitzki Will Return for the Dallas Mavericks https://t.co/950x6877nJ https://t.co/O1zPPEzuGT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How a Small Bank Became a Go-To Lender to the Trump Family https://t.co/Ze1P5Xdy4i https://t.co/yMltb83Ph8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Carmelo Anthony Set to Sign With Rockets https://t.co/noVFR6Efw6 https://t.co/wAP8AIyRNw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New York Is Said to Open Tax Inquiry Into Trump Foundation https://t.co/RbPEDfC1fR https://t.co/S3sxhFWDBw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One Dead and 13 Injured in Toronto Shooting, Police Say https://t.co/UYKt0J7msZ https://t.co/lZlzaavJW9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maria Butina, Suspected Secret Agent, Used Sex in Covert Plan, Prosecutors Say https://t.co/Dleva8dOLf https://t.co/obAZW8YsOJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[12 Men Indicted in Machete Killing of Bronx Teenager https://t.co/aLF7guQLzt https://t.co/xPRMdLFRYz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suspect in Houston Crime Spree Is Charged With Capital Murder https://t.co/yyKmXgrira https://t.co/aTiCSVJ8B7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As ISIS Fighters Fill Prisons in Syria, Their Home Nations Look Away https://t.co/WhuurUofSl https://t.co/3YySWdOZ5X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Annabelle Neilson, Muse of Alexander McQueen, Dies at 49 https://t.co/q8Eri4Zpgn https://t.co/F4IhslLyZb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How WhatsApp Leads Mobs to Murder in India https://t.co/qVyyQa3Nxg https://t.co/4aY0x5CbNM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inside the Trinitarios: How a Gang Feud Led to the Death of a Teenager https://t.co/E5RovUgTyX https://t.co/d7tZybDuT1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Administration Considers Unprecedented Curbs on Asylum for Migrants https://t.co/1Y3C625auX https://t.co/Bb3IQmPZjY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Besieged Trump Says He Misspoke on Russian Election Meddling https://t.co/ihnpFkV5AG https://t.co/TTftZcyfDH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Killings of 4 Teens, Within 6 Miles of Each Other, Shake Brooklyn https://t.co/IYBl5wvdII https://t.co/Z2zprB2nqH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘An Entire Community Got Together to Rape a Child’: India Recoils at Girl’s Assault https://t.co/MRn3ITwh2T https://t.co/ylWMKAKUZh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dozens of Hostages Freed From Trader Joe’s in Los Angeles; 1 Woman Is Dead https://t.co/5vcgKGA2Um https://t.co/nH2IALxNZc]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>