<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Art enables us to find ourselves and lose ourselves at the same time. - Thomas Merton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think when we read we have to hear with no ears and realistically see with no eyes and doing that does something good to us. - U.L. Harper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you can't change your fate, change your attitude. - Amy Tan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We make a living by what we get, but we make a life by what we give. - Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I cannot give you the formula for success, but I can give you the formula for failure: which is: Try to please everybody. - Herbert B. Swope]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breathe. Let go. And remind yourself that this very moment is the only one you know you have for sure. - Oprah Winfrey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being busy is better than being bored. Bored left a long time ago. Busy is always around for me. - Tabitha Robin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Most Dangerous Things You Can Do With An NFL Player - https://t.co/ytegYCKDEG https://t.co/F5QkgHE6PG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every day Look - Less is Better - https://t.co/lCk7Q3ktH7 https://t.co/N6TGsniUry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Truth is neither ojectivity nor the balanced view; truth is a selfless subjectivity. - Knut Hamsun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is very short, and there's no time for fussing and fighting my friends - John Lennon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always listen to what others has to say, but at last you are the one who should decide. - Santosh Kalwar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any profession of faith…entrusts the mind and heart to a truth that cannot be proven but can be lived. - Luke Timothy Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A somebody was once a nobody who wanted to and did. - John Burroughs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The moment you stop worrying about success is when success will happen. - Glenn Beck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A wise man gets more use from his enemies than a fool from his friends. - Baltasar Gracián]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Movies That Ruined the Book - https://t.co/HYIEx1mggU https://t.co/Am5cIvmEz6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I could but know his heart, everything would become easy. - Jane Austen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In actual life a downward movement may sometimes be made the beginning of an ascent. - Aldous Huxley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lives, like money, are spent. What are you buying with yours? - Roy H. Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is like a taxi. The meter just keeps a-ticking whether you are getting somewhere or just standing still. - Dorling Kindersley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any emotion, if it is sincere, is involuntary. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Self-esteem comes from being able to define the world in your own terms and refusing to abide by the judgments of others. - Oprah Winfrey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we don't change, we don't grow. If we don't grow, we aren't really living. - Anatole France]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What we see depends mainly on what we look for. - John Lubbock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The mind has a thousand eyes, And the heart but one; Yet the light of a whole life dies, When the love is done. - Francis William Bourdillon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An aim in life is the only fortune worth finding. - Robert Louis Stevenson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[None of us come to this earth to gain our worth; we brought it with us. - Sheri L. Dew]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let yourself be silently drawn by the stronger pull of that which you really love. - Mawlana Jalal-al-Din Rumi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never travel faster than your guardian angel can fly. - Mother Teresa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are - your life, and nothing else. - Jean-Paul Sartre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take care of my heart, I've left it with you." (Edward's note to Bella) - Stephenie Meyer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grace is the face that love wears when it meets imperfection. - Joseph R. Cooke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the end, we will remember not the words of our enemies, but the silence of our friends. - Martin Luther King Jr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever since time began, people have recognized their true love by the light in their eyes. - Paulo Coelho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always remember, your focus determines your reality. - George Lucas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When friendships are real, they are not glass threads or frost work, but the solidest things we can know. - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Behind every trial and sorrow that He makes us shoulder, God has a reason. - Khaled Hosseini]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kind words can be short and easy to speak, but their echoes are truly endless. - Mother Teresa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If they gave you a ruled paper, go write the other way. - Alice Sebold]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our most significant opportunities will be found in times of greatest difficulty. - Thomas S. Monson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anything that makes weak - physically, intellectually and spiritually, reject it as poison. - Swami Vivekananda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We loved with a love that was more than love. - Edgar Allan Poe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You were born with wings, why prefer to crawl through life? - Mawlana Jalal-al-Din Rumi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blaze with the fire that is never extinguished. - Luisa Sigea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The past cannot be changed. The future is yet in your power. - Mary Pickford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world is a tragedy to those who feel, but a comedy to those who think. - Horace Walpole]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life without risk is life wasted. - Santosh Kalwar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it easy? Usually not. But you don't forgive people for their benefit. You do it for your benefit. - Andrew Matthews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best way to prepare for life is to begin to live. - Elbert Hubbard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A problem is a chance for you to do your best. - Duke Ellington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future belongs to those who believe in the beauty of their dreams. - Eleanor Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instead of asking WHY you had to do it, how about just thanking Him for safely bringing you THROUGH it. - Cupcake Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is well to be up before daybreak, for such habits contribute to health, wealth, and wisdom. - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7 Cult Movies that Will Make You Laugh - https://t.co/ZWKQRQrlUl https://t.co/8T6zpAimTN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dishes Your Guests Will Love - https://t.co/9QrW6LHN5Y https://t.co/0qKfilcvNr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am always doing that which I can not do, in order that I may learn how to do it. - Pablo Picasso]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The great end of education . . . is to persuade and to inspire the sincere love of virtue. - George Turnbull]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Relationships are like an algebraic equations:what happens on one side affect the other. - Kim Barnes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You change the mind set about the things surrounding you, surely you would change the world. - Mary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lots of people want to ride with you in the limo, but a true friend will take the bus with you when the limo breaks down. - Oprah Winfrey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God's extraordinary work is most often done by ordinary people in the seeming obscurity of a home and family. - Neal A. Maxwell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two persons cannot long be friends if they cannot forgive each other's little failings. - Jean de La Bruyère]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To accomplish great things, we must not only act, but also dream; not only plan, but also believe. - Anatole France]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The highest function of love is that it makes the loved one a unique and irreplaceable being. - Tom Robbins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are a lot of things I wish I would have done, instead of just sitting around and complaining about having a boring life. - Kurt Cobain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love has no uttermost, as the stars have no number and the sea no rest. - Eleanor Farjeon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest accomplishment is not in never falling, but in rising again after you fall. - Vince Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone should always have two books with him, one to read and one to write in. - Robert Louis Stevenson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happiness is a perfume you cannot pour on others without getting a few drops on yourself. - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We make a living by what we get, but we make a life by what we give. - Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why are old lovers able to become friends? Two reasons. They never truly loved each other, or they love each other still. - Whitney Otto]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Action is the antidote to despair. - Joan Baez]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intelligence, Kant reminds, is not so much a result of genius, rather it is a consequence of a determination to use it. - Michael R. LeGault]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every natural love will rise again and live forever in this country: but none will rise again until it has been buried. - C.S. Lewis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My life is a perfect graveyard of buried hopes. - L.M. Montgomery]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arriving at one goal is the starting point to another. - John Dewey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman who surrenders her freedom need not surrender her dignity. - Wally Lamb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It doesn't matter who you are, where you come from. The ability to triumph begins with you - always. - Oprah Winfrey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All thinking men are atheists. - Ernest Hemingway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you don't like something, change it. If you can't change it, change your attitude. Don't complain. - Maya Angelou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pop Stars Who Were Born Rich - https://t.co/yPoU3uqL8J https://t.co/JQ4lM45Kh3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting Pictures from the Past - https://t.co/2JoW3VN4OY https://t.co/QL7c3X5zTT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[May you get more out of life than a cup of tea. - Rebecca St. James]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is the great lesson of 'Beauty and the Beast,' that a thing must be loved before it is lovable. - G.K. Chesterton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the name of God, stop a moment, cease your work, look around you. - Leo Tolstoy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Champions are made from something they have deep inside of them-a desire, a dream, a vison. - Mahatma Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who love deeply never grow old; they may die of old age, but they die young. - Sir Arthur Pinero]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first rule is to keep an untroubled spirit. The second is to look things in the face and know them for what they are. - Marcus Aurelius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flesh and blood needs flesh and blood, and you're the one I need - Johnny Cash]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You educate a man; you educate a man. You educate a woman; you educate a generation. - Brigham Young]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Communication is the skeleton key of life. It opens all doors. - NO AUTHOR GIVEN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is rather like a tin of sardines - we're all of us looking for the key. - Alan Bennett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to keep growing, you have to challenge everything. Even your own thinking and beliefs. - Bill Gould]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happiness is not a matter of intensity but of balance, order, rhythm and harmony. - Orison Swett Marden]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The soul should always stand ajar, ready to welcome the ecstatic experience. - Emily Dickinson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take care of my heart, I've left it with you." (Edward's note to Bella) - Stephenie Meyer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone should always have two books with him, one to read and one to write in. - Robert Louis Stevenson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a great believer in luck and I find the harder I work, the more I have of it. - Thomas Jefferson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you don't like the road you're walking, start paving another one. - Dolly Parton]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>