<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Because who need scientists https://t.co/ORm7nrKEKC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reminder: There are no sanctuary cities in VA, never were, and research shows they have no effect on crime rates. https://t.co/2LppGIfLjE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Con Chávez todo
Sin Chávez nada https://t.co/JLGkKpF4uw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrislhayes @jbouie And the vulgar kind above all others]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @brfreed: The publication I gave two years of my life to is gone because its billionaire owner would rather kill journalism than recogni…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WindingDot: Rude teens are saying “Hey man, what’s happening?” to John Kasich https://t.co/LCVikVFaSU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was involved in some early work on this, but graduated. Hopeful to be following news. GU could set a precedent. https://t.co/msNG1TnGKT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shows how whoever brings up the issue sets the terms for it in the debate, even if it’s a nonissue https://t.co/xoIj4a48SZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GOP party leadership is about ideology, base is about identity https://t.co/v9YaL20s92]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@profmusgrave @YuMingLiou Such a sad decline from Star Trek VI which at least scripted a false flag conspiracy based on actual events from the real Cold War]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hard to see how this would be a good political strategy in Edison, which is 43% Asian https://t.co/wfCLO5k97p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YuMingLiou I swear the 9/11 truthers will someday be the basis for an award winning gritty TV drama a la HoC/Mr. Robot https://t.co/e9EgoNUtYh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Misfits' shelved classic Static Age. Great review by @maggieserota https://t.co/uO5KYgeFHS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good riddance to House of Cards, peddling naïveté about politics as cynical realism https://t.co/EJ5kyXPNuc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @greenhousenyt: The Democrats add 8 muscular, pro-union ideas to their  platform, e.g. scrapping all right-to-work laws @daveweigel http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @m_clem: The President declaring “Islam hates us”—thereby defining 3 million Americans as not being “us”. 
https://t.co/B4aFZMYuGj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Gizmodo @pbump Like to imagine the only mirth in that man’s life was laughing at truthers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@miweintraub83 Maybe if they considered changing their name...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NickMiroff: Brilliant Venezuela humor here: "Load of contraband chicken found in shipment of cocaine" https://t.co/GNxY2nMT1P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jaketapper: WaPo: Historians respond to John F. Kelly’s Civil War remarks: ‘Strange,’ ‘sad,’ ‘wrong’

https://t.co/Ig2kUhitrV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TBF no member of Congress actually reads reports or transcripts, that’s what staff do. Who are not doing their jobs, prob at Ryan’s behest. https://t.co/cJR9aIbbzA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@toddntucker On the upside, this will encourage active participation in model UN clubs in high schools across the country]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helpful survey guide: margin of error doesn't mean what people often think it means https://t.co/wfqDcRMenF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Random digit dialing is the survey industry standard but increasingly eschewed for more accurate voter list sampling https://t.co/DaEhpe8PBU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reminder: “moderate” ≠ centrist; hyperpartisanship perfectly compatible w/ ideological inconsistency, by @EricLevitz https://t.co/W3hQ0mnpTL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They should change all those monuments to read “the war over lack of ability to compromise” https://t.co/qI0rPrKxsy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agree, it’s never too early to incentivize child care over child labor https://t.co/F9SFuGyb2c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caceres was almost certainly killed under orders of DESA https://t.co/2aHFdyefgE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AoDespair: Thread. After which not even a single scorched stone of General Kelly's intellectual facade remains standing. https://t.co/E…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@smotus Also lack of compromise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @aiww: Who will stop Stephen Miller, the man behind America's anti-refugee policy? | Opinion | The Guardian https://t.co/GyvSL9Yg81]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Game theorists are so excited right now https://t.co/dYRsJHXQJX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey sometimes people can surprise you https://t.co/FVpQCC0v2c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @thehill: Labor Dept appeals judge's decision to scrap Obama-era overtime rule https://t.co/13g7qg8yBu https://t.co/sKbpwCd7vP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Years later, wonder what could be Trump’s equivalent legacy to “Nixon at least established OSHA and the EPA.” Probably nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one will not be prosecuted for “collusion,” there is no relevant federal law for that. It will be for perjury and obstruction of justice. https://t.co/tjnFFq0JGC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One person is under federal investigation by a special counsel, the other is not
One person is president of the USA, the other is not https://t.co/GXf80AAwxJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PatrickW: To be clear: Manafort &amp; Gates indictments allege they committed criminal acts in 2016 and 2017. Not years ago. The president…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@realDonaldTrump “While not at all presidential” is implicit in every statement you make, no need to waste your characters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YuMingLiou @monkeycageblog ...rather than people whose sole job it is to have opinions about stuff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YuMingLiou I think the public is better served by writers giving opinions based on their own research or professional expertise like @monkeycageblog...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YuMingLiou Yeah I’m not saying opinion journalism shouldn’t exist but the whole idea of professional pundits is a really weird historical accident]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mmgarrity: While focus is on the Mediterranean a larger mass migration is happening in South America #Venezuela @business https://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...get themselves designated “public intellectual” and everyone else just kind of buys it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m generally confounded by how some people, mostly men with enormous egos but no particular skills or profession other than “writer”...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As far as I know he wrote pretentious essays in which he had opinions about other people’s books.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did he do any groundbreaking research, discover some new species or cure for a disease?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remind me, what exactly did Leon Wieseltier do that earned him this reputation as an intellectual titan?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Polygraphs indicate DTOs trying to infiltrate Border Patrol https://t.co/s7yJzZnLbT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TravelLeisure: Alaska flights delayed by 450-pound seal sunbathing on the runway https://t.co/wFhmGn7ni7 https://t.co/OzlaRntsPc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jbouie It’s also untrue https://t.co/oaiDFJ1XBb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America is already great https://t.co/42sCSuen3E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over 300,000 in US are under TPS protection and may have it taken away https://t.co/vOy8suxscd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NickMiroff: The list is designated classified but two govt sources confirm it’s these 11. All but two are majority-Muslim https://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattyglesias Oddly Penn has been much more keen on promoting Joe Biden, who didn’t go here, as a standard bearer than Trump, who did.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AndrewKirell @SanhoTree Pretty sure he’d say wrong kind of Christian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[United Fruit, Anaconda didn’t get much payoff from the Guatemala, Chile coups they sought https://t.co/F09Md3AcS8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump is lowering cap on refugees by 45%, coincidentally also proportion of refugees in recent years who were Muslim https://t.co/mdmcyRavqo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man. I went to a DODDS but apparently wouldn’t have fared well in military boarding school because I was bad at DDR https://t.co/qiv8nk0rwA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Reaganesque https://t.co/bvzrZXDnqN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unions should follow the jobs but mostly don’t. Five biggest US companies are tech, none unionized. https://t.co/3NIZPtb7DR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Refugees pay more in taxes than they cost taxpayers, but White House suppressed evidence. My op-ed in @GdnUSopinion https://t.co/mdmcyRavqo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lorenc2 Sorry, my mom is Reviewer #2 when it comes to other people’s kids. Too fat, nose too big, is vegetarian, etc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lorenc2 Henceforth I would like all of my journal submissions to be reviewed by my best friends from high school and my mom.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great idea by Rand Paul: peer review by people explicitly chosen to be non-experts, i.e. non-peer review https://t.co/w5IPP0LXmF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SanhoTree: I spoke w/a Montgomery County official at a party. Said they were getting lots of pressure “from above” to find major crime…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clickhole’s got the best coverage of Amazon’s HQ2 https://t.co/MV3YluYF98]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don’t say, WSJ: Toronto pitched “how the country’s health-care system could save Amazon another $600m a year” https://t.co/wmLCiMyW7G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a remarkable coincidence https://t.co/VczpVgP9iv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NickHanauer: The entire Republican agenda appears to depend on voters not understanding the difference between median and mean. https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@maggieserota @kenklippenstein Surely you can make them address you as Maggles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maddow's conspiracy theorizing about Niger isn't helpful. Good background by @texasinafrica https://t.co/yuMpFspctM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good question, and would honestly love to hear the administration's justification 
https://t.co/JYZxIMx8cE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Koreans love squid. You know that famous satellite photo of the peninsula, with the mysterious lights in the ocean? Those are squid boats https://t.co/NvmEKFgR2l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Squid jerky at mom’s house https://t.co/6knS4X9TJR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What did Ted Cruz do to piss him off this time https://t.co/JpMddIpPRG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The poisoning theory suddenly sounds a lot more plausible https://t.co/0E2oMJJyzf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daveweigel Fact that sanctuary cities can be an issue in state where there are none and even though research shows no link with crime is troubling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm quoted in this Washington Times article about the Virginia governor's race &amp; MS-13: “It’s simply fear-mongering" https://t.co/lqhk18yOzs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[University of Chicago Graduate Students Vote to Unionize https://t.co/HOGQnJm40P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nationalparke Whoa whoa whoa let’s not jump to any conclusions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CasMudde: We don’t know anything about #populism but surely we can write something about it, thinks almost every economist these days.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education suffers when donors are convinced by their own solutions and don’t listen to local needs, by @NadiaNavi https://t.co/Ibt1jbVuE1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @grossdm: amazing headline: Chipotle downgraded by Bank of America on new concern: It's paying employees too much
https://t.co/BJhpD1sT8b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @noamscheiber: Highly recommend this @fstockman story on a steelworker whose job went to Mexico &amp; today's Daily episode about it https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Matt_D_Cohen Yes, as evinced by the Real Housewives stuff. Whereas the big money answer is staring at you from Rosslyn and Tyson's: defense contractors.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boo to the NOVA hate https://t.co/oF8VzZFglr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dataandpolitics OJ/White Ford Bronco. Teachers pulled us out of class for that like it was the moon landing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Malta car bomb kills Panama Papers journalist https://t.co/byqOHptRtV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matthewstoller @MattBruenig @JoshuaMound @samanthajcsmith @nashfacer @RoKhanna @MatchewB @SenSanders @DeanBaker13 @PplPolicyProj Being trusted by public isn't same as providing more stable, well paying jobs. Lots of valuable institutions poll low in trust eg newspapers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[n.b. 늙다리 미치광이 can be more prosaically translated as "crazy old man" but KCNA translator went with "dotard" for some reason]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[North Korea knows "dotard" has become a catchword so they're putting it into their propaganda now. This says "death to the dotard Trump" https://t.co/jvahodUYfd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White Supremacist Group Hangs Banner Over American Immigration Lawyer's Association Downtown Office https://t.co/NdAoplhMw9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now everyone can hate higher ed: profs make conservative students more liberal &amp; liberal students more conservative https://t.co/yUC8IE9ub0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ninalakhani: My take on tomorrow's elections: Honduran president makes contentious bid for second term

https://t.co/xcFfnxmpTd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@profmusgrave Yeah but powerpoint]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Passing of an opera great https://t.co/vu1sEkDgou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @hcjewell: there is a great tide of millenials in train stations and airports right now travelling from the only cities where they could…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@YuMingLiou The fraudulent LaCour/Science study is instructive and should have set off alarms because it found what we all want to believe but isn’t true: that you can change people’s minds about deeply held beliefs by appealing to empathy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DuffelBlog: Turkey pardoned by Trump had multiple contacts with Russian officials https://t.co/BVuRltF32Q https://t.co/VDqILXNG1D]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>