<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NutmegMagazine: There's been some lovely words said about #mindthetime this week. 
You can still buy it here &gt;&gt; https://t.co/C9Hw95Pnhq…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving DAVE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Roy_Isserlis: Oh My Fuckin God, I am dying. 
Surely this guy has one Scottish friend who should have told him? https://t.co/9A9wO8kynF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @hiddendoorarts: Quiz Night Sunday May 6 at the fab @ostaracafe in #Leith will be raising cash for our outreach project to involve the l…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving @stefmowords @HeatherParryUK @metpoliceuk yeah stef no one likes a grass]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stefmowords @strongmisgiving @HeatherParryUK it's my fault for telling him his other idea was good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving It's maybe at "having your tweet stolen without credit" levels]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JillianKarger: [bread prison]

JEAN VALJEAN: what you in for

ALADDIN: baguette, you?

JEAN VALJEAN: sourdough

ALADDIN: *whispers* hol…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sure https://t.co/dRkuRkN43J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YES. https://t.co/7CDJOtYIHN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who wants to do fantasy casting for this show? It's screaming Matt Damon as far as I'm concerned. https://t.co/kFuGuK92Jn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SketchesbyBoze: when some kid refers to The Killers as ’classic rock’ https://t.co/hxBRK43lYR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rakelrank: Scotland is smashing the shortlist and longlist for the 2018 Saboteur Awards! Have a read at the nominees below, which inclu…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@David_Mac13 Try on a Thursday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @strongmisgiving: I'm just a poet, standing in front of another poet, asking you to stop explaining it and read your piece.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@David_Mac13 They do have a page for people like you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@David_Mac13 @strongmisgiving May I refer you to @readersdigest ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SabotageReviews @davepoems Dave you look like this has been cropped from a snow patrol publicity photo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving Lunchtime]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rhymewithrankin: Enjoy Hings by @ChrisMcQueer? Did you attend The Ambassador's Reception, hosted by @poetryasfuck &amp; @InterrobangEdin? H…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DenofGeekUS thank you for the strength of feeling in that tweet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving always gets a big laugh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving maybe. the twist is you come out of it but everything's still shite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving how do you feel about starting the show in a cage?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving it won't make *that* much money]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving I will absolutely monetise it if you fall apart in a way that lends itself to absurdist narratives.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @shockproofbeats: If, after living in the UK for half a century, you are deported "back" to Jamaica, HM Govt gives you a helpful little…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @strongmisgiving: This is factually accurate, yes https://t.co/L2qohbdBcZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laurafjones this sound like an ideal time to pitch a book of poetry and prose inspired by Robert Pattinson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@laurafjones might pitch some poetry today then and see if it sneaks through]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving @HarryGiles this is what you're ambassador of]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BowlsTm cheers. think i can make it to the next one too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving well, that in no way slots neatly into a show we've already done]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @michaelwhalley: Sky pay around £11m per Premier League match. If you assume the average game lasts for 94 minutes (1min stoppage time a…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @davepoems: co-directed by @Josherick3 https://t.co/Lu2W7ULHGF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meanwhile, about seven years ago https://t.co/kpDYAb3Ucf
#McInnesBottlingPlant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CAT HQ: anything to report
CAT: they're asleep
CAT HQ: ACTION STATIONS!
CAT: knocks everything off a shelf just to get one hair bobble]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sothernfriedJ: Good to see buckfast now putting fighting instructions on the boxes https://t.co/yzTLBUR4He]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Browtweaten: Captain: *opens treasure chest* Arrgh! It be just a mirror!

First Mate: Look closely, Cap'n

Captain: *studies* The treas…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Extreme At the Drive In voice https://t.co/QUdcbH2ERm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottish_meta I'm a new man]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@scottish_meta I'm the one on the right with the beard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@periwinklewine That's what he does when we're out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@periwinklewine Okay cool can you help me please?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's me in the picture. https://t.co/waeX7w1FLz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@periwinklewine i'm going to build hux a fribo costume]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fifty_GS Neville Southall's.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd listen if, every time there was a factual inaccuracy, someone rang a bell and then explained in detail why this point was also bullshit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This better be part of Chat Shit Get Banged season https://t.co/Gv9DIkmaau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I relate to a lot of this. https://t.co/Tu1eom9ATp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DaftLimmy: Kelvingrove Art Gallery &amp; Museum https://t.co/6HLQqNG1Vj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dashmundo You expect him to remain ice cool and sweat free through that match?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeatherParryUK pioneer hatefic instead then]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeatherParryUK pls write this fanfic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[tbh I reckon he's only doing this so he doesn't have to do his luvvie voice at work https://t.co/RsvF4mjg5b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OneNightStanzas I'm free on Mondays/have previously led a poetry workshop.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @strongmisgiving: We (@poetryasfuck and @InterrobangEdin) have been shortlisted for a @SabotageReviews award for Best Collaboration for…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CTrevien: Nominations are open for this year's #sabawards18! Exciting! Head over to https://t.co/fb4pUW3pDj to vote now.... @SabotageRe…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone genuinely referring to Big Finish bringing back Eighties Cybermen actors as 'innovative and exciting' there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Dashmundo 'do you own any pets' 'nah but there's a dugout on my street']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimultimate the status quo rocked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jimultimate they mean UKIP will be on question time slightly less]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SamSykesSwears: I really don’t think we need a Lord of the Rings TV show. But if it’s a spinoff about this dude solving crimes in Hobbi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Fifty_GS I'm a poet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jntod: Let’s do this https://t.co/kmGGNmZ9Ft]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Mitromann: Sheffield Wed away on Saturday

Time to dig out this classic. https://t.co/A2cSxRxlQI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving @KatieAiles Liar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KatieAiles or you've been @strongmisgiving in disguise all along]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @samsax1: This poem by Ken Chen’s haunted me since I first read it https://t.co/liHOEc806Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @strongmisgiving: [The middle ages]
me: can I have coca cola?
waiter: is pepys ok?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @heyheymaimai: Workload management with Czeslaw Milosz https://t.co/8fiSXfWUyH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving @Dashmundo @afrendlypingu @ringo_starrrr the public
the real public
the provisional public]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving https://t.co/MO6Szayu7l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EamoV1: Jonny Greenwood and Thom Yorke while recording their seventh album "In Rainbows" (2007) https://t.co/yq7d0vr7PB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ni- oh. 
Wait.
Shit. https://t.co/wFX53VTMnY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ladyhaja: hi, i’m a little nervous because this is my first slam poetry event...

[leans too far into mic] https://t.co/gW1sCb05KW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it's a bad time to be a russian andy samberg fan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[america and europe have no taste]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving that's all i read of it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thecolleencg tweet the official feed and ask]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thecolleencg no, he is the lovechild of hucknall and that detective no one likes on sherlock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thecolleencg well, they can give gervais money to make stuff, why not something good?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DalePMcMullen 'we heard viewers' complaints, this season is back to the quality of 1-3']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thecolleencg netflix might pick it up i guess?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DalePMcMullen ach, maybe netflix'll pick it up, they seem to have limitless resources]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thecolleencg low viewing figures because americans just want to ruin everything for everyone else]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[it's fine @FOXTV will just do another twenty series of the simpsons until lisa joins the NRA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BOOOOOOOO https://t.co/9dZZpweylU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KirstySF also looks like a guy I know called Mark but he's not as well known]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nixie09 i did think that but - in a rare moment of not going for the niche gag - thought fewer people would get the reference]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving i'll try something from the comics if necessary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[denmark are fronted by jared leto and can therefore fuck off]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@strongmisgiving i hope so]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[a slytherin trying too hard #eurovision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[europe is shit at clapping, i'm glad we're out]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[possibly there is a connection between the two]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[dick and dom had a very boring baby #Eurovision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sweden looks like he was raised in a dark room by Justin Timberlake cds and a vhs of knightrider/thinks he's woke but has sexually harassed at least three people #Eurovision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[cool, dark willow's done eurovision]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this is what a multi doctor story by bidmead would have looked like #Eurovision]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>