<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Do clever men make good husbands? "No, clever men don't become husbands!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Great Book - The Majestic Tree of Life  http://t.co/y78hrpPG7b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Babysitter: a teenager who acts like a Grownup while grownups are acting like teenagers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 7 - No Luck!  http://t.co/Qtcg66INwj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consider the Tuba an Amazing Instrument  http://t.co/2RRn9fMFY7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always laugh heartily at your boss' jokes - he may be giving you a loyalty check.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Politicians should read science fiction, not westerns and detective stories. - Arthur C. Clarke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I mean, we're lost on an island, running from boars and monsters -- freakin' polar bears.  Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never go to a movie in Poland, you'll end up setting behind a Pole.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hire character. Train skill. - Peter Schutz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overview Of Major Children's Shoe Brands  http://t.co/1IvyRPeFuH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is what happens to you when you're busy making other plans - John Lennon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space is the stature of God. - Joseph Joubert]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out Why Technology Is Helpful To Seniors  http://t.co/MacXmynGtQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no black magic to successfully attracting customers via the web.  Rand Fishkin, Founder SEOMoz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no psychiatrist in the world like a puppy licking your face. - Ben Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never realized how boring this game was.  - Homer Simpson while watching baseball while sober]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Small Dogs Can Make Great Pets - Picking the Right Breed  http://t.co/fInNdWdcWC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sorry, Dave. I'm afraid I can't do that. - HAL - 2001: A Space Odyssey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who wish to sing, always find a song. - Swedish Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating history of Baseball Cards!  http://t.co/x520HI5OPF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be successful, the first thing to do is fall in love with your work. - Sister Mary Lauretta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who dares to teach must never cease to learn. - John Cotton Dana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've destroyed my feet completely but I don't care. What do you really need your feet for anyway - Sarah Jessica Parker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's an edge to real rock 'n' roll. It's all that matters. - Neil Young]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why does a girl with the least principle draw the most interest?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't really see science fiction as fiction. I can imagine colonies on Mars and everything. - Sigourney Weaver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The Best of ABBA  http://t.co/p6XjdTc93l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Green Acres is an American sitcom classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/NhjRUId4in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cheap Divorce Lawyers: Avoiding Exorbitant Legal Costs  http://t.co/arWG9iOrLN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go Big, or Go Home - Eliza Dushku]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are so many things you can learn about. But you'll miss the best things if you keep your eyes shut. - Dr. Suess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome tennis t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the tennis lovers in your life!   http://t.co/6WAuCVvMSp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If having a soul means being able to feel love and loyalty and gratitude, then animals are better off than a lot of humans - James Herriot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Players have been bought, sold and exchanged as though they were sheep instead of American citizens. - John Montgomery Ward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think about what a user is going to type. - Matt Cutts - Google]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips for Using Facebook Pages for Your Business  http://t.co/Z1XfCuE8J3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Major Shoe Retailers  http://t.co/J3E6Whk82v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Mike Clifford - A One-Hit Wonder  http://t.co/Q3qQfK8FTl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome biking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the biking lovers in your life!  http://t.co/Bz4z2jIwy1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Put on your red shoes, and dance the blues. - David Bowie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still love her. But she's retarded, too. Guy Ritchie on Madonna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Pet Insurance  http://t.co/99p6tj0Dmi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money, if it does not bring you happiness, will at least help you be miserable in comfort. - Helen Gurley Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Caring for Pet Teeth – Ways to Keep Your Pet’s Teeth Clean  http://t.co/gykEqdbA2l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you go to buy, don't show your silver - Chinese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Bobby Darin    http://t.co/JnC8I91ZZe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome tennis t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the tennis lovers in your life!   http://t.co/6WAuCVvMSp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your culture is your brand.  Tony Hseih CEO, Zappos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read about the interesting history of Garland Texas - http://t.co/3QCpvCkGZe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Neil Young  http://t.co/0iHkMigpEg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You’ve got to give us Americans a lot of credit.  How else could we buy a new car every year?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Planning Beach Camping Tips  http://t.co/cpWOt3V1iv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I prefer the company of peasants because they have not been educated sufficiently to reason incorrectly. - Michel de Montaigne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Search Engine Optimization (SEO) to Drive Traffic to Your Website  http://t.co/PGxLkLG1Ek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flattery, like perfume, should be smelled, not swallowed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every day, in every way, I am getting better and better. - Emilie Coue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 meals a day a roof over my head, two cars, a boat, a power mower and a contented  wife -- why shouldn't I be in debt?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turbochargers are for people who cant build engines. - Keith Duckworth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Billy J. Kramer and the Dakotas  http://t.co/rwjiyfDBeT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Why You Should Consider a Creative Writing Degree  http://t.co/OshrfRktcj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Locate Your Garage Space Before Installation Of Cabinets  http://t.co/6Ac4MFN43m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never look back unless you are planning to go that way. - Henry David Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That which is bitter to endure may be sweet to remember. - Thomas Fuller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The glass is neither half-full nor half-empty: it's twice as big as it needs to be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strikeouts are boring - besides that, they're fascist. Throw some ground balls. More democratic. - Bull Durham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bad habits are like chains that are too light to feel until they are too heavy to carry. - Warren Buffet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gin and Titonic Ice Cube Tray - Add the Titanic To Your Drinks http://t.co/i7gdSmJjG2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may be dumb, but I'm not stupid.  Terry Bradshaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the animals: God has given them the rudiments of thought and joy untroubled - Fyodor Dostoyevsky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Barbara Acklin - The Popular Singer  http://t.co/EGFVZMO1uC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of David Gates  http://t.co/vw4LxoyfHS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Everly Brothers  http://t.co/PNRhG6OyJ7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Experience is not what happens to a man. It is what a man does with what happens to him. - Aldous Huxley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They call him "magician".  He walks down the street and turns into a saloon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boys are Whatever, Shoes are Forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Andy Gibb  http://t.co/JQp03kNAMI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Trade School Programs  http://t.co/4p7o1ds3fR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lacing Up The Facts: A History of Shoes  http://t.co/M7UZ32phmK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatness of a nation and its moral progress can be judged by the way its animals are treated.- Mahatma Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The client is not always right. - Enzo Ferrari]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just as soon as some people get up in the world they immediately start looking down on others. . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any pitcher who throws at a batter and deliberately tries to hit him is a communist. - Alvin Dark]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Ramones  http://t.co/RsMD0swfYQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah Robe You Must Have - Star Wars Master Yoda Bathrobe! http://t.co/NWOP6UdTYg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Pat Benatar  http://t.co/8q0w0y001m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[London Weight Loss Salon sign: "We value the pound."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Youth is when we want to set the world on fire... Middle age is when we hope our children won't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was a science fiction junkie for a long time. - William Hurt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why should society feel responsible only for the education of children, and not for the education of all adults of every age?  - Erich Fromm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of State Farm Insurance  http://t.co/XJBfibJpBo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do you judge me as a musician, John? All I'm interested in is making money. Glenn Miller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The trouble with most people today is that they're too fond of people that agree with them and with food that doesn't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Steely Dan  http://t.co/Gp7Cr67pmU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prometheus is reaching out for the stars with an empty grin on his face. - Arthur Koestler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The eternal silence of these infinite spaces fills me with dread. - Blaise Pascal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A twelve-year-old Ben Linus brought me a chicken salad sandwich. How do you think I'm doing? - Sayid Jarrah, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Barbara Acklin - The Popular Singer  http://t.co/EGFVZMO1uC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever wonder about the history of the coffin?  http://t.co/rVgPG2VTvZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would you say a parachutist is a fall guy?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>