<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn Marketing Secrets for eCommerce Business  http://t.co/JfumtDTe0c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every great batter works on the theory that the pitcher is more afraid of him than he is of the pitcher. - Ty Cobb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One deer to another:  "I wish I had his doe"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to WordTracker SEO Tools http://t.co/orDOm7xYen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, where's the Cannes Film Festival being held this year?  Christina Aguilera]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where there is an open mind, there will always be a frontier. - Charles F. Kettering]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn the Keys to Using LinkedIn for Your Company  http://t.co/e2LwhJ8JoD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Top 10 Burger Chains in the US  http://t.co/SavhOMdJg2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no psychiatrist in the world like a puppy licking your face. - Ben Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The less a man knows --  the more he tells it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boys, baseball is a game where you gotta have fun. You do that by winning. - Dave Bristol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So my degree was in political science, which I think was - the closest I could come to marketing is politics. - Steve Case]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seniors Gain from Social Networking Technology  http://t.co/8bsHUxHVLf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Strategy Consulting Firms to Avoid  http://t.co/RfuHTTfBA2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone can steer the ship when the sea is calm. - Publilius Syrus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My advice if you insist on slimming: Eat as much as you like - just don't swallow it. - Harry Secombe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take care of your body. It's the only place you have to live. - Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is what remains after one has forgotten everything he learned in school. - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She's got double D's! You can't cover those suckers up! Jessica Simpson's Dad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Whispers  http://t.co/jGjKOppBKH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A women with good shoes is never ugly. They are the last touch of elegance. - Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I look at modeling as something I'm doing for black people in general. Naomi Campbell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jin Kwon: Good... to see... you. Sawyer: Well look at that! Somebody's hooked on phonics.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Windows has detected you do not have a keyboard. Press 'F9" to continue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Success is dependent upon the glands - sweat glands. - Zig Ziglar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Bob Dylan -- His Biography    http://t.co/GzZOjcFIP3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame Champions: Confused Much?  http://t.co/LyaA80DaOZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Kool and the Gang  http://t.co/QaCs3OYs5V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time is a friend. Do not kill it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Dave Mason  http://t.co/FTtrPMrKfd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lend your friend $20, if he doesn't pay you back then he's not your friend. Money well spent - Ted Nicolas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I read Shakespeare and the Bible, and I can shoot dice. That's what I call a liberal education. - Tallulah Bankhead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding a way to live a simple life is today's complicated problem!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very "COOL" Titanic Ice Cube mold - http://t.co/aqDbCzLNuj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome disco t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the disco lovers in your life!   http://t.co/sdMafzCA5J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes a man to admit he's wrong but it takes a woman to prove it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dream house is one that cost twice as much as you ever dreamed it would…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome ping pong t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the table tennis lovers in your life!   http://t.co/k8X7VDjy4A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Out the Top Football Teams of the 2011-2012 Season  http://t.co/2KjXdAa1j0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're really getting old when your work is less fun and your fun is more work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Use SEO on Multiple Websites to Drive Traffic in Your Direction  http://t.co/Ou57dttGMn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bring the best of your authentic self to every opportunity.  John Jantsch - Author of Duct Tape Marketing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Ringo Starr  http://t.co/f1licQVn8Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep you can keep your devices charged via solar power - find out here - http://t.co/BzwrNQFGF9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Little Feat  http://t.co/nU30GOSAzm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is A Hedge Fund?  http://t.co/zyyLsi5CkE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest thing in this world is not so much where we stand, as in what direction we are moving. - Oliver Wendall Holmes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you don't do what's best for your body, you're the one who comes up on the short end. - Julius Erving]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because the human history is the history of shoes. The history of places where we ever tread and stand.  - Stebby Julionatan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A university is what a college becomes when the faculty loses interest in students. - John Ciardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space isn't remote at all. It's only an hour's drive away if your car could go straight upwards. - Sir Fred Hoyle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Three Dog Night  http://t.co/Gu1NutdrVv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome darts t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the darts lovers in your life!   http://t.co/ndNkNAie0Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana’s Lyme Journey - Part 5 - Test Results In!  http://t.co/IEpY41VUtX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winners take time to relish their work, knowing that scaling the mountain is what makes the view from the top so exhilarating. Denis Waitley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lassie is an American TV classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/mZex0AryEj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education ... has produced a vast population able to read but unable to distinguish what is worth reading. - G. M. Trevelyan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And in the end, the love we take will be equal to the love we make. - The Beatles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picking Earphones for Fitness Activities  http://t.co/yfmkOfyx2a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Breaking News” Michael Jackson Song Stirs Controversy  http://t.co/5nZp7FssHR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A hamburger by any other name costs a lot more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to http://t.co/JICIyaDraD  http://t.co/66c5Rjhipl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Leif Garrett  http://t.co/e1yveaE76X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Heart  http://t.co/ndpTlr8bTA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Pink Floyd  http://t.co/P1XjEq3m9Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's rough to go through life with your contents looking as if they settled during shipping. - Milton Berle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Alice Cooper  http://t.co/HiHL1r58i7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fancy that extraterrestrial life is by def of a higher order than our own is one that soothes all children, and many writers. - J Didion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Donovan  http://t.co/cYqH2c5U6I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An extravagance is anything you buy that is of no earthly use to your wife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 11 - Waiting  http://t.co/5Qi24oCAlv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Cool History of Science Fiction  http://t.co/TdVprsUkmN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good pitching will beat good hitting any time, and vice versa. - Bob Veale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Love Unlimited  http://t.co/Ckz9C5pgRr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is easy for me to go play a rock show, I have been doing that all my life and I love that. - Sebastian Bach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it time to go home yet? I keep clicking these damn shoes, but nothing happens. - Robin Hecht]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It isn't necessary to blow out the other person's light in order for yours to shine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to David Bowie  http://t.co/C465ssmQyg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating - the Space Elevator - can they build it?  http://t.co/GvZHybf5I6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Journey  http://t.co/rxsQ4TqIY5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome tennis t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the tennis lovers in your life!   http://t.co/KLs7t12BOV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never threw an illegal pitch. The trouble is, once in a while I toss one that ain't never been seen by this generation. - Satchel Paige]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada - Learn About Best Places to Tour  http://t.co/rSYrfgTxqk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love cats because I enjoy my home; and little by little, they become its visible soul. - Jean Cocteau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Europe – Best Places to Tour  http://t.co/CWJJQScAfP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interested in Solar Power?  Find out about all the different ways to pay for adding solar to your home - http://t.co/Qc9vNAzY6A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've met many thinkers and many cats, but the wisdom of cats is infinitely superior. - Hippolyte Taine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome - An Easy Toilet Seat Lifter - keep the girls happy :&gt;) http://t.co/Lo1qtQbrBN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You call the driver of a car a motorist, until he comes just little too close.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Left Banke  http://t.co/jFXkopUbYE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A college is a place where pebbles are polished and diamonds dimmed. - Robert Ingersoll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is like a sixth sense - and you can't make use of the other five without it. - William Somerset Maugham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Confucius say it is better to be looked over than overlooked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Planning Beach Camping Tips  http://t.co/j32f1aBtVZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating History of ESPN  http://t.co/w3p3JgAkQK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one can make you feel inferior without your permission. - Eleanor Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the hot new Minecraft Youtube channel Crimson Mine - https://t.co/4VxuPHy0yL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any trip is short when you're in good company]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Brady Bunch is an American sitcom classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/ek0w2Bh8vm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The studios have been taken over by marketing people and accountants. - Joe Eszterhas]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>