<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BBCAfrica: As Melania Trump arrives in Africa for her big solo tour, we asked locals of the countries she plans to visit what they make…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“The top leadership of the Somali region of Ethiopia acted like hooligans for a long period of time: you had mafia-style leaders who were killing their own people” https://t.co/rc3BTzK5ey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mary_harper: 48-hour curfew imposed in anglophone #Cameroon. Movement severely restricted. Bars, night-clubs and liquor stores closed.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let’s be clear: these are not economic sanctions. They are arms sanctions and restrictions on some leaders. No impact on ordinary Eritreans https://t.co/7wZVT61uyU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life returning to Eritrean ports as Ethiopian trade resumes https://t.co/Lo9dy6Oegk https://t.co/ULKhYitmDi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Report on life returning to Eritrea's ports as Ethiopian traders and shipping begin to use them again
https://t.co/kpaNfvdWbA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Urgent appeal on behalf of refugees trapped in Libya https://t.co/7GLjTquwpV https://t.co/9CvFKrbGfh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A forensic analysis of the ‘rescue’ at sea of refugees – in which 20 die https://t.co/2wYQFSauFF https://t.co/biZQqinifE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#PeoplesVote Our Camden for Europe campaign gets a big boost as people going to Sainsbury's flock to oppose Brexit and back a People's Vote! https://t.co/UZzUlwBL2A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Out today campaigning for a People's Vote outside Sainsbury's Camden Town, in central London. https://t.co/m723NytI4G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jailed in Eritrea at 15 she dreamed of being a fashion designer. No trial and six years later, she's still missing @CNNI https://t.co/iVrnR2hP7a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is this the price of ANC failure? https://t.co/QMR3TsAdhy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How China uses Djibouti’s debt to control it.  Worrying for many other African governments in debt to Beijing  https://t.co/EwZ0BMMVmX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @helenzille: We will soon be below 40 train sets in the Cape Town. We require 88 train sets to run our basic service.  Someone somewhere…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eritrea lays out approach to peace in the Horn https://t.co/qrUno3TB5W https://t.co/3jQUipELWJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pdanahar: So it looks like Brett Kavanaugh will clear the Judiciary committee hurdle. https://t.co/trLrSfhsXN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @woudena: CEO of @Unilever should read this emotional letter from #Kenya tea workers raped and attacked on company plantation. A clear f…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @woudena: The massive challenge facing Cyril Ramaphosa in turning around #SouthAfrica https://t.co/5782G4RVM0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @woudena: #Congo state #gold mining company warns Randgold about the transfer of Kibali mine in northern #DRC to Barrick. Perhaps hoping…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An assessment of Eritrea https://t.co/d4aUqP9BPj https://t.co/jUrUfP0hmg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The South African miners buried in un-marked graves https://t.co/gJffbede3m https://t.co/M44e6UUSes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheEconomist: In Ethiopia, child marriage has dropped by a third in the past decade, the world's sharpest decline https://t.co/cx4fIyfN…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Selkid: Issias Afworki of Eritrea today gave an interview for the first time since a 'peace deal' with  Ethiopia was struck some five m…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Selkid: The border issue that was an answer to every concern raised over the last 20 years was a means to an end then and it is a means…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ChukaUmunna: WATCH: Voters in every seat held by @UKLabour support a #PeoplesVote on the Brexit deal, according to a large-scale new po…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TomGardner18: Another day another illegal arms intercept ... alarming trend https://t.co/HQgNJlfOB7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Majority in all Labour seats back second referendum, study says | Politics | The Guardian https://t.co/k6UD0y99QJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BillFrelick: “I see no threat requiring this kind of deployment,” said retired Gen. Colin Powell, former chairman of the Joint Chiefs o…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nigerian army posts Trump video to justify shooting protesters https://t.co/V4qKhyaewA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ethiopia: Climbing Mount Uncertainty https://t.co/UKc2XKeAuM https://t.co/tsBvP2LMng]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After Eritrea thaw, Tigray’s southern border with Amhara heats up https://t.co/ZM25qmz940]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Selkid: UN to lift sanctions on Eritrea after US shift https://t.co/9A6vzsWFHH via @FRANCE24]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The head of the European Union delegation in Tanzania Roeland van der Geer has been “recalled to Brussels for consultations” says EU. No further details yet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[African Union Human Rights Commission takes up case of arrested Eritrean former minister https://t.co/bVuAaeJXRP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Catholic priest to President Isaias – respect the people, introduce the rule of law https://t.co/RC47qh1n3F https://t.co/pahlqhAFCn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's hope President Isaias will finally give the Eritrean people some insight into how the Eritrea-Ethiopia relationship will work. At the moment they are completely in the dark. https://t.co/jb79Bp16dN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inaccurate: Keir Starmer tweeted: “These are serious allegations and it’s important that the National Crime Agency is allowed to investigate this matter in full.” https://t.co/pBfAtARgdG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TomGardner18: The return of re-education camps shows what hasn't (as well as what has) changed in Abiy Ahmed's Ethiopia. My latest for…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South Africa corruption: Ramaphosa says 'dark period' ending https://t.co/kulBhzFies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @geoffreyyork: Almost five years after the brutal strangling of Rwandan dissident Patrick Karegeya in room 905 of the luxury Michelangel…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ReutersAfrica: South Africa's finmin Mboweni says state airline should be closed down https://t.co/X99gdlV43F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @geoffreyyork: After nearly 5 years of official silence, South Africa has finally called an inquest into the 2013 strangling death of Pa…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ethiopian poor planning of Djibouti railway “cost Chinese bank $1 billion” https://t.co/PDgyye81AL https://t.co/HPIvjwuzp8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the University of Cape Town continues to censor art
 https://t.co/815wKGfTTG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WillKnocker Indeed!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sheila Keetharuth did a remarkable job in extremely testing circumstances. https://t.co/VY5j7qlCHh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Al-Shabab's former No. 2 leader, Robow, runs for office in Somalia https://t.co/0mvboFXRcV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Prince of Wales and The Duchess of Cornwall will visit The Gambia, Ghana and Nigeria. How about South Africa? https://t.co/kztdb7tzwS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LukePatey: The smiles from China's high level Africa summit are fading now. 
China places blame on 'Ethiopia’s planning capabilities' f…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the SS Mendi's bell was bell returned to South Africa after being handed to a BBC reporter
 https://t.co/f8Ow94va0v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Eritrean maintains control over its exiles https://t.co/EE5a9xO1qc https://t.co/owQyfHEpmJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US missionary Charles Wesco shot dead in Cameroon in cross-fire between the security forces and separatist fighters https://t.co/blNPLBd2vJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South Africa in World War One: how race divided and united the nation
 https://t.co/bMjF7YKdK0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @willintune: A committee to find and arrest homosexuals has been set up in Tanzania by the Regional Commissioner of Dar Es Salaam, Paul…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eritrea: Abune Lukas explains why Patriarch Antonius was arrested https://t.co/Blg8Be2Z06 https://t.co/j9ipBDt38j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How China and the Soviet Union supplied weapons to apartheid South Africa https://t.co/xBifmrULza https://t.co/ICMqUXlxpV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a fantastic response! https://t.co/IAxgFbP29u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @bobeabobea: Ethiopia To Offer Visa On Arrival To AU Members Starting November https://t.co/y55eizNiVT via @kenyanwalstreet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South Africa state broadcaster could axe a third of jobs https://t.co/XBX3lJi5sc via @BBCNews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ethiopian government soldiers clash with OLF militia =&gt; https://t.co/FqQSeOq9jb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @markc_anderson: #Uganda suspends its commissioner for refugees Apollo Kazungu after an investigation found that his office falsely infl…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greenpeace declares South Africa the World's worst pollution hotspot: its coal fired power stations  https://t.co/7GCIrLcCql]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apartheid, guns and money: book lifts the lid on Cold War secrets https://t.co/5fDIJdpowR via @TC_Africa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uganda: UN finds “ghost” refugees  https://t.co/iQMoScPuTM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EthiopiaInsight: In-depth report: 

Rallies supporting  OLF and rejecting rumored plans to disarm it have taken place across western Or…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The London vigil for the victims of the Pittsburgh synagogue massacre. So full this is part of the overflow room. Jews, Christians and Muslims are here https://t.co/WDSnJfYFZD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An attack helicopter with a “peacekeeping” mission. Interesting https://t.co/od71BPkwqS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EconomistRadio: It's taken 20 years for Ethiopia and Eritrea to make peace. What happens now? @TomGardner18 is in Ethiopia speaking to…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Woman blows herself up' in Tunis https://t.co/29DWSzJy0t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eritrea and Sudan to mend fences? https://t.co/KL1iEizHsT https://t.co/RQDZf9STcg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ZimMediaReview: CIO at State House harassing journalist @violetgonda as she interviewes officials after Mnangagwa meeting with business…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Africa’s democracy under seige on social media https://t.co/PSTftFserX https://t.co/Ao6DJ6sFTi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[African Job Creation Lags Developmental Gains, Study Finds https://t.co/5F1tvghqxo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MikeDwyerMike: Terror in focus: the photographer who captured the rise of Nazism https://t.co/XH23cJJPHH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BBCAfrica: "I will not stand and watch this ****. There's no slavery anymore. We're not animals."

Foreign maids in the Middle East are…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BBGAfrica: #Somaliland offers #Ethiopia a pipeline alternative - competing with #Djibouti
https://t.co/umglP1dPgH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mnangagwa has already shown himself incapable of jettisoning the state centrist, rent-seeking predilections of his predecessor. Zimbabwe trapped in crony capitalism https://t.co/TEnqJQ3tkF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s not defying voters, MPs, to try to make them think again on Brexit  | Nick Cohen https://t.co/u0oLaLbQFe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MweneGahaya Governments are elected. Regimes are not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Germany infuriates Eritrean regime by accusing it of “major human rights violations” https://t.co/LjDyXTk6ud https://t.co/de7P0a9tEV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the apartheid regime burnt books -- in their tens of thousands. But the rantings of North Korea's Kim Il-sung were not destroyed - piles of his work were freely available at Wits University. Neither students nor police understood them
 https://t.co/KOoGeCn4rZ via @TC_Africa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Revealed: ANC’s R2m VBS loot  https://t.co/okIwP9PnDR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pittsburgh shooting: At least 8 killed in anti Semitic attack https://t.co/FOu9UR6ZHJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Security Council Committee on Somalia and Eritrea Considers Final Reports of Its Monitoring Group | Meetings Coverage and Press Releases https://t.co/rWdYhcaUAS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GiuliaRastajuly: @MSF_Sea @MSF @IOM_Libya @ICRC_lby @UNHCRLibya ~230 Eritreans(56 minors)in Alfurgi Sebha in Tripoli desperately need f…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A large Camden contingent out campaigning in Sittingbourne in Kent! Sunny and a warm reception! https://t.co/QErEKcjePV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @saayounis: Even #SouthSudan is freeing political detainees. 

#Eritrea? “We need more time.”  Time to cook up another distaster we can…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sheila Keetharuth – special rapporteur – presents her Human Rights report on Eritrea to UN https://t.co/dD8uICcTlb https://t.co/LdZ9aSx7gK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sheila Keetharuth – special rapporteur – presents her Human Rights on Eritrea to UN https://t.co/D81ryZoi88 https://t.co/HrMk4WU5q9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh yes you are! https://t.co/tZSguSYx8T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Smith_JeffreyT: In #Cameroon, Paul Biya is just one of a number of regional leaders -- including Museveni and Nkurunziza -- who have fo…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GvanOnselen: Things Helen Zille has been called by ANC/alliance members, all without repercussion: a “witch”, a “monkey”, a “cockroach”…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tax on drinks to raise funds for HIV treatment in Uganda https://t.co/6fGAsP0lnr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The smear of “apartheid apologist” https://t.co/rD2Te2a7dC https://t.co/ahAMQe7yD4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Can Eritreans drowned in the Mediterranean not be buried back home?” – Father Mussie Zerai https://t.co/5un6jYMmQc https://t.co/VZBAV19495]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Libya Update on the 300 Eritrean refugees in Qaser Bin Ghashir and Alfarghi Sebha https://t.co/YouPJaVi4O https://t.co/yIDboEzx4n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GTemare @TomGardner18 @wdavison10 It depends on the circumstances. Essentially it is the decision of the Prime Minister and her cabinet.  She would consult the Queen but only as a courtesy. Any decision would have to be endorsed by Parliament.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @woudena: A crucial win for victims standing up against corporate crimes. Perhaps the Alien Tort Claims Act still has some life left in…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why big money and big data can’t prevent famines https://t.co/fYcCgrjeaS https://t.co/o3GzQTUd7e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the campaign against Rhodes at UCT led to the death of one of South Africa’s greatest young academics: Prof Bongani Mayosi. https://t.co/tWqvhyLk3g]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>