<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[java dveloper: java dveloper Ref No.: 18-26771 Location: chicago, Illinois Hi, Hope you are doing great!! We are currently looking to fill urgent full-time permanent job positions as Java Developer with the client based in multiple locations . Please let… https://t.co/wXFpwdvX1f https://t.co/HGTX1rGGb5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jr. Java Developer: Jr. Java Developer Ref No.:18-11065 Location: Milford, Ohio Position Type:Direct Placement Start Date: 06/21/2018 Jr. Java Developer/Entry Level Software Engineer Must have a Bachelors Degree Diverse Lynx LLC is an Equal Employment… https://t.co/XjsJ7lAgsn https://t.co/eTvZ78vLs0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior IT Security Engineer: Senior IT Security Engineer Ref No.:18-00289 Category: ************* Location: Rockville, Maryland Position Type:Contingent Experience Level: 7 Years Start Date: 06/28/2018 Job Req -Additional Info Shift Work?:No Work… https://t.co/88LThdD0n1 https://t.co/9W8RoPyffm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tech Leader / Technical Project Manager, Automotive: Project Description Luxoft is searching Product Owner to join innovative project in Automotive domain. Currently Luxoft is gathering a new team, which will create new generation of virtualized testing… https://t.co/vOUTW6bHYc https://t.co/INq3HF1QGE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[API Developer: API Developer Ref No.:18-11969 Location: Loveland, Colorado Start Date: 07/09/2018 Responsibilities – Works closely with end-users to identify and capture business requirements – Develops composable services and API’s to support front-end… https://t.co/OgwesbMBi8 https://t.co/2dqJlJgwWL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Full Stack Developer: Java Full Stack Developer Ref No.:18-10406 Location: Buffalo Grove, IL Position Type:Contract Start Date: 06/11/2018 Position: Java Full Stack Developer Location: Buffalo Grove, IL Type: Contract Roles and Description: ‘ – Web… https://t.co/z6dxm9cMkw https://t.co/E4TlSRUyIB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. System/Software Developer: ***Only applicants with a Top Secret (TS) Clearance need apply*** General Dynamics Information Technology (GDIT), a leading provider of systems engineering, integration, IT service operations and support solutions, is… https://t.co/SqDoR6q5mo https://t.co/3M0ukSiSxg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Analyst: Job Title Business Systems Analyst Requisition # PCC-US.****** Job Type Full-time Shift Type Location TIMET – Toronto – Toronto, OH 43964 US (Primary) Job Description Summary Develop interactive tools that convert enterprise… https://t.co/YxiwDSqPKp https://t.co/2BFSxAPr4l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Project Analyst/Engineer: Laboratory Corporation of America Holdings (NYSE:LH), an S &amp; P 500 company is a leading life sciences company, providing comprehensive clinical laboratory and end-to-end drug development services. With a mission to improve… https://t.co/pzXhxP7xIw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Senior Software Engineer: As an Associate Senior Software Engineer, you will write and configure code for new and upgraded solutions in accordance with technical specifications. You will make enhancements to existing software with minimal… https://t.co/vR360ozaml https://t.co/1UM8i7CQRS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETL Software Engineer: ETL Software Engineer Jobs in Annapolis Junction at Boeing–&gt;’,’identifier’:’4204′,’title’:’ETL Software… https://t.co/GoMkuJyKNq https://t.co/c5eyddP4Jv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Informatica Developer: Informatica Developer Minneapolis, Minnesota – United States Job Start Date – 06/21/18, Posted Date – 06/21/18 Primary SkillsinformaticaTax TermsC2COverview Informatica Developer Location: Minneapolis, MN Duration: 6 month contract… https://t.co/ktW42SQvBJ https://t.co/BYaBk8QzT7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Manager, IT – Enterprise Service Bus: At CoBank, our Sr. Manager of Information Technology directs the development and implementation of the CoBank’s service-oriented architecture and Enterprise Service Bus (ESB) platform. This includes management… https://t.co/RriJIx8cQa https://t.co/0Pea4fIMVf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director, Risk Product Management – Consumer Experience: Director, Risk Product Management – Consumer Experience A Great Place to Work Last year, we transformed the P2P payments industry with Zelle. 247-million transactions and $75-billion later,… https://t.co/VNaVk0Ylxc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Administrator: Requisition ID 2018-41789 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Top Secret/SCI Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description Posting title: Network Administrator SUMMARY: Applicant will provide… https://t.co/qBSdzzoeQf https://t.co/SEbFIg2Pb3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MongoDB DBA: MongoDB DBA Ref No.: 18-28695 Location: Philadelphia, Pennsylvania 5+ Years of MongoDB Database Experience in a Linux Environment – MongoDB – CRUD Operations, Document based Data Modeling, Design of Collections and Documents Experience with… https://t.co/BpFHdtbRcF https://t.co/9tf464OKYg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Manager, Enterprise Technical Support: Job ID 2018-3694 Location US-CA-San Jose Category Service &amp; Support About the Job Job Description: 8×8 Inc. is looking for a Sr. Manager, Enterprise Technical Support to join our dynamic team. The ideal… https://t.co/2bXHBGSFHS https://t.co/v39da9gj9r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[R&amp;D Engineer IC Design 3: Broadcom Corporation has an opening in Irvine, CA for R&amp;D Engineer IC Design 3 (IRYHW) for definition, design, verification, &amp;docu-mentation for ASIC Development. Ref job code &amp;mail resume to: Broadcom Corporation, Attn: HR… https://t.co/ZfkM7zvg4A https://t.co/RbZ6lODZbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Developer: For BNY Mellon Lead Developer job – Asset Servicing – Wellesley, Massachusetts Skip to Main Content – – – – Toggle navigation – Who We Are – What We Do – Who We Serve – Our Thinking – Client Access – Careers – Investor Relations – News –… https://t.co/tW5A7LWwA4 https://t.co/O082632ihh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator Virtual and Remote Access Services TS/SCI with Polygraph: – Maintains network security and ensures compliance with security policies and procedures – Evaluates hardware and software, including peripheral, output, and related… https://t.co/YLdtDJG9lb https://t.co/UisaRRobsw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Looking for your next challenge? MicroD is seeking an expert Software Engineer with a true passion for changing the world with their contributions. Do you have strong software development experience? Do you desire to be a part of a… https://t.co/ctyJU6CqO2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Manager: *Ideal candidate will be located in or near Cincinnati or Toledo, OH metro area* Why naviHealth? naviHealth is the result of over a decade of dedicated visionary leaders and innovative organizations challenging the status quo for PAC… https://t.co/kiDnevcjmL https://t.co/agkIJro0jL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Specialist Project Manager 3rd party Governance, Tech Knowledge: Job Description Specialist Project Manager – 3rd party Governance, Tech Knowledge As a Third Party Governance engagement manager, you are responsible for the oversight of bank’s governance… https://t.co/kyaB7sD9Lw https://t.co/mRJcw3xz5y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GIS Analyst: GIS Analyst Full time position in our Glenwood Springs Headquarters assists with maintenance of ESRI GIS database and provides data drawings and assistance to aid in the planning, design, analysis, installation and maintenance of HCE’s… https://t.co/RLTq9Q6ZY8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fellows, Software Engineer: Discretionary Business Title Job Title Fellows, Software Engineer Location WESTMINSTER, CO – Westminster, CO 80021 US (Primary) Security Clearance None Relocation Offered No Job Type Internship Category Engineering Education… https://t.co/1197Zs5Gfz https://t.co/QhkyqgldGf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Job Description ******** JOB SUMMARY Thank you for your interest in CBRE. This position is being published in an effort to build our candidate pipeline for our upcoming opportunities. If an opportunity opens that matches your… https://t.co/3jnK433UiG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pega Decisioning Architect: Job Description What you’ll be doing. The Pega Business Decisioning Architect will collaborate with marketing and technology application teams to understand the business requirement, the business processes, and convert the… https://t.co/TripqBX8CJ https://t.co/D34fiLBdFV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: DESCRIPTION: Employer Corporate Information Security Group has an immediate opening for an experienced and motivated Software Developer to join our Cybersecurity Intelligence &amp; Response Center (CSIRC) in Gaithersburg – MD. As a… https://t.co/GZYy1dkMVx https://t.co/8WUIchklLd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager (Water Resources/Drainage): SNC-Lavalin’s Atkins business is one of the world’s most respected design, engineering and project management consultancies. SNC-Lavalin’s Atkins business has been providing infrastructure planning,… https://t.co/ZDHwEY7Trb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer Sr: Req ID : 429049BR Job Code/Title : E1073:Software Engineer Sr Job Description : Software engineer to participate in the design, development, test and maintenance of complex mission application software and database applications.… https://t.co/TnMmoBVyh2 https://t.co/AoNBhRvpzR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Who is Markit Digital We design, develop, and host data rich, full featured, high-traffic web and mobile applications for financial institutions, brokerages, and media clients all over the world. We leverage a combination of… https://t.co/TNEqGhcrzw https://t.co/RfezhA1VIV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Entry Level Software Developer: Company Description . Job Description No Computer Science degree? No problem. We love self-taught developers! LaunchCode offers paid, software developer apprenticeships at one of our employer partners that include… https://t.co/AtMklwT3Wu https://t.co/FOLDwiG0YG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ServiceNow Business Analyst, Senior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: McLean, VA Job Type: Strategy – Planning Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 7/5/2018 Job Description Job Number: R******* ServiceNow Business Analyst, Senior Key Role: Work with… https://t.co/bJkzGlYYA2 https://t.co/SSZs6CDBjL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SENIOR APPLICATION DEVELOPER: Job Description SENIOR APPLICATION DEVELOPERRequisition # 72948Position Basics Working Title SENIOR APPLICATION DEVELOPER, TELEMEDICINE Advertising Ends on: Thursday, June 21st, 2018 Advertising Started on: Thursday, June… https://t.co/6KCMOc3ERx https://t.co/qWzVdxF7vi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[174- Systems Administrator: OVERVIEW The Technical Systems Administrator is responsible to provide systems engineering and administrative support across a wide array of software and hardware systems and components used to deliver production services. The… https://t.co/qBLrqUyNjy https://t.co/vi4Uz8g3ix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Engineer (Jr): POSITION-FULL-STACK ENGINEER (JR/MID) OVERVIEW This work is to support an enterprise scale program in the federal space developing a microservices environment for data enablement. Small teams of 10 or less Agile groups led by a… https://t.co/h7t1FiX46C https://t.co/eoQYKU0zsV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Operations Analyst: Save job Job ID ******* Primary Location Houston, Texas, United States of America Date posted 06/12/2018 Applies intermediate level of subject matter knowledge to solve a variety of common business issues. Works on problems… https://t.co/PWdcrfdAcd https://t.co/9PUxuc9Uju]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Business Analyst: Recruiter Skyworks Location Irvine Irvine United States Salary Competitive Posted 14 Jun 2018 Closes 12 Jul 2018 Job role Accountant Sector Management consultancy Contract type Permanent Hours Full time You need to sign in or create… https://t.co/i5sKAXxCyQ https://t.co/uTyJjMahM0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer in Test: . Please contact ******************** if you need further instruction on how to do that. Software Engineer in Test Engineering | San Francisco, CA | Full Time Job Description Software Engineer in Test About us: With over 14… https://t.co/kI2bo4ixDR https://t.co/2o7s81VGEr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Performance Engineer: The Performance Engineer will support complex architectures by serving as a technical subject matter expert and an advocate for application and system performance. Design, create, and execute performance tests and analyze… https://t.co/zD2brThWBo https://t.co/gCJKAngjTq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Intelligence Developer, Mid-Level: Business Intelligence Developer, Mid-Level – Spalding Consulting, Inc. ************** *************** – Home – About – Solutions – Careers – Contracts – Contact – My Account Job Openings &gt;&gt; Business… https://t.co/Tjql9LIc38 https://t.co/fcCzgavPiE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Manager Solutions Architect Pre Sales Engineering: Job Description What you’ll be doing. You will lead a team of Architects with subject matter expertise in intelligent networking and application enablement, to drive excellence in solutions… https://t.co/mAen1obyrK https://t.co/mw2m22IN2Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MicroStrategy Developer: MicroStrategy Developer Ref No.:18-10261 Location: Charlotte,NC Position Type:Contract Start Date: 06/07/2018 Role :: MicroStrategy Developer Location:: Charlotte,NC /WALTHAM, MA Duration:: W2 Contract only (No C2C ) Role… https://t.co/3AU0x6QBdr https://t.co/HlqjtzNgzb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Systems Safety Engineer II: 113611BR Sr Systems Safety Engineer II MA – Tewksbury 113611BR Whole Life Engineering Directorate (WLED) has an opening for a Software Safety Engineer. The Safety Engineering role will support a large scale, real time,… https://t.co/wPlKBxeoMS https://t.co/GZECgaoQ4p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Delivery Director: Overview Our IT Delivery Director is responsible for the successful and thoughtful delivery of IT projects and IT systems within the assigned business unit, including creating strong relationships with the business leaders to… https://t.co/8RWRgdoglG https://t.co/GfKiHN79dU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jr. Systems Programmer: Jr. Systems Programmer at DELUXE CORPORATION Skip to main content Recruitment Fraud Alert X – Life at Deluxe – Our Recruiters – Recruiting Events Search Keyword Location RadiusRadius5 miles15 miles25 miles35 miles50 milesSearch… https://t.co/zEB5SATOlT https://t.co/QZ2JxpEqa5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Technical Lead: SR Number APPS/APPS/2018/****** Designation Senior Technical Lead Location Iowa Job Family Development (Development) Job Description (Posting). To be responsible for managing technology in projects and providing technical guidance… https://t.co/Diy5ao1f2Z https://t.co/mmdUZMkdb5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Scientific Research Corporation is an advanced information technology engineering company that provides innovative products and services to government and private industry, as well as independent institutions. At the core of our… https://t.co/Rso4Px3VPo https://t.co/vlHmTRt8pJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Software Developer: Job Description What you’ll be doing… – Design, develop, analyze, evaluate, test, debug, document, and implement moderately complex software automation applications and solutions from collected specifications or requirements. –… https://t.co/MIin2BlO8T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Security Operations Specialist, MID (CSOC) #204: Req ID 99058BR Business Title Cyber Security Operations Specialist, MID (CSOC) #204 Group MCIS Location USA VIRGINIA Springfield Clearance Level Needed TS/SCI Category Cyber Job Duties and… https://t.co/9ISPXjRTbw https://t.co/GBqaA424v4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Architect – Tech Lead: To provide expert level IT technical lead services, including the direction, evaluation, selection, configuration, implementation, and integration of new and existing technologies and tools. DUTIES AND RESPONSIBILITIES: *… https://t.co/UVFokjJXhR https://t.co/OYHFPRbpTv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Administrator: Primary Responsibilities: * Primarily focused on maintaining security system standards and mitigating vulnerabilities reported by FS-ISAC and internal/external security penetration tests. * Apply OS patches, hardware firmware… https://t.co/CZi9pVt8Wd https://t.co/r9UypcKLk9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Lead: Technical Lead Photon Infotech, Inc. Dallas, TX Photon Infotech, Inc. has opening for Technical Lead (Develop applications in Java, J2EE, Spring, Selenium and Cucumber. Analyze business requirements &amp; determine technical feasibility of… https://t.co/xsKba9V4pd https://t.co/BxZspc5Ihu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GI/Critical Care Specialty Sales Executive (St. Louis area, also covering Springfield MO): GI/Critical Care Specialty Sales Executive (St. Louis area, also covering Springfield MO) at NESTLE Skip Navigation HomeExplore our Brands – Home – Nestle USA –… https://t.co/ZaF1YBHS44 https://t.co/ZZqLGCL9AO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Data Scientist Prescriptive Analytics: Job Description What you’ll be doing. You’ll be part of a leading-edge advanced analytics team helping us bring the best possible experiences to our customers by helping us to identify what they like, and… https://t.co/CSHLcgwYxD https://t.co/WKEttegiTc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, JAVA, C/C++, Android Development: Req ID : 432499BR Job Code/Title : E1074:Software Engineer Stf Job Description : This dynamic Software Engineer position is responsible for hands-on software engineering, programming, and scientific… https://t.co/fl9th0hD69 https://t.co/hdGaR4Nocq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Embedded Software Engineer: Sr. Embedded Software Engineer Tracking Code ******** Job Description What you’ll be doing: We’ve have been named one of the fastest growing insulin pump companies in the U.S! Why? Tandem has created the simple-to-use… https://t.co/Gi6o5uOcDA https://t.co/K5llirR61M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketing Operations Analyst II: The Loyalty &amp; Analytics Department has an opening for a Marketing Ops Analyst I. This position is located in Pleasanton, CA. Position Purpose The Loyalty &amp; Marketing Analytics Team is a business group at Albertsons, LLC… https://t.co/DeKFpeawTT https://t.co/OuyQfck38z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering Quality Expert: Quality Expert for Ariba, Inc. (Palo Alto, CA) location to work on programs or unit levels or across organizational boundaries with special focus to quality assurance and test related tasks within the product creation process.… https://t.co/5zZxRMTiix https://t.co/K5JCycvI3O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[User Experience Designer: User Experience Designer Jobs in Seattle at Boeing Skip Navigation SearchMenu – News – Investors – Employee/Retiree – Merchandise – Suppliers – Features &amp; Multimedia – Commercial – Defense – Space – Services – Innovation – Our… https://t.co/jHegxFHXuf https://t.co/k2oaV57E3c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer: Scientific Research Corporation is an advanced information technology engineering company that provides innovative products and services to government and private industry, as well as independent institutions. At the core of… https://t.co/IuYMbDvFhQ https://t.co/sKFS0oeqvk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer: Senior Software Developer at EXPERIAN Skip Navigation – Consumer – Small Business – Business – More.X Experian Site Sections – About Experian – Consumer Support – Credit Advice – Global Sites – Company Profile – Corporate Fact… https://t.co/AKZ91tkgo8 https://t.co/oJjE5TS9tZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. IT Specialist- Mission Critical Facility Support: Sr. IT Specialist- Mission Critical Facility Support ==================================================== Req #: ******Location: Herndon, VA USJob Category: Information TechnologySecurity Clearance:… https://t.co/22lpcx9LkP https://t.co/OVcagXd8zc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Product Designer:   Job Description – Sr. Product Designer (PRO00950) Job Description*  Sr. Product Designer-PRO00950 Description Sr. Product Designer For twenty years, Asurion has led the technology protection industry around the globe. We help our… https://t.co/hX956xRi0T https://t.co/8SGghKBJXL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Project Manager: Technical Project Manager ========================= Req #: ******Location: Washington, DC USJob Category: Project and Program ManagementSecurity Clearance: NoneClearance Status: Must be Obtainable Job Description We are looking… https://t.co/CuWyaZ25ae https://t.co/kayfVXkAMd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Engineer II: https://t.co/xz8dnMELdb Services, Inc. – East Palo Alto, CA. Software Development Engineer II – Design SW apps, tools, systts &amp; servs. Multiple job openings. EOE. recblid 0ucrpc3d9m6zjbs11l34wnn9bksm9w https://t.co/Uli0oDrDXs https://t.co/gHENc2FOxQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mega Fall Job Fair: What: Mega Fall Job Fair When: Friday, September 21, 2018 10AM – 2PM Where: The Hagerstown Elks Lodge 11063 Robinwood Drive Hagerstown, MD 21742 Thanks to our Co-Sponsors: Purdue University-Global Washington County American Job Center… https://t.co/z9An9RmkYs https://t.co/ILUCDomC22]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Job Description What you’ll be doing. As a part of the Information Technology team, you’ll design and develop improvements to our Network applications. You’ll also work across the business to vet and deliver small to medium sized… https://t.co/dpRrDfVtAN https://t.co/in3s49K3PQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Target Digital Network Analyst 2: Company Overview For 29 years, clients in the private and public sectors have relied upon SOS International LLC (SOSi) for critical operations in the world’s most challenging environments. SOSi is privately held, was… https://t.co/cBFgMM7oDI https://t.co/p6UbgGT40v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Section Manager: 111568BR Section Manager CA – El Segundo 111568BR This position requires a U.S. person or the ability to obtain an Export Authorization from the appropriate government agency for non-U.S. persons Job Description: The Systems Development… https://t.co/T6ZRIjdSvt https://t.co/7Mzm3xwZDB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Specialist Project Manager — 3rd party Governance: Specialist Project Manager ‘ 3rd party Governance Within the Asset Servicing division, as a Third Party Governance engagement manager, you are responsible for the oversight of division’s vendor based… https://t.co/L1A3QkB2Kb https://t.co/KISgy4QpDs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director of Product Management, Experience Cloud User Experience: Job Description The Challenge Come help us build the next generation of Adobe’s industry-leading Experience Cloud. As Director of Product Management, you will be responsible for defining… https://t.co/lTsOU2S0YT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software License Coordinator: Job Description Software License Coordinator (17573) The Johns Hopkins University Applied Physics Laboratory (APL), a national leader in scientific research and development, located midway between Baltimore and Washington,… https://t.co/Wjg3Iuq5Yp https://t.co/OnYSlAsoD5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETL Data Mart/Data Warehousing Specialist: DCCA is a veteran-owned high-technology company specializing in providing information technology services to a variety of government agencies and commercial enterprises since 1982. DCCA is proud to offer a… https://t.co/iF5hhiUD4j https://t.co/ZZNO45986o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Expert Applications Tester Polygraph: Requisition ID 2018-40733 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Top Secret/SCI with Polygraph Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description Reviews and evaluates software products… https://t.co/hxlvrEOdCc https://t.co/zZvTyIW67C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer Level 0 (05) (SS): Software Engineer Level 0 (05) (SS) Category Security Engineer Clearance Level TS/SCI with Polygraph Location US-MD-Annapolis Junction Overview No demonstrated experience required. Perfect entry-level position for… https://t.co/FXvQtaWOx4 https://t.co/u3hKVrhbAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Operational Concept Analyst Systems Engineer: Location: Washington Job type: Permanent Sector: Manufacturing Category: Analyst Jobs Boeing Defense/Space/Security (BDS) Phantom Works is looking for an Operations Analyst/Systems Engineer who is interested… https://t.co/RlfHgGRoN0 https://t.co/Db1MeJsY2Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Linux Systems Administrator Openstack Deployment: Job Description What you’ll be doing. Collaboratively work on multiple large-scale projects with a high level of technical complexity that industry expertise and in-depth analysis will be required to… https://t.co/9UvLPmmRGR https://t.co/9SNsk9lhbV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Management/Technical Support Security Specialist- Level 3 with TS/SCI clearance: Requisition ID 2018-39779 # of Openings 1 Job Function Administration Security Clearance Level Top Secret/SCI with Polygraph Full/Part Time Full Time Job… https://t.co/J5D0UXFsXD https://t.co/8xB2pYXZ6h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Localization Engineer: Localization Engineer ID 2017-9307 Category Localization Engineering Location US-NY-New York Responsibilities We are looking for a Localization Engineer to be a part of our internal technology team responsible for managing… https://t.co/vgxp1USDwE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mechanical Engineer: Glendale, CA Full-time $90k – $110k Posted Today If you are a Mechanical Engineer with AutoCAD experience, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us – Competitive Base Salary – Great Benefits What You Will Be Doing – Meet with… https://t.co/XlibOibzsB https://t.co/WkLdjnZlP6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mission Ops System Administrator: Company The Boeing Company Job ID ********** Date posted 08/01/2018 Location Herndon Virginia United States Job Description Boeing is searching for motivated candidates to support a growing program that provides… https://t.co/YQpP0jE3FC https://t.co/1IkGWXeXM7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Designer – Referral Partnership: Are you an independent web developer with a large network of clients who process e-commerce transactions? Do you design web pages that require an e-commerce solution? Are you looking for proven opportunities to… https://t.co/XBGUx6N6wV https://t.co/MvGOm2yC1F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Developers: Application Developers About the Company The Tampa Bay Times, which is Florida’s largest daily newspaper, has been part of the Tampa Bay community for more than 130 years. Locally owned and independent, the Times has long been… https://t.co/lO9ILCcthY https://t.co/fb6iKdkMhn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finance/Data Analyst: Requisition Number 18-2118 Title Finance/Data Analyst City Herndon State VA Description Finance/Data Analyst K12 is a technology-based education company that offers proprietary curriculum and instructional support services to… https://t.co/XmQNwGdyGc https://t.co/mCLcnBiFcv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Program Manager (Block 50 GCS): San Diego California : California Job Summary: General Atomics Aeronautical Systems, Inc. (GA-ASI), an affiliate of General Atomics, is a world leader in proven, reliable remotely piloted aircraft and tactical… https://t.co/nUa3uNBjVc https://t.co/qB2IeY0Muj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Member Of Technical Staff: ENGINEERING Big Switch Networks seeks Member of Technical Staff in Santa Clara, CA to work w/ software-defined networking &amp; cloud technologies. Send resume w/ad to 3111 Coronado Dr, Bldg A, Santa Clara, CA 95054. Attn: HR/HC… https://t.co/m9fGo7aaDe https://t.co/YEp3fxlpUN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It: IT POSITION – Multiple positions available in Sunnyvale, CA. https://t.co/xz8dnMELdb Services, Inc. seek candidates for the following positions: Software Development Engineer in Test II, Job Code AZJM-SDET2: Create and execute test plans and cases… https://t.co/YfsnWirhKQ https://t.co/laGAR2LJ9Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist, Senior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Springfield, VA Job Type: Science Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 7/15/2018 Job Description Job Number: R******* Data Scientist, Senior Key Role: technical and analytical expertise to… https://t.co/RdGX2lKGgq https://t.co/96Ggatlp8A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior UX Product Researcher: Job Description The Senior User Experience Researcher will lead product research efforts to better understand our users, and how those users interact with our mobile, digital, and future products. Responsibilities: –… https://t.co/YLggQvCfcu https://t.co/f2dfVJ5OcW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Careers Center | Project ManagerPlease Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome page Returning… https://t.co/An1mPFu53J https://t.co/Ao3ukFyJDM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ERP Account Executive: Irvine, CA or US | #1259: * BS/BA in Marketing, Business, Engineering/Computer Science. * Proven ability to create and present a compelling business case, which aligns with executive level strategic imperatives. * Demonstrated… https://t.co/ii1WV2dIR5 https://t.co/XjNPWoxJtf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer/Senior Engineer, IT Quality Assurance: Engineer/Senior Engineer, IT Quality Assurance View Profile – Join Our Talent Community – Featured Jobs – Jobs at the Airport – Professional – Technical Operations &amp; Maintenance – Customer Service – Pilots… https://t.co/gYotFXaUIy https://t.co/JAydTzDiOs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Construction: Construction Professionals, are you ready to take your career to another level with an organization that will have your best interest in mind? Since its inception, Timothy Jon &amp; Associates has matched top talent in the… https://t.co/UZxoG5DiDV https://t.co/jYlTrciw95]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Transportation Engineer 2 – Intelligent Transportation Systems (ITS): Title: Transportation Engineer 2 – Intelligent Transportation Systems (ITS) Location: Tumwater, WA Salary: $56,580 – $76,092 Job ID: 41579 col-wide Job Description: The Opportunity:… https://t.co/36zDOohpo9 https://t.co/tZAlKelGME]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Administrator: Posting title: Network Administrator SUMMARY: Applicant will provide On-Site tier 1 technical support for JEXC2. Responsibilities for this position will include weekly report preparation including the WAR and also to participate on… https://t.co/mHNEJ8RR1w https://t.co/vaIaZsLDVa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer: Boston, MA Through a combination of smart technology and unique relationships, our client is transforming the way that clinical trials are run. They are on a mission to allow companies to do more trials and get life-saving drugs to… https://t.co/FzvS0m5hIx https://t.co/dqXBvrQowe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best Weekend Deals: SNES Classic, Apple Watch, Dell XPS: What's on your weekend shopping list? Roku, Apple, and Nintendo have a few ideas. https://t.co/tHXmSQAV4x https://t.co/O57wiRosy5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Automation Test Lead: QA Automation Test Lead Ref No.: 18-29620 Location: Dover, New Hampshire Mandatory Technical Skills: UFT, Client ALM, Quality Center, Performance Center / Load Runner, JIRA Desirable Technical Skills: Oracle SQL knowledge… https://t.co/cpn6WtjZOp https://t.co/3CkDjg0Ump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid-Level Finance Systems Integration Analyst: Location: Missouri Job type: Permanent Sector: Finance &amp; Accountancy Category: Analyst Jobs Job Description: The FSI Offer to Cash team is seeking a Finance Systems Integration specialist with proven… https://t.co/nqkJ9GpNTe]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>