<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AlexanderRugaev: The Crypto Finance Ecosystem by @BlackmoonFG  
#ico #blockchain
https://t.co/3CEHHIRUWq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Ellevest: Women are not a “niche market.” (You wouldn’t believe how often I hear this.)

https://t.co/cE7tYcb3gA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @aantonop: New to #Bitcoin and open blockchains?

I have a playlist for you! https://t.co/1oLJb9Txk6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @madelinekelleyg: Do Women-Only Networking Groups Help or Hurt? Quick answer: they help. @EllevateNtwk @SallieKrawcheck @jess7bennett ht…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kristinhull: Even the #Marines have more woman than #VentureCapital. Time to #changethegame. #changethefaceoffinance https://t.co/xDG8Y…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SustainableMan: What other forms of money are possible, or could we possibly get on without any money? #ParadigmShift https://t.co/hSE8…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LizFraserRM: If you're advocating for girls to have access to masculinity but not for boys to have access to femininity, you're reinfor…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chijs: Holy cow, this is HUGE! Bitcoin in the Browser: Google, Apple and More Adopting Crypto-Compatible API https://t.co/V5RsBmp8HF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @akwyz: The latest The Social Navigator ! https://t.co/zV0KLLXhuJ Thanks to @LauraGlass64 @MarkAWilcock #accessibility #disability]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Rotary: “Decisions we make today matter.” - @MelindaGates #Goalkeepers17 https://t.co/tEDSFD4K4S https://t.co/7L0Qo5LfDm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Payments on apps for smartphones are one thing, but payments by text? #accessibility #financialinclusion #risingtide https://t.co/2bYqev7lYU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AMKlasing How much would it cost to bring adequate drinking water to First Nations Communities in Canada per capita? I'd love to read stats]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just found the Financial Access Initiative. Fantastic materials and directions. https://t.co/pa2rGw5Jr5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LATTICE80: Women and Manbassadors in Fintech https://t.co/0pZpxk6vnV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Dashpay: #Dash Copay Wallet going into closed Alpha Testing 
#DigitalCash #Crypto 
https://t.co/sK8jZzgkB8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @wintonARK: "Bitcoin isn't a currency"

"Netflix isn't cable TV"

"Facebook is only for college kids"

"The iPhone is not a business dev…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tgr: Thank you @melindagates for focusing on closing the gender gap in VC and in #tech Working together we can make things happen https…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow. Science &amp; history are great, but if its practitioners don't consider the possibilities, it's hard to discover the truth. #diversity https://t.co/JTU2eLPSqT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @drewconway: Somewhere in a coffee shop  someone is feverishly putting together a pitch deck entitled "Decentralized Credit Rating on th…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KencoinCrypto Your project has potential in a human way. I think crypto could help give sex workers more tools for their financial well being.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/ElkEFkg7eJ The white paper for an adult industry crypto called Kencoin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kristinhull: Encouraging women to get up off their a$$ets, to invest in the world they want to see. #socent #genderlens #impinv #divers…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ConanOBrien: I'm ready for the all-female reboot of America.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @awards_watch: WONDER WOMAN ends its domestic box office run with $412,563,408.
#1 film with a female director (Patty Jenkins)
#1 superh…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justinemusk @IamLungile_ @MarinaAdshade Anytime :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pierre_rochard: Wow! Square making a big move into Bitcoin! Ever since Circle backed out of Bitcoin, Coinbase has had no major brokerag…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For one, I don’t think it’s all about bitcoin. Ethereum is looking pretty good for building new systems. https://t.co/gpGcml9BiX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @justinemusk: @IamLungile_ Nature didn't bring patriarchy into existence did. Agriculture did. The question of who owned what became a q…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justinemusk @IamLungile_ Have you heard of @MarinaAdshade ‘s book Dollars &amp; Sex? She’s got a great Ted Talk on it too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @haydentiff: Don’t tell me what #BitcoinCash *might* become while #Bitcoin HAS been removed from my reach, after 5yrs of advocacy, outre…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WomenEffect: New report on #Genderlensinv by @ESADE @LeonoraBuckland https://t.co/iI4Aqi8sTa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nancyhammondmtl: Women and Millenials are leading the impact investing momentum.  The 10th annual @SocialFinance Forum kicks off with a…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Glad to hear the connections were vibrant! ^_^ tweet at me updates anytime @priyaksamra https://t.co/2m0m7bHEPB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kristinhull: We each align all of our #money with our values, choosing smart banks and #investing in solutions-focused companies with d…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @UN_Women: Women’s economic empowerment is at the heart of sustainable development and prosperous societies. RT if you agree! #Planet505…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DalaiLama: The most crucial use of knowledge and education is to understand the importance of developing a good heart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SallieKrawcheck: 5 Women of Color Making D.C. The Next Impact Tech Hub -  https://t.co/GRFWKEV7J3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cindygallop: The only place to be tonight. @3PercentConf @TwitterWomen #3percentconf https://t.co/i3Uj1oGC1b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MaRiEagar: Employee owned business https://t.co/3gt9ipIkkx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HeForShe: Now, more than ever, it's time to be #HeForShe. #MeToo https://t.co/73Ounc5S1H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @UN_Women: “When we talk about women, peace &amp; security, the engagement of boys &amp; men is crucial" - @LiseGvH @NLatUN https://t.co/aeFsUEG…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got Consent? https://t.co/1WlUOytwJg gets their workshop underway at this week’s @unbounce #Octieber event https://t.co/QHTPIeS8aa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AdamMGrant: The more objective we think we are, the more we discriminate. To end bias, we need to start admitting bias: https://t.co/8L…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @VanessaGrellet_: Join us on 11/17 w/ for Blockchain for Social Impact conference
https://t.co/HdMWVRYr0K #Ethereum #IMPINV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rightwingmadman @KatTheHammer @Hoosiers1986 @POTUS Anyone who tries to win an argument using the words “race card” looses it in my eyes, along with my respect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheBitcoinCoop: We've already breached $6,000! https://t.co/1lL2AKosjD #bitcoin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Drveck: At 28% women, the solar industry is already more diverse at this stage than the tech industry was  at this stage #Bioneers2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let’s compensate it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“The Silent Rise of the Female Driven Economy” by Danielle Kayembe https://t.co/WViv1dxsNP https://t.co/JJDeDmu6EJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RickandMorty: Simulation theory confirmed. https://t.co/2sAHlIXV4v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @UN_Women: To women who are survivors of violence, we hear you and we believe you. #MeToo https://t.co/HWJNn4MScR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Blockchain4Everyone with @icomply https://t.co/xbgwsWfKyW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thomas Linder and Lukas Sieber talking about crypto valley, ICOs and pro-Blockchain government environments #blockchain4everyone #vancouver https://t.co/8HjFdue9Ib]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you could change something about #masculinity to make it #healthier, what would it be? #chooseyourmasculinity #octiber https://t.co/ggL0Pr4HZO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HealthierMasculinities with Ryan at @unbounce for @octiber Raising funds for WAVAW in #Vancouver. Full house! https://t.co/HIxZHsg6GP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @democracynow: Meet @TaranaBurke, the Activist Who Started #MeToo Campaign to Ignite Conversation on Sexual Assault https://t.co/OOy6iKS…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @austinchanning: Thank black women by supporting black women. Pay us. Vote with us. Hire us. Read our writing. Fund our projects and min…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Luvvie: White women. Nothing is as determined as a desperate white man who feels like he’s losing his position in the web of oppression…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DianacBiggs: The earliest computer programmers were #women—then men decided it was a good career  https://t.co/LEIeaFpFDI via @mims @WS…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mistressmatisse: Funny how everybody is upset that we have a Prez would call a SENATOR *a whore*, but nobody is upset that we have a so…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @solomongeorgio: Just a reminder that black people are the only group trying to stop a pedophile from becoming senator. So maybe ask us…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SarahKSilverman: Let’s all take a beat &amp; internalize this quote from the transcendent James Baldwin:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NeerajKA: December so far: 

- CryptoKitties clogs Ethereum
- Bitcoin price rally
- Litecoin price rally 
- SEC / Munchees ICO 
- Bitco…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SallieKrawcheck: My thoughts on what I want to tell my daughter and nieces as we close out a can-you-believe-it 2017: "A Letter to Youn…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justinemusk Stay safe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @davidgsmithphd: “Men play an important role in counteracting sexism.Research shows that people take men’s complaints about sexism more…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AdamMGrant: Overconfidence is a product of ignorance. Doubt is a sign of developing expertise. 
(I say this with 72% confidence) https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @paulvigna: Here are your top 10 apps in Apple's App Store right now:

10 Amazon
9 Bitmoji
8 Google Maps
7 Snapchat
6 Facebook
5 Gmail
4…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @neiltyson: I dream of a world where the truth is what shapes people's politics, rather than politics shaping what people think is true.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aedwardslevy *cue singing voice of Marilyn Manson*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@slicespodcast Cool bit. Thanks Sean!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the time when I shot an Indy feminist porn. #HerPOV #SexPositivity #Erotica Thanks @slicespodcast ! Let’s deweaponize sexuality and emphasize #Consent https://t.co/KcdsgN75uZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cindypinkceo: Don't fear taboos. Run towards them. #TuesdayThoughts @WomenatForbes @MacaelaMack https://t.co/dt4vV5zkNi https://t.co/8I…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wouldn’t mind a Merry Christmas! PM me if I’m picked :) https://t.co/c51988TNAe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So happy to see @aantonop get flooded with $Value for his #TrueValue contributions. HELLS YES. Congratulations! :D #compersion https://t.co/yNYHg9fht4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @starkness: Achievement unlocked: We've created a fully compatible Lightning Network on bitcoin! ✅⚡️https://t.co/wTqI4uKhkd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TIME: Find out why the Silence Breakers were chosen as TIME's Person of the Year 2017 #TIMEPOY https://t.co/jOS7zksnw7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It never fails to amaze me: We systematically undervalue #Femininity despite women overachieving, just in order to belong. "Revolution happens at the edge" How about society comes and meets us at that edge? #TrueValue #ValueFemininity #PayHer #FundHer https://t.co/GHh2dT4ISV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[THIS is what I'm talking about. Thank you for your Vulnerability, Andreas. It reads as Courage. @BreneBrown P.S. Someone give this guy a crypto million already. https://t.co/nkBqkPYHzl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ryaneshea: CryptoKitties = digital pet trading on Ethereum

Highest kitty sale price: $117K
Median kitty sale price: $11
% of Ethereum…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LanceUlanoff: Trickle Down Economics
Trickle Down Economic
Trickle Down Economi
Trickle Down Econom
Trickle Down Econo
Trickle Down Eco…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @keithellison: Trickle down economics is a proven fraud. When you give the wealthiest few a big tax cut, they do 3 things with that mone…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DalaiLama: His Holiness the Dalai Lama meeting with former US President Barack Obama in New Delhi, India on December 1, 2017. (Photo by…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AdamMGrant: "I wasn't tired physically... No, the only tired I was, was tired of giving in."
-Rosa Parks https://t.co/RVhMITWINT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AustenAllred: I’m deeply skeptical of all of these people who claim they think perfectly critically and that whenever someone disagrees…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @schlaf: What all high schools should teach: 
-Opportunity cost
-Diminishing returns
-Compounding
-Self sufficiency
-Sales 101 (aka deal…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @aantonop: Libertarians telling other people what name they can and can't use to refer to the system they created to defeat censorship o…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @fer_ananda: @H_O_L_O_ and @holochain are doing a lot of hackathons for public participation for decentralized systems. Working for comm…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @katgordon: Hey #tech #advertising + other fields where women and POC are underrepresented: here’s your answer when someone says “we wan…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @devnullius: Google: Bitcoin Is Now Bigger than Paypal and Bank of America https://t.co/Fc4IuMBonC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @zachlieberman: noise stack https://t.co/v1k3VLjoFH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EmmanuelMacron: Il ne s'agit pas de nier la différence entre les femmes et les hommes. Il s'agit de se battre pour l'égalité non négoci…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @UN_Women: 5 things you can do to end violence against women. 
#16days #orangetheworld https://t.co/g1cgrrI7Ql]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep! When it comes to financial services, they just care about what works, and that it’s easy. #mainstreamadoption #crypto https://t.co/FS6ANztKut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @UN_Women: Today is the International Day to End Violence against Women!
1 in 3...
https://t.co/msPVglSFLh #16days #orangetheworld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jesslivingston: If you want to support female founders this holiday season, give their products as gifts this year: https://t.co/zcFNfu…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HeForShe: No emotion is actually feminine or masculine. #HeForShe https://t.co/kYCBVisKvo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SallieKrawcheck: Powerful women lend their voices to help others speak out on sexual harassment https://t.co/xNvrXPJY20 via @cbsnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cindygallop: Yay @womenofsextech! @KirstieJBrewer @guardian covers @afinehuman @DameProducts @StephanieAlys @mysteryvibe @wisp_me @tani…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HeForShe: Offering longer maternity leave than paternity leave suggests that taking care of a child is the mother's job. Let's ensure f…]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>