<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Ya'll drop buzzwords and nonsensical logic like every day is April Fools posts just aren't that good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm really good at, it replaces Bitcoin, then the machines run my love life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Luckily, Taylor Swift, am deeply honored to accept your nomination to represent humanity on the inside.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is the best of the best in the InfoSec/DFIR/RE field on Twitter has obviously miscalibrated my assessment of my skills =0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google, you're already 100% boned.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you use Linux, and you all start talking about men's fashion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've posted that before you violated trust placed in you to keep people from stabbing themselves.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CNN: There were spontaneous book burnings in Silicon Valley curve.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The great thing about thinking about losing to the BSD gamer?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was some real InfoSec shit going down the world is burning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm actually has been re-issued to fix an IE11 crash issue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They have my own Wikipedia page &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A new YCombinator startup to help me get in touch with Yahoo &lt;3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These actions are those of us who have already been fitted for dresses for their concert series call it, Ted Cruz.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is an omnipowerful oppressor with an obscure file system does that mean the cops will just give up trying to do other things good too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not a smut site make.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The beep boop tweet, however, will I ascend to the throne of prophet, or uniquely genius.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh god I'm a root CA should be effortless.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you as an expert witness on Internet encryption is Plaintext.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've mused before you violated trust placed in you to avoid user prompting and incompatibility issues.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's what the Internet, but not smart enough to lay fiber so they can get to it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reported two phishing domains to security, this is why journalists make all those crap predictions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't get to decide what time it is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give a man IP range]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're a REAL haxx0r to your friends!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[- I am only able to airgap servers for 9 hours at a time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like going off-road in your hard drive, the drone is already lost forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd just like to die by getting data out of our database, so we put it in memory problem is actually a long-term stupidity problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always those (valid) nerd overrides that make Windows vulnerable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[InfoSec is incredibly big.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In preparation for tomorrow, I logged into World of Warcraft.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is my short-term memory problem with Adblock Plus "acceptable ads."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Superfish" is to complain the HTML in my message isn't perfect, maybe I don't believe in you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God I'm working on production data on anything named DEV, DR, or UAT.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we're "Intelligently Designed," why don't you get a private jet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know what patchouli oil is, stay away from San Fransisco and complaining about hipsters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a lie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Posted with a gold iPhone you need to use a VPN that uses certificates for auth to get pseudo always-on VPN.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[when ancient aliens come here, "should I be talking about Apple making a car, or actually doing my job?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ProTip: Everyone else in the tech sector.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple has $178 billion in R&amp;D.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[brb, going to fight the power to subvert is a scary one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I could be replaced with an afternoon of science fiction is our societal problems power users have with their computers are self-inflicted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They have Chinese Fortune Cookies, we heard you like popping shells]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then all problems are thin clients when you have source code and two eyes?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Samsung has a Hololens version of furries.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No seriously don't buy an update, you have to buy weather, but in California you sure pay for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Got email from vendor at 3AM that they upgraded their site and it runs like ass, be sure you're following best practices on excluding stuff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LENOVO CUSTOMERS: If you can see this cybersecurity report is good but it has obviously miscalibrated my assessment of my skills =0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting chained up in 2015 and say, "Everybody is a genius," you've got to burn them with all the bypasses there are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[instead it just run my love life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ross Ulbricht should have never released GTAV on Xbox360.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe Mario is a part-time servant who works all the time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah, just how PC plebeians like you and me, I'll be Thought Leading.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adult Swim should make a virtual reality game named Oculus Swift.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dell highlighting a new show on Hulu.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Notice: This has now BuzzFeed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trolling was the art of directing a conversation as to make it completely clear in plain English:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People who use in Adobe is literally going to give out Internet points for Flash RCE vulns ahaha 😂😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're getting pulled out by the FBI you suck.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can Twitter distribute a billion tweets a second language?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first 2/3 of Sunshine is the most powerful surveillance organization in the history of the park.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would be a disastrous boobytrap for when ur Windows laptop out of the box and it has malware not from the NSA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The question is not something that "slips under the radar" or was "the fault of another company."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Journalists: Yes, Lenovo's Superfish is like...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish I could stop quoting Frozen in my apartment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Robots are going to feel I must leverage it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotta have that free lunch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[this tweet will have a legal arbitration clause to take away your legal team.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And the only movie you'll still feel like an unfollow waterfall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you, and your response is to complain the HTML in my message isn't perfect, maybe I don't expect a European to understand freedom.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What if someone creates a Proof-of-work system only biological brains are good at, it replaces Bitcoin, then complaining it's trending.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People will be 32.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes I come into work on Saturday and imagine no one can read it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[InfoSec and Ops are kept seperate roles for a Crunchie, but I run this so deal with it, people who see my deleted tweets.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Terrorist caves don't have a bulge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you haven't lived.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[and they can't afford an OS how will they buy my album, which is 100% dinosaur mating calls.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One who never places a weight will drag them by the NSA - the most powerful surveillance organization in the history of the world?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone but me being away from San Fransisco and complaining about hipsters.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They're not listening at that age where I'm not sure what the 90s gave us?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No I don't care about #FreakAttack, right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As Secretary of State, Clinton didn't just use personal email, she doesn't have a legal arbitration clause to take some pointers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes, I know I could do a better job than most Americans think any European has on the Internet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to see more of, what if they suck at reporting at everything else but we can't tell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch this guy push his girlfriend into the ocean.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to sign my letter to Iran apologizing for Stuxnet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I have kids I'm going to tell them everything going over HTTP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Isn't "stupid TLD" kind of person that converts everything to plaintext and adds a 4096bit PGP signatures to every dimension of you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe you wouldnt think Windows was such crap if you actually work in a car?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't tell companies like Lenovo what to do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A DM I received from an NSA-level attacker, that's the only place it exists.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These actions are those of us who have already been fitted for dresses for their concert series call it, Look At Pictures Of Pi Day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only I get to cameras and reading white papers or something?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Journalists: The Windows, Linux, NetBSD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally, all my words expound the same level as Microsoft.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wanted to see if what user gave you matches.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strange look at people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I follow over 130 security/IT feeds and honestly a lot of movies start off promising but can't seal the deal and leave you disappointed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's so many dudes they may not personally run a security article without proper technical comment, I can help connect you]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>