<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Discusses the "Good-News Story" of Ghana: 

    President Barack Obama and Professor John E... http://t.co/1Ih1umn0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[El Vicepresidente Biden visita la Basílica de Nuestra Señora de Guadalupe en la Ciudad de México: 
	El Vicepresi... http://t.co/ZqLb7CCf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Libyan Prime Minister ElKeib Visits the White House: 

    President Barack Obama meets with Prime Minister... http://t.co/rntvIrN7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First Lady Michelle Obama Speaks at the International Women of Courage Awards: 
	Earlier today, First Lady Miche... http://t.co/C9BWL6II]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the Archives: Talking Healthy Lunch with Elmo: 
	Agriculture Secretary Tom Vilsack has declared March 8, 20... http://t.co/SkXIOizo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We Can’t Wait: Strengthening Our Democracy Through Open Government: 
	At the United Nations General Assembly in ... http://t.co/wRIIo9WY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Announces $1 Billion Fund to Promote Energy Efficient Vehicles: 

    President Barack Obam... http://t.co/TH0WJD7q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Champions of Change: Honoring Mentors who Support America’s Entrepreneurs: 
	This afternoon, the White House hon... http://t.co/XSTYPD1O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Meets with the Business Roundtable: 

    President Barack Obama takes questions following ... http://t.co/Q7YUq6o4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hiring Veterans: Good for a Company’s Bottom Line: 
	This week, Syracuse University’s Institute for Veteran and ... http://t.co/9hFZiW6g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vice President Biden Visits the Basilica of Our Lady of Guadalupe in Mexico City: 
	Capping his day of official ... http://t.co/N9QXQztV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Help for Military Homeowners: 
	Ed note: this was originally posted on the CFPB's blog

	When I was at Fort Drum... http://t.co/hKQvFok3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What You Need to Know About Today's Housing Announcement: 
	In the State of the Union, President Obama introduce... http://t.co/PYHYNkXJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calling All Students: Last Chance to Enter the White House Poster Contest: 

		The White House is inviting e... http://t.co/KKoneLnI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Lending Showing New Signs of Strength: 
	Over the past three years, the Obama administration has made i... http://t.co/PxM6kCdE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Meets With Prime Minister Netanyahu: 

    President Barack Obama and Prime Minister Benjam... http://t.co/sJLhEexo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nominations Open for National Medal of Science or National Medal of Technology: 
	Last month, during the second ... http://t.co/lwKLcm8Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Data: The Affordable Care Act in Your State: 
	For the past year, Amy Ward of West Des Moines, Iowa has been... http://t.co/C94SfKVZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Speaks at the AIPAC Policy Conference: 
	This morning, President Obama addressed the AIPAC Polic... http://t.co/hxo3z7fQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Address: Taking Control of Our Energy Future: 
	President Obama talks about how the American auto industr... http://t.co/ldGTLC9a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Wrap Up: A Nation's Gratitude: 

	Your quick look at this week on http://t.co/4TLTiIEJ:

	Welcoming the Da... http://t.co/uQJK9e0O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Growing America’s Outdoor Heritage and Economy: 
	There is no doubt that our nation’s public lands – national pa... http://t.co/fV4kD6Io]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nine New Administrative Patent Judges Will Help Entrepreneurs Turn Ideas Into Jobs: 
	As part of our ongoing eff... http://t.co/WqhKTCx3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Wing Week: 3/2/2012 or "That's Worth Fighting For": 

	This week, the President touted the resurgence of th... http://t.co/TV75j7UW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Clean Energy Standard for America: 
	This week, answering the President’s call in the last two State of the Un... http://t.co/743z4owj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama on Gas Prices and Oil Subsidies: 

    President Barack Obama delivers remarks on the econo... http://t.co/Fbzd92Ff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our Dependence on Foreign Oil Is Declining: 
	America’s dependence on foreign oil has gone down every single yea... http://t.co/GLYpjSsJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ticket Lottery for the White House Easter Egg Roll Opens Today: 

	On Monday April 9, 2012, the First Family w... http://t.co/mz3ZhAIH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[National Guard Adjutants General Visit the White House, Meet with Vice President Biden: 

    VP Biden shak... http://t.co/sx3wPxHM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Home and Abroad, Breaking Down Barriers for Women and Girls: 
	Yesterday, I had the opportunity to speak at t... http://t.co/6ihqRtQx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FACT CHECK: All-of-the-Above Approach to American Energy: 
	Lately, there have been a lot of misleading claims a... http://t.co/vUKQ6VTZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Honors Iraq Vets With White House Dinner: 
	Tonight, a group of Iraq veterans will join Presiden... http://t.co/v9iJWlrj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vice President and Dr. Biden Host the Third Annual Black History Month Reception: 

    Vice President Bide... http://t.co/MiG8yxKM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[USDA Offers More than Employment Opportunities for Veterans: 

    U.S. Secretary of Agriculture Tom Vilsac... http://t.co/1IuMwpM0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making Medicare Stronger: 
	Over the past few years, health care cost increases have been slowing – both for Med... http://t.co/ARhmMNOn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Following Through: Detention & Interrogation Consistent with our National Security, Our Laws, and Our Values: 
	... http://t.co/QcFQRPjw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today’s Suspension of Payments and the Affordable Care Act: 
	Today, thanks to the Affordable Care Act, the Depa... http://t.co/q4TpWbRy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honoring Unsung Heroes During Black History Month: 

	During Black History Month, we pause to salute and refle... http://t.co/nfB3HA8Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Building a 21st Century Government by Cutting Duplication, Fragmentation, and Waste: 
	Today, the Government Acc... http://t.co/Nq4zFJNg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch: Behind the Scenes at Red, White and Blues at the White House: 
	On February 21, 2012 the President and Fi... http://t.co/YVdw3xVX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Small Manufacturers Driving Job Creation, Economic Growth: 
	Ed note: This was originally published on Open for ... http://t.co/r3OJ2MRG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Training Workers with the Skills Employers Need: 

    Vice President Joe Biden, Dr. Jill Biden, and Secret... http://t.co/7nUoOTzZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Challenges Governors to Invest in Education: 
	Today, President Obama challenged state governors... http://t.co/MVFjIcOW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First Lady and Dr. Biden Urge Action from State Governors on Military Spouse Hiring: 
	Earlier this morning, the... http://t.co/Gi8lzSs6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Backstage with Keb Mo: 
	Keb Mo is a singer, songwriter, and blues guitarist. He's a three-time Grammy award win... http://t.co/YdGTSTsf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Together We Must End Dating Violence: 
	Over the past month, college newspapers across the country have run an o... http://t.co/ugZLJDSp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Backstage with Warren Haynes: 
	Warren Haynes is one of Rolling Stone's 25 greatest guitarists of all time. He's... http://t.co/6Fhm1zZa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By the Numbers: $4 Billion: 

	Oil companies receive $4 billion every year in taxpayer-funded subsidies, despi... http://t.co/KjZEfqB7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Address: An All-Of-The-Above Approach to American Energy: 
	President Obama talks about how important it ... http://t.co/428kewy9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eliminating Barriers to Growing our Economy: 
	Throughout today and the rest of the weekend, President Obama wil... http://t.co/XNt7vfFj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Wrap Up: "Sweet Home Chicago": 

	A quick look at the week of February 20th on http://t.co/4TLTiIEJ:

	Y... http://t.co/0Z3TPjow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Backstage with Susan Tedeschi and Derek Trucks: 
	Susan Tedeschi and Derek Trucks are American music royalty. Te... http://t.co/VIbxklJp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nearly 2.1 Million Records Released: 
	In September 2009, the President announced that—for the first time in his... http://t.co/rwgBGFMb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Contracting Smarter, Saving More: 
	From the start of the Administration, President Obama has charged agencies t... http://t.co/Amfl2Pvu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Highlights Smart Energy Training at University of Miami: 
	Ed note: this post originally appeare... http://t.co/jYkKwr2x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Wing Week: 2/24/12 or West Wing Week 100!: 
	It's hard to believe that when West Wing Week was born, "Don't... http://t.co/UAWgzQl4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Describes an All-of-the-Above Strategy for Energy: 

    President Barack Obama tours the U... http://t.co/VJ2ir2hM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We Can’t Wait: Obama Administration Calls for A Consumer Privacy Bill of Rights for the Digital Age: 
	Today at ... http://t.co/ZFrBvKbe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Computer Contract Expected to Save Taxpayers $20-25M: 
	Ed. note: This was originally posted on The Commerce... http://t.co/k6mpPdWs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We the People Petition Response: Chief of the National Guard Bureau Joins the Joint Chiefs of Staff: 
	Yesterday... http://t.co/ldx2QeTv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helping Americans with Pre-Existing Conditions Get Needed Care: 
	Before the Affordable Care Act, Americans like... http://t.co/OQSlDvr3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A New Generation of Nurses: 

    Secretary of Labor Hilda L. Solis and Dr. Jill Biden start the Community ... http://t.co/FrlCihOr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Report from the Road: An Ambitious Plan to Train Ohio Workers for New Jobs: 

    Secretary of Labor Hilda ... http://t.co/wO3CNQVX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch: First Look at the Museum of African American History and Culture: 
	When the Museum of African American H... http://t.co/hKcDW1cL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the Archives: Celebrating Black History Month Series: 
	The theme of this year’s National African American ... http://t.co/e2nnb5cg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calling All App Developers: $10,000 App Challenge Looking for Ways to Connect Businesses with Government: 
	Ed n... http://t.co/JJmMy0tB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Sings "Sweet Home Chicago": 
	Last night, President Obama and First Lady Michelle Obama hosted a... http://t.co/qFp0lEdM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama at the Ground Breaking Ceremony for the Smithsonian National Museum of African American History ... http://t.co/PFoTVKkY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Report Highlights Wireless Broadband Benefits for Public Safety and Job Creation: 

    Vice President ... http://t.co/YofmtQ6o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We Can’t Wait: Bringing New Investments to Rural Communities by Leveraging Existing Programs: 
	Since the format... http://t.co/tCsC3Cbi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kicking Off the Community College to Career Bus Tour: 
	Tomorrow, Dr. Jill Biden and Secretary of Labor Hilda So... http://t.co/1suO8aXh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/7z6kWCSJ: Remaking Public Participation: 
	On January 18, 2011, the President issued Executive Order ... http://t.co/2qCKojwa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enforcing Trade Agreements Protects Jobs: 
	Last Friday, President Obama traveled to the Boeing aerospace factor... http://t.co/vdghrzHq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We Can’t Wait Update: Preventing Prescription Drug Shortages: 
	On October 31, 2011 President Obama signed an Ex... http://t.co/AC4ursge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Building the Workforce of the Future at Community Colleges: 

	Dr. Jill Biden was at the Mercer County Communi... http://t.co/IKMBybud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vice President and Dr Biden Celebrate Women's History Month: 

    Dr. Jill Biden gives remarks at a recept... http://t.co/nR71x6Vg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First Lady Michelle Obama Marks the Cherry Blossom Festival Centennial: 

    First Lady Michelle Obama par... http://t.co/WlaDtD7l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Sees Progress on Nuclear Security: 

	Two years ... http://t.co/MhDFkHju]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Leaders Respond to President Obama's Executive Order on Infrastructure Permitting: 
	Last week, Preside... http://t.co/Vp4kRUEI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dr. Jill Biden: Military Support Will Define Future Leaders: 
	Ed note: This article was cross-posted from the D... http://t.co/4dLstjFX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Discussing the Global Economy and Nuclear Security in Seoul: 

	... http://t.co/AlURKxqE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Talks Title IX: 

    (Official White House Photo by Pete Souza) Feb. 5, 2011

       ... http://t.co/POXmBOAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Invest in a Clean Energy Future by Ending Fossil Fuels Subsidies: 
	 Earlier this month, President Obama called ... http://t.co/FuPxrQQj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ask President Obama: 

    President Barack Obama delivers remarks at Hankuk University of Foreign Studies ... http://t.co/gfiYfeEA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama in South Korea: 
	Just midnight on Saturday morning, President Obama boarded Air Force One and d... http://t.co/qbi5npLk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Address: President Obama Says House Must Pass Bipartisan Transportation Bill: 
	President Obama is callin... http://t.co/bp4PwyAr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's Move! Tweetup at the White House: Easter Egg Roll: 
	We're excited to announce the next Let's Move! tweetu... http://t.co/ZGK1yfWx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the Archives: 22 Pens: 
	When President Obama signed the Affordable Care Act into law on March 23, 2010, he... http://t.co/MC5w3TVr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exceeding My Expectations: The White House Internship Program: 
	Ed. note: The application for the Fall 2012 Whi... http://t.co/xp9BeimX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Nominates Dartmouth College President to Lead World Bank: 

    President Barack Obama anno... http://t.co/QEnKYf7y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By the Numbers: 100 Percent: 

	Before the Affordable Care Act was signed into law, insurance companies had fr... http://t.co/zkzlPhB3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Faces of the New Health Care Law: 
	Each day this week, you’ve heard stories about what the new health care law ... http://t.co/2tx8ks0q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Wing Week: 3/22/12 or "Slainte!": 

	This week, the President celebrated his fourth St Patrick's Day in the... http://t.co/hvKXGNw6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Expanding Our Oil and Gas Pipeline Infrastructure: 

    President Barack Obama delivers remarks on energy ... http://t.co/WLmC7wan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Week in Office Hours: Two Years of Health Care Progress: 
	This week, we are holding a series of White Hous... http://t.co/2nYMF70L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Discusses Domestic Energy Production in New Mexico: 

    President Barack Obama delivers r... http://t.co/2NlvBiY5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Health Care Reform in Action: One Family's Story: 

	We met Nathan and his son, Thomas, in 2009. Thomas was bo... http://t.co/Cy4RibrS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breaking it Down: The Health Care Law and Cost Control: 
	For too long, too many hard working Americans paid the... http://t.co/1XPJMdCt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David Plouffe: "We did the math": 
	This morning, David Plouffe, Senior Advisor to President Obama, sent the mes... http://t.co/HWyaaa3O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MarkCare: Making Health Insurance More Affordable for Small Businesses: 
	Mark Hodesh, the owner of a home-and-g... http://t.co/Yurazd6A]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>