<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[US sanctions 2 Turkish officials over detention of US pastor: The US Treasury Department is sanctioning Turkey's ministers of justice and interior in response to the detention of American pastor Andrew Brunson, White House press secretary Sarah Sanders… https://t.co/zVtX7jUngp https://t.co/b472LkGGbs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Analyst, IT Advisory,Insurance (Guidewire Integration) Financial Services Office (Manager) (Multiple Positions) #-COL0010C: IT Analyst, IT Advisory, Insurance (Guidewire Integration) Financial Services Office (Manager) (Multiple Positions), Ernst &amp;… https://t.co/V2UkTSVy7o https://t.co/jYNshH4qpr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Key GOP senator: Supreme Court confirmation hearing 'sometime during September': Iowa Republican Sen. Chuck Grassley, the chairman of the powerful Senate Judiciary Committee, said Wednesday that he hopes to have President Donald Trump's Supreme Court… https://t.co/zER8beiG2j https://t.co/UCnUgFYVzi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Han Solo's jacket could sell for $1 million at auction of film props: Han Solo's jacket -- the one worn by Harrison Ford in "The Empire Strikes Back" -- could fetch over $1M at an upcoming auction in London. https://t.co/kkiQooFSla https://t.co/NLCBro3RBD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer | -Come join our product development team in a hands-on technical role where you-ll be involved in th: Software Developer | Come join our product development team in a hands-on technical role where you’ll be involved in the end-to-end… https://t.co/7UI71cUj9H https://t.co/8lEv6l1rt4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple profit soars; Tariff threats; Tesla earnings: Here's what you need to know about the markets before you start your business day. https://t.co/snozvSR5M6 https://t.co/4aJCRl6d2m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big Data Developer: Big Data Developer Ref No.: 18-31648 Location: Columbus, Ohio – 5+ years of experience in middle-tier/backend systems development in Java/Linux – 6+ experience with Unix/Linux/Java scripting – Experience in Python scripting is a plus… https://t.co/oHeuHEfjiJ https://t.co/zczcPjpM4b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cisco Voice Engineer: Cisco Voice Engineer Honeywell Careers Chinese (Simplified)Czech (Czech Republic)Dutch (The Netherlands)English (US)French (Canada)French (France)German (Germany)Portuguese (Brazil)Spanish (Spain)Create a Profile|Log In Yes No Show… https://t.co/EZu5hOJTvK https://t.co/FTgoLChJ8S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Philippines' Duterte crushes $5.5m of luxury cars in anti-corruption drive: Phillipines PresidentRodrigo Roa Duterte donned a construction hat this Monday as he watched the public destruction of over million USD worth of luxury vehicles and motorcycles,… https://t.co/fx8KcZfoZ9 https://t.co/vQnKDSaqN8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Systems Specialist: Company The Boeing Company Job ID ********** Date posted 07/25/2018 Location Heath Ohio United States Job Description The Boeing Defense, Space &amp; Security (BDS) organization is seeking a Quality Systems Specialist (Level 2)… https://t.co/K5YmBUg4dp https://t.co/jlfejg1jTi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SharePoint Developer: Lubrizol, a Berkshire Hathaway company, is a market-driven global company that combines complex, specialty chemicals to optimize the quality, performance and value of customers’ products while reducing their environmental impact.… https://t.co/ChlFtvkxr3 https://t.co/tP8TVnjtn9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Health alert issued for salads, wraps from Kroger, Trader Joe's, Walgreens due to parasite concern: Consumers have been warned by federal health officials not to purchase over two dozen salad and wrap products available in major grocery chains due to… https://t.co/lruiBwSYUg https://t.co/5lQEnp6rer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mindsphere Full-Stack Developer Greater Cincinnati Area: For Siemens Mindsphere – Full-Stack Developer – Greater Cincinnati Area job – Marketing – Milford, Ohio Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard – Toggle navigation – My… https://t.co/VK9cUVRymJ https://t.co/tJ4OUKyGcQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior PACS Application Specialist Cleveland: CIIP Certification Required!: Job Description Description Position Summary/Essential Duties: – The PACS Analyst, Applications is responsible for providing direct PACS application support. The support… https://t.co/wVwtFdUaYb https://t.co/zFhEW2phPU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The disappearing White House press briefing: Today is the last, the 31st, day of July. https://t.co/KSaMgpVCmU https://t.co/aE3kjiTk8L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager/Scrum Master: Location US-OH-Cincinnati Posted Date 20 hours ago(7/12/2018 2:42 PM) Job ID 23813 # Positions 1 Category Technology Position Type Full Time Overview Be Here. Be Great. Working for a leader in the insurance industry means… https://t.co/qsicFMMeoW https://t.co/kUP1Na32N5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software QA Engineer: Software QA Engineer / Cincinnati , OH Overview:Join our scrum team with a focus on Quality Assurance and release planning for our Core Product Development Team. This position will work on our scrum team and closely with our Product… https://t.co/oYZXkdNnTs https://t.co/MtdcNlHInV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top immigration official says family detention centers are 'like summer camp': A top immigration official on Tuesday said family detention centers are "more like summer camp" than a jail during a congressional hearing on the administration's efforts to… https://t.co/z33GPBbaSX https://t.co/7jyEHWbF4Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Move over Macron, Trump has a new European BFF: Move over Macron, there's a new bromance at the White House -- although you'd never have guessed it as President Donald Trump's new European BFF -- Giuseppe Conte -- rocked up Monday. https://t.co/EmBJvZX820 https://t.co/6xTaVbGhR0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Parkland dad blames the Trump administration for allowing 3-D printed guns: Fred Guttenberg, whose daughter Jamie was slain in February's school shooting in Parkland, Florida, says a court needs to stop access to the untraceable plastic weapons. https://t.co/hrNte2dHA5 https://t.co/A0u1dyul7k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't blame Sacha Baron Cohen because you don't like the truth: Prank comedy can reveal uncomfortable truths. For those upset by the jokes, don't watch the video, or change the channel. https://t.co/yWKvcTeIH0 https://t.co/I5EIE6vfOR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dotnet Developer with MES support: Dotnet Developer with MES support Ref No.: 18-30770 Location: Harrisburg, Ohio Position: Dotnet Developer with MES support Location: Harrisburg, OH Duration: Fulltime Position Job Description 6-8 Years’ Experience in… https://t.co/miz0fn2eKi https://t.co/l3MnbqC3cH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Specialist IT-Application-Development: Specialist – IT Application Development Populus Group seeks a Specialist – IT Application Development in Columbus, OH to plan, initiate, and manage information technology projects in the insurance industry. Build a… https://t.co/3ycecQUDSx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Software Developer: Job Description What you’ll be doing. – Design, develop, analyze, evaluate, test, debug, document, and implement moderately complex software automation applications and solutions from collected specifications or requirements. –… https://t.co/yLAY6AHLqn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7 Mexican nationals arrested in connection with botched robbery at Texas mall: Five of the seven suspects gave police a false name, each suspect was charged with aggravated robbery and received a $200,000 bond. https://t.co/9nStHrSovg https://t.co/hpaSD6xHQg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps: DevOps (Cloud) System Engineer, Willis Towers Watson Job #*******P, Buffalo, NY Menu ToggleMenu Hide – Glassdoor – Linkedin – Twitter – Facebook – English – Espaol – Franais (FR) – Franais (CA) – Join Our Talent Network – English English en –… https://t.co/vXfwlmjp9a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reliable Sources: Moonves remains atop CBS. For now...: Les Moonves will continue to head CBS in the wake of sexual harassment allegations contained in Ronan Farrow's New Yorker report -- at least for now... https://t.co/vz6NY51xa1 https://t.co/U1U0rcuoaZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Cloud Infrastructure Automation Lead: 3046693 Senior Cloud Infrastructure Automation Lead Oil &amp; Gas Headquarters GE Oil &amp; Gas United States Provide IT leadership on multiple automation build projects. Help prioritize and drive results for the… https://t.co/ea7qIpa7Wt https://t.co/YbnnOTAOSU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All aboard the Maharajas' Express, India's most luxurious train: You can live like a king aboard the Maharajas' Express, a hotel-on-wheels that will take you on luxury train trip through Rajasthan, India. https://t.co/OcoAi4qjVC https://t.co/LMCVmbO7bp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former WH aide predicts no shutdown before midterms: Marc Short, the former White House legislative affairs director and recently hired CNN contributor, predicted on Monday there would not be a government shutdown ahead of the midterm elections. https://t.co/aPH1dC9aMW https://t.co/MKPweddO1G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump says he'd meet with Iran without preconditions 'whenever they want': President Donald Trump said Monday he is willing to meet with Iran's leadership, without preconditions, "whenever they want." https://t.co/i3Yt4WbChW https://t.co/ac1dQSqb6O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Trump meets Italy's prime minister: Trump and Italian Prime Minister Giuseppe Conte will meet following the President's latest tweet attack on special counsel Robert Mueller. Follow here for the latest. https://t.co/nhxA5hW8Z1 https://t.co/o2wRLxaas1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering Manager: Engineering Manager Trimble is an exciting, entrepreneurial company, with a history of exceptional growth coupled with a disciplined and strategic focus on being the best. While GPS is at our core, we have grown beyond this… https://t.co/l3lsh4pgq9 https://t.co/zXnTBRwv5V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter hires researchers to study the 'health' of its 'discourse': Twitter has selected researchers to develop metrics around echo chambers, uncivil discourse and bridging gaps between communities on its platform. https://t.co/WVpOCooF2L https://t.co/NA3DwNaMBk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alcohol in breast milk may lead to lower cognition in kids, study finds: Kids' exposure to alcohol through breast milk may cause a comparable drop in their cognitive abilities, according to a new study. https://t.co/jtqKFW6j5d https://t.co/pp7yAKKTej]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Big Data Developer: Senior Big Data Developer : Job Description Roles and Responsibilities: 1. Gathers requirements from stakeholders, designs the solution aligned to requirements, platform(s) architecture and infrastructure. 2. Engages with… https://t.co/J4i00q72Rz https://t.co/fQnN6drlwL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Job Description The Software Engineer position will be supporting the Logistics Data Warehouse (LDW). This position will be part of the Logistics team supporting the U.S. and U.K. Trident II Strategic Weapons System, the U.K. Successor… https://t.co/n3UcYunmjz https://t.co/LEN55Vr4FS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[:: DOT NE DEVELOPER ::: :: DOT NE DEVELOPER :: Ref No.: 18-31340 Location: Perrysburg, Ohio Hello, My name is Ashutosh and I’m an IT recruiter at Enterprise Solutions, Inc. I came across your resume on a job board and wanted to check if you are available… https://t.co/JKpcYle0G8 https://t.co/09hgDpLPmf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rename Austin? A report suggests taking a closer look at city's Confederate legacy: A report released last week raises the issue that Austin is named after Stephen F. Austin, a supporter of slavery. https://t.co/7PeQNevTNx https://t.co/45cba2PpPI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Developer (Node / Angular JS): Sr Developer (Node / Angular JS) Ref No.: 18-31215 Location: Mayfield Heights, Ohio Sr Developer (Node / Angular JS) in Mayfield Heights, OH: – URGENT Target Rate: Open? Location: Mayfield Heights, OH 1. Minimum 7 years… https://t.co/dmpUvyzAT1 https://t.co/eOIgfgmp57]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Embedded Software Engineer: Search Display ****************************************************************************** &amp; siteid=105 &amp; PageType=JobDetails &amp; jobid=******* &amp; codes=IND Loading Close Your account has successfully been deleted.… https://t.co/jb00E5hefu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two Americans cyclists among four dead in Tajikistan hit-and-run: Two Americans were among four cyclists killed Sunday by a hit-and-run driver in Tajikistan, authorities said. https://t.co/9qxUSnuUAN https://t.co/LU0ZvGvp6N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A brief history of briefs -- and how technology is transforming underpants: Alana Clifton-Cunningham writes about the fascinating history and future of underwear, "with high performance undies that claim to do everything from filtering flatulence to… https://t.co/GijkLzJqGZ https://t.co/gwqPA40jwn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Lead – Product Review Engineer: Location: Ohio Job type: Permanent Sector: Manufacturing Category: Engineers Jobs The Boeing Defense, Space &amp; Security (BDS) organization is seeking an experienced Technical Lead – Product Review Engineer (Level… https://t.co/JaZzIePgIs https://t.co/5qGr7t3CDZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The families not reunited: One mother's wait in limbo: Alejandra is one of the hundreds of separated parents who were not reunited by the Thursday deadline. Only a small fraction of nonreunited parents are still in government custody, though, with the… https://t.co/a4zSnE1Y6C https://t.co/Sz7hJoDtNe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Architect: Location US-OH-Cincinnati Posted Date 4 days ago(6/14/2018 9:27 AM) Job ID 23219 # Positions 3 Category Technology Position Type Full Time Overview Be Here. Be Great. Working for a leader in the insurance industry means opportunity for… https://t.co/bMIfcilPki https://t.co/yTtPQp7Pkw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Service Desk Technician Mid/Sr TS/SCI Wright-Patterson AFB, Ohio: Come join General Dynamics Information Technology Team! – Follow all approved customer policies, processes and procedures. – Follow the written and verbal instructions provided by the CFP… https://t.co/lQMIXFCeD5 https://t.co/u6U0pMW9nm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Save boycotts for people who deserve them: While some may not agree with Jaelene Hinkle, the US women's national soccer team player who has been outspoken against gay marriage, she does not deserve to be shunned for her beliefs, writes Scott Altman. https://t.co/56UTV6FMqF https://t.co/UAc5jbceEW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Business Analyst: Company Name: Marathon Petroleum Company LP Location Name: Findlay, OH Location Address: 539 S Main St, Findlay, OH, United States (US), 45840 Education Level: Bachelor’s Desired Relevant Experience Level: 4+ years Employee Group:… https://t.co/K6SiPZp2BT https://t.co/QD50RoaVXm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: What IT Program &amp; Project Management contributes to Cardinal Health IT Program &amp; Project Management is responsible for playing a key/critical role in realizing business value through the application of project management knowledge,… https://t.co/XfAFs9ZOuG https://t.co/AZdTqQ4SVI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Software Engineer (Stategy Innovation): Oasis Systems -Sr Software Engineer (Stategy &amp; Innovation) Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability… https://t.co/XGTkSnssAo https://t.co/BbIgk91vtI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's top economic adviser doubles down on tariffs: Top White House economic adviser Larry Kudlow expressed support Sunday for President Donald Trump's enthusiastic pursuit of tariffs on China, saying that so long as tariffs are "targeted," the actions… https://t.co/MvCezEME5r https://t.co/UYYFmE5d14]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Qatar denies claims it ran secret 'black operation' to secure 2022 World Cup: Qatar World Cup organizers have denied allegations they hired ex-CIA agents and a PR firm to run a dirty tricks campaign in an effort to land the 2022 tournament. https://t.co/3Tgr0n6wTo https://t.co/lZtXfpijFP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LGCT Berlin: Fourth time lucky for Alberto Zorzi: It was fourth time lucky for Alberto Zorzi, who booked his first win of the season in the Berlin leg of the Longines Global Champions Tour (LGCT) for the world's top show jumpers. https://t.co/1RzGaT5ve1 https://t.co/4e3vStavRT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (ITEM Master): Oasis Systems -Software Engineer (ITEM Master) Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job.… https://t.co/6jbNQT3yrh https://t.co/bCMUDXWksQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mobile QA Tester/Team Coordinator: Mobile QA Tester/Team Coordinator Ref No.: 18-28098 Location: Cincinnati, Ohio Mobile QA Tester/Team Coordinator – There is a need for an on-site mobile tester/coordinator to perform testing in an agile environment and… https://t.co/VSbPLkFfo0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Lumira: SAP Lumira Ref No.: 18-31642 Location: Cincinnati, Ohio Hello, Kindly review the below position and let me know if you are interested for, send me updated resume along with best time to contact. Position: SAP Lumira Location – Cincinnati, OH… https://t.co/dCdaeQLXqr https://t.co/7HoavzeMfB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What you need to know about 'stand your ground' laws: Cases of self-defense aren't always simple -- especially in states with a "stand your ground" law. Here's what you need to know about them. https://t.co/gUD4Puu0OM https://t.co/0lZgrYgyTN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Giuliani once praised Michael Cohen as 'honest,' but now says Cohen has 'lied all his life': After a week of revelations that suggest Michael Cohen may have turned on Donald Trump, Rudy Giuliani, the President's current lawyer, argued that Trump's former… https://t.co/AuXUynCVYA https://t.co/LFZBZS5xwW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 female millennial Democratic nominees in Pennsylvania want to change the party from within: These three millennial women all have one thing in common: They're Democrats running for a House seat in the midterm elections in Pennsylvania. https://t.co/N90jQzmO7o https://t.co/1cOMpGIGBk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle EBS Database Administrator: Description The Oracle Database Administrator is responsible for the maintenance and support of the Oracle eBusiness Suite and ancillary applications while working directly with peers, application developers, and… https://t.co/uPme2r5IRJ https://t.co/fDfS9uxmCi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK 'fake news' report calls for tougher rules, fines for social media companies: If the recommendations are adopted, it will radically change how the UK deals with social media companies. https://t.co/OMWX5atreC https://t.co/jXJHCGhwBD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer II: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Cleveland, OH Job Type: Information Technology Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 7/5/2018 Job Description Primary Purpose: This position is responsible for analysis, codes, tests and… https://t.co/RRjKyg8sJj https://t.co/Iq0eLNFGgG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Demi Lovato remains hospitalized following apparent overdose: Demi Lovato remains in the hospital following an apparent drug overdose at her home on Tuesday. https://t.co/gpNJuUVlMz https://t.co/0hsyB3ssmD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Web Developer: Headquartered in Dublin, Ohio, Cardinal Health, Inc. (NYSE: CAH) is a global, integrated healthcare services and products company connecting patients, providers, payers, pharmacists and manufacturers for integrated care… https://t.co/rUHCWHRxar https://t.co/v51We2qC00]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Family rushes to find missing children, great-grandmother as deadly Northern California wildfire grows: A frantic search is underway for woman and two young children who went missing this week as a deadly wildfire reached the Northern California city of… https://t.co/frFH4Drrx9 https://t.co/S6f4PYa1wV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consultant, Business Intelligence: What Business Intelligence contributes to Cardinal Health Business Intelligence is responsible for applying business process knowledge and data analytics to develop, recommend and communicate timely, accurate, relevant,… https://t.co/LqmwduytoO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Julian Assange looks for deal to end 'diplomatic isolation': Julian Assange's possibly imminent departure from the Ecuadorian embassy begs the question: what will happen to the WIkiLeak's founder when he does walk out? https://t.co/klZ9tAnf3m https://t.co/HkUwEWw9NK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[User Experience Designer Advanced – Milford, OH: **User Experience Designer Advanced – Milford, OH** Locations:Milford, Ohio Job Family: Research &amp; Development New Search Apply English (US) **Job Description** **Division:** Digital Factory **Business… https://t.co/Yv0KO2dZPP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – AECOM Hunt: AECOM is actively seeking a highly talented Project Manager for immediate employment for a project in Canton, OH. Provides overall management administration to project and assists in establishing project specific objectives… https://t.co/RELQ1afbjL https://t.co/DwfUVarEsJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps-JAVA: DevOps-JAVA Ref No.: 18-31422 Location: Independence, Ohio Location – Independence, OH Full time Max 110K base Only GC/USC/EAD – H4 or L2 Skills: – Core: 5+ Years of Experience in Java Development experience – DevOps: 3+ Years of Experience… https://t.co/hMet6GvmHK https://t.co/wIW88tNRft]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Application Developer: Exodus Integrity Services, Inc is a rapidly expanding technology company headquartered in Northeast Ohio. EIS provides quality services to our clients by instilling honesty, commitment, and hard work to find the most qualified… https://t.co/j16RP4vT6A https://t.co/65fGNG3DJa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2018 is on pace to be the 4th-hottest year on record: Sunburned? You're not the only one. https://t.co/RzM5OVVjaQ https://t.co/ZJWxL1QZZU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NTSB report: Captain of duck boat said he checked weather radar before departing: The man who steered a duck boat on a Missouri lake as a thunderstorm approached is heard on video earlier as saying he checked weather radar before the two-man crew set out… https://t.co/eLesU2YwOX https://t.co/e2Vlq80fYO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US and allies looking at options to protect shipping lanes from Iranian threats: As tensions between the US and Iran ratchet up, the Trump administration is looking at what military options may be needed to keep vital waterways in the Middle East open in… https://t.co/SEWlmbcTEC https://t.co/n6IZM6e33d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior/Lead System Administrator: Location US-OH-Cincinnati Posted Date 3 days ago(6/29/2018 11:44 AM) Job ID 23766 # Positions 1 Category Technology Position Type Full Time Overview Be Here. Be Great. Working for a leader in the insurance industry means… https://t.co/tvDbFZuZx2 https://t.co/nnUrzaOOPF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mystified friends recall slain Houston doctor as warm, hard-working and unpretentious: A week after an unknown cyclist shot Houston doctor Mark Hausknecht, friends remained mystified as to why anyone would harm the warm and hard-working man they knew. https://t.co/ZYOcuiu1wn https://t.co/cvSVUOB8uR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump sought Israel's help to free American pastor in Turkey, officials say: The US President asked Israeli Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu to assist in the release of an American pastor detained in Turkey, Israeli and US officials tell CNN. https://t.co/HgbZsdxd8Q https://t.co/RJx88Yusop]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data analyst: Job TitleData analyst – ID:31412 Duration3 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsSAS, SQL, PL/SQL LocationHilliard, OH Date Posted04/05/2018 Our client, a Fortune 50, global telecommunications company is looking for Data analyst to join their… https://t.co/PZKR1maC3o https://t.co/l3y6AHjqPI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BP is going big on American shale: BP announced Friday it is spending $10.5 billion to buy several high-prized oil assets in the United States. https://t.co/UmuLJmzpvo https://t.co/hx7N5pGSUg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mobile QA Tester/Team Coordinator: Mobile QA Tester/Team Coordinator Ref No.: 18-28098 Location: Cincinnati, Ohio Mobile QA Tester/Team Coordinator – There is a need for an on-site mobile tester/coordinator to perform testing in an agile environment and… https://t.co/AYGacLyYhD https://t.co/bWkEgYYgxL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP BASIS non-HANA: SAP BASIS non-HANA Ref No.: 18-30214 Location: Johnston City, Illinois Job title: SAP BASIS – Non-HANA Location: Johnston City, IL Duration: 12 months. Strong ECC conceptual knowledge and hands on experience. Good AS ABAP and AS JAVA… https://t.co/UgElXDoaLh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 things for July 27: Russia probe, North Korea, family reunions, Pakistan, Facebook: Here's what else you need to know to Get Up to Speed and Out the Door. https://t.co/TW1yrmfUtr https://t.co/dPaX7YFp2t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Khan waits for confirmation of victory in election tainted by rigging claims: Pakistan's election commission is expected to confirm former cricket star Imran Khan's victory Friday after polls marred by widespread allegations of vote rigging. https://t.co/fUT9fKTo5s https://t.co/aj6GP9oFSP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Representative Tier I: Windstream is seeking entry level Specialist’s for Tier I Repair. Our Specialist will assist Windstream Broadband Internet customers with troubleshooting and incident creation to resolve customer trouble. In this… https://t.co/8LzoraUNvl https://t.co/ZJ3ZOa5GzZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook removes four videos on pages operated by Alex Jones and InfoWars: Facebook removed four videos on pages maintained by InfoWars and its founder, Alex Jones, a spokesperson for the social media company said Thursday night. https://t.co/AGVYyb84Sl https://t.co/2CoeID1Sgc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cohen claims Trump knew in advance of 2016 Trump Tower meeting: Michael Cohen, President Donald Trump's former personal attorney, claims that then-candidate Trump knew in advance about the June 2016 meeting in Trump Tower in which Russians were expected… https://t.co/3KUCbOUn1g https://t.co/YKJD6OyeX4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats pitch plan to reauthorize Violence Against Women Act: Democrats turned the spotlight on the expiring Violence Against Women Act on Thursday, introducing their own bill to reauthorize the legislation for another five years. https://t.co/FwtU6ZHWPA https://t.co/1s1jaH0cxa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mercedes-Benz is trying to get cheap luxury cars right: The Mercedes-Benz A-class has the difficult job of inviting new customers to the world of luxury cars. https://t.co/Sl5lRASb8Q https://t.co/rbrTGc8Lqx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RadioShack is back. Kinda: The 97-year-old brand is being reborn. https://t.co/zSjyesJFl4 https://t.co/SfITTkmsjO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Commercial Network Security Project Engineer: Sr Commercial Network &amp; Security Project Engineer Business Group Global Sales &amp; Marketing No. of Positions 1 Requisition Number 77739BR Job Category Engineering and Technicians Position Type Full Time… https://t.co/NnAP12di4D https://t.co/JW5pBSloOs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beyoncé posts new photo of twins: A year after she debuted a look at her newborn twins, Beyoncé has shared a new photo of the toddlers. https://t.co/xbc6WMN39E https://t.co/K6chXGZglh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lexi Thompson withdraws from British Open to 'recharge mental batteries': American golf star Lexi Thompson has withdrawn from next week's British Open, revealing that the last 18 months have taken a "tremendous toll" on her wellbeing. https://t.co/PCM2YktuYr https://t.co/7aev5QFd97]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps: DevOps (Cloud) System Engineer, Willis Towers Watson Job #*******P, Buffalo, NY Menu ToggleMenu Hide – Glassdoor – Linkedin – Twitter – Facebook – English – Espaol – Franais (FR) – Franais (CA) – Join Our Talent Network – English English en –… https://t.co/Jxo41Wkqlv https://t.co/YeAlz8TA77]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Mat Fraser overcame injury to become the 'Fittest Man on Earth': Forget soccer rivals Cristiano Ronaldo and Lionel Messi. In CrossFit, there's Mat Fraser and Mat Fraser. Alone atop his sport -- even through an injury. https://t.co/rUyG6fQcVZ https://t.co/LGhCOeVQQV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NodeJS Developer: NodeJS Developer Ref No.: 18-31270 Location: Cincinnati, Ohio Integration of data storage solutions {{may include databases, key-value stores, blob stores, etc.}} Strong proficiency with JavaScript {{or CoffeeScript depending on your… https://t.co/BKeAQ4fYum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Developer (EyeMed): Sr Developer (EyeMed) – ABOUT US – Company – Business Model – Eyewear Brands – Retail Brands – OneSight – Luxottica Factor – FEATURED JOBS – Design and Product Innovation Jobs – Global Functions – Operations Jobs – Wholesale Jobs –… https://t.co/TBXjk65c8d https://t.co/sENUAomA3B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon is primed for rapid growth: Amazon reports its second quarter results after the bell on Thursday. Analysts expect business to keep booming thanks to Prime, cloud computing and advertising. https://t.co/sFfxGjfhCi https://t.co/9flfFFjAgs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Software Developer Job in US – OH – Wickliffe for Precision Castparts Corp. | Information Technology Software Developer US – OH – Wickliffe Search Other Jobs search again Job Attributes Job Id 17109 Req. Id 317 Req. Code ******.2… https://t.co/mtVSp9HPBb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emails: Trump officials wanted citizenship question on 2020 census shortly after taking office: Newly released emails from Trump administration officials show a desire to add a question on citizenship to the 2020 census shortly after President Donald… https://t.co/vb8wzFk1hY https://t.co/iygSfKCU01]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>