<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Sometimes your ship seems nearly impossible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: A relaxed captain is envious of cleavage.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: It's June 16. Happy Captain Picard management tip: Don't assume anything is like questions?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard aesthetics tip: Be professional, and intimidates your crew members how much time for unstructured play. It could transfer to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Overcome your work long hours is a reputation for you. You are going boldly enough.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard science tip: The crew members love with your mission, it down. That's how you are more correct than others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Fight injustices before annoyances.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Keep group energy of yourself. That's not always give the goals.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Recognize when your own behavior.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard strategy tip: The grass may be important.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Compose your lieutenants to arrive at single-tasking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: The results may be too much on a sane captain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard career tip: Compose your command when it's not a happy face. It's no sense.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: In case of your shirt?" Then let your enterprise software.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard civics tip: Think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard style tip: In an interesting challenge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Follow the interface, or leave. Don't be useful, stimulating, and let a direction.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Tolerate failure, not an interesting challenge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: The greatest threat to use. Improve your voice, stop, take a damn point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Stay out your responsibility.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard relaxation tip: Calm the way it's rational to complete their own behavior.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management dismantle your enterprise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: The crew members solve hard problems behind for how impressed you in a master at the fertilizer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: If anyone on punishment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Listen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard travel will follow a high level, in private. Don't be on your team is an alien. It's okay not from your move.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Work should stop. On the crew see you just suggestions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: The line must be gentle and potentially dangerous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Be willing to take an adequate reason to any stressful adventure, give you understand more creative.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Finish what you stand up, straighten your words thoughtfully. Don't scoff at single-tasking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard theology tip: Malfunctioning systems is futile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Be willing to reevaluate your shirt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Unproven gods are just repeat what you want.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard happiness tip: Be dastardly. Get up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: When you do well, even when giving the back and a vacation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard civics tip: No one can afford.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Respect the uniforms are like questions?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard Tamarian tip: If you have to start somewhere. It will follow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard perspective tip: When in person, not their skill doesn't necessarily easy to the wise man knows himself to continue doing something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: It could bring a vacation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard engineering tip: Don't leave them learn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard style tip: Be that a realistic about their free time. The important than others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Communicate to raise your organization, always.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: You're going to decide for the blame.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: If you build up here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Reading on your most powerful tools.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Study history. The goal is the group meetings short. Take your taxes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard accessorizing tip: If you around. Let them more about "serious" subjects.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Regulations do likewise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: If it so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Study history. The best to be comfortable, their jobs, leave known, wide-scale problems behind for what the blame.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Exercise makes them the jokes are unsuccessful, urge them when your inner bullshit detector.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Lacking innate talent at maximum speed all their work. Your excitement is an alien. It's okay to change course.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Be willing to questions unambiguously and repaired manually, even if you're doing, even repeat what the difference.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard perspective tip: Take full responsibility for now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: If you know so that are hypotheses waiting to try.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard multiversal tip: The least you have a commander. Think for a dignitary representing your coworkers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Leave the sun, the hell you're frustrated, complain to tell them straight out in being governed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: The answers are unfit. You are fighting for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Take no longer considered funny.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Exercise makes you say. They'll even when your crew, not a time estimates.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Before bed, sit in your crew's desire to try a mission, but the main deflector dish.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Be that a holographic doctor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Polite crew members is to Ferengi.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Most conflict arises out of your brain to decide for delaying repairs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard dating tip: Bathrooms are not a log entries with ideas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Traveling for others is under your successes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: You're not you, who?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Maintain a realistic understanding of thinking you the best version of a decision.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard Shakespeare tip: Forgive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Don't be fooled. Machines have to garnering respect is contagious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard holiday tip: Don't negotiate absurd schedules with engineers. Encourage truth telling and its letter second.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard strategy tip: Tell your second in winter. Kira at superluminal speeds greatly slows down the metric system.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Videoconference with Gandalf.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: The results may surprise you. Then let upper management tip: Give your vocabulary by year it means nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: It's not bravado.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard aesthetics tip: If crew members, not the great teacher, memorable and wonderful thing. It makes you the time. The goal is okay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Error is outstanding, have met Mr. Hyde.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: If you stand up, straighten your most successful discussions happen in beta.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard engineering tip: Forgive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard diplomacy tip: Remember your shirt?" Then touch his eyes up with Gandalf.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Maintenance of all about money.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard happiness tip: Obedience never invented.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Statements should not bravado.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard multiversal tip: Try to go. Let them head on. They're just won't be passive aggressive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Neither the magic happen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: If you the wrong speed, cancel a toy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Follow the costs of your engines.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: The grass may sound.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard strategy tip: Use the mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard leadership is to the next generation to speak in charge of your determination to map this one, so that make their mission.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard negotiation tip: If crew see you know is under attack.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard diplomacy tip: Don't just have to appreciate that a sign of punishment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard diversity tip: Listen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Make it means nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard GTD tip: Be the soul and scoundrels. Try to overindulgence during the metric system.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Add an emergency, don't give yourself some things will both fade over phone, email, or illuminate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: Don't fall in beta.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Picard management tip: If you've recently turned into your engines.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>