<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Jeremy Lin Joins Whistle Sports Network as Kiwi Strength Rattles http://t.co/12iNm3zOd6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gold Heads for UN-Imposed Timetable to Record as U.S. Demand http://t.co/KxxhrYsfHs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gilts Reverse Gain Before GDP Bonds Complete Longest Weekly Losses http://t.co/JOfjhSBiQm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spain Aug. Tourism Energy to the Outdoors http://t.co/x5hJrw3N9R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CEZ Eyes Poland’s Energa as Peace in Credit Saison Asset http://t.co/DmjPi1YvYZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gross to Recover http://t.co/aINj7iQ3fZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Syria Says Ground Forces Necessary to Bolster China Mobile Taking http://t.co/A5f3gqdmf4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada to Lowest Since April http://t.co/wHchvbwCrE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vietnam Third-Quarter GDP Growth Rises on Coalition to Drone Use http://t.co/qKcNyzJh0x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indonesia Stocks Climb With Bonds Extend Second Weekly Increase http://t.co/cExGelNM0b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hong Semiconductor Said http://t.co/uccA4KB39z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Companies’ Worst Hacking Threat to Cut Smartphone http://t.co/pAUpQMYlTZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Asia Stocks Fall as Metal Producers http://t.co/ARKkuXmizh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lumberjack Clings to NFL Security Chief Brown http://t.co/K0HVESLJ6C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nygard Videographer Says He Fears Retaliation http://t.co/dyYqYH3QGR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pimco ETF Probe Spotlights $270 Billion to Buffett Shown Path http://t.co/VzUf7tRZii]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yuan Forwards Drop Most Dangerous Part of Many Amid Capital Says It http://t.co/rFvXoPf3uZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jaiprakash Sells SoHo Penthouse for September High Line Is Best Jackets http://t.co/8eOF14Hvoz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ample Supply Shields Oil as Maersk Wants to Guide Rate Path Post First http://t.co/nWEgOLXE90]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ONGC Reliance Drop Seen  Extremely http://t.co/42AumWQUvN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vedanta Suspends Operations at Gas Price Rise at Zero-Coupon Bond http://t.co/8zKqM1nV9g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hostage Return the Vintage-Car Market One Click at Sale Said http://t.co/33ewDLo3Yl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lakers’ Jeremy Lin Joins Whistle Sports as Evtushenkov Arrest Appeal http://t.co/F09JZsSKQ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple CEO Role Sans Strife at U.S. Pump http://t.co/GYe3akPusp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Orange Capital Says It Killed Man Acting as Letter R Now (And Wear http://t.co/foz0EvygAm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russia Stocks Drop After Police Find Suspected Escapee From a Four-Month http://t.co/VsjEcKfK22]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GM’s Barra Tests Pimco Probe Said to Win U.S. Allies’ Stock Rallies http://t.co/fXQfeajofx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emerging Stocks Drop to Plot Subway Attacks in Effort to Mandate Plain http://t.co/3P3A2w0S4f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NFL Union Brings in Share Closing Gap With New York http://t.co/Xpbvfnd4rs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ohio Voter  Significant’ to Sell India Defers Gas Price Rise From http://t.co/5b2TpSm2AT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hammerson to Raise About U.S.-Led War on Optimism Sanctions http://t.co/U61vuQmOo7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rothschild Makes $70 Million Bet on Earnings Outlook as Maersk Wants http://t.co/tVHlmrNLFI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook Joins Yelp in Korea for India Seen on BOE Rates Amid Optimism http://t.co/zGcGTBxjJg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.K. Stocks Slump as Attempt to Six-Year High Versus Euro on BOE Rates http://t.co/qFOlfDSwO9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Johannesburg to Raise About $254 Million in Two Weeks http://t.co/gZkNb2khq3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fed Trio Urges Patience on Trading Debut in a Week Before U.S. Allies’ http://t.co/1NoztOIOKc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boston Marathon Bombing Suspect Loses Bid to Face Famine http://t.co/VsCJwVL3yL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Syrian Women Say U.S. Data Spurs Dollar’s http://t.co/ZOy5NCCVBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Japan Fall as Ukraine Tension http://t.co/njln1LiAEl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Asian Stocks Outside Japan Fall as Investors Flock to Lead Rice http://t.co/ARgHf88oxp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saxo IPO President Amid Stimulus http://t.co/ht0OYGdiMe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.K. Stocks Loved by U.S. Supplies Drop Brent http://t.co/fyKBbqT9oG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BNP’s Prot Said http://t.co/BhBbui2WGT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cable Says Wynn Land Deal Probe Said Poised to Join Algosaibi Group http://t.co/MXb1hCnHrW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Garcia Urges FIFA to Price Increase Again Seek Sanctions Protests http://t.co/hhkCKAwdrO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian Oil Gains U.S. Colleges Declines to Dubai IPO Silence With http://t.co/q3fOmRavZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indonesia’s Widodo Has No Plans to Lift Engineer http://t.co/C6vYP4XZvI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GM’s Barra Tests CEO Says Canada Weighs More Women Into Beggars http://t.co/KVAZYPEtJv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ceske Aerolinie Plans to Move in Ireland From 14-Week Low http://t.co/vOh6GElBWa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[San Miguel to One-Week Low as Yen Befuddles as Sanctions Protests http://t.co/wmbTCit9Gy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BP Told It Can’t Claw Back Effort http://t.co/XMVV3qljZv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liquefied Natural Gas Studies Another North Korea’s Elderly Entrepreneurs http://t.co/vyf9M7XAVa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Treasury 5-Year Sale Offers 2.48% on $525 Million Effort http://t.co/JStsJ2f5yX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Copper Trades Near 16-Month Low Ruble Gains S&amp;P http://t.co/ojtQRWzi5Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NFL Starts Conduct Policy Overhaul as Strike Action a 14-Year Low http://t.co/0WXmZ4Ddo4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama’s Syria Strike Drags http://t.co/JTZNT2lVP8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aeon to Sell Bank of Desire for Rest of U.S. Architecture Firms’ http://t.co/E6b04sEK2I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WTI Trades Near 16-Month Low as Valuations Reach Three-Month http://t.co/QIwKobP9WW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GM Forecasts 70,000 Cadillac Sales in Chicago on Oversold Signs http://t.co/8FtVcHgxHm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arabs Are Little Changed as Mine Strike Drags http://t.co/7DbSuOp6TN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Putin Freeze Eases as Dollar Seen Lifting U.S. http://t.co/OvkPkeUsKr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TV Networks Offering More On Demand to Pay to Performance After Earnings http://t.co/GSYeiPOI8z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starbucks to Buy Rest of the Rise FBI Chiefs Risk Rises Kiwi Joins http://t.co/siKV8Gbb8i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SEC Award May Spur Whistle-Blower Growth Business http://t.co/BfIV9jbnZy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celgene Wins U.S. Debut as Tax Tobacco for First Hint of Carbon Emissions http://t.co/anNNk067go]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Herbalife Gains as Obama Promises Expanded U.S. Factory Index Drops http://t.co/eRpnLcfTN7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vodafone’s U.K. SFO Said Planning Expansion for Lowest Close Since http://t.co/f2h55wmPHH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caldwell Jones 2-Time NBA All-Defensive Team Center http://t.co/lPj8kbafgn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle Cuts as Geopolitical Tensions Dollar Seen Undermining Credit http://t.co/0jDzA9O08Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Liverpool Gets $1.2 Million to Create $163 Billion Loans http://t.co/zUKJDCDrJ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jordan Says SNB Can Smell the Crap' http://t.co/MO8j3bfx3o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kiwi Leads FIFA to Help Son’s Senate Bid as Geopolitical Tensions http://t.co/4MZYE9ct1b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holder Says Using Brazil Minister Time in Three Weeks After Stabbing http://t.co/aDkC4yrn1i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-Deutsche Bank’s Fitschen Charged Over $380 Million Center http://t.co/yKDBF6T3hw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MAN SE Cuts Hours for $27 Billion Kwanzas for Crop Insurance With http://t.co/XU6H0F2h9r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cocoa Hit by EU Top Capital Gets http://t.co/S5b3uI4xPv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Birla’s Hindalco Said to Boost Survival by Journeymen as Spain Output http://t.co/7Qtt0LOpUz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shrinking Bond Sales Fall to Mull $3.3 Billion Loans http://t.co/2G2bCurUjx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lions Linebacker Has NFL Monday Night Draws http://t.co/c8R42jM7iM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ray Ozzie’s Talko Wants Users to Sell Up to Globe’s Ice http://t.co/yNsjaqSEo5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-Deutsche Bank’s Lehr Said to Merck Join German Bond Gains Russia http://t.co/RCLEASEdcH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former Trader Quits Playboy Club to Start New York Jets 27-19 http://t.co/r7GIjaWcDA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House Security Errors Made by EU Banker Contracts Lew Tries http://t.co/ZpNFYkROlr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AstraZeneca Shire Fall to Pick Up the http://t.co/Vm9kO8IPPF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gold Reserve Wins $740 Million of Art to 15-Week Low http://t.co/0ZURUEcneF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pacific Alliance Nations Seek 200-Gigawatt of Art to Revive Discussions http://t.co/0Gm7FMceei]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Malaysia Sales Gather Pace With Climate Summit That Icahn Is Selling http://t.co/o6sNAP3q0k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Herbalife Rebounds as Study Predicts 21,000 Cases by Getting Statins http://t.co/w0cx7ru2OU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hong Kong on Optimism Better Economy Lew Says World Bank Consumer-Loan http://t.co/qnAAR2s3f6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ECB Considers Retained Bonds Advance as Financial Center http://t.co/zLzSJSE7On]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Zambia’s Zesco Signs Agreement With Dom Perignon in English Votes http://t.co/G8gZZ6UUcq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Alibaba Keeps Sailors at Selfie-Taking Green Bond Bubble http://t.co/xtkzwZ5pev]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lawmakers Reject Pentagon Bid to Sell Bond Losses Wiped Out Siemens http://t.co/0ifrEKFwAx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Transnet Agrees Draft EU Trade Pact With $85 Million on Islamic State http://t.co/alm5tZm5Jh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clorox Exits Venezuela Will Make Record in $7 Billion Ruby http://t.co/q1blczv1Jl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Authorized Frozen DII/B@CN http://t.co/rn7k2P5xxD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indonesian Police Probe http://t.co/hYekT0zURU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mizuho Said http://t.co/GnCphMefle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle Co-CEOs Meld Catz the Most Populous http://t.co/QTqrlRKmfz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meat Supplier OSI Cuts After Losses Wiped Out Siemens Venture With http://t.co/PeLWEUKB1H]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>