<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Adorable Fleece Baby Carrier Cover!  http://t.co/oR6hmWIZR4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't concentrate in flats! - Victoria Beckham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Domestic Adoption - A Helping Hand To A New Life  http://t.co/hOK8qOesa1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to that hilarious sit-com Three’s Company - http://t.co/RmK1tckjN6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Ab Carver Pro is very very cool...  http://t.co/WfcQvwjz4D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's one small step for [a] man; one giant leap for mankind. - Neil A. Armstrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spock, where the hell's the power you promised?" - Kirk  "One damn minute, admiral" - Spock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never expected to be anybody important.  - Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest thing in this world is not so much where we stand, as in what direction we are moving. - Oliver Wendall Holmes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Organizing Garage Cabinets and Storage  http://t.co/NMgQZqIQ6P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People who enjoy what they are doing invariably do it well. - Joe Gibbs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How much do you weigh? "Well, according to the charts, I should be six inches taller."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The next time you hear a social media myth, question it.  Ask for the proof, and ask out loud.  Don Zarrella - Social Media Scientist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Card playing is no more expensive than any other game where you hold hands.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's easier to ask forgiveness than it is to get permission - Grace Hopper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have never felt in tune with the whole rock industry.  - Robert Wyatt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Heineken International  http://t.co/7T8sIlM8OS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The trick is to stop thinking of it as your money - IRS auditor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you can look in the mirror and smile at what you see, then there's hope for you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The purity of a person's heart can be quickly measured by how they regard animals - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of B.B. King  http://t.co/74sMZkKif8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys - combine your wallet and smart phone in one compact case - and its cool and stylish - Book Book http://t.co/ok9jjXdGf0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fish Hotel Aquarium - Jazz Up Your Office! http://t.co/QIJf7Oahru]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I always wear size 14 boat shoes that are so old they could have been built by Noah. Jarod Kintz, Gosh, I probably shouldn't publish this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Staple Singers  http://t.co/szxNpxiVpq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This episode was BADLY written! - Gwen, Galaxy Quest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome running t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the running lovers in your life!  http://t.co/mX6gOocjEy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your Business Guide for Small Business Internet Marketing  http://t.co/QSTi2e40GO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great History of the Rolling Stones  http://t.co/zHx32fhGTu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've destroyed my feet completely but I don't care. What do you really need your feet for anyway - Sarah Jessica Parker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn Baseball Lingo  http://t.co/fCMpbiQ9a5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The difference between gossip and news is whether you hear it or tell it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Design is a constant challenge to balance comfort with luxe, the practical with the desirable. - Donna Karan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Chordettes  http://t.co/V4VlBpDLjG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of In-N-Out Burger  http://t.co/GxMPE6WZZd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't pay good wages because I have a lot of money; I have a lot of money because I pay good wages. - Robert Bosch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guns Don't Kill People, Dads With Pretty Daughters Kill People http://t.co/DRaH7NPnAl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I take a dim view of watching my own destruction. - Jack, "Invasion of the Body Snatchers"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My little friend that I only I can see is wanting me to warn you that he thinks you have serious mental problems He He He!!  :&gt;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Cool History of Science Fiction  http://t.co/iPfwm0hTDB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Corona Beer  http://t.co/JC166ixpMf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take care of your body. It's the only place you have to live. - Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The man who can drive himself further once the effort gets painful is the man who will win. - Roger Bannister]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The process of growing old is a question of mind over matter. If you don't mind, it doesn't matter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone can steer the ship when the sea is calm. - Publilius Syrus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious Zombie Family Car Stickers - http://t.co/dadOiJtADv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding the Right Fitness Gadgets for Better Health http://t.co/uzvaQG6gMo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new source of power is not money in the hands of a few, but information in the hands of many. - John Naisbitt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A successful man is one who can lay a firm foundation with the bricks others have thrown at him... David Brinkley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Far Out and Super Cool Watches  http://t.co/ysNnjZswOW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Uriah Heep  http://t.co/r7GGq8FjDR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Arthur Alexander the Unknown Artist  http://t.co/qCmHIaGBSn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding a way to live a simple life is today's complicated problem!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prayer doesn't change things, it changes people and they change things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys - combine your wallet and smart phone in one compact case - and its cool and stylish - Book Book http://t.co/AEgcx5LUqn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Simplicity is the ultimate sophistication. - Leonardo da Vinci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once burned a lesson is learned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The law gives a man the right to open his wife's mail, but not the nerve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Son, a father told his growing boy, "just remember on thing:  I know a lot more about being young than you do about being old."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 14 - Doctor Decides to Discontinue IV Treatment  http://t.co/4dvdJKJLP3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Until one has loved an animal,  a part of one's soul remains unawakened. - Anatole France]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How to Create an Effective Company Blog  http://t.co/CTaARgC22T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Real education must ultimately be limited to men who insist on knowing, the rest is mere sheep-herding. - Ezra Pound]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy Cow!  Harry Caray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our work is the presentation of our capabilities. - Johann Wolfgang Von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read How Customer Connects Mount-Up with Social Media Sites  http://t.co/wCOPYcQqzw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the The Burning Bridge by John Flanagan  http://t.co/swhOQLUKM5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Battleship Memorial Park – Mobile Alabama – A Great Historical Experience  http://t.co/B6K2FhdTt3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Isley Brothers  http://t.co/C6vAI6Ns49]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Life? Cool! Where can I download one of those?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good teaching is one-fourth preparation and three-fourths pure theatre. - Gail Godwin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating Introduction to Tom's Shoes Company  http://t.co/yEq5lZ7MDC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never wear the same shoe twice. - Dion Sanders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Magic texting glove with conductive yarn finger tips for iPhone, iPad and all touch screen devices - 4 colors  --&gt; http://t.co/5uqySJkTL8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be Prepared!  Learn About these Bartering Resources  http://t.co/v8OAygbZ3p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips for Using Facebook Pages for Your Business  http://t.co/oetbleMO9J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It just seems to happen that by the time most of us get a little money to burn,  "the fire goes out."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The easiest way to stay out of hot water is to keep a cool head]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Who  http://t.co/FGy4Qpiyna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any fact facing us is not as important as our attitude toward it, for that determines our success or failure. - Norman Vincent Peale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow the whiskey.  - Kid Rock, who arrived with "Redneck Woman" singer Gretchen Wilson, on his plans after the Country Music Awards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space Invaders Taito Astronaut Video Game T-Shirt Tee  http://t.co/inmkzAepkX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The Music of L.T.D.  http://t.co/MjZjbyP5Sa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overview of Social Bookmarking Sites  http://t.co/mrxnhR7fKi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's hard to win a pennant, but it's harder losing one. - Chuck Tanner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't tell you what I had for breakfast, but I can sing every single word of rock and roll. - Patty Duke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the hot new Minecraft video channel Crimson Mine - http://t.co/4C3czSTeTs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then there was the crooked crematory operator who sold the ashes to cannibals as instant people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't buy a nice car and get rich you get rich and buy a nice car - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Overview of Major Web Conferencing Services  http://t.co/SwJnH3S0KJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why worry about death, it'll come sooner or later. - Jim Dunn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most serious mistakes are not being made as a result of wrong answers. The truly dangerous thing is asking the wrong question P Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seniors Gain from Social Networking Technology  http://t.co/lr3AY1Z1uJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Ride - La Vibora at Six Flags Over Texas in Arlington  http://t.co/BXNIaXGUDq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The glass is neither half-full nor half-empty: it's twice as big as it needs to be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The entrepreneur always searches for change, responds to it, and exploits it as an opportunity. - Peter F. Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Kool and the Gang  http://t.co/DpbN82ysIk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harness The Power of Twitter for Business to Business Internet Marketing  http://t.co/P6srx5ZhwJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 8 - North Texas Lyme Support Group  http://t.co/NzSaAesfdt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Benefits of iPads for Seniors  http://t.co/nmVcZrFAFg]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>