<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[We (San Francisco) have football weather during baseball season, and baseball weather during football season. - Herb Caen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Don Henley  http://t.co/qdgdxQSkX0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never go to a movie in Poland, you'll end up setting behind a Pole.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where everything is possible miracles become common place, but the familiar ceases to be self-evident. - Eric Hoffer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How To Find The Right Gluten Free Foods  http://t.co/cFOnDJNUKJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wasn't satisfied just to earn a good living. I was looking to make a statement. - Donald Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Buffalo Springfield  http://t.co/16CfqVE04L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automatic rotating laser light that provides hours of fun for your feline and canine friends - Keep the cat happy!  http://t.co/DHsJg72LfN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Top 10 Asian Beers  http://t.co/TKvXidL4RT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Canada - Just Across the border and Beautiful! http://t.co/prn4SPmKqI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Very Interesting History of Shoe Sizes  http://t.co/UlWJNqskLQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Chiffons   http://t.co/Vhl94PdEJV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, where's the Cannes Film Festival being held this year?  Christina Aguilera]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys, that Chinese dude is going to get pretty crispy out here. How long are you going to keep him tied down like that? Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You cannot dream yourself into a character: you must hammer and forge yourself into one. - Henry D. Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very "COOL" Titanic Ice Cube mold - http://t.co/zXBOnMfDNv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LinkedIn Used Effectively Helps Companies to Grow  http://t.co/GrfzMf8Qbx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The internet has turned what used to be a controlled, one-way message into a real-time dialogue with millions - Danniel Sacks, Fast Company]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't do fashion. I am fashion. - Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Colonize Mars: Can This Dream Become a Reality?  http://t.co/cta2tlJdIK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going Mountain Climbing? - Equipment Advice  http://t.co/YXlms7gfCz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow these Steps to Clean Your Credit  http://t.co/4rR0AqtVCs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is more than a game to me, it's a religion. - Bill Klem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow the whiskey.  - Kid Rock, who arrived with "Redneck Woman" singer Gretchen Wilson, on his plans after the Country Music Awards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Search Engine Optimization (SEO) to Drive Traffic to Your Website  http://t.co/ZFrkKn4iBl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is not the filling of a pail, but the lighting of a fire. - William Butler Yeats]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to Robert A. Heinlein  http://t.co/ctGaset2DY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What --  is the air-speed velocity of an unladen swallow? - Bridgekeeper, Monty Python and the Holy Grail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It isn't the mountains ahead to climb that wear you out; it's the pebble in your shoe. - Muhammad Ali]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding the Right Fitness Gadgets for Better Health http://t.co/AxB1SGe7rU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bird does not sing because it has an answer...  It sings because it has a song. - Chinese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoot your co-workers with this Miniature Ballista Kit - Wooden Desktop Warfare Ballista - ROFL -  http://t.co/6C6UZwE4VA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You gotta love that - an aquarium coffee table!  Drink with the fishes! http://t.co/CRpjfG9jrC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would you say I have a plethora of pinatas? - El Guapo, ¡Three Amigos!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If man is a little lower than angels, then angels should reform.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Janis Joplin  http://t.co/EHK3GtF9K3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have not failed. I've just found 10,000 ways that won't work - Thomas Alva Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Redrum. -  Danny, The Shining]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Try not. Do, or do not. There is no try. - Yoda, The Empire Strikes Back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sovereign invigorator of the body is exercise, and of all the exercises walking is the best. - Thomas Jefferson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the The History of the Chambers Brothers  http://t.co/NpdNKSAzCY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is what happens to you when you're busy making other plans - John Lennon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Highland Village, Texas  http://t.co/83dXWjkgSa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Leapy Lee the Classic Rock Artist?  http://t.co/L5PyIXYY9b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A respectable appearance is sufficient to make people more interested in your soul --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you don't do what's best for your body, you're the one who comes up on the short end. - Julius Erving]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If there are kids who want to follow in my footsteps, I'd say that my shoes are 2 big for them to! Their shoe size is perfect. Q. Latifah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your visit has climaxed an already dull day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The History of Rolex Watches – The Start of Something Great  http://t.co/MZuF545yMc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I did not have three thousand pairs of shoes, I had one thousand and sixty. - Imelda Marcos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The road to success is dotted with many tempting parking places. - Unknown Author]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Utilize Strategy Consulting Firms: Gain a Competitive Advantage  http://t.co/dffQQB6Q3I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the Icebound Land by John Flanagan  http://t.co/GjWdKlsjJQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be successful, you have to have your heart in your business, and your business in your heart. - Thomas Watson, Sr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must remain focused on your journey to greatness. - Les Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Who is The Grass Roots Classic Rock Group?  http://t.co/RFH5ZxIRiK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's only during an eclipse that the Man in the Moon has a place in the sun. Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Link Building With Social Media Sites  http://t.co/o4EnHy8mjO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is the opposite of the weather. Nobody talks about it, but everybody does something about it. - Rebecca Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes are the quickest way for women to achieve instant metamorphosis - Manolo Blahnik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome basketball t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the basketball lovers in your life!   http://t.co/n2CtkQISu0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may be dumb, but I'm not stupid.  Terry Bradshaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't think and hit at the same time. - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I find your lack of faith disturbing. - Darth Vader, Star Wars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I'm hungry, I eat. When I'm thirsty, I drink. When I feel like saying something, I say it. Madonna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Foreigner  http://t.co/rUtsVLkmn8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Great Book - The Majestic Tree of Life  http://t.co/nLtB6SQHnC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Marvin Gaye  http://t.co/nuPufDOeKg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I accidentally forgot to graduate from college.  - Anne Lamott]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here Kitty Kitty Kitty! - Tony Stewart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If my uniform doesn't get dirty, I haven't done anything in the baseball game - Rickey Henderson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can tell whether a man is clever by his answers. You can tell whether a man is wise by his questions —&gt; Naguib Mahfouz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like wrestling a gorilla- you don't quit when you're tired, you quit when the gorilla is tired - Robert Strauss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So say we all. - Battlestar Galactica]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most games are lost, not won! - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love cats because I enjoy my home; and little by little, they become its visible soul. - Jean Cocteau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Great Resort in Palm Coast Florida  http://t.co/xBb30Kx5pn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1f u c4n r34d th1s u r34lly n33d t0 g37 l41d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can say any foolish thing to a dog, &amp; the dog will give a look that says, My God youre right I never wouldve thought of that! Dave Barry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are no oaths that make many perjurers as the vows of love]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think MTV should consider using subtitles. Half the time, even I can't understand what the **** I'm talking about.  Ozzy Osbourne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the History Of Pac-Man  http://t.co/dncPeOOYqG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sign on a greenhouse: Fresh flowers just out of bed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its better to own the racecourse then the race horse - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Star Trek Enterprise Pizza Cutter! http://t.co/xJz2ewpRg4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 6 - Follow-up Appointment  http://t.co/biap3DVft3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of White Castle  http://t.co/B3z5uRgfKm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About GPS Technology and Fitness Watches  http://t.co/2VXuwMvQof]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have a very striking face. How many times were you struck there?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Samsung Galaxy Gear Watch  http://t.co/7Aq3aWmgx0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the Hillbilly 10 Commandments ROFL - http://t.co/vCVQcXegAs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Search Engine Optimization (SEO) to Drive Traffic to Your Website  http://t.co/ZFrkKmdvd9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Uriah Heep  http://t.co/GVsjUtWWaI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Careers with a Creative Writing Degree  http://t.co/rd2AmjhgN2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peter Townshend shows us it's all right to grow up. There is dignity after rock'n'roll. - Sting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Return the shoes?! I can't talk to you when you're being hysterical! - Gabrielle, Desperate Housewives]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've never heard a Jay-Z song.  Miley Cyrus on Jay-Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahh Read About Loving Fine Wine  http://t.co/3wTY2NQT3Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Small Dogs Can Make Great Pets - Picking the Right Breed  http://t.co/DpZKDgT2f4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A family man is one who has replaced money in his wallet with snapshots.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>