<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @VancouverSun: Video: Metro Vancouver’s hot condo market surges - Condo sales and prices have gone from being flat for around ... https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nausea sucks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HeyBarber: 9 Drills to get FASTER HANDS...in flip flops!
Full video: https://t.co/MMVxCmYr6n https://t.co/F44Qx5GKso]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just got out of gum graft surgery.   The freezing is still working...kind of.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[May 2-4.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's weird when you see someone you know however you don't know where you know them from.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WhatTheFFacts: If we could shrink the world's population to a village of 100 people, we would have: 57 Asians, 21 Europeans, 14 America…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As expected @cmcdavid97 with the GWG at the #WHC.    Anything less would be...uncivilized.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CKNW: Coming up with @shanefoxman on @cknw @WHLGiants Gm Glen Hanlon 12:33, @elysiarotaru 1:07, Screen Relish Jeff Alexander 1:33 and J…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The cause of the power outage in Yaletown. #LinesDown https://t.co/3APWOhCinD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The power is out in Yaletown. #FirstWorldProblems https://t.co/dJQGbMB6Dm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uh oh.   Full moon. https://t.co/HpCHVMkjxe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My @cbc feed in English isn't working well on the tv so I'm watching the Pens/Lightning feed on the Punjabi network. #interesting #OMNI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ScanBC: #Vancouver Fire is on scene with a small fire in an apartment at E Hastings &amp; Columbia St. Hastings blocked Eastbound.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Shanbrennan1130: New tool means police can catch distracted drivers from over 1km away https://t.co/Cm6E4BaHr3 #distracteddriving https…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @globalnews: April was 7th consecutive month of record high temperatures for our planet. https://t.co/yizKeShMbd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having a Baconator.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's Friday the 13th.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just found out that Clamato juice is a combination of clam juice and tomato juice.   I honestly had no idea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Draft day is almost over.   That means it's vacation time for @TSNBobMcKenzie.  Well deserved.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good payday today. #BoutTime]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today is the last day of the first half of the year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you to @CKNW for having me on your show.   Much appreciated. #Foxman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm going to be on CKNW tonight at 8pm.   Tune in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HuffPostCanada: Meet Demyte, winner of Lithuania’s goat beauty pageant https://t.co/vhOp5Ffv5c https://t.co/pusFF6NoKu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @VancouverSun: Sportsnet confirmed today that Ron MacLean will replace George Stroumboulopoulos as #HNIC host. https://t.co/BeD5Yvdjsl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wallysnipes. Getzlaf and Perry for The Twins?  Straight up?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @richardbranson: Leaving the EU is a very sad decision that will do huge damage to Britain’s prosperity &amp; Europe’s stability: https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@nytimes: The final numbers of the Brexit vote are in: 
51.9% for 'leave' 
48.1% for 'remain'
https://t.co/Ekyf9REMnU"  So now what?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @globalnews: Chicago police on the lookout for Sinead O'Connor after receiving a report she threatened to jump from a bridge. https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Forbes: Asia's most expensive cities for expats:

1. Hong Kong
2. Singapore
3. Tokyo

See the rest: https://t.co/VcpTW0kuSL https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Sportsnet: WATCH: Here's the moment NHL commissioner Gary Bettman confirmed the Las Vegas expansion. https://t.co/5zQmFBsoJz https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Accident at Main and 28th. https://t.co/BxiNbErE2j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Forbes: The highest-paid athlete in the world: Cristiano Ronaldo, making $88 million a year https://t.co/Y67dFZFshx https://t.co/UWIYUN…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jonsmolensky: Looking to help hire 2 bartenders for upscale Vancouver restaurant DM me only pls.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Inspire_Us: We cannot become what we need to be by remaining what we are. -Max De Pree]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[About to pull the pork. https://t.co/Gwlxgj6KIm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BBHwest: Last month, the average index price of a Vancouver condo climbed 13.9 per cent year-over-year: https://t.co/NWWxrZudEA #VANre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LeafsPR: .@MapleLeafs have acquired G Frederik Andersen from Anaheim for the 30th pick in the 2016 NHL Draft &amp; a 2nd round pick in 2017…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@Fact: Worldwide, females earn $18 trillion, but spend $28 trillion." Sounds about right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Late night cleansing session happening.   Nature abhors a vacuum. #deep]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ExcuseThePuns_: https://t.co/JRGljcY3VD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A very Happy Father's Day to my dad. Theo - you're awesome.   Keep going.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @georgiastraight: George Stroumboulopoulos is out as the host of Hockey Night in Canada https://t.co/kwSGqQZYSa #Strombo #hockey https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HuffPostCanada: Truck carrying deli meats collides with truck carrying bread https://t.co/fHUK7T2Dhi https://t.co/szLg5T5SUC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GuardianTravel: Done Paris, Rome, Madrid? Try Ljubljana: green &amp; charming with vibrant food &amp; drink scene https://t.co/EzBJ1681hG https…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Slovenian buffet breakfast.   #TheBestBaconInTheWorld #HotelLev https://t.co/VmQOKVMXEG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MayorGregor Can we not tone down the bike lane thing a bit?   Do we have to do every road downtown? #Smithe #Nelson #RoyalPain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WhatTheFFacts: The losers of the Super Bowl still get rings.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WhatTheFFacts: The large Santa with a white beard and red clothing that we are used to today was actually created by Coca Cola.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I closed my biggest deal ever tonight.   Good times.    And it's already time to break that record. #Biggie #BK  #Representin']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok peeps....I need new eye glasses and new prescription sunglasses.  Where am I going?   Suggestions please.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MyVancouver: The crowds, the sights, the food and the people watching! Italian Day on The Drive is today https://t.co/JsucGFnQjb https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GrangerDarren: Check out what Chaser has been working on! Check him out @HkyDignity @AnzeKopitar @JonathanQuick32 @LAKings @dewyy8 http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NEWS1130: The Israeli military revokes all permits for Palestinians to visit Israel and travel abroad during Ramadan after deadly shoot…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @the_ironsheik: I SUPLEX THE VEGAN https://t.co/UKFRIaF2QW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nationalpost: Don Cherry, Sportsnet agree to multi-year deal to keep 82-year-old icon on the air https://t.co/PZT8OKeCY2 via @npsport]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CTVNews: Clinton steps into history as 1st female White House nominee https://t.co/fCEGzHnF1M #DNCinPHL https://t.co/hLKyuT7Nin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @travel_slovenia: Acc. to the 2016 Environmental Performance Index #Slovenia is the 5th most environmentally friendly country on Earth h…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thinkin' of hittin' South Africa.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NEWS1130: 15% tax on sales of Metro Van homes to foreign nationals will mean $300k extra charge on $2-million home. https://t.co/EbFAHG…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wearing a compression sock on my left leg.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At @TheKeg.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was asked to go to Rio to captain the Men's Olympic Beach Volleyball team.   I have declined to attend due to Zika virus concerns.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @georgiastraight: #Vancouver councillors complain about aggressive realtors going around neighbourhoods #VanRE #vanpoli https://t.co/Nol…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ScanBC: #Vancouver Police are responding to Gore St &amp; E Hastings St for a report of a male mooning passing vehicles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ScanBC: #Burnaby #RCMP are responding to Metrotown for reports of 200 people playing pokemon and setting off fireworks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hittin' the links for the first time in a few years.   This should be interesting. #FORE!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HuffingtonPost: ISIS claims responsibility for Nice terror attack https://t.co/M9COW5p1C5 https://t.co/mSf3YPrEPn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @georgiastraight: Vancouver realtor suspended for misconduct in $1.3-million property deal #VanRE #Vancouver https://t.co/AgSyou1IGe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@globalnews: Parents lose custody of malnourished toddler fed vegan diet. 
https://t.co/w71o2rODgh" Been sayin' it for years. Told you so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I need a cabinet guy.   I have a client doing a reno. Anyone out there have any recommendations?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GlobalBC: Toddler in Italy taken from parents after a strict vegan diet reportedly led to a severe case of malnutrition.  
https://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @shaunalshatti: Manager: Jon Jones ‘lost out on an eight-figure payday' at UFC 200 https://t.co/yFb6t4PghI https://t.co/At0qiIJ2QZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is anyone French who is on team France? None of the names seem...well...French.  #Euro2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boom. Another subject removal this week.   That's 4 for 4.    Is there not some sort of all star team that I can try out for? #VRE #legend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be frank I rarely ever hear of Buyers remorse - even in this market.  Even with some of the prices that are being paid out there.  #VRE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GeorgesStPierre: Vancouver fans, I will be in your city this Sunday July 10th to meet you! https://t.co/S3ct4hKJoU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CommercialD: #TheDrive has serious issues (homeless, garbage &amp; lack of mental health resources) needing $$$ BEFORE spending on bike lan…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 for 3 so far this week in firming up deals.   One more to wrap up. Do I bat .750 or 1.000?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Subject removal update this week. 2 for 2 now. Congrats KC on your purchase!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 Subject removals due in 4 days.   Day 1 - a success. Thank you @PatrickWeeks.  A pleasure doing business with you.   #1For1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @georgiastraight: #Vancouver rental tower and boutique hotel planned above #Denman Place Mall https://t.co/bbrl9S8rQq #WestEnd https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Miss604: Smoke from #BurnsBogFire seems to be hanging above Downtown Vancouver. Heavy campfire smell has woken me up, you too if you're…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a week I'm having and it isn't even Monday yet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jason Day is playing the 16th the way I play golf. #PGA #tree #water #long #SomehowMovingForward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jarmstrongbc: Transmitter building for radio station @AM730Traffic going up in flames #BurnsBogFire https://t.co/OVdnuVj10l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @michaelkusswx: Burns Bog is on fire and spreading east. Winds still 25-35 km/h @GlobalBC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@ExcuseThePuns_: Professional cyclists legs after 250 km on bike in Tour de France. https://t.co/edKthFVgfr" Whoa. Veiny.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DavidRoads: Don't make excuses for why you can't get it done. Focus on all the reasons why you must make it happen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HuffPostCanada: The shiny Tongan Olympian finally explains all that oil https://t.co/97hCwl5Uf6 https://t.co/PZO8s90RUB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thinking of having mixed greens with salmon on top.  This is different.   I wonder if I have the flu.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nytimes: Usain Bolt and the fastest men in the world since 1896 – on the same track https://t.co/TsrtGz5TFA https://t.co/Nlh7hiPwWo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Fact: If your house was on fire while you were asleep, you wouldn't wake up. Sense of smell is off when you're sleeping.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WTFFacts: “If you can’t explain it to a six year old, you don’t understand it yourself.” - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DalaiLama: Different religious traditions can live together on the basis of mutual admiration, mutual respect, and learning from each o…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would think that my body fat has lots of flavour.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think I would like a swimmer's body.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thinking of heading to the Abbotsford Air Show tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FriedgeHNIC  Gretzky never scored every shift.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>