<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Clinton Diagnosed With Pneumonia Days Before Struggling To Walk At 9/11 Memorial https://t.co/IlaQ6Uz4Lx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rubycramer: Statement from Clinton's longtime physician, Dr. Lisa Bardack, M.D.: Clinton has pneumonia, has been advised to rest https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Bats Away Pro-Russian Criticism, But Some Supporters Like Putin Better Than Obama https://t.co/JyKA87R58c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gary Johnson Struggles, Again, While Explaining Syria https://t.co/4zfeABOZfG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mike Pence Once Called Putin's Treatment Of Journalists "Deeply Troubling" https://t.co/EFJsrgH9WR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Slogs Through Another Pitch To The Religious Right https://t.co/8x7MyUZM6F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clinton Says Half Of Trump Supporters Are In The "Basket Of Deplorables" https://t.co/48XMdNWtUH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Alt-Right Wants To Professionalize https://t.co/5Gv5r8azmm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Beach Resort In Florida Seeks More Foreign Workers https://t.co/4udzzpnQuC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NBC News Chairman Andy Lack Praises Matt Lauer For Widely Panned Presidential Forum https://t.co/Xg1dV6kavk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Missouri's Execution Drug Supplier Pleads To Stay Anonymous https://t.co/u9eYugQzyN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Evan McMullin Says He Might Want Mark Cuban As VP — And Cuban Is Open To It https://t.co/6BOZyxSarp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[House To Vote On Bill Allowing 9/11 Victims' Families To Sue Saudi Arabia For Terrorism https://t.co/Tkfe3SOEfc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supreme Court Allows Michigan Straight-Ticket Voting To Continue For November https://t.co/eh2LYvnMHN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chrisgeidner: "We’re committing $20M to help Democrats in the 2016 election." —  @moskov, https://t.co/VPpps83ZX4 https://t.co/mTBWwIBL…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mat: Holy crap. @moskov putting some serious money into defeating Donald Trump

https://t.co/0YPAniAPPs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chrisgeidner: If #SCOTUS does not act, or eventually denies the request, that means straight-ticket voting will remain in Michigan for…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chrisgeidner: Well, it's Sept. 9. The Michigan Secretary of State said she needed a stay by Sept. 8. #SCOTUS has not granted a stay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sean Hannity Didn’t Change. We Did. https://t.co/20DEtfllLl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joe Biden Comes To Capitol Hill To Pressure Republicans https://t.co/BdzKYJw6CD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Ryan Won't Comment On Trump's Praise For Putin https://t.co/D04i7HkUSz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mark Kirk On "Ransom" For Iran Hostages: "We Didn’t Have To Get Our Guys Back" https://t.co/gH05q2cJGC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump: Clinton's Cough Is Not Appropriate To Discuss But "Very Sad To See" https://t.co/ZFR2GEANrE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pro-Trump PAC "Liberty Action Group" Sued Over Unwanted Robocalls https://t.co/dZCxYvZELF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could Sheriff Joe Arpaio Actually Lose This Time? https://t.co/hvzgPZQVvG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hillary Clinton Has "No Sympathy" For Republicans Who Nominated Trump https://t.co/vTRd7ndj2T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RosieGray: Julian Assange will be on @seanhannity's radio show for an hour today, Hannity tells me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rubycramer: Rare harsh words for GOP from Clinton -- “No Sympathy” For Republicans Who Nominated Trump https://t.co/sN3jSdLxjQ https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump Jr. On Undocumented Immigrants: "Everyone Does Have To Go" https://t.co/jl87WyxWI7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Book Alleges Link Between Louisiana Congressman And Prostitution Hub https://t.co/P4CDm7MQU9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hillary Clinton On Gary Johnson Flub: "You Can Look On The Map And Find Aleppo" https://t.co/TXKd4BKvY0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump Lies That He Opposed Iraq War From Beginning And Goes Unchallenged https://t.co/EDlwknpyuM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Says He Would Work With Undocumented Immigrants Who Plan To Serve In The Military https://t.co/HRTn4laOex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump On Putin Praising Him: "I'll Take The Compliment" https://t.co/OX53kAU5bS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arrest Warrant Issued For Green Party Presidential Candidate Jill Stein https://t.co/gJ2LH6Qx1a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republicans, Democrats Spar Over Looming Gun Control Sit-In Punishment https://t.co/5yMmrT1ma2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clinton Apparently Did A Berlusconi Impression After Her 2010 WikiLeaks "Apology Tour" https://t.co/S6Ow4SP28U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Ryan “Fully Confident” Election Will Be Carried Out Fairly, Spokesperson Says https://t.co/XMdORIU2m4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Says He And Clinton Should Take A Drug Test Before The Next Debate https://t.co/0kAwXCgPdp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where Is Trump's War On Media Headed? https://t.co/5u68Fdpptl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clinton Has Little To Say Directly About Allegations Against Trump https://t.co/UscNy1zB2q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republican Women Blast Trump For Mocking Accusers' Looks https://t.co/IXFJrLP2zv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Romney: "It Will Be Very Difficult" For Party "To Be Put Back Together Again" https://t.co/7qGonIXOSc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Carrasquillo: This, btw, is a good one from @mckaycoppins w/ Trump yesterday: Trump Gets Desperate https://t.co/zXXIr3Pe1F via @buzzfee…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two More Women Accuse Donald Trump Of Sexual Misconduct https://t.co/wscVftcGsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Justice Ginsburg Says Her Earlier Kaepernick Criticism Was "Inappropriately Dismissive" https://t.co/et3fNl588H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump Is Causing Bitter Fights Inside Cuban-American Families https://t.co/4RsrechyJk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Florida's New Death Penalty Law Is Unconstitutional, State Supreme Court Rules https://t.co/fIWQrd1tRw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leaked Polling Doesn't Reveal Plot Against Obama — But Does Show Clinton's Weaknesses https://t.co/MiZHq0v5x0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Jr. Suggested Women Who Can't Take Harassment “Don’t Belong In The Workforce" https://t.co/8nAbmPz9NB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Gets Desperate https://t.co/6x96Bn5Rdd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Central Park Five Member Rails Against Trump's Appeals To "Mob Justice" In New Ad https://t.co/cPzWxDafIE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Major Latino Group To Endorse Clinton Ahead Of Final Las Vegas Debate https://t.co/RmjM01cnuf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's Donald Trump's Response To Being Called A "Sexual Predator" In 2006 https://t.co/EqSEf3Y67k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Appeals Court Reverses Itself, Says Missouri Execution Drug Supplier Can Stay Secret https://t.co/25ZVWT6L8T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The Apprentice" Producer Mark Burnett Says He Is Not A Trump Supporter https://t.co/069l4XvwPE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Supporters Unfazed By Story Of Him Walking In On Teen Beauty Queens Changing https://t.co/7uAMcMNC50]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More Women Say Donald Trump Touched Them Inappropriately https://t.co/GDyB7jDNy4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Don’t Try To Defend Trump," Newt Gingrich Tells Republican Candidates https://t.co/qrxGHEL48U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At White House, First Latino My Brother's Keeper Event Spotlights Hispanic Kids https://t.co/U0EBVuUG3o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pence Makes The Case At Liberty University That Christians Should Forgive Trump https://t.co/99Rfnydzhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Targeting Black Voters, New Pro-Clinton Super PAC Ad Analyzes Trump's Rhetoric https://t.co/BkUOrAb7JZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama Gave Himself A "Sulfur Test" After A Trump Supporter Called Him A Demon https://t.co/EBb3ouzRY0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Supporters Unfazed By GOP Civil War At Low-Key Florida Rally https://t.co/nFd0CayJKR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Podesta: "Reasonable" Assumption That Trump Orbit Knew About Hacked Emails https://t.co/9GjP50AAf8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Digs In During His First Interview Since Video Leak https://t.co/aUK3FzK76I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Justices Grapple With Racial Bias In Juror Deliberations https://t.co/dnRkk2ydJ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's Audio Of Trump Campaign CEO Saying: "What We Need To Do Is Bitch Slap" The GOP https://t.co/f6cE49CRye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Federal Appeals Court To Reconsider Case On Gay Protections https://t.co/El39iihVH0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People Are Defending Trump’s Lewd Comments From 2005 With “Fifty Shades Of Grey,” Which Was Published In 2011 https://t.co/5v0WrwikDr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gov. Chris Christie Calls Trump’s Vulgar Comments “Completely Indefensible” https://t.co/GXEttQnlYJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump Doesn’t Seem To Get Why Saying #TheAfricanAmericans Is A Problem https://t.co/Co3GJI9tZi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Newt Gingrich: “Trump Crossed Into Being A Historic Figure" At The Debate https://t.co/755QENzaS0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The Apprentice" Producer Says He Can't Release Any Trump Tapes https://t.co/5nQc0mbU1W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump Suggests More Damning Videos Could Be Released https://t.co/YcA5e6AnR0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clinton Campaign Staffers Knew She Was Wrong About DOMA Claim https://t.co/xXACwCm5pW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frustrated Latino Republicans To Call For RNC's Reince Priebus To Resign https://t.co/fsVN6F6wM8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mike Pence Offers Unqualified Support For Trump After Debate https://t.co/Ls9Gc35VtE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democratic Rep: "Deplorables" Remark May Be "Worst Line I've Ever Heard In Politics" https://t.co/OmysEiJQQP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul Ryan Tells House Republicans: Do What's Best For You When It Comes To Trump https://t.co/9IZEBxrAtR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KateNocera: Lotta anger on this call. "We're upset Trump put us in this position," one member tells me. https://t.co/y4m9C4Peml]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Goes Full Breitbart https://t.co/9d0TcNLDfF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, That Was Easily The Craziest And Most Surreal Debate In Modern History https://t.co/fzdrVnsRVo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republicans Say Donald Trump Did Well Enough To Keep Himself Afloat https://t.co/s6kdUznRnD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clinton Unfazed As Trump Unloads Personal, Aggressively Attacks https://t.co/oXffz0Xe5h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's Campaign Manager Says Some Congressmen Have Sexually Harassed Women https://t.co/40gjxL5KG7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RNC Didn't Know About Trump Event With Women Who Accused Clinton Of Misconduct https://t.co/bEVeWWCQAb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Giuliani: Trump Has A "Pretty Solid Basis" For Saying Central Park Five Are Guilty https://t.co/FWPMuyeqzH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People Are Calling This Guy Glaring At Donald Trump The Real Winner Of The Debate https://t.co/9IMFivZaDa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's Twitter Account Becomes Top Result Under #RapeCulture https://t.co/2KxOLlyvjP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Black People Would Like Donald Trump To Know They Don't All Live In The Inner City https://t.co/In7RvuIXSe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[18 Very Real Tweets About Trump's "Locker Room Talk" https://t.co/OYGe47ca6l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Parents Don't Think The Debate Is Going To Be Appropriate For Their Kids https://t.co/2sbO6v0dUP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Activists Want To See Hillary Clinton Attack Donald Trump On Central Park Five https://t.co/v2z9FpqaFF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump On His Womanizing In 1993: "It's Fortunate I Don't Have To Run For Political Office" https://t.co/1UNbFYBHee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama Says The Trump Tapes Show He's Too Insecure To Be President https://t.co/lBuCGYldL1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Conservative Mormons Revolt Against Donald Trump https://t.co/b5K4aSz2J5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hillary Clinton Already Knows The Bad Thing You Said https://t.co/mS2mxqcTji]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @katherinemiller: Yesterday, we found the people in the office who HADN'T seen the Trump video and filmed them watching it
https://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Shame On You!": Trump Supporters Clash With Republican Leaders https://t.co/B6VGjMlfOc]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>