<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to ZZ Top  http://t.co/9d778vLQGk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these different types of beer - lots of options including ales, lagers, hocks and more!  http://t.co/koNwsDf0bF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I take a dim view of watching my own destruction. - Jack, "Invasion of the Body Snatchers"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pessimist: A man who thinks that all woman are bad Optimist: A man who hopes so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I read Shakespeare and the Bible, and I can shoot dice. That's what I call a liberal education. - Tallulah Bankhead]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome - An Easy Toilet Seat Lifter - keep the girls happy :&gt;) http://t.co/ekZDu7w48f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advertising is the life of trade. - Calvin Coolidge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is A SERP exactly?  http://t.co/svR5oOzH4s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gluten Free Recipes - Making a Gluten-Free Gravy  http://t.co/pPWlSPLR2W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love Cute Kids Watches - Having A Watch Can be Fun for Kids!  http://t.co/TH2kH3Z15a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Chiffons   http://t.co/MEJjBoTcn4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of that Odd Olympic Sport – Curling  http://t.co/WMuN422lEU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Europe – Best Places to Tour  http://t.co/4JatcjnDz8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A hamburger by any other name costs a lot more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips on Getting the Cheapest Car Loan  http://t.co/hTG5U95oJA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Flea and Tick Control For Your Pet  http://t.co/cOoBTP0gQl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You will never change your life until you change something you do daily. - Mike Murdock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Different Types of Beer  http://t.co/koNwsDf0bF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Neil Diamond  http://t.co/fzkUu8oZKK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cowboys, Mavs, Rangers and more read about the Sports teams of the Dallas Fort-Worth Metroplex - http://t.co/vHpXxHzMKq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even on the most solemn occasions I got away without wearing socks and hid that lack of civilization in high boots --&gt; Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep you can keep your devices charged via solar power - find out here - http://t.co/e4LFIeV7hm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The groundwork of all happiness is health. - Leigh Hunt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we're growing, we're always going to be out of our comfort zone. - John Maxwell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kate Austen: So what, I'm your prisoner? James 'Sawyer' Ford: If that sort of thing turns you on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read Great Outdoor Camping Equipment Tips  http://t.co/A8AykaMxGX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take care of your body. It's the only place you have to live. - Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the math geek in your life - the math clock... http://t.co/zs47hzPWix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The main part of intellectual education is not the acquisition of facts but learning how to make facts live." - Oliver Wendell Holmes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Five Guys Burgers and Fries  http://t.co/jDDoOLuyTZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In difficult times, fashion is always outrageous. - Elsa Schiaparelli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a world without fences and walls, who needs Gates and Windows?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awww How Adorable! A Smile Star Design - Color Changing - LED Light Toss Pillow! http://t.co/fG8Kz2G5Gc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Manolo Blahnik  http://t.co/aWrbdwsvyw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1,000 Incredible Costume and Cosplay Ideas http://t.co/ciCcNigqrF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give a girl the right shoes, and she can conquer the world. - Marilyn Monroe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The iPaperPad is not magical or revolutionary. It's a paper pad. A poor man's iPad LOL http://t.co/Acc5XGUmRA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the Little House on the Prairie Episode The Nephews  http://t.co/YxQ8sxZq8w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know money is the root of all evil if you would like to find out more - just send me $10 - DM me ASAP !!  :&gt;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you are thin, don't eat fast. If you are fat, don't eat fast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes a man to admit he's wrong but it takes a woman to prove it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome football t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the football lovers in your life!  http://t.co/exYr8RGaJi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is better than poverty, if only for financial reasons. - Woody Allen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where to find Great Gluten Free Recipes  http://t.co/O1pwsuKkFi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It wasnt a mission to be a rock star. It wasnt a mission of mine to even be a movie star. I just intended to be a good actor. - Don Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You Have Never Seen Knives Like These - They Interlock with in each other - stylish and modern! http://t.co/5fPhXLzDjP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Lewisville, Texas  http://t.co/KfRSTWzwnX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the animals: God has given them the rudiments of thought and joy untroubled - Fyodor Dostoyevsky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every boy should have two things: a dog, and a mother willing to let him have one - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Understanding Government Resources for Small Business  http://t.co/njz5J0eTm7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 14 - Doctor Decides to Discontinue IV Treatment  http://t.co/GXKQ8Lnmt4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dammit, man! I'm a doctor, not a physicist! - Leonard 'Bones' McCoy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Narcotics Detection – Technology's Place in the War on Drugs  http://t.co/VbvjwNNywJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Benefits of iPads for Seniors  http://t.co/XGeVsmPTGP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The whole purpose of education is to turn mirrors into windows. - Sydney J. Harris]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You will never change your life until you change something you do daily. - Mike Murdock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Foghat  http://t.co/VoZHta0YRS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education ... has produced a vast population able to read but unable to distinguish what is worth reading. - G. M. Trevelyan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame: Capture the Flag  http://t.co/uElsrQodmJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The aim of marketing is to know and understand the customer so well the product or service fits him and sells itself. - Peter F. Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Overview of the USSSA Youth Sports Organization  http://t.co/9ydDRZ9Rca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't sweep if you don't win the first game, and it's tougher to win two out of three if you lose the first one. - Todd Helton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Grapevine, Texas  http://t.co/t2W03Q0CzK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A girl should be two things: classy and fabulous. - Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Aerosmith  http://t.co/m8CxZsR9y1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dogs come when they're called; cats take a message and get back to you later. - Mary Bly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is 10% what happens to us and 90% how we react to it. - Ennis P. Kimbro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One Person’s Musings on Elvis  http://t.co/vveGhU0PnQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is better than poverty, if only for financial reasons. - Woody Allen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Snow Beer  http://t.co/8PUCvQwu1g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crack is cheap I make too much $ to ever smoke crack. Lets get that straight. OK? We dont do crack We dont do that Crack is whack - Whtney H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To succeed --  You need to find something to hold on to, something to motivate you, something to inspire you. - Tony Dorsett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I prefer the company of peasants because they have not been educated sufficiently to reason incorrectly. - Michel de Montaigne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Importance of Keywords for Search Engine Optimization (SEO)  http://t.co/N5A6BsrAOr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Cowboy Boots  http://t.co/Yt4zpm4Rxl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we knew what it was we were doing, it would not be called research, would it? - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are what you do. If you do boring, stupid, monotonous work, chances are you'll end up boring, stupid, and monotonous. - Bob Black]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Health and Mana Video Game Inspired Earrings with Key Charms!  Cool! http://t.co/UgwfFLz9yC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellence is to do a common thing in an uncommon way. - Booker T. Washington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Left Banke  http://t.co/LUxZeOlEPY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some of the worst mistakes in my life were haircuts --&gt; Jim Morrison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who wish to sing, always find a song. - Swedish Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What we want is to see the child in pursuit of knowledge, and not knowledge in pursuit of the child. - George Bernard Shaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Tom Petty and the Heartbreakers  http://t.co/T9yP30vvp8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's an edge to real rock 'n' roll. It's all that matters. - Neil Young]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just in time for winter - Touch Screen Texting Gloves  - http://t.co/f7Qf2y1pW3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've never heard a Jay-Z song.  Miley Cyrus on Jay-Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first thing you lose on a diet is your sense of humor. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome marriage t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the lovers in your life!   http://t.co/MffOELcRbM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Publishing Management with HootSuite  http://t.co/yRCrbPqdDK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jazz up  your pool or patio with these trendy light cubes - cool!  http://t.co/nzGj0GlrDQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It ain't over 'til it's over - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every instructor assumes that you have nothing else to do except study for that instructor's course.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is an admirable thing, but it is well to remember from time to time that nothing that is worth knowing can be taught - Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the The Burning Bridge by John Flanagan  http://t.co/y5KepZnVXl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I believe you are your work. Don't trade the stuff of your life, time, for nothing more than dollars. That's a rotten bargain - Rita  Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay, that thing in the woods, maybe it's a monster, maybe it's a pissed off giraffe, I don't know. Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't be melancholy in fashion because people don't respond to it. - Isaac Mizrahi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In youth we learn in age, we understand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people are born on third base and go through life thinking they hit a triple. - Barry Switzer]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>