<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Quality Assurance Lead: We are looking for an experienced Software Quality Assurance Lead to join our team. You will make a significant contribution to our existing software development department here at Christopherson Business Travel. The… https://t.co/ZD7hKkcOl3 https://t.co/mb0gKF6o2p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer – V3Main ************** – Home – About – Mission, Vision, &amp; Values – Leadership – Government – Cybersecurity – News – Services – IT Managed Services – Agile Software Development – Custom Software Development &gt; – Web… https://t.co/FLTlTyjzvq https://t.co/XrPVi0yTg4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agile Project Manager/Scrum Master: Agile Project Manager/Scrum Master St. Louis, MO 6 month contract to hire Equifax Workforce Solutions is looking for an agile project manager/scrum master who is a change agent to drive software development agile teams… https://t.co/OUTTcwiC7g https://t.co/pxwz0K4Qtt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IVR Developer: IVR Developer – Job Location:Headquarters – Alexandria, VA – Job Status:Full Time – Position Type:IT – Operations – Date Posted:11/15/2017 – Location Address:880 S. Pickett Street Alexandria, VA 22304 – – Job Description: – BoatU.S., a… https://t.co/aKyNPzcPkd https://t.co/PbwfeeqFWo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java API Developer (Java, Rest API, JS), Secret Cleared (Req# 00013): SENIOR JAVA API DEVELOPER (JAVA, REST API, JS) Title: Senior Java API Developer (Java, Rest API, JS) Location: Centreville, VA Terms: Regular, Fulltime Clearance: Qualified… https://t.co/0VJbnmNP96 https://t.co/QGd9aO5wgA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: Infosys DXEMP Technology Lead US – J2EE – WebServices Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to create and execute strategies for their digital transformation.… https://t.co/9bgZUmUcRw https://t.co/W6uofjqY7R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CW Scrum Master: CW Scrum Master (******) Georgetown, Kentucky – United States Job Start Date – 03/15/18, Posted Date – 03/15/18 Primary SkillsScrumTax TermsC2C,W-2,1099Overview Dear, I am Mohammed Dastagir with Saxon Global Inc wanted to let you know… https://t.co/M1nVos0HDi https://t.co/c6dnCQSryt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Project Manager/Scrum Master: SemanticBits is looking for a seasoned Scrum Master/Product Manager to manage the design, development and delivery of digital health services using a Scrum-based agile software development methodology. You will be working… https://t.co/ZPWeN1SmLm https://t.co/liexy1Fqgu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Who we are? Aquila is one of the fastest growing FinTech companies in Silicon Valley. Aquila delivers cash analytics and cash access to thousands of small businesses, that operate with volatile cash balances. We are a platform… https://t.co/EfN5p7DO0e https://t.co/5j5xNCXssb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital Commerce Business Analyst (US): Zaelab is a dedicated team of focused, agile and innovative consultants who work to bridge the gap from vision to delivery of B2B commerce technology projects. Our commitment to evolving commerce beyond traditional… https://t.co/gQZKwaLzdL https://t.co/mmvny0vXce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Lead- QA: Technical Lead- QA Indianapolis, Indiana Fulltime position Job Description: * Written Unit tests * Used version control * Database experience with writing, reading stored procedures and complex SQL * Ability and experience… https://t.co/hTMmsX2EAj https://t.co/q61yCRHKSS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stock market principles needed in crypto world: SEC official: NEW YORK (Reuters) - The cryptocurrency trading marketplace could be improved by applying some of the principles from the stock market such as best execution and surveillance, a senior U.S.… https://t.co/IN0VZAXK2d https://t.co/cOCLjacwsy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UI/UX Designer: Aristotle is looking for a UI/UX Designer (with some JS development experience) that believe those companies that champion a design-centric approach to their product interfaces are the ones that rise above the rest. You live and breathe… https://t.co/rqFtirk5fk https://t.co/xTCoxaysAr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL &amp; Hadoop Developer: SQL &amp; Hadoop Developer THIS IS A W2 CONTRACT TO HIRE OPPORTUNITY. CORP TO CORP REPRESENTATIVES OR APPLICANTS NEED NOT APPLY (NO C2C) ALIS Software is seeking an experienced SQL Developer for a contract to hire opportunity with an… https://t.co/v0V9ygFmzi https://t.co/IuFWIiGAWR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital Commerce Project Manager (US): Zaelab, based in USA is a dedicated team of focused, agile and innovative consultants who work to bridge the gap from vision to delivery of B2B commerce technology projects. Our… https://t.co/hhmzJrlb3P #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/zAri6fWDkP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Responsibilities * * Develops, maintains, and enhances complex and diverse software systems (e.g., processing-intensive analytics, novel algorithm development, manipulation of extremely large data sets, real-time systems, and business… https://t.co/X9nOQXxmXL https://t.co/5cdEQavtiU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Scrum Master: Senior Scrum Master at Cox Automotive Skip Navigation – Careers Home – Early Career – Join Our Talent Community – Blog – Manage Your Profile – Cox Enterprises – Cox Communications – Cox Automotive – Cox Media Group Search all Cox… https://t.co/ThaN32kWgI https://t.co/o0BQlPtqJU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer- Platform: About the Role: We are looking for a platform engineer. This role is responsible for creating solutions that allow for the management of relationships and transactions globally. The… https://t.co/8BEf4K5Alv #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/E9X4SPjOuw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead, .NET Developer: Do you have the right stuff? Gullview Technologies is an exciting new and rapidly growing technology company focused on taking on the most vital and challenging business and technical challenges our clients face in competing in our… https://t.co/2s0HRzdmgr https://t.co/pzQgbdwBKr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BA / Scrum Master: Position Overview: The Scrum Master leads the Agile process for one or more Scrum teams, ensuring predictable delivery of software releases within scope. This position is also responsible for the ongoing… https://t.co/qiFr9ts2Q1 #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Softheon is looking for several Software Engineers who can help in developing solid products to meet clients needs and improve end-user experience using new technologies such as microservices, single-page web applications, RESTful web… https://t.co/Ot7n2KRkFU https://t.co/fnD00JGWX8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Agile Coach: Position Purpose: Lead software development teams in project initiation, organization, goal and change management aspects of AgileDiscover opportunities to champion agile values and adoption across ITDevelop… https://t.co/97NTImAKQJ #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/CxmJiiRnnx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BlackBerry to provide software for Jaguar Land Rover vehicles: (Reuters) - BlackBerry Ltd and Tata Motors Ltd's Jaguar Land Rover (JLR) said on Thursday they reached a licensing agreement to use the Canadian company's software in the luxury car brand's… https://t.co/3R5QQHmfaz https://t.co/XcWU1UBoiE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Lead: Java Lead Ref No.: 18-08484 Location: Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania Hello, Greetings for the day ! We have an urgent requirement for Java Lead in Pittsburgh, PA. Please let me know if you are looking for a new… https://t.co/mA1VxxJONR #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/T6MAU7Plj7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aerospace Software Engineer: Category: Development/Engineering City: Lafayette, Louisiana, United States Position ID: J0617-0864 Employment Type: Full Time Meet our professionals Build a Career that Matters at CGI’s… https://t.co/20DU8TTy41 #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principle Scrum Master: The Sr Manager, Principle Scrum Master acts as the overall leader of agile scrum practices across IT and business team members delivering technology capabilities. This role not only coaches, but also provides hands on assistance… https://t.co/zsW6H7ymE9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer II – UI Angular and Java Developer: Job Summary: The Treasury Services department of the Federal Reserve Bank of Kansas City is seeking a Software Engineer II. The Federal Reserve plays a major role in… https://t.co/YqWNUEnxGs #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/yEIHF2g6Bp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master/Coach: Scrum Master/Coach (******) Plano, Texas – United States Job Start Date – 03/05/18, Posted Date – 03/05/18 Primary SkillsScrumTax TermsC2C,W-2Overview * escription: We are looking for a really strong SM/coach for our registration team… https://t.co/2HZ9Q6n130]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ruby on Rails Developer: RUBY ON RAILS Do you like writing mean and clean Ruby code? Come join our team and help us build amazing things. Were looking for someone with a passion for programming and for writing beautiful… https://t.co/zTjtz5woT1 #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Application Developer: Senior Application Developer CSI Leasing (CSI) is one of the largest independent equipment leasing specialists in the world, with customers in more than 36 countries. Established in 1972, we have helped thousands of… https://t.co/n6vNE42nOa https://t.co/zkue3Gjj9n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ruby On Rails Developer: [Let’s face it, you’re probably more interested in looking at the technology before really considering us right? Take a minute to learn more about our platform Here… https://t.co/VRY6Fu6F6D #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Front End Engineer: Sallie Mae is a company created with great purpose. We make the dream of higher education a reality. We do it by being a resource for families who want to save, plan, and pay for college. Our vision,… https://t.co/ZyF4Z57qtg #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/Dvj7KM0AXg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: We currently have an opening for an IT Project Manager in our PRS IT team. The IT Project Manager will have responsibility for the management and coordination of multiple concurrent projects within the PRS… https://t.co/gfFRe74JUa #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Networking Software Engineer: Were looking for a dedicated and passionate Sr. Engineer to join our cloud networking team. If you have experience building scalable, cloud based, web applications, are excited about… https://t.co/JeeBOmNW0H #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Scrum Master: Senior Scrum Master – Careers Home – About Us – People &amp; Culture – University Recruiting – Total Rewards – Growth &amp; Learning – Featured Locations – Europe, Middle East &amp; Africa Jobs – Asia &amp; South… https://t.co/VTHe8uvw7C #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Zuckerberg says Facebook made mistakes on user data, vows curbs: SAN FRANCISCO (Reuters) - Facebook Inc Chief Executive Mark Zuckerberg said on Wednesday that his company made mistakes in how it handled data belonging to 50… https://t.co/yFWbIS3PBa #news #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/ZM2vq6f1UW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer III, OTC Technology:: CME Group: Where Futures Are Made CME Group (****************) is the worlds leading and most diverse derivatives marketplace. But who we are goes deeper than that. Here, you can impact markets worldwide. Transform… https://t.co/xmkqmHjHH6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Architect (JAVA): The Software Architect is responsible for development activities for FanThreeSixtys back-end RESTful web services and data integration application, collaborating with Product Development, Mobile and Web Development teams. In… https://t.co/fLxuEhgB8J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Category: Project Management City: Chattanooga, Tennessee, United States Position ID: J0218-1797 Employment Type: Full Time Meet our professionals CGI: An employer of choice Position Description: Dynamic and innovative information… https://t.co/KrpL8lNqgi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager/Scrum Master: JOB DESCRIPTION: Resource 1 is in need of a Project Manager/Scrum Master for a 8-12- month contract in Rosemont, Illinois. Client is open to either long-term contract or conversion to permanent. Individual should have at… https://t.co/l7eWbpEVBq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer (Node): SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER (NODE) Los Angeles. Full-time. As soon as possible. inShare ‘" style="border: none; padding: 0px; height: 20px; visibility: visible; width: 67px; background: transparent;" height="20" width="67"&gt;… https://t.co/twqbghHBNs https://t.co/vc2X3Uzmsm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master Job: Scrum MasterLocation: Bloomfield, CTDuration : 6+ months?Scrum Master CertificationPMP certification is a plus, agile?Raeela ******************************************?? – provided by Dice Scrum Master Certification – ID#:… https://t.co/vtfuQe7irt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack .NET Developer: Saturno is hiring a full stack .NET developer to help us with a variety of web-based projects, including mid to large size websites and implementation of our industry-leading software. Our ideal candidate is a self-directed,… https://t.co/P19ryJ8qwk https://t.co/LqFVqMGwZI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Des Moines, IA.: Project Manager Full Time Position Des Moines, IA Job Description: Looking for Scrum Master who has got expertise in Java, J2EE. Must have experience working as Scrum Master for at least 3 years. Should have good client… https://t.co/vPKARqEsA1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior DevOps Engineer: As a DevOps Engineer at Athlinks, a division at Life Time fitness, you will be an embedded member and hands-oncontributor of an Agile/Scrum Delivery team. You will be in an environment that fosters… https://t.co/pUyaVR3fvl #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/GVMAAjPhuS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: We are a growing team of highly talented engineers working on very high volume, low latency transactional platforms that run in the cloud. We provide highly available, scalable, secure and fault-tolerant service interfaces and SAAS… https://t.co/71K5KKcPsZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agile Coach: Looking for an experienced Agile Coach to join our team supporting SSA in Woodlawn, MD MUST be US Citizen or green card holder Key Required Skills: Agile Coaching, Training, Agile Implementation experience… https://t.co/lPMkvT3WuF #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Academic behind Facebook breach says he is a 'scapegoat': BBC: LONDON (Reuters) - A Cambridge University academic who harvested data on millions of Facebook users said he has been made a scapegoat by the social network and a… https://t.co/BjsQ3TT5KC #news #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/m2sh69mvQm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer II: Software Engineer II with Cox Enterprises Skip Navigation – Careers Home – Early Career – Join Our Talent Community – Blog – Manage Your Profile – Cox Enterprises – Cox Communications – Cox Automotive – Cox Media Group Search all… https://t.co/9PNOLP7wRJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Development Engineer – C# or Java: Senior Software Development Engineer – C# or Java at Go Daddy Skip Navigation Careers Open Menu – GoDaddy Life – Our Teams – Benefits – University Students – Blog – GoDaddy… https://t.co/BdUmyjphFv #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Scrum Master: Senior Scrum Master – Careers Home – About Us – People &amp; Culture – University Recruiting – Total Rewards – Growth &amp; Learning – Featured Locations – Europe, Middle East &amp; Africa Jobs – Asia &amp; South… https://t.co/mqK6aDI8YP #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full-Stack Javascript Web Developer: We are seeking a Full-Stack Javascript Web Developer for a client that specializes in agricultural biotechnology. This company’s mission is centered on finding agricultural solutions for… https://t.co/B5PJhTr2xQ #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer IV- Embedded: Software Engineer IV- Embedded As an IV Solutions team member, you will work with a creative, experienced and dedicated team of engineers on delivering innovative solutions for the pharmacies throughout the world. Our… https://t.co/FhE3FC6XZ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Analyst: BUSINESS SYSTEMS ANALYST 120VC exists to enable our clients to complete their Projects efficiently and cost effectively; to light a fire under innovation and crush the cost boundary, ensuring a… https://t.co/payxlwL8Nu #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer/Cloud Engineer: 7+ years engineering experience with Agile/Scrum methodologies. Solid understanding of algorithm complexity, parallel/distributed systems, advanced data structures, computer networking,… https://t.co/qcV1fwQHNh #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[devops engineer: Below is a snapshot of our DevOps Engineer role within our Product Operations team. If this role takes your fancy and you are in interested in a career at Clarabridge please apply here and let’s chat – we… https://t.co/vhTuheLysS #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/a0gRgeIabg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – US: Infosys Retail, CPG &amp; Logistics Project Manager Java, Agile Scrum Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to create and execute… https://t.co/givh1HhXeL #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Team Lead, Information Systems: Company Description Thinking Capital is the leader in the Canadian Alternative Lending space, leveraging technology to be at the forefront of the FinTech industry. Since 2006, they have… https://t.co/bxkCdU9Cln #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/IDiUcXfqCv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spotify CEO eligible to sell up to $2 billion stake in public listing: (Reuters) - Daniel Ek, the CEO and co-founder of streaming music leader Spotify Technology SA , is eligible to sell up to 15.8 million shares of the company… https://t.co/8hzwI28if0 #news #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/aeqSA4UcBl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager (Certified Scrum Master) for HP Inc.: Paradigm is looking for an experienced Project Manager to support our client, HP Inc., in San Diego, CA. The individual were seeking is skilled in managing technical… https://t.co/7Ni64EmAvH #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Quality Assurance Engineer: QA Engineer Responsibilities: Review quality specifications and technical design documents to provide timely and meaningful feedback Creating detailed, comprehensive and well-structured… https://t.co/vOJTwD4t5H #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer- Platform: About the Role: We are looking for a platform engineer. This role is responsible for creating solutions that allow for the management of relationships and transactions globally. The… https://t.co/zESfR7TCED #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (Java): POSITION SUMMARY The Software Engineer is responsible for development activities for FanThreeSixtys back-end RESTful web services and data integration application, collaborating with Product… https://t.co/ac4r0cgc4y #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Development Expert: Development Expert for SAP Labs, LLC (Palo Alto, CA) resp for dvlpmnt focus on dsgn, cdng, tst, QA of cmplx prdct feat in a dvlpmt team. Bach in Comp Sci, Engg, Math, or rltd field &amp; 7 yrs exp req’d, or… https://t.co/XSQCgjBdGN #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/36AXV8th9j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Test Automation Engineer: Company Corporation (NYSE: Company) is the global leader in consumer transaction technologies, turning everyday interactions with businesses into exceptional experiences. With its software,… https://t.co/6vaN1rYQIT #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[scrum master: scrum master Ref No.: 18-10389 Location: plano, Texas Hi, Hope you are doing great!! Enterprise Solution Inc. is currently looking to fill urgent full-time permanent job positions as Scrum Master with the… https://t.co/l1H44x1C8i #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Automation Engineer: About Sellbrite Sellbrite (***************** [************************************************************ is a leading ecommerce SaaS solution that helps brands and retailers build, manage and grow… https://t.co/Wupx4KVQn8 #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior C# .NET Programmer: Developing great software takes more than just writing code. It takes a cohesive team, passionate about developing elegant products that scale exponentially in an extremely short time-frame and… https://t.co/2nUhvPm6yS #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Technical Project Manager: Paper Street Media, LLC (***************************** is a successful, web-based adult entertainment video on demand network, located in the heart of Downtown, Miami. We are a fun, hip,… https://t.co/BiKeZoVomT #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Scrum Master – Engineer: Client Reference Code: 214149 Job Scope: The Technical Scrum Master – Engineer is is responsible solutions architecture, development, configuration management, and deployment efforts on… https://t.co/YAmWpQFLJF #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/2EuzSU2fu9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master II: Job TitleScrum Master II – ID:30847 Duration6 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsJira, SCrum Master, Agile/SCRUM LocationIrving, TX Date Posted01/24/2018 Our client, a Fortune 50, global telecommunications… https://t.co/7StrEamHq3 #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[G20 leaders to hold fire on cryptocurrencies amid discord: sources: BUENOS AIRES (Reuters) - The world's financial leaders gathering in Argentina on Monday are likely to stop short of any specific action aimed at regulating… https://t.co/yf02HtRBsH #news #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/BMXuasR8aI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[iOS Developer: Austin, TX Full-time $100k – $130k Posted Today If you are a iOS Developer with experience, please read on! What You Need for this Position More Than 5 Years of experience and knowledge of: – iOS Development… https://t.co/TOBCntDH9J #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior Cloud Developer: Category: Development/Engineering City: Arlington, Virginia, United States Position ID: J1117-2429 Employment Type: Full Time Meet our professionals CGI: A place to build an IT career Position… https://t.co/bWVVb2P5pB #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back-End Developer: At Ad Hoc we build government digital services that are fast, efficient, and usable by everyone. Ad Hoc brings small teams of highly skilled professionals from the private sector to build government… https://t.co/UeGxuwdQYv #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SOFTWARE DEVELOPER: BRIGHTREE HOME Healthcare &amp; Hospice (Morrisville, NC) seeks Software Developer/Scrum Master – Develop, create, &amp; modify general computer applications software or specialized utility programs. Req. M.S.… https://t.co/OvQr0CCJRW #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/gE949efeGP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Visual Systems Engineer: Responsibilities/Qualification Play a critical role in preparing today’s and tomorrow’s Warfighters! Alion is dedicated to helping the Warfighter be ready for challenges they will face on and off… https://t.co/AfwlbGzHMh #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/35Ch21C3hs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Automated Test Engineer: Who We Are Would you like to join a company whose mission is to save lives? Practice Fusion is a leader in the electronic health record space with 112,000 active practices and over 80 million… https://t.co/HesBb8EI0N #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/m5wewAQJJF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[software engineer: Web Applications Software Engineer Job Location: Denver, Co. or Salt Lake City, Ut. Our Company – Helix Education We understand the serious challenges facing higher education – namely a shift in student… https://t.co/0EuxyaoXvJ #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/S9uqF1ASFg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Project Manager / Scrum Master: Senior Project Manager / Scrum Master Description Position Summary * Responsible for the successful delivery of one or more medium to large sized Waterfall or Agile, and moderately to… https://t.co/0LSTgletbX #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager (SCRUM/AGILE): Job TitleProject Manager (SCRUM/AGILE) – ID:31152 Duration12 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsAgile, Scrum Master LocationPlano, TX Date Posted03/02/2018 FOR IMMEDIATE DETAILS ABOUT THIS… https://t.co/CKWmTKOZVt #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Software Engineer: Lead Software Engineer Job Location Cambridge, MA Req Number 2018-0140 Department Business Systems Apply Now Overview: Foundation Medicine is a molecular information company focused on fundamentally… https://t.co/z1exmmI76D #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/Rghwryk11Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master Ref No.: 18-10518 Location: Columbus, Ohio Hi, Hope you are doing well Enterprise Solution Inc. is currently looking to fill urgent full-time permanent job positions as Scrum Master with the… https://t.co/d2pK2SGgeb #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge weighs what evidence U.S. can use to block AT&amp;T, Time Warner merger: WASHINGTON (Reuters) - AT&amp;T Inc sought to persuade a judge on Monday to throw out evidence the government seeks to use in a trial that begins this week… https://t.co/pwxAL2SEdI #news #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/f8AQnIPYhP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum master: Scrum master philadelphia, Pennsylvania – United States Job Start Date – 02/28/18, Posted Date – 02/28/18 Primary SkillsScrumTax TermsC2COverview Required Skills Set: Years of Experience: 5+ years Scrum Master… https://t.co/QyX1LtelAE #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SDET- Python: About Us Gorilla Logic provides custom application development services on the ground and in the cloud to many of the world’s leading software-driven organizations. It has a rich history of applying software… https://t.co/yzGaSH9CPM #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/U0GSQn5jIE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bus Analyst w/ QA Experience: Bus Analyst w/ QA ExperienceIWD77529865*Des Moines, IA*Strategic Business Analyst skilled at consulting with executive-level stakeholders to define business need or problem.CLIENT MINIMUM… https://t.co/OAUzm1MsN6 #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/BzDBervCSH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Software Developer: Next Century Corporation is seeking an innovative Cloud Software Engineer to join a stellar team working at our customer site in Reston, VA! This position provides the opportunity to play a key… https://t.co/9y5MkwoTCQ #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/lEdgEaIPAc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager: Position Overview: The Sr Project Manager is responsible for managing key projects as it relates to Operations, Vendor Implementations, New Product Development and major software enhancements.… https://t.co/5moMvpMMlU #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master Responsibilities: Facilitate all scrum ceremonies: Sprint Planning: help the team commit to a sprint goal with your product owner and decompose all stories and defect work into tasks with owners… https://t.co/y9qN83iiGP #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Applications Developer: Senior Applications Developer Senior Applications Developer We’re the obstacle overcomers, the problem get-arounders. From figuring it out to getting it done… our innovative culture demands… https://t.co/LRtvZPwSEM #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/4GnVyYEF3Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application/System Security Engineer – Active Secret Required: Clearance Level Must Currently Possess: Interim Secret Clearance Level Must Be Able to Obtain: Secret Suitability: No Suitability Required Job Family:… https://t.co/21VVt86GzF #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/aLo0idJaEV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior API Developer: Delta Air Lines, Inc, seeks a Senior API Developer with REST Web Services. The Senior API Developer will participate in the design, development and testing of REST API’s using Java to develop and… https://t.co/yI727ti4Qn #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/IIzV3sAGe9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master (SR782) Job: Scrum Master (SR782) (Job Number:434574) Description: SAIC is looking for an experienced Scrum Master Job Description: You will work in a highly collaborative and agile team environment to… https://t.co/4SKcfpG3Ly #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alibaba to invest extra $2 billion in Lazada in aggressive Southeast Asian expansion: BEIJING/SINGAPORE (Reuters) - Alibaba Group Holding Ltd said it will invest an extra $2 billion in Southeast Asian e-commerce firm Lazada… https://t.co/adjmMSOsou #news #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/zpVEuGMMKs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UX Design Engineer: UX Design Engineer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Design, Optimize, and add features to an existing HTML/JavaScript user interface Debug and fix all issues related to new features… https://t.co/WbFcGgSQhu #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior Cloud Developer: Category: Development/Engineering City: Arlington, Virginia, United States Position ID: J1117-2429 Employment Type: Full Time Meet our professionals CGI: A place to build an IT career Position… https://t.co/dQKVTMTIw8 #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce Systems Architect: Salesforce Systems Architect Ref No.: 18-09501 Location: Mt. Laurel, New Jersey Title- Salesforce Systems Architect Location- Mt. Laurel, NJ Duration- 12 Months Core Responsibilities Maintains… https://t.co/tH0GBkNES1 #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Software Engineer: Lead Software Engineer with Cox Enterprises Skip Navigation – Careers Home – Early Career – Join Our Talent Community – Blog – Manage Your Profile – Cox Enterprises – Cox Communications – Cox… https://t.co/vMUAcY17IZ #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Software QA Engineer: Summary:The Principal Software QA Engineer will be responsible for developing and lead test strategies and automation for NSC’s Software platform and IoT products. This person will also be… https://t.co/bDb8wp2UB6 #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/kUW3FNMnpD]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>