<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Limiting social media use reduced loneliness and depression in new experiment: The idea that social media can be harmful to our mental and emotional well-being is not a new one, but little has been done by researchers to directly measure the effect;… https://t.co/X6rrnqDwAu https://t.co/FJlRAWJk5C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Global Head of IT Strategy and Architecture:   Job Description – Global Head of IT Strategy and Architecture (41492) Job Description  Global Head of IT Strategy and Architecture-41492 Description   Are you looking for opportunities to work on high… https://t.co/U1DRx1UpAM https://t.co/OBI5hIvDHY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Data Scientist: Senior Data Scientist/London/£600-£700 We are searching for a Senior Data Scientist for a SME healthcare organisation, based in London. Ideally looking for someone to start ASAP, but will to wait for the right person. Paying a very… https://t.co/DXvMdu3Gjg https://t.co/2fuuHmnf8g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gift Guide: The best security and privacy tech to keep your friends safe: Libertarian on lockdown? Privacy minded or paranoid? Security is more front of mind today than ever before. If it’s not a company vacuuming up your data or nation states trying to… https://t.co/TnFxPfWwx8 https://t.co/p3l7VryDqQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C# Software Developer: We are looking for passionate C# Software Developers for our client based in Southampton. Responsibilities: • Design, build, and maintain efficient, reusable, and reliable C# and T-SQL code. • Deliver high quality functional… https://t.co/MHC9fDjsiq https://t.co/cF9E0SBzk5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Test Analyst: Test Analyst Overview A leading Software Services organisation are looking for a new experienced Senior Tester. The role provides the opportunity to work with an organisation creating innovative web and mobile applications within the… https://t.co/Psvf2Zw6jp https://t.co/3IhAkrIo5M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Implementation Manager: Our client is an exciting young Fintech business with big plans. Working with the country’s leading employers, they aim to turn the UK into a nation of investors, using their innovative online savings and investment platform. With… https://t.co/SePyhbtZpw https://t.co/647HQEarG0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Office 365 Consultant: Office 365 / Migration / Technical / Project / Management / Domino / Lotus Notes / Infrastructure My client who are based in the North East are currently on the lookout for a Technical Consultant to join their team on an initial 3… https://t.co/3GGdFllUrJ https://t.co/cu3rGGEWSq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst: Business Analyst £350 – £440/day – 6 month initial contract Based in Milton Keynes Our client is a well established Nationwide Rail company whose professionalism and well respected name have been instrumental in their success.They… https://t.co/AEBJENVeqY https://t.co/krhHSbMNVi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why you’re about to see a lot of drifting Tesla Model 3 videos: Tesla Model 3 owners who opted for the Performance variant now have a reason to go to the track. Or, if history is a guide, they’ll skip the track and try the newly released Track Mode… https://t.co/iOeJLI8Jdo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Brexit box: The people stockpiling food https://t.co/NWjs2qOnqF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Government-subsidised plug-in cars may never have been charged https://t.co/ue3sYKhVRj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior PHP Developer, New Division, Global Software Group: My client are driving new standards in the innovation and design of software solutions for the Education Sector. As part of a global group, we continuously challenge our great team to extend and… https://t.co/FUJITCWQ3q https://t.co/umm3Z6zqBy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Entry level/Experienced IT Recruiters/Resourcers – Permanent role in C: Entry level/Experienced IT Recruiters/Resourcers – Permanent role in Central Edinburgh Are you looking for something different to the usual Office Admin role? Are you fed up of jobs… https://t.co/hsuaR2aP7U https://t.co/Bf734wYmJF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can the startup building a Fortnite for VR become the Fortnite of VR?: Virtual reality hasn’t proven itself to be the lucrative escape of the every-man, but the medium has done a fairly good job enticing the gaming community and keeping that niche… https://t.co/TXE4yCf8iP https://t.co/OybeNAtW9w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solution Architect: We currently have an urgent requirement for an experience Banking Solution Architect to work on a client network programme focussed on lead generation for relationship managers within the bank using Quantexa. The project is basically… https://t.co/76CpYa2jOk https://t.co/EOBT73UCrz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Business System Analyst: The Senior Business System Analyst – Oracle Manufacturing has significant impact on achievement of operational goals by ensuring that any new software integration into company systems meets functional requirements, system… https://t.co/1bVgepMKuS https://t.co/XTyeW7qoxR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disney to invest in more original content for Hulu, expand service internationally: In addition to plans to launch its own Netflix rival, Disney+, next year, the company says it also plans to increase investment in its other streaming service, Hulu.… https://t.co/j9fcmNDQ6j https://t.co/3XyrnuA2Oc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Product Owner / Senior BA – Dorset £50-55k: Product Owner / Business Analyst required by our prestigious and fast growing Dorset based client. As a Product Owner, your primary responsibility is to maximise the value of the product delivered based on the… https://t.co/FbVZsZgKTT https://t.co/63ACTCmzgR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior Back-end Web Developer: Junior Back-end Web Developer Are you a back-end Web Developer with some industry experience post bachelor’s degree qualification looking for a new and exciting opportunity that offers excellent opportunities for… https://t.co/aRwMWKiGKL https://t.co/O1dB4nGDaL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sharepoint and O365 Consultant: Sharepoint and Office 365 Consultant To £60k + £Car allowance + 37 days holiday! ***Home Based &amp; Client site travel &amp; remote consulting project work*** The Opportunity As a Sharepoint and Office 365 Consultant, you will… https://t.co/OAadBUPzmC https://t.co/NKAv5bJLla]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Growing pains at venture-backed Moogsoft lead to layoffs: Moogsoft has laid off 30 employees and completed two C-suite hires. Its new COO Amer Deeba recently resigned from Qualys following SEC charges of insider trading. https://t.co/aHqgorhe70 https://t.co/FvA8myVcE7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apprentice Computer Engineer: Description Apprentice Computer Engineer £16,000 to £17,500 DOE Melksham, Wiltshire Permanent   My client is a leading independent rugged computer server and data storage manufacturer, based in Melksham, Wiltshire.     They… https://t.co/psq4iK7nkJ https://t.co/kklkFXHM5p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Analyst (Service Provider Authority): Principal Analyst (Service Provider Authority) Job Title: Principal Analyst About IHS Markit IHS Markit harnesses deep sources of information, analytics and expertise to forge solutions for the industries… https://t.co/VXjFlsIZjW https://t.co/oyzVi6EnfU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sony’s PlayStation Classic uses an open-source emulator to play its games: The worm has turned, it seems. Emulators, which let people run old console games on their computers, were once the scourge of the gaming industry. Now Sony is using one of the… https://t.co/FZfOg93E5Y https://t.co/2PNXghebT8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: Senior Java Developer (Java 8, Spring Boot, Agile) Location: Edinburgh (&amp; work from home 2 days per week) Benefits: Stock, Pension, Medical Insurance, Life Assurance, income protection etc. Salary: £60-£75k Depending on experience… https://t.co/uPvzJyLR23 https://t.co/vHsx2kAKUa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front End Developer: Front End Developer – Sheffield Ash Consulting are working with a Sheffield based client who currently seek to appoint an experienced formally trained Front End Developer on a permanent basis. The appointee will have input and… https://t.co/QIB76cqUtQ https://t.co/4dn3gIdFsK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer – Mid-Level: Python Developer – Full Stack – Mid-Level Python Developer – Full Stack – Mid-Level A Python Developer for a governance data platform in London. The company provides analysis of critical bank governance data and information… https://t.co/sPVUCtgMta https://t.co/5m8JS4iTYa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SoftBank’s debt, Ford buys Spin and Chinese coffee is huge money: Hello and welcome back to Equity, TechCrunch’s venture capital-focused podcast, where we unpack the numbers behind the headlines. This week was a blast. Connie and I were in the studio… https://t.co/bzX0dIcROj https://t.co/Q35YMpi3ib]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gracie: Pay discrimination 'embedded' in our culture https://t.co/zKVLFxB0Sn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NET SECURITY ARCHITECT – ANTWERP (12 MONTHS +): SECURITY ARCHITECT (.NET) – ANTWERP (12 MONTHS +) Senior Security Architect with a background in C# .NET development is needed by my client in Antwerp to start in January. Role: The Security Architect will… https://t.co/xmTjnz0JNG https://t.co/9YZqagSXDr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David Attenborough to voice Netflix’s nature conservation series, Our Planet: Netflix has persuaded everyone’s favorite naturalist, David Attenborough, to voice its forthcoming original nature documentary series, Our Planet, which is slated to put… https://t.co/Mncyl6GcYm https://t.co/wTK85gvja4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Security Architect: Security Architect A skilled Security Architect is wanted to become a valued and respected member of our client’s existing IT Team. You will report to the Technology Director, with the primary purpose of the role as Security Architect… https://t.co/dyzBTyI36m https://t.co/FOMJMVEzWr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google walkout organizers aren’t satisfied with CEO’s response: Organizers of the massive walkouts at Google last week are — rightfully so — not letting up on their demands. Earlier this morning, Google CEO Sundar Pichai responded to some of their… https://t.co/zR186IX4W4 https://t.co/zAqy1bgkDN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Service Desk Manager: An exciting opportunity has arisen for a Service Desk Manager to join a friendly team in Manchester Northern Quarter. You will be part of a dedicated, hardworking team delivering first point of contact for clients across the Greater… https://t.co/w7sqHVZf9s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UX/UI Designer: UX/UI Developer- Chessington- Salary (£Neg.) DOE + Bonus + Benefits An exciting, well-funded and innovative start-up company seeks exceptional UX/UI Developers to design and develop their bleeding edge products. The company has… https://t.co/kSDiTvSbVD https://t.co/RAdkeRHbkY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook removed 14 million pieces of terrorist content this year, and the numbers are rising: Facebook must exert constant vigilance to prevent its platform from being taken over by ne'er-do-wells, but how exactly it does that is only really known to… https://t.co/o03wb2a9JB https://t.co/YJLV2dN6Hk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brexit stockpiling: No room at food warehouse in Cardiff https://t.co/ZW8NpsCW5s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could these balls help reduce plastic pollution? https://t.co/9GgWHEhReS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walmart is building an AI lab inside one of its store: Walmart has just announced its plans to launch what it’s calling an Intelligent Retail Lab inside one of its stores in Levittown, New York. The idea is to test both associate and customer… https://t.co/zomjTAygbg https://t.co/lUOxyAqKZ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chatbot Architect – Conversational Architect: We are looking for a Chatbot Architect to work on a UK/USA project within HRs modernisation programme. This new piece of technology requires help drive and develop the chatbot product to enhance the delivery… https://t.co/ahNLZH1l6Z https://t.co/9Uc36L5gLK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three challenges facing blockchain technology: Blockchain technology will eventually impact many industries, but there is still a long way to go before blockchain technology can realize its true potential. Here are the three most important challenges… https://t.co/jIkVf0IAVz https://t.co/mOosYy94vR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manual Tester: Software Tester Burton upon Trent Permanent My client is a leading software house in the pharmaceutical industry having established themselves as one of the world’s leading providers of automation solutions for in-vitro diagnostics and… https://t.co/YbhiAMfdKb https://t.co/pi8WdiqIbo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Graduate/Junior Software Developer: Graduate/Junior Software Developer – £25,000 – £30,000 – Brighton C#, .Net, HTML, CSS, JavaScript We have a fantastic opportunity for a Graduate software developer to join a well-established software company based near… https://t.co/KpITUTUZxB https://t.co/TUGqIzSxLK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In House Penetration Tester – Multinational environment: A financial services company based in Sweden is looking for a pen tester to join their team in Sweden. They work in a multinational environment with people from all over the world working there so… https://t.co/zDZk5W4aKZ https://t.co/5uspuKVnIY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager- Data: Project Manager/Data- £30 a hour Umbrella- London- Contract My Client has released an exciting opportunity to join their team in London on a contract basis. The Senior Project Manager role is responsible for developing and project… https://t.co/8B9t5sQBTb https://t.co/xJkOv7VckP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PHP Software Engineer: PHP Software Engineer We are looking for a PHP Developer with experience in web based applications. As a PHP Software Engineer you will used to working in an AGILE environment. Experienced in PHP frameworks (Symfony/ Laravel etc),… https://t.co/yA52BUMTAK https://t.co/f4kMjlXOCI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Dir Product Manager: Associate Dir Product Manager Job Title: Associate Dir Product Manager About IHS Markit IHS Markit harnesses deep sources of information, analytics and expertise to forge solutions for the industries and markets that drive… https://t.co/o5B8nyD0iK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vine co-founder plans to launch successor Byte in Spring 2019: Vine — the much loved and mourned short video hosting platform — will return, kind of, sort of. Co-creator Dom Hofmann announced on Twitter today that its spiritual successor is set to arrive… https://t.co/6cSw9VAPnl https://t.co/69Mqo6suDA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big Data Engineer – Hadoop: My client is a leading health-tech startup headquartered in London. They are looking to hire a Big Data Engineer to build their next-generation big data solution. This a fast-growing, well-funded businesses with cutting-edge… https://t.co/M6wwulSOzK https://t.co/PD7pU0tWEO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer (Java, Golang , Linux ) A high growth, entrepreneurial company is looking for talented Java Developers– you will be part of a leading £1.5bn turnover, global online technology business that due to growth are expanding their… https://t.co/9Ob9CXnDza https://t.co/pY5PXuxGXQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Tester: Lead Tester Are you looking for a Lead Tester position where you will: • Test industry leading software applications • Work within an Agile software environment alongside a talented team • Earn up to £40,000 depending on experience •… https://t.co/1vkEOqPFSb https://t.co/vbbNCp5kJU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[National Grid unveils $250M corporate venture capital arm: Former Intel Capital managing director Lisa Lambert has launched National Grid Partners. https://t.co/TDSoKS8MsX https://t.co/XM1MDdV7JE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Helpdesk Engineer: My client is a rapidly growing IT re seller with a strong focus on IT Security, IT Managed Services and Support are seeking to appoint a Senior Helpdesk Engineer who will have responsibility for delivering 3rd Line Support… https://t.co/0cskoB4syd https://t.co/rAuRJdJ1z1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How the VBS 'bank heist' sparked a parliamentary brawl in South Africa https://t.co/RQG8kwl0s9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developers/C#/.Net Nottingham £35-40K: Software Developers/C#/.Net Nottingham £35-40K Greywood Associates are recruiting for a Market Leading company based in Nottingham who urgently require Software Developers to join their development team as… https://t.co/wSoKbTvNCl https://t.co/IijFlC724l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YouTube arrives on the Nintendo Switch: Nintendo has sold over 22 million Switch consoles since launch, with plans to sell another 20 million this fiscal year. That said, Nintendo hasn’t seemed too focused on building out its portfolio of non-gaming… https://t.co/qiGB0Zgxhf https://t.co/v9i5wW0yF6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior IT Engineer: Senior Infrastructure Engineer- Shrewsbury- £35,000-£50,000 + Benefits I am currently recruiting for a Senior Infrastructure engineer to join a large Software provider in Shrewsbury. This role will be joining a talented team of… https://t.co/4hoqHoH9AE https://t.co/PAp58zhol2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BI Developer: BI Developer Location – Birmingham Salary – £45,000 to £50,000 A large, well known company are looking for a BI Developer to join the growing Business Intelligence division. You will play a key part in the introduction of BI to the business… https://t.co/Cc5aBNqImw https://t.co/HP5hapNlVL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Security flaw in DJI’s website and apps exposed accounts to hackers and drone live feeds: It took about six months for popular consumer drone maker DJI to fix a security vulnerability across its website and apps, which if exploited could have given an… https://t.co/8Xb6pIRZmj https://t.co/vjbvRvsmYd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst: My client are keen on a Business Analyst joining joining them to capture, model and apply business and data requirements so that innovative technology solutions can be designed and developed to underpin their business processes. The… https://t.co/vmLPL5dY7o https://t.co/czREeguXaO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla names Robyn Denholm as chair to replace Elon Musk https://t.co/nnvbLvIV7d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toshiba's UK withdrawal puts Cumbria nuclear plant in doubt https://t.co/7JHnptApXJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grab lands $50M from Thailand’s Kasikorn Bank to further its fintech push: Southeast Asia ride-hailing firm Grab is continuing to add strategic investors to its ongoing Series H round — which is targeted at over $3 billion — after it revealed Thai bank… https://t.co/Xs8dOc2m2j https://t.co/vHz51uSHFc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – £35k – £55k – Southampton: Software Engineer – £30k – £55k – Southampton C/C++, C#, Java Software Engineer required by a growing technology company based in Southampton. The company are looking for a well-rounded Software Engineer to… https://t.co/AGXAn8LSmc https://t.co/hELV3hHbTQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Development Executive Fintech Surrey: Business Development Executive Fintech Surrey Are you looking to join one of the UK’s most forward thinking Fintech Company’s where you can make a real difference. If you have, a passion for sales and a real… https://t.co/FZV3QDIaUV https://t.co/CrZ30edtk8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla picks telco executive Robyn Denholm to replace Elon Musk as chairman: Elon Musk’s replacement as the chair of Tesla has been named and it is Robyn Denholm, an Australian executive who has been a director with the electric vehicle firm since 2014.… https://t.co/PhP4YD7bB1 https://t.co/uYRoKedNmV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Net Web Developer: Web Developer We have an exciting opportunity that is ideal for a .NET web developer looking to develop their career with a forward thinking and highly successful digital marketing agency. This Kent based award winning digital agency… https://t.co/B0Vy4hzE0p https://t.co/PTSWcygkAb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Developer /Middleware /SOA Integration Developer – Essex: Senior Integration Developer (Java 1.8) – High profile integration project – Essex Salary/Rate £525/day Location Essex Agency People Source Consulting Description Senior Developer – High… https://t.co/6y9OaRbkqt https://t.co/KdqcZKt4yd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Samsung’s dual-screen folding phone is very strange and probably doomed: Let me just say that I love the idea of a folding phone/tablet device. I was a Courier fanboy when Microsoft floated that intriguing but abortive concept device, and I'm all for… https://t.co/UbOoJtGQz7 https://t.co/LSOx6OSE50]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Software Engineer: Working for one of the world’s leading supplier of technology, integrated project management and information solutions to customers working in the oil and gas industry worldwide. This company are currently recruiting for a Cloud… https://t.co/uVGDZNKLud https://t.co/yWtpw9DVnK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2nd Line IT Infrastructure Engineer – large training budget: Do you have some good 2nd Line IT Support based skills? Are you looking to work as part of a great team with a fun positive culture? Are you looking to work with a growing company that is able… https://t.co/uTQz1wfvhd https://t.co/0SVvSx2AQx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Engineer – Cloud / Hosted: Do you have experience of assisting in the architecture and deployment of secure highly available cloud and on-premise services? Want to work for an expanding multi-award-winning organisation who value their staff,… https://t.co/jRuJynWsy8 https://t.co/QxASbEDQZj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[20 startups take center stage at Berkeley SkyDeck’s demo day: A robot that can clean your house, a blockchain-powered social network and 18 other startups presented to investors at SkyDeck's 8th demo day. https://t.co/hZToVPz2TI https://t.co/EjC79jmuBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check team leader – Security Consultant: This innovative global consultancy is looking to bring one more Check Team Leader on board. This is an amazing opportunity to join a company that really invest in you and the technologies. KEY EXPERIENCE REQUIRED… https://t.co/DscFrkDtkw https://t.co/OZRcY9ncow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learning and Development Manager:   Job Description – Learning and Development Manager (26562) Job Description  Learning and Development Manager – 26562  Profession : HR Specialist  Work Location : Europe-United Kingdom-London  Schedule :Full-time … https://t.co/SaAA78TUTF https://t.co/09fiEhheeZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer: Full stack developer required to join a rapidly expanding AI software consultancy, candidates will benefit from a highly autonomous environment with regular interesting projects within a range of UK Clients. Travel is not a requirement for… https://t.co/TezNV5PV9Y https://t.co/VLHNAeFdQr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CircleCI launches Orbs, a package manager for software delivery automation: DevOps platform CircleCI today announced a new partner program that will open up its platform and allow third-party tools to integrate with it. In addition, the company is… https://t.co/RlmPACGInP https://t.co/qb25JlBvUB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test Automation Engineer: Test Automation Engineer Selenium/AWS/Docker Are you a Test Automation Engineer who wants to work in a complex Microservices environment? Enjoy end to end testing? Want to lead and owning test strategy and implementation for a… https://t.co/Qwv0shrV95 https://t.co/OhRgHyVyH0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Packager: Application Packager – Glasgow – 3 Months Location – Glasgow Rate – £300 – £340 Per day Length – 3 Months initial contract with view to extend You will be responsible for full application life cycle from Packaging and User… https://t.co/JDoSO2yXvl https://t.co/sQpNh8s7DG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sling TV’s growth further slows in Q3, but still leads rivals in terms of subscribers: It appears Dish’s live TV streaming service, Sling TV, has been impacted by the increased competition from rivals like YouTube TV, Hulu with Live TV, AT&amp;T’s DirecTV… https://t.co/SvXfjOzkoV https://t.co/rCiMCm3F9S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Project Manager / Account Manager / BA An experienced Project Manager is required ideally with an exciting blend of Project Management and account management experience for a leading software and business intelligence provider based in… https://t.co/3mzor0EDfR https://t.co/y7L7axGef5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PHP Developer: We are currently working with a leading development agency with office in Central London and in the South-West, Salisbury. The client are a recognised name on the Agency side of development and are a true testament to the industry, leading… https://t.co/jNhUfQcx8U https://t.co/kEsZA1d1wE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JK Rowling sues former employee for £24,000 https://t.co/AMmSlDhxdG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brooklinen launches a pop-up shop in NYC: Brooklinen, the direct-to-consumer bed linens brand, has today announced the opening of a four-month pop-up shop in NYC. The company has been around for four years thus far, and recently hit $100 million in… https://t.co/RByXLRjEnK https://t.co/MCjpF5Sa2N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Consultant: Network Consultant – Cisco, Juniper, Network design and implementation, pre sales support, Layer 2/3, LAN/WAN Fantastic opportunity to join an innovative Company in a senior Network role that provides specialist services to its client… https://t.co/YIZ9rrnv1L https://t.co/flbnmrgFIu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Support Analyst: One to One Recruitment is working with Family Fund to recruit a full time, 12 month fixed term contract System Support Analyst to join their team in York. Are you looking for a role where your talents benefit the lives of… https://t.co/u2PezIjuQJ https://t.co/Zbkr2kN0LK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spotify Connect speakers will soon work with its free-tier: Spotify’s ad-supported tier has long been one of the service’s differentiators. Naturally, the model’s not nearly as feature rich as its paid counterpart, though the company’s removing one of… https://t.co/x7dpKenqVA https://t.co/2N6RV9Wmp6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solutions Architect (remote working available): Solution Architect £80,000 Remote working I am currently looking for a Solutions Architect for a global Ecommerce organisation based in Solihull. Due to the continuous growth, and the need to improve the… https://t.co/KlZNHqcs3S https://t.co/vWbRZTycrH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BI Developer – PowerBI: Our Client is an industry leading organization with over 4,000 employees spanning the UK. Human Capital Ventures has been selected to recruit a Business Intelligence Developer, working for our Client Headquartered in Northampton,… https://t.co/wyf0CPyELP https://t.co/2TMw3XYy2W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social media 'lifts' are becoming an 'illegal industry' https://t.co/RLhWQYwYi0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Female pilots: Which airline has the highest number? https://t.co/qyGbA4nP67]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Home Made raises further £2M for its premium online lettings agency: Home Made, the London premium online lettings agency, has raised a further £2 million in funding. The round is led by Athens-based venture capital firm VentureFriends, and follows the… https://t.co/oMhgtiWuwM https://t.co/fHwtX9EzOc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Net Software Developer: NET Developer Job description The .NET Software Developer role is a vital part of the development team responsible for creating, designing, maintaining and implementing large software projects. You will also be involved in the… https://t.co/KzM9P8agSu https://t.co/FJ1puOXbVg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook connects Russia to 100+ accounts it removed ahead of mid-terms: The 115 accounts Facebook took down yesterday for inauthentic behavior ahead of the mid-term elections may indeed have been linked to the Russia-based Internet Research Agency,… https://t.co/Gmydl67uk5 https://t.co/8qfk6rBOQA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Change: Project Manager – Change, Permanent, Dublin City Centre I have an exciting opportunity for a Change / Project Manager to join my Clients Dublin City Centre office where you be part of creating a Change Management team. The… https://t.co/E6q1QfVlEf https://t.co/CUh54X3sVO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Performance Tester (Loadrunner) – SC Cleared – Hampshire: I'm looking for a security Cleared (SC Level) Perfomance Tester that has strong skills using Loadrunner – this role is based in Andover in Hampshire and will be a rolling 6 month contract https://t.co/sNXcriEFL6 https://t.co/5Qf9iVfq3E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst – Manufacturing (ASTONJOBS): Gi Group are working closely with Aston Martin to introduce to them the highest level of candidates to work within the new Vehicle Plant. A career at Aston Martin means joining one of the world's most… https://t.co/DMC5rQIGgN https://t.co/awFueN6hZo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tinder now has 4.1M paying users, expects $800M in revenue this year: Tinder is leading growth for Match Group (NASDAQ: MTCH), which posted third-quarter earnings of 44 cents per share on Tuesday. https://t.co/j6eY79VUOv https://t.co/gAGN4twj9V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Service Desk Coordinator: Are you exceptionally well-organised with outstanding communication skills over the phone and emails? One of the largest and most well-established logistics organisations in the world is looking for you. They have a need for a… https://t.co/cTijUT50Hf https://t.co/5NPSCOd5AT]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>