<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Applications Software Engineer II: Overview Do you excel in an environment that values exploration and discovery? We have a universe of opportunities waiting for you! The Jet Propulsion Laboratory (JPL) is NASA’s… https://t.co/HwXYxqCrlH #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/AtnO8xlGje]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[software engineer: Web Applications Software Engineer Job Location: Denver, Co. or Salt Lake City, Ut. Our Company – Helix Education We understand the serious challenges facing higher education – namely a shift in student… https://t.co/vuT3BDffNL #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/ZFVT8lgqkI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Database Engineer: Sr. Database Engineer Location Pasadena, CA Department Development Job Code 2583 Apply Now Green Dot Corporation, along with its wholly owned subsidiary bank, Green Dot Bank, is a pro-consumer… https://t.co/6WZUI3yZuR #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/9NsqaMRlzF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Applications Developer: Senior Applications Developer Senior Applications Developer We’re the obstacle overcomers, the problem get-arounders. From figuring it out to getting it done… our innovative culture demands… https://t.co/p05BOojqRS #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/PfAtbB2ahf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technologist – Full Stack Solutions Architect: Technologist – Full Stack Solutions ArchitectWe deliver our customers peace of mind every day by helping them protect what they value most. Our passion for placing the customer… https://t.co/Qhru6DbUf2 #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/MHlJVZl7nH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineers – Cloud: Please note that this position is located in Newark, DE or Boston, MA. Object Oriented Software Engineers – Platform SevOne strives for excellence in application-aware network performance… https://t.co/4ktRv9UQkh #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/82Uu7S4clY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[iOS Mobile Developer – Expert: Where good people build rewarding careers. Think that working in the insurance field cant be exciting, rewarding and challenging? Think again. Youll help us reinvent protection and retirement… https://t.co/VzhiZr9ZDs #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/Aqrrqykszi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republican lawmakers concerned by Facebook data leak: WASHINGTON (Reuters) - Several U.S. Republican lawmakers expressed concern over privacy violations on Sunday after media reports that a political consultancy that worked on… https://t.co/XjIPmAjRcy #news #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/xkDezqOa9q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[software engineer: Do you consider yourself a progressive and innovative Java software engineer? Are you looking to provide technology leadership and hands-on coding skills with technologies and tool chains such as: Spring,… https://t.co/SXXtQ8yqTJ #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/EyGDpQFGzZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Software Developer: We deliver our customers peace of mind every day by helping them protect what they value most. Our passion for placing the customer at the center of everything we do is driving a… https://t.co/h9pYQZWked #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/2Yoo40E66O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Scrum Master: Job Title: Senior Scrum Master Location: Chicago, IL Duration- 6 Months Roles &amp; Responsibility Guiding the team and organization on how to use Agile/Scrum practices and values to delight customers –… https://t.co/PE4Ynrztsa #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer (Node): SENIOR SOFTWARE ENGINEER (NODE) Los Angeles. Full-time. As soon as possible. inShare ‘" style="border: none; padding: 0px; height: 20px; visibility: visible; width: 67px; background:… https://t.co/8BzC7G2gzV #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/39wScLcPYd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Backend Developer: The Senior Backend Developer’s primary responsibilities are to code robust solutions and assist in managing a flexible pool of vendor and freelance developer talent to expand BlueprintNYC’s core… https://t.co/hslmz0ouE0 #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/vr0pr49xbK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Job TitleScrum Master – ID:29933 DurationPermanent Start DateASAP Job SkillsA minimum of four years of related project management. A minimum of two years of scrum master experience. Kanban methodology… https://t.co/B23f2OdW3A #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Scrum Master: Senior Scrum Master – Careers Home – About Us – People &amp; Culture – University Recruiting – Total Rewards – Growth &amp; Learning – Featured Locations – Europe, Middle East &amp; Africa Jobs – Asia &amp; South… https://t.co/z2fe1h4q6D #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Build Engineer: Software Build, Release, and Tools Engineer Keurig Brewers utilize advanced technology to deliver the Perfect Cup, in every cup. The brewer firmware monitors sensor inputs, controls… https://t.co/9ifPHCKTDP #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/7HNQmbHsVj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Cloud Software Engineer: Company Corporation (NYSE: Company) is the global leader in consumer transaction technologies, turning everyday interactions with businesses into exceptional experiences. With its software,… https://t.co/saHNqSav5l #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer System Analyst ( Java Developer): Internal_Careers | Marvel Technologies Inc Skip to main content – – – – Call :+1 ************ – ********************* – Employee Login Main navigation – Home – Company – About –… https://t.co/pOKDMhNrUZ #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook critics want regulation, investigation after data misuse: SAN FRANCISCO (Reuters) - Facebook Inc faced new calls for regulation from within U.S. Congress and was hit with questions about personal data safeguards on… https://t.co/PYQbnA2jcE #news #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/Z9VnF5QP8b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Category: Project Management City: Phoenix, Arizona, United States Position ID: J0218-1065 Employment Type: Full Time Position Description: POSITION DESCRIPTION The person who fills this position will be… https://t.co/3pwHYncoYy #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/fZokXNe7wc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager (SCRUM/AGILE): Job TitleProject Manager (SCRUM/AGILE) – ID:31152 Duration12 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsAgile, Scrum Master LocationPlano, TX Date Posted03/02/2018 FOR IMMEDIATE DETAILS ABOUT THIS… https://t.co/YYfJUplnoL #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/Uky9Vnu0eg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP BI/BOBJ HANA Cloud Analytics Senior Consultant – Virtual USA Job: Date: Mar 8, 2018 Location: Newtown Square, PA, US Company: SAP Requisition ID: ****** Work Area: Consulting and Professional Services Expected Travel: 0… https://t.co/2zeHDf9hsi #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master (SR782) Job: Scrum Master (SR782) (Job Number:434574) Description: SAIC is looking for an experienced Scrum Master Job Description: You will work in a highly collaborative and agile team environment to… https://t.co/sZ90WVzPnm #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer Software 2: At Northrop Grumman, our employees have incredible opportunities to work on revolutionary systems in air and space that impact people’s lives around the world today, and for generations to come. Our… https://t.co/Pkw6kytEH0 #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Assurance-Assurance Support-Innovation Solutions-ASR INNOV – QA-Manage: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for… https://t.co/F8rHyYiUJ8 #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/xoxKb22bFf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embedded Software Developer: Why join Irdeto? We are on a mission! A mission to secure the world’s digital platforms. Why? Because a secure platform allows our clients to produce and deliver great content. In return, you… https://t.co/hx4hgM9rYm #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer: Were Hearst Autos and we are going to change the way consumers buy automobiles. With a recognized brand Car and Driver and the best editorial team in the automotive industry were cutting a new… https://t.co/tpWg3SanmG #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/LHSIabdcEt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager/Scrum Master: JOB DESCRIPTION: Resource 1 is in need of a Project Manager/Scrum Master for a 8-12- month contract in Rosemont, Illinois. Client is open to either long-term contract or conversion to… https://t.co/PVvw48PVwb #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/Fk465Ll9Xv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Consultant 6: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at… https://t.co/ashKNYc5SW #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/ZFH2ZlQBbX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9060_Android Developer: Back to Jobs Location: Atlanta, GA, United States Salary: DOE Posted: Oct 12 Reply ASAP to – sachin@reqroute.com OR Call at- 408-300-9060 Android Application Developer Atlanta, GA Hire-type: C2C/W2… https://t.co/HHCHWLzLzu #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rocket Internet explores IPO of online shopping group Jumia: sources: FRANKFURT (Reuters) - German start-up investor Rocket Internet is exploring a stock market listing of loss-making African online shopping platform Jumia,… https://t.co/178QueltXa #news #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/yhaXSSTpmj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid-Level Java API Developer (Java, Rest API, JS), Secret Cleared: DescriptionMID-LEVEL JAVA API DEVELOPER (Java, Rest API, JS) Title: Mid-Level Java API Developer (Java, Rest API, JS) Location: Centreville, VA Terms:… https://t.co/soKl8JQNwk #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (Entry-Level): There are 7 billion people on this planet. And by 2050, there will be 2 billion more… many moving into urban centers at an unprecedented rate. Making sure there is enough food, fiber and… https://t.co/yLuGuOqTY5 #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BA / Scrum Master: Position Overview: The Scrum Master leads the Agile process for one or more Scrum teams, ensuring predictable delivery of software releases within scope. This position is also responsible for the ongoing… https://t.co/pD7DeWRQ4m #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/SiGHCNIgSK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (PHP): Akkadian Labs focuses exclusively on creating collaboration inspired software that maximizes business results by improving the way people communicate and work together. Our solutions include turnkey… https://t.co/PprrtCDx5P #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/LFl7yabn77]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager (SCRUM/AGILE): Job TitleProject Manager (SCRUM/AGILE) – ID:31152 Duration12 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsAgile, Scrum Master LocationPlano, TX Date Posted03/02/2018 FOR IMMEDIATE DETAILS ABOUT THIS… https://t.co/L1AUwJLSUU #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/uO9IV401cd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Masters: Scrum Masters San jose, California – United States Job Start Date – 02/15/18, Posted Date – 02/15/18 Primary SkillsScrum,DPM,artifactsTax TermsC2COverview Job Scope * Partners with Engineering Lead to create… https://t.co/CzPK4ZxFKc #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/1rgtIKXORW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Technical Project Manager: Paper Street Media, LLC (***************************** is a successful, web-based adult entertainment video on demand network, located in the heart of Downtown, Miami. We are a fun, hip,… https://t.co/kSjHmqUgUh #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/bK2awPB4Xv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Team Lead (Scrum Master) Job: Team Lead (Scrum Master) (Job Number:431672) Description: JOB DESCRIPTION: Team Lead (Scrum Master) – Scrum Master certification from accredited organization, i.e., Scrum Master Certified… https://t.co/1EDJc9LRqK #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior EA Modeler/Developer: Supports the development, configuration, testing and deployment and integration of PeopleSoft/OIAM Application Security for the IPPS-A project. Provides support for systems development and… https://t.co/XuDQMAx52c #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/DUsURDg2Bj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Manager 3 – WIM SQA Manager: Job Description Wells Fargo Enterprise Systems Quality Assurance (ESQA) Testing Center of Excellence is accountable for Systems Quality Assurance strategies, standards, execution and… https://t.co/GqOGHGeOZG #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/LHfUgHsmCj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior DevOps Engineer: As a DevOps Engineer at Athlinks, a division at Life Time fitness, you will be an embedded member and hands-oncontributor of an Agile/Scrum Delivery team. You will be in an environment that fosters… https://t.co/mA0wOf2xF8 #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/ejHMdxGI0Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK city Birmingham wants further details from Uber before license decision: LONDON (Reuters) - Britain's second city Birmingham is seeking clarity from Uber [UBER.UL] on its business model as it decides whether to renew the taxi… https://t.co/LOBL0Y3PG2 #news #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/yXpwabj4JJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Staff Engineer: Senior Staff Engineer (job location is Seattle, WA) Design &amp; write code for video services designed to enhance HBO’s video streaming capability &amp; content associated w/ company’s interactive endeavors.… https://t.co/eutB2Jpjhq #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/pt8liJvcP7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Project Manager: ***CLIENT UNABLE TO SPONSOR AT THIS TIME** NO C2C VENDORS JOB DESCRIPTION Plans and coordinates all aspects of internal information system-specific projects from initiation to delivery. Projects… https://t.co/DaXLfokhBH #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/wUix7d6oqJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Masters: Scrum Masters MEMPHIS, Tennessee – United States Job Start Date – 03/07/18, Posted Date – 03/07/18 Primary SkillsAgile,ScrumTax TermsC2COverview Requirements * Requires thorough knowledge of general… https://t.co/dloC7eTaQd #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/myTtRuY1zH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full-Stack Ruby on Rails Developer: THE OPPORTUNITY KleerMail is looking for a experienced and talented Full-Stack Ruby on Rails developer to contribute to the implementation of our Software-as-a-Service (SaaS) product… https://t.co/mTaqZSVEUH #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/etiYqcV7D7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Developer: Are you a software craftsman? At HealthStream, we build scalable Web applications that assess and develop healthcare professionals in hospitals all over the United States. Our solutions must balance… https://t.co/eJGkfUcTmS #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/IVQ4pQMiCr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer: The Senior Software Engineer is responsible for the designing, developing, and supporting an existing .NET C# application and will work closely with the Architect and other developers within a scrum… https://t.co/ZPvq4y5rKL #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/Jh8e8j5KAg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Project Manager: Senior Technical PM with Strong Mobile application and API Contract: 6+ Months Location: Chicago, IL Qualifying area : Strong mobile application and API/Integration. Responsibilities: * Standard… https://t.co/tvgcSbUWOH #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/7pTbKECE0D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Applications Software Engineer II: Overview Do you excel in an environment that values exploration and discovery? We have a universe of opportunities waiting for you! The Jet Propulsion Laboratory (JPL) is NASA’s… https://t.co/JOU19hYR8G #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/ubZuYUyaFu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Manager 3 – WIM SQA Manager: Job Description Wells Fargo Enterprise Systems Quality Assurance (ESQA) Testing Center of Excellence is accountable for Systems Quality Assurance strategies, standards, execution and… https://t.co/L06keYXMFO #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/UdkyN9Dr1w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master We’re Hearst Autos and we are going to change the way consumers buy automobiles. With a recognized brand Car &amp; Driver, and the best editorial team in the automotive industry, we’re cutting a new… https://t.co/be6D433nzh #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/jOBrYmhTgr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: globaledit, the brand behind the leading secure cloud-based creative collaboration service for professional digital photography and digital media, is seeking an experienced, digitally savvy Project Manager /… https://t.co/G6WtqN9aSW #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/axSKSaeydx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coca-Cola, U.S. State Dept to use blockchain to combat forced labor: NEW YORK (Reuters) - Coca-Cola Co and the U.S. State Department along with two other companies said on Friday they are launching a project using blockchain's… https://t.co/syk0aGSwB3 #news #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/kz0V5PtDNj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior C# .NET Programmer: Developing great software takes more than just writing code. It takes a cohesive team, passionate about developing elegant products that scale exponentially in an extremely short time-frame and… https://t.co/wkc6AzszTT #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/UyN61VdLSG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CNO Developer: Req ID 96669BR Business Title CNO Developer Group MCIS Location USA VIRGINIA Herndon Clearance Level Needed Secret Category Cyber Job Duties and Responsibilities Independently develops hardware or software… https://t.co/BltFCl1hJW #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/9JpusmXRI7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Oracle Application Developer – EBS, OAF, Forms: Are you an Oracle application developer with strong experience in Oracle E-Business Suite (EBS) and Oracle Application Framework (OAF)? Are you proficient in general… https://t.co/szMn6s0UmP #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/zcedqtl7K0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master – US IT SOLUTIONS: Scrum Master Job Description Deliver value to Assurant by working as the Scrum master to help Agile based teams successfully and effectively deliver Sprints: * Facilitates activities… https://t.co/H2pIo6dZnY #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer Columbus, OH. Design &amp; write code for web or mobile apps. that scale to high-volume production quality. Job #: 180016184. Duties:  Design and write code for web or mobile applications… https://t.co/AMXXxIy3Vb #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/dcuXWdDfzq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Automation Engineer, Accurate Background: QA Automation Engineer will ensure the delivery of world-class high-quality applications for the various Accurate Background platforms. You will be triaging bug reports,… https://t.co/5N1FRF3BWd #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/2wPu9pyTPB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Secure Environment Software Developer (CO-OP ): Why join Irdeto? We are on a mission! A mission to secure the world’s digital platforms. Why? Because a secure platform allows our clients to produce and deliver great… https://t.co/juHm0DRMJv #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/SrK5StMg2H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Application Developer: Senior Application Developer CSI Leasing (CSI) is one of the largest independent equipment leasing specialists in the world, with customers in more than 36 countries. Established in 1972, we… https://t.co/djyv3tKedR #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/yrfP9SsGvP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master Denver, Colorado – United States Job Start Date – 02/13/18, Posted Date – 02/13/18 Primary SkillsScrum master,Agile – Certified Scrum Product Owner,CSPOTax TermsC2COverview * 10-14 Years * 1… https://t.co/IjJ1S9H65N #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/rpcEc6VBXE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer Senior: Req ID : 406384BR Job Code/Title : E1073:Software Engineer Sr Job Description : This position is for a software engineer to support the Advanced Programs projects. The candidate will work in an… https://t.co/hkTZ8JGd4V #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/RzmLlxqVnO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bike-sharing companies face an uphill ride in U.S.: SAN FRANCISCO (Reuters) - A bike-sharing craze that has swept China over the past two years is picking up speed in cities across the United States, but with a different spin as… https://t.co/3GB02oqw6D #news #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/BGcD5XxIAh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Who we are? Aquila is one of the fastest growing FinTech companies in Silicon Valley. Aquila delivers cash analytics and cash access to thousands of small businesses, that operate with volatile… https://t.co/NuHKgT4mXe #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/asv6zyQImX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Assurance-Assurance Support-Innovation Solutions-ASR INNOV – QA-Direct: PwC/LOS OverviewPwC is a network of firms committed to delivering quality in assurance, tax and advisory services. We help resolve complex issues for… https://t.co/BtTIM5In28 #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/4ZCx9XdoAO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Web Developer: Web Developer Equus Software, a rapidly growing technology company, needs passionate web developers for the AssignmentPro software product development team in Denver, Colorado. We are looking for… https://t.co/4a8NfMc1XY #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/NvXm4xf4ea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer: Developing great software takes more than just writing code. It takes a cohesive team, passionate about developing elegant products that scale exponentially in an extremely short time-frame. A team… https://t.co/r0xOCBA8PC #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/QQxUC4RzLQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master – SAFe, CSM, CI, Back-end: Do you want to be part of a dynamic, fail-fast environment where the spirit of experimentation is recognized and encouraged? Do you want to work with some of the smartest people you… https://t.co/HoLGcl6okr #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/Nb2uqPKw5H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Manager 3 – WIM SQA Manager: Job Description Wells Fargo Enterprise Systems Quality Assurance (ESQA) Testing Center of Excellence is accountable for Systems Quality Assurance strategies, standards, execution and… https://t.co/t8T3t5iLuw #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/0ObQH7SuzA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Category: Project Management City: Phoenix, Arizona, United States Position ID: J0218-1065 Employment Type: Full Time Position Description: POSITION DESCRIPTION The person who fills this position will be… https://t.co/Vx7pIgNdzl #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/SQ9vnUoqpO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solution Architect – Digital Platform: The Senior Enterprise Client Executive is responsible for both identifying and selling to new clients while continuing to develop and grow business with existing clients. The selected… https://t.co/oRrouViaDC #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/jfmYLjujBl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: OM1 is a leading healthcare technology company focused on providing outcomes measurement and predictive analytics for value-based and personalized healthcare. Leveraging big clinical data,… https://t.co/cOvHkLiTZF #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/Di5R7M2zwo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK's CMC Markets launches cryptocurrency trading: (Reuters) - Online trading platform CMC Markets Plc said on Thursday it had launched contracts for differences (CFDs) and spreadbetting offerings for cryptocurrencies following… https://t.co/TdVPHbnVvu #news #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/PbwKa7CAnT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big Data Architect: Join our Big Data Team and work on dynamic long-term projects. The majority of our team members are long-term employees who enjoy consistent work and a collaborative team approach! KEY ACCOUNTABILITIES:… https://t.co/CuqEC3jSla #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/18mczlvUqI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETL Software Developers: Rx Savings, LLC d/b/a Rx Savings Solutions – ETL Software Developers in Overland Park, KS   Support the implementation and development of ETL (Extract Transform Load) processes for data warehousing… https://t.co/Awl7M9zaDH #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/eaTVrhchSS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Test Automation Engineer: Company Corporation (NYSE: Company) is the global leader in consumer transaction technologies, turning everyday interactions with businesses into exceptional experiences. With its software,… https://t.co/vLHXJbbdjB #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/cNUExDY8X0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer: As a Senior Software Developer at Ascensus, you will be working in a high-energy team, writing beautiful code by using the best engineering practices in the industry today (e.g. unit testing, source… https://t.co/poyWvaETgE #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master Responsibilities: Facilitate all scrum ceremonies: Sprint Planning: help the team commit to a sprint goal with your product owner and decompose all stories and defect work into tasks with owners… https://t.co/NHYtwWbEYz #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/Rds9ZaGspK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Long Term Care: Software Engineer – Long Term Care – Swisslog designs, develops and delivers best-in-class automation solutions for forward-thinking hospitals, warehouses and distribution centers. We… https://t.co/vcmgiiY5Az #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/HG9aogugx5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Agile Coach: Position Purpose: Lead software development teams in project initiation, organization, goal and change management aspects of AgileDiscover opportunities to champion agile values and adoption across ITDevelop… https://t.co/HjjJ6p6ouY #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/NdqG8b4J1Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South Korea's Lotte Data Communication says plans IPO: SEOUL (Reuters) - Lotte Data Communication Co, a unit of South Korea's Lotte Group, said on Thursday it has sought approval from the country's stock exchange for an initial… https://t.co/D4DZrcmvov #news #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/0yyKQg1RRi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[iOS mobile application developer II: iOS mobile application developer II – Y &amp; L Consulting Inc. – Austin, TX – 02-27-2018 | ******** Toggle navigation – Tech Careers – Job Search – Skills Center – Dice Careers Mobile –… https://t.co/LSHoy2bpRI #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Software Developer: Sentry Insurance Talent Network If you are hard-working and dedicated – create a future with Sentry. OVERVIEW Want to get a head start on your Major? Jump-start your career opportunities? Build… https://t.co/RSZBotICAs #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/gL87zlIxHP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MDM Technical Lead: Job TitleMDM Technical Lead – ID:31097 Duration3 Months to Hire Start DateASAP Job SkillsRequired minimum of 5 Years application development experience with proven track record of success. Expertise with… https://t.co/6mh7OvVepr #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/7Y3xHEotGn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Assurance and Release Specialist: Quality Assurance and Release Specialist / Cincinnati , OH Overview: Join our scrum team with a focus on Quality Assurance and release planning for our Core Product Development… https://t.co/JoYG8CjqqA #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/3JB349i9rw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology Lead – US: Infosys Retail, CPG &amp; Logistics Technology Lead US DevOps Infosys is a global leader in technology services and consulting. We enable clients in more than 50 countries to create and execute strategies… https://t.co/LLW3P0HPBG #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Integration Test Lead: Sr. Integration Test Lead – (1800004E) Description JOB SUMMARY: The Senior Integration/Test Lead will be responsible for systems integration, test plan, design and support technical activities… https://t.co/DDZtrJ3kuD #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer: Were Hearst Autos and we are going to change the way consumers buy automobiles. With a recognized brand Car and Driver and the best editorial team in the automotive industry were cutting a new… https://t.co/bY08Yr8Wza #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embedded Software Developer: Why join Irdeto? We are on a mission! A mission to secure the world’s digital platforms. Why? Because a secure platform allows our clients to produce and deliver great content. In return, you… https://t.co/xV9H0bjU3P #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer – Corporate – St. Louis, MO: Role Overview: We are seeking an Angular developer with a C# .NET background to join our team in St. Louis, MO. You will have the opportunity to utilize a wide range of new… https://t.co/D6Htx0HHHI #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer Analyst – Mobile App Developer: Aon Hewitt has announced BCAA as a 2018 Canadian Gold Level Best EmployerBusiness &amp; IT SolutionsBCAA is looking for a versatile regular full-time Senior Software… https://t.co/NwtCHpBgFx #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[France to sue Google, Apple over developer contracts: minister: PARIS (Reuters) - France said on Wednesday it will take Google and Apple to court and seek fines of 2 million euros ($2.5 million) over what it termed "abusive"… https://t.co/JFku8M2ndy #news #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/x8HyPRV3Jv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer in Test: Software Engineer in Test The Software Engineer in Test is responsible for designing, developing, and analyzing automated test suites and tools for Accruents asset management software.… https://t.co/k3LLOEMkik #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/lEn3eolvyo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Automation Engineer, Accurate Background: QA Automation Engineer will ensure the delivery of world-class high-quality applications for the various Accurate Background platforms. You will be triaging bug reports,… https://t.co/14LYRiTr8G #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job https://t.co/vhwKWSsiO5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Oracle Application Developer – EBS, OAF, Forms: Are you an Oracle application developer with strong experience in Oracle E-Business Suite (EBS) and Oracle Application Framework (OAF)? Are you proficient in general… https://t.co/IZEgldqviI #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front End Engineer: Become a part of the family, become a TaxSlayer! At TaxSlayer, our products radically transform the way people use technology, allowing them to spend less time on the things they have to do and more on… https://t.co/fCj1kEizuy #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Business Analyst(Scrum): Business Analyst Alpharetta, GA Full Time Position Job Description: Strong experience in working as a product owner and senior business analyst. Prior Experience in working on projects using… https://t.co/q61oWPKpsl #IT #scrum #hiring 👇👀👇 #job]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>