<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Human sacrifice, dogs and cats living together --  mass hysteria! - Dr. Peter Venkman, Ghostbusters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need to tie some kerosene rags around his ankles so the ants don't eat his candy #$@ - Dale Earnhardt speaking of Mark Martin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Breaking News” Michael Jackson Song Stirs Controversy  http://t.co/dRcfQM7eCp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't call me a mindless philosopher, you overweight blob of grease! - C3PO, Star Wars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am not a glutton - I am an explorer of food. - Erma Bombeck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Experience is not what happens to a man. It is what a man does with what happens to him. - Aldous Huxley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only undertake what you can do in an excellent fashion. There are no prizes for average performance.- Brian Tracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Videos Games and Fitness with Wii and XBOX  http://t.co/ZtTy3hnbqc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Are the Different Types of Web Hosting?  http://t.co/hIyRuWOJY1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is the opposite of the weather. Nobody talks about it, but everybody does something about it. - Rebecca Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the shoe fits, you're not allowing for growth. - Robert N Coons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is the world flat? I never thought about it. Sherri Shepherd, The View, after Whoopi Goldberg asked her if she thought the world was flat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Tin Can Robot Kit - Kids Have a Blast Building a Fun Robot! http://t.co/6pdpQpNVcC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding good players is easy. Getting them to play as a team is another story. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heredity:  what makes the father and mother of a teen-ager wonder about each other]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome football t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the football lovers in your life!   http://t.co/okYEsHwCeJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What we want is to see the child in pursuit of knowledge, and not knowledge in pursuit of the child. - George Bernard Shaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What really decides consumers to buy or not to buy is the content of your advertising, not its form. - David Ogilvy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome fine wine t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the wine lovers in your life!  http://t.co/4Tackj54sa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About How Technology Has Helped Seniors to Make Great Strides in their Lifestyle  http://t.co/4AZ2JJVjri]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Johnnie Tayor  http://t.co/CBpvDd4CKC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first one gets the oyster the second gets the shell. - Andrew Carnegie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Organizing Garage Cabinets and Storage  http://t.co/sKK2cvglJs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It isn't necessary to blow out the other person's light in order for yours to shine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Clear Lighted Skateboard with green LED Lights  http://t.co/27xnkc8qtJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The glass is neither half-full nor half-empty: it's twice as big as it needs to be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In 1905 Albert discovered Relativity, in 1906 he invented Rock and Roll.  - Yahoo Serious]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Girls are like internet domain names, the ones I like are already taken.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Auto racing is boring except when a car is going at least 172 miles per hour upside down. - Dave Barry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Overview of Major Web Conferencing Services  http://t.co/dZVrYoS9Xb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the History of the Nautilus Fitness Equipment  http://t.co/HwrlhwDrpF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Earth is too small a basket for mankind to keep all its eggs in. - Robert A. Heinlein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nowadays there are two sides to every story --  the book and the movie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The right people to start video blogging are those with a passion to tell a story.  Steve Garfield - Author Get Seen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wanted to make the lightest shoe possible, but still be able to perform at the same time. - Carmelo Anthony]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Maxine Brown  http://t.co/mk9K0Vpoyf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame Quakecraft: FAILURE IS AN OPTION!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! http://t.co/iVr89mcmtt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about the Bay Area city of Pleasanton, California http://t.co/ILjE3jfwPa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introducing to the SEO Power Suite  http://t.co/4F49eUfhdY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Monopoly Money Extra Long Tie - Fun! http://t.co/vlUv6zP9xi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The way you can understand all of the social media is as the creation of a new kind of public space - Dana Boyd, Social Media Research MSFT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boys, baseball is a game where you gotta have fun. You do that by winning. - Dave Bristol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Men I may not know, but shoes, shoes I know. - Carrie Bradshaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft House Showcase: Touring the Winning House  http://t.co/KjAo4pQLO5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys - combine your wallet and smart phone in one compact case - and its cool and stylish - Book Book http://t.co/KBXqMuhWc3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Firefall  http://t.co/Rvmfg8EKRf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do you judge me as a musician, John? All I'm interested in is making money. Glenn Miller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The dog was created especially for children. He is the God of frolic. - Henry Ward Beecher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Emmylou Harris  http://t.co/jqUQsGZPlI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love Minecraft?  Check out the hot new video blogger Crimson Mine - http://t.co/UJLwDvlmp9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Kim Carnes  http://t.co/XY7Y4V1z3n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think education is expensive, try ignorance - Derek Bok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If man is a little lower than angels, then angels should reform.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Christianity as a Profession  http://t.co/jJWjO1fvUt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mr. Spock, the women on your planet are logical. That's the only planet in this galaxy that can make that claim. - James T. Kirk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The difference between try and triumph is just a little umph! - Marvin Phillips]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's later than we think and most of us aren't even thinking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Running SUCKS! How to Run for Fast Weight Loss - For Busy Women Who HATE Running --&gt; http://t.co/bO1WKFN2vA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Options for Using Slimmers and Trimmers for Weight Loss  http://t.co/TFQycO6WxQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a rock 'n' roll thing to have one-night stands. - Rick Springfield]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it's too close to bother to buckle your seat belt it's close enough to walk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Chemistry  http://t.co/tMeothPxts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Reviews By Children Affect a Product’s Sale  http://t.co/WZyDh1Wwff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You may delay, but time will not. - Benjamin Franklin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest lie you can make is to lie to yourself. - Matt Zotti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Simple Way to Bond with Kids? Use Cooking!  http://t.co/gkq9Q34fnO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Frustrations of Youth Pitching  http://t.co/Rje8bwEr0Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not wait to strike until the iron is hot; but make it hot by striking - William B. Sprague]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can lead a boy to college but you can't make him think. - Elbert Hubbard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I prefer the company of peasants because they have not been educated sufficiently to reason incorrectly. - Michel de Montaigne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is Ununpentium?  http://t.co/wCfeqYeV5s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About these Burial at Sea Options  http://t.co/6FWy2lktmr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cheap Divorce Lawyers: Avoiding Exorbitant Legal Costs  http://t.co/Yb2MsgriMY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My advice if you insist on slimming: Eat as much as you like - just don't swallow it. - Harry Secombe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must begin to think of yourself as becoming the person you want to be. - David Viscott]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read about the Emerging Threats From An Electromagnetic Pulse Attack  http://t.co/i8itupRlOk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Rose Royce  http://t.co/s88AJZos5C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life started getting good when I started making money. Balthazar Getty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hating the (New York) Yankees is as American as pizza pie, unwed mothers, and cheating on your income tax. - Mike Royko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Far Out and Super Cool Watches  http://t.co/BHnR60qwiE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I started racing my father told me, "˜Cristiano, nobody has three balls but some people have two very good ones. - Cristiano Da Matta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was sad because I had no shoes, until I met a man who had no feet. So I said, Got any shoes you're not using? --&gt; Steven Wright]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doctor, giving prescription to a patient "Let me know if this stuff works. I'm having the same trouble myself."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Experience is a hard teacher because she gives the test first, the lesson afterward. - Vernon Law]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is more than a game to me, it's a religion. - Bill Klem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about the Bay Area city of Pleasanton, California http://t.co/ILjE3iXVH6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He who laughs last, didn't get it!!  :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Race cars are neither beautiful nor ugly. They become beautiful when they win. - Enzo Ferrari]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The dog was created especially for children. He is the God of frolic. - Henry Ward Beecher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mama always said you could tell an awful lot about a person by the kind of shoes they wear. - Forrest Gump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of George Harrison  http://t.co/TrtgnUL1Hc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Speed has never killed anyone, suddenly becoming stationary --  that's what gets you. - Jeremy Clarkson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making the Most of Twitter for Your Business  http://t.co/hHUhhG7sUh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You see things; and you say "Why?" But I dream things that never were; and I say "Why not?" - George Bernard Shaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See you in another life, brother. - Desmond Hume, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The eternal silence of these infinite spaces fills me with dread. - Blaise Pascal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I started out writing much more science fictiony stuff and writing about science fiction. - Neil Gaiman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are not traffic jams along the extra mile. - Roger Staubach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Modern Homesteading  http://t.co/IpsRfIURUT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Barbara Acklin - The Popular Singer  http://t.co/I7lRRYsQ7r]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>