<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Helpful Tips for Web Marketing  http://t.co/K1RNDlw8u6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is 10% what happens to us and 90% how we react to it. - Ennis P. Kimbro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who wish to sing, always find a song. - Swedish Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you know of the Klingon proverb that tells us revenge is a dish that is best served cold? It is very cold in space. - Khan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The blunt people make the most pointed remarks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Buddy Holly  http://t.co/HsFnUp8qhf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A cat is a puzzle for which there is no solution. - Hazel Nicholson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the top science fiction books of all time!  http://t.co/ueqxC4vXEv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nowadays there are two sides to every story --  the book and the movie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Horse! A Horse! my kingdom for a horse! - Shakespeare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Guide to Mountain Biking  http://t.co/m6dCEo5CC4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heredity:  what makes the father and mother of a teen-ager wonder about each other]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our greatest weakness lies in giving up. The most certain way to succeed is always to try just one more time. - Thomas A. Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 6 - Follow-up Appointment  http://t.co/4O5btNv66A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making money is not gonna change anything about what I am, except I won't answer the door. Abel Ferrara]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A family man is one who has replaced money in his wallet with snapshots.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strikeouts are boring - besides that, they're fascist. Throw some ground balls. More democratic. - Bull Durham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Barbara Mason  http://t.co/E6pKsa3CrI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When money talks these days, it's probably asking what happened]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prometheus is reaching out for the stars with an empty grin on his face. - Arthur Koestler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Find Gluten Free Recipes  http://t.co/MikXdGmEsU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DC Comics Ultimate Character Guide http://t.co/U23qZyY7Mb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love Cute Kids Watches - Having A Watch Can be Fun for Kids!  http://t.co/KSX7WIFXgU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Horse! A Horse! my kingdom for a horse! - Shakespeare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To succeed --  You need to find something to hold on to, something to motivate you, something to inspire you. - Tony Dorsett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL - A Runny Nose In Your Shower Dispensing Soap - Love It!  http://t.co/ZuUU2UTMzs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blogging Season 1 of Lilyhammer by Netflix   http://t.co/5y2Ufu41z0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love Minecraft?  Check out the hot new video blogger Crimson Mine - http://t.co/of6X94cYVI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Resources for Home Brewing  http://t.co/2IcXyzeztb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If there are kids who want to follow in my footsteps, I'd say that my shoes are 2 big for them to! Their shoe size is perfect. Q. Latifah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A respectable appearance is sufficient to make people more interested in your soul --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A shoe has so much more to offer than just to walk. - Christian Louboutin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The roots of education are bitter, but the fruit is sweet. - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is 10% what happens to us and 90% how we react to it. - Ennis P. Kimbro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Writing Company Blogs that are Effective  http://t.co/54DG4IB52e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Far Out and Super Cool Watches  http://t.co/NgZ3ooMoun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is only one success - to be able to spend your life in your own way - Christopher Morley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some of the greatest Hollywood actors are not the award winners, but those congratulating them on their triumph]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read about the Emerging Private Space Industry  http://t.co/nGeETAnGg8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Spencer Davis Group  http://t.co/RiyJEJxco0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Renowned Tuba  http://t.co/KrBvTJ6q59]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have never felt in tune with the whole rock industry.  - Robert Wyatt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It isn't the mountains ahead to climb that wear you out; it's the pebble in your shoe. - Muhammad Ali]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn the Keys to Using LinkedIn for Your Company  http://t.co/VuwITAusCG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Star Trek  http://t.co/OiBTIbi7I1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I looked and looked but I didn't see God. - Yuri Gagarin, 14 April 1961]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two big firms are fighting for his services, the loser gets him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing is really work unless you would rather be doing something else. - James M. Barrie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Barbara Acklin – “Love Makes a Woman”  http://t.co/eFqwIanFTW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Out the Top Football Teams of the 2011-2012 Season  http://t.co/cPOTCF7ez9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think education is expensive, try ignorance - Derek Bok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahh Read About Loving Fine Wine  http://t.co/4Qcgdzh1km]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Old age means realizing you will never own all the dogs you wanted to. - Joe Gores]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It cost more to amuse a child that it cost to educate the father.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest thing in this world is not so much where we stand, as in what direction we are moving. - Oliver Wendall Holmes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of 'em, any of 'em that have been in front of me over all these years.  Sarah Palin on the newspapers she reads]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 10 - Support Group Meeting  http://t.co/zYrWJd9AYO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Review of The Little House on the Prairie Episode Called "Four Eyes"  http://t.co/iBbLZgEm0a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't tell you what I had for breakfast, but I can sing every single word of rock and roll. - Patty Duke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sign on a greenhouse: Fresh flowers just out of bed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dog is the only thing on earth that will love you more than you love yourself. - Josh Billings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Temptations  http://t.co/A05IhFPCnc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Green Acres is an American sitcom classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/ReE3mBn91X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Billy J. Kramer and the Dakotas  http://t.co/E1kUWHLnrC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Rolling Stones  http://t.co/BtsQXUvNj9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Careers with a Creative Writing Degree  http://t.co/p1H7TIM3Yx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opera in English is, in the main, just about as sensible as baseball in Italian. - Henry Louis Mencken]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Remote Control Inflatable Flying Shark! AWESOME! http://t.co/lLBSdKhjtC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is like a poker game, nobody wants to quit when he's losing: nobody wants you to quit when you're ahead. - Jackie Robinson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Hamstring Rehab  http://t.co/zjmOaH6T4C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read a Short Introduction to ABBA  http://t.co/TAVNLK3gVH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women should look like women. A piece of cardboard has no sexuality. - Alexander McQueen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Grateful Dead  http://t.co/Q0EyIW69DI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Major Watch Retailers and Brands  http://t.co/KdgA8Tnf9t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is nothing so stupid as the educated man if you get him off the thing he was educated in.  - Will Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Danger Will Robinson! Danger! - Robbie the Robot, Lost in Space]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These aren't the droids you're looking fore. - Obi-Wan, Star Wars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read The Story of Traffic the Classic Rock Group http://t.co/BxTL1dY5f4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Steve Miller Band  http://t.co/ec5dAbR9eC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Product Reviews Through the Eyes of a Child  http://t.co/ryehC5JYXp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Wonderful History of Tulips  http://t.co/bY2pmUZ7EQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very "COOL" Titanic Ice Cube mold - http://t.co/tHrnSsYGyX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actually, I majored in marketing and I have a bachelor of science. - Wanda Sykes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The worst examples of snap judgment are usually found in the old family album]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turbochargers are for people who cant build engines. - Keith Duckworth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion Note: Little change in men's clothes this year.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman is the only hunter who uses herself for bait]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ultimately, the only power to which man should aspire is that which he exercises over himself. - Elie Wiesel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know kung fu. - Neo, The Matrix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A pedestrian is someone who thought there were a couple of gallons left in the tank. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Magic texting glove with conductive yarn finger tips for iPhone, iPad and all touch screen devices - 4 colors  --&gt; http://t.co/AvA3H868VW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome biking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the biking lovers in your life!   http://t.co/BXpzAnZz0z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Who  http://t.co/lRRW5U4pbR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn from yesterday, live for today, hope for tomorrow. - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good teaching is one-fourth preparation and three-fourths pure theatre. - Gail Godwin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 7 ages of a woman are the right one and 6 wild guesses!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One is never over - or underdressed with a little black dress. - Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Dells  http://t.co/9CtUG3EGB9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Paul McCartney and Wings  http://t.co/pvBpPw0OSN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our health always seems much more valuable after we lose it. - Unknown]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>