<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Specialist Developer – Monitoring: TECHNOLOGY SERVICES GROUP (TSG) is the central infrastructure services group with a proven track record of innovating to help BNY Mellon and its customers have most reliable, nimble and cost-effective solutions… https://t.co/ivpJtE8Dk9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Full-Stack Developer: Description How You Can Make An Impact We are looking for a motivated developer who will play a key role in taking our proprietary trading UI components to the next level. The ideal candidate enjoys working with the latest .NET… https://t.co/eKjuJOZOq4 https://t.co/PBggT9AjC5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Software Analyst: Icertis seeks Sr Software Analyst in San Jose, CA to Undrstnd how prdct wrks &amp; how its used by cstmrs. Reqs: BS in IT, CS, or rltd + 5yrs exp in: App Dev/Supp or sustng eng role; Dev &amp; trblshtng skills on MS pltfrm w/ exp in C#,… https://t.co/iIMU5S8nhT https://t.co/VsPlN5214j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET/SharePoint Developer: MetroStar Systems Careers ========================= .NET/SharePoint Developer Web Development Washington, District Of Columbia Apply MetroStar Systems is looking for a .NET/SharePoint Developer that has a passion for design,… https://t.co/brqOk4REz2 https://t.co/7OCWac9mVd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer Ref No.: 18-33194 Location: Mount Laurel, New Jersey Position: .Net Developer Location: Mount Laurel, NJ Duration: 12 Months 5+ years of experience in .net 3.5, Csharp, ASP, WinForms Experience in utility design… https://t.co/1S45cVkPH5 https://t.co/UIEimIZ7sB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Application https://t.co/3ZbwIib2mf / MVC / Mongo DB: .Net Application ***************** / MVC / Mongo DB Ref No.: 18-02056 Location: Alpharetta, Georgia Position Type: Direct Placement Start Date: 08/01/2018 Job description .Net Application… https://t.co/q2SEAdlAsB https://t.co/7flyBbfe9g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.net UI Developer: .net UI Developer Ref No.: 18-33170 Location: Erie, Pennsylvania Title:- .net UI Developer with ITIL Location:- Erie PA Contract Role – ITIL (Information Technology Infrastructure Library) – using Service Now – Expert in Microsoft .Net… https://t.co/Ja3osqmvQA https://t.co/oLgSI2y1RY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .NET Software Developer: Summary As a member of our Development group you will design, develop, deliver and support Data Management/Data Access Products within the Energy Analytics space. You will work with small multi-functional teams to deliver… https://t.co/aoBV3nAv6V https://t.co/IJ5jszxV4a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Systems Engineer / Developer: ‘ The Certification service which is part of the broader Identity and Access Management program at BNYM is a critical shared service that supports the entire employee base and over 700 applications.’ ‘ SailPoint… https://t.co/4tbSAWuilO https://t.co/rBTgO017NF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .NET Developer: Senior .NET Developer | EastBanc Tech – Services – Solutions – Our Approach – Our Work – Tech Insights – About Us – News – Careers – Events – Contact Us – Services – Solutions – Our Approach – Our Work – Tech Insights – – About Us… https://t.co/VdF37PagpA https://t.co/qK0MRzLRhK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .NET Developer: Senior .NET Developer Charlotte, NC $90-100K An Application Developer who is a team player with 3-5 years Web development experience and excellent communication skills. This exciting position is for a developer who will work on a… https://t.co/0BH450zSjh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exclusive: Alibaba merging China food delivery units to counter Tencent-backed Meituan - sources: Alibaba Group plans to merge its food delivery units and raise funds for the combined business, intensifying a battle with Tencent-backed Meituan Dianping… https://t.co/qXMQHdY7gr https://t.co/aMJNlAw3yD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer Profit Sharing): Full Stack Developer (~25% Profit Sharing) in Aurora, CO | CACI International – Small Business | – Suppliers – About Us – | – What We Do – | – Media &amp; Events – | – Investors – | – Careers – | – Contracts – | –… https://t.co/7NXzobk6AQ https://t.co/NjFiOygaVJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Web Developer: SUMMARY Digital agency with over 30 years of tenure, specializing in website conception and execution. Clients include a broad range of industries such as healthcare, non-profit, education, government, retail, and security. OFFERS… https://t.co/d2itao9p9v https://t.co/dS0L0008LM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Application Developer (C#, https://t.co/itZFk9aFeI): Senior Application Developer (C#, https://t.co/itZFk9aFeI) Posted Date 2 weeks ago(6/6/2018 3:35 PM) ID 2018-31637 Job Location USA-MD-Hanover Required Clearance TS/SCI with Polygraph Category… https://t.co/NOiuhd2tsM https://t.co/2M4oxjj4ot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/BKeTHRUc7v Developer, Senior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Washington, DC Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 8/2/2018 Job Description Job Number: R******* ******* Developer, Senior Key Role: Lead a team of… https://t.co/sFfNx2SLzu https://t.co/lLuxD3eItq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (.NET): Job Location US-DC Job ID 10298 Job Location United States Overview American Institutes for Research (AIR) is a leading professional services firm with a growing software engineering and product development team. We design and… https://t.co/51VIvR7d0P https://t.co/Qbr1TeBAbK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer: .NET Developer Ref No.: 18-32534 Location: St. Louis, Missouri Primary Skills: Over all .NET Experience should 6+ years ******* , C#, MVC, Angular, DevOps, AGILE Javascript Experience (jQuery, Lightbox, etc) CM Tool experience (Git or… https://t.co/XRtKEarhiv https://t.co/TlLU0oCaSA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead/Manager .Net Software Engineer:   Job Description – Lead/Manager .Net Software Engineer (40526) Job Description  Lead/Manager .Net Software Engineer-40526 Description   Lead/Manager .Net Software Engineer  POSITION SUMMARY: A Lead/Manager .NET… https://t.co/DSQpKZoX4Q https://t.co/05zJIvx65Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Manager, Architecture: GENERAL PURPOSE: The Manager, Technology Architecture works in conjunction with Senior IT Manager, Technology Architecture and a team of solution architects responsible for evaluating and developing strategic solutions focusing… https://t.co/lasdEyHdbx https://t.co/SAn03IF4cU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer – TCI: Tax Compliance, Inc. develops market-leading state and local tax software solutions for corporations. PTMS property tax software helps minimize property taxes and expenses. LicenseHQ helps minimize the time and expense related to… https://t.co/Oi31VvcXiU https://t.co/El0RnkUDVo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net developer: .Net developer Ref No.:18-18622 Location: Ames, Iowa .Net developer to make modifications to the system that tracks driver’s license issuance, driving records, and vehicle registration/titling. This resource will work within a project… https://t.co/hzoOWnua2P https://t.co/fNHfWr66FS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (.Net Software Engineer / Front-end Software Engineer): Translates and develops requirements into workable software solutions. Maintains and develops programs for use in business and IT automation. Incorporates various accepted… https://t.co/QOpto97BCr https://t.co/th0xWUEr5Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer: JOB ID: ****** .NET DEVELOPER ST LOUIS, MISSOURI REGULAR / DAY ADDITIONAL JOB INFORMATION TITLE:.NET Developer CITY, STATE: Detroit, MI LOCATION: MI Detroit – Offsite DEPARTMENT: Exp Web and Mobile ADDITIONAL JOB DETAILS:FT, Days ABOUT US… https://t.co/FMvpsqq196 https://t.co/11WCiKbZvd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer Ref No.: 18-32734 Location: Cleveland, Ohio Hi Hope you are doing well Number of position : 6 (Not Contrect or C2C) I, Salman Shaikh (Enterprise Solution Inc.) would like to share a job opportunity as .Net Developer based… https://t.co/7iMDCAIAye https://t.co/BwvWFp11AN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer: JOB ID: ****** .NET DEVELOPER ST LOUIS, MISSOURI REGULAR / DAY ADDITIONAL JOB INFORMATION TITLE:.NET Developer CITY, STATE: Detroit, MI LOCATION: MI Detroit – Offsite DEPARTMENT: Exp Web and Mobile ADDITIONAL JOB DETAILS:FT, Days ABOUT US… https://t.co/Sor5YtNuNh https://t.co/M4aqdORdRX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ServiceNow Developer: Summit Technologies, Inc. has a full-time position for a ServiceNow Developer. A successful candidate will provide hands-on development, administration and support of ServiceNow. You must be a US Citizen or a permanent US resident,… https://t.co/3GOIDy5o7d https://t.co/hg09uIjM5R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/A1uhjIADAJ Developer: Biztalk developer Ref No.: 18-33180 Location: Chicago, Illinois Job title: Biztalk developer Location: Chicago IL Duration: 12 months Technical skills: 1. Hands on development and maintenance of BizTalk implementations,… https://t.co/GxxtqT4rm5 https://t.co/3HEeaUwBsZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer, Full Stack .NET: Careers Center | Senior Software Engineer, Full Stack .NET Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability… https://t.co/AXfsnd2wBh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer/Sr. Software Developer (.NET) Job: Company Information PACCAR is a Fortune 500 company established in 1905. PACCAR Inc is recognized as a global leader in the commercial vehicle, financial, and customer service fields with… https://t.co/4hIoIpyuNJ https://t.co/AtlMiCuvBn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Software Engineer: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Herndon, VA Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 7/16/2018 Job Description Job Number: R******* Java Software Engineer Key Role: Research, design, develop, and modify… https://t.co/Mms0RFV3lO https://t.co/LtENLUAJf6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .NET Developer – Loop (Great Manager!) – 125K: We are looking for a permanent onsite Senior Developer for a great client downtown. They are a casual dress, casual atmosphere with a great flexible Manager. There is opportunity here to get into… https://t.co/QBkUdpdDKx https://t.co/o4fShCt6fG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Desktop Support Specialist III: Tracking Code FTEUS-18-0969-F Job Code 18-0969 Posting Title Desktop Support Specialist III Post Date 7/31/2018 Full Time / Part-Time Full Time Travel No Travel Required City Newport News State VA Country US Description… https://t.co/bxtJlRVkCE https://t.co/HcHhpXlPbW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .Net Full Stack Developer: Senior .Net Full Stack Developer – CAREER HOME – ABOUT US – Culture and Diversity – Benefits – Awards – Community – University Relations – Our Hiring Process – FEATURED JOBS – Engineering – Information Technology –… https://t.co/U3rIglZxpI https://t.co/6LxDJCSe5V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, Back End .NET: Software Engineer, Back End .NET | Tesla Tesla, Inc – Model S – Model X – Model 3 – Roadster – Energy – – Shop – Shop – Tesla Account – Sign In More – News – Inventory – New Inventory – Used Inventory – Corporate –… https://t.co/9jcBp4X0Ln https://t.co/OVKKwAMswt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Core Java Developer (C#/.NET 4): The candidates should be mid-level with between 5-10 years of experience. These are hands-on CORE JAVA developer positions. Candidates need experience with front end C#.NET4+, WPF, Back End Java Spring, Messaging, and… https://t.co/604PNWeNxK https://t.co/VSoy938Kmz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer Ref No.: 18-31131 Location: Wausau, Wisconsin Role: .Net Developer Location: Wausau, WI Duration: 12 Months Contract Skills Required Strong exp. with .net development with *******, C#. https://t.co/pwJD9lnG9R https://t.co/XufJ90TZVP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook fakers get better at covering tracks, security experts say: Creators of fake accounts and news pages on Facebook are learning from their past mistakes and making themselves harder to track and identify, posing new challenges in preventing the… https://t.co/N0HI9zL21x https://t.co/OtshKyEc8N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Architect – Jersey City: Responsibilities: Analyse business requirements Plan and develop a technical solution Development and deployment of the solution Collaboration with the QA team Documentation of the solution you should be comfortable… https://t.co/rGREMvB1jl https://t.co/QkKclCKB7n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Software Engineer (Mid Level): Job ********* Software Engineer (Mid Level) – ID:32239 DurationPermanent Start DateASAP Job SkillsExcellent communciation, Outgoing and personable, .net, Fintech experience LocationIrvine, CA Date Posted07/30/2018 We… https://t.co/QoTWFF2eRT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C#.NET Developer: Our direct fortune 500 client is in need of C#.NET programmers to join their dynamic team. Contract and Contract-to-Hire positions available. Required: – 5+ years C#.NET experience – 3+ years SQL programming experience – 3+ years SQL… https://t.co/bRz7mGEiRI https://t.co/YTP3JAWq8l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Global IT Transformation Partner: Global IT Transformation Partner There are four major trends transforming global IT today: Cloud, Mobile, Big Data and Social Networking. Dell Technologies comprises a unique federation of strategically aligned… https://t.co/9a7lT9Nw92 https://t.co/WrV5fOIkg9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C# .NET Developer: * Must have a Bachelors Degree and high GPA from college.* Dynamic Global Financial Software Firm, located in the Chicago Loop, is currently seeking a C# .NET Developer with strong OO experience. Candidate will join a group a… https://t.co/63fDXwjvDy https://t.co/scD4W5InI9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr .Net Developer, Washington D.C: Jun 21 2017 Sr .Net Developer, Washington D.C YSI Jobs – YSI HR ID Job Title Job Description #3Sr .Net DeveloperResponsibilities: 1. Analyzes, designs, develops, troubleshoots, implements &amp; supports enterprise complex… https://t.co/bWrx5KvV3U https://t.co/7FHjdXJhdd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Software Developer: Summary: Job Description The Senior Web Developer builds quick concept prototypes, program for capabilities using client side technologies as well as frameworks, offer cross platform compatibility/support. Responsible for… https://t.co/K4t2U9U5ez https://t.co/AsOkuvb1Pd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer – .Net: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Fort Worth, TX Job Type: Information Technology Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 7/17/2018 Job Description SUMMARY: This individual will assist with the development and… https://t.co/sessDt1Cba https://t.co/9Wq2AUEBgQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.net developer: .net developer Ref No.:18-13309 Location: Long Beach, CA Position Type:Contract Start Date: 07/26/2018 .net developer Location: Long Beach, CA 6 + month Contract Job Requirement: Client Side: – Bootstrap (HTML5 and CSS3) – Angular… https://t.co/S4ODIbiHPF https://t.co/5sh1LHMQor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer Ref No.: 18-31562 Location: Washington, District of Columbia TITLE: .NET DEVELOPER POSITION TYPE: CONTRACT(W2) LOCATION: WASHINGTON DC SKILLS REQUIRED: Microsoft .NET framework 3.5/4.0+/Visual Studio (2008/2012),… https://t.co/KtcqIT9IiS https://t.co/ntd5VIWbnl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Systems Analyst: IT Systems Analyst Salary: $70,140 to $93,984 annually Requirements: Any equivalent combination of education and experience that provides the applicant with the knowledge, skills and abilities required to perform the job. A typical… https://t.co/iMI4J3oMST https://t.co/10QzywqM2a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer (.NET): Job Description – Senior Software Engineer (.NET) Job LocationUS-DC Job ID9410 Job LocationUnited States Alternate locations Reston, VA and Naperville, IL CategoryInformation Technology/Software Overview Be part of… https://t.co/206sVVz5ke https://t.co/o7voUu0wAj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Member Of Technical Staff: ENGINEER: Aquantia seeks Sr Member of Technical Staff in San Jose, CA to co-design product &amp; develop manufacturing processes &amp; test strategies. Send resume w/ad to 91 E Tasman Dr #100, San Jose, CA 95134. Attn: HR/YL… https://t.co/7dMOvbUbFt https://t.co/QY17Ftok8p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer, Senior: .NET DEVELOPER, SR. RESPONSIBILITIES/QUALIFICATIONS * 3+ years experience with ASP .NET web development. * 3+years experience using OOP with C# and SQL. * Develop and maintain C# code and SQL. * Involved with the performance… https://t.co/08bnzZRIPn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Integrator Sr: Requisition ID 2018-41551 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Secret Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description Responsibilities A System Integrator performs systems administration activities… https://t.co/qGP6laaMbF https://t.co/O4rGtGu62i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Research Software Engineer: Job Description Job Title: Research Software Engineer Job ID: 4880 Location: Multiple locations Full/Part Time: Full-Time Regular/Temporary: Regular Title Research Software Engineer Overview of RAND The RAND Corporation is a… https://t.co/fcujJAFVjG https://t.co/7cT93Bi4pK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Architect: .NET Architect Ref No.: 18-29573 Location: Springfield, Illinois Seasoned (at least 15 years of experience) solutions architect Although .Net is not the only technology involved, having real world experience designing &amp; building… https://t.co/Ml3iC2o49v https://t.co/Ti3eyWtkL6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Data Warehouse Technical Project Lead Job: Enterprise Data Warehouse Technical Project Lead (Job Number:437505) Description: JOB DESCRIPTION: Technical project lead for a contract supporting a natural resources agency and oversight of a team… https://t.co/9kiDTAiN3v https://t.co/r7YkO2Wjs3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C# .Net Developer: C# .Net Developer Ref No.: 18-29733 Location: Seattle, Washington Position: C# .Net Developer Job Location: Seattle, WA Job Title: Full time permanent Mandatory Technical/ Functional Skills: A minimum of 5 years of professional… https://t.co/UuRm8gfR4q https://t.co/BnqJpWOCe5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET/SharePoint Developer: .NET/SharePoint Developer ========================= Req #: ******Location: Washington, DC USJob Category: Information TechnologySecurity Clearance: SecretClearance Status: Must Be Current Job Description What You ll Get to Do:… https://t.co/LlX0CX5FEN https://t.co/qmlEVPE5XA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net/SharePoint Specialist: Ace Info Solutions, Inc. (AceInfo) is a leading Federal contractor with a focused vision: empower our clients, challenge our employees, and grow our business. Founded in December 2000, we are deeply committed to ensuring… https://t.co/qZKGjLnt5a https://t.co/n6LfYuSpJt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tech Lead .NET: ******/Tech Lead .NET Ref No.: 18-30134 Location: Webster – New York, New York LEAD-L1 Job Description(As per hiring manager) – Good functional exposure to Supply chain and manufacturing domain – Experience in managing large production… https://t.co/ul7xFaFvAR https://t.co/7EBqkaMAf2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .Net Developer: Requisition ID 2018-41090 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Top Secret Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description ONLY applicants who possess an Active Top Secret Clearance need apply***… https://t.co/h5rM6mgxy9 https://t.co/7baBvIqhKi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .Net Developer: Location US-OH-Cincinnati Posted Date 1 month ago(6/18/2018 9:45 AM) Job ID 23422 # Positions 1 Category Technology Position Type Full Time Overview Be Here. Be Great. Working for a leader in the insurance industry means… https://t.co/mhMsRd0AfY https://t.co/LMTW5Roqv6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer (C#) Programmer: .Net Developer (C#) Programmer – Salient CRGT – San Antonio, Texas | ********** Loading…Server error, please try again laterSorry! It looks like you are in private browsing mode, which is not supported. Please switch your… https://t.co/nV5vxNS8ZC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior/Principal Engineer (C#/ASP.NET): We are looking for a strong C# software engineer to build out the next generation of our software test automation infrastructure as part of our Quality Assurance Infrastructure team. The team is responsible for… https://t.co/N0lSI9Ppp9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Tech Lead: Java Tech Lead Ref No.: 18-31128 Location: Montvale, New Jersey Position: Java Tech Lead Location : Montvale, NJ Duration: 12 Months Experience- 6-8 Years Minimum Role- Java Technical Lead Technology- Java, Hibernate, Spring, REST… https://t.co/KCSuRkVT9I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer job | Deloitte United States job in Mechanicsburg, Pennsylvania, United States Toggle menu – Deloitte home – About Deloitte – – Location: United States Available in locations and languages – Students – Experienced –… https://t.co/EEFBAb5kp1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Southeast Asia's Grab mops up $1 billion funding from financial firms: Southeast Asian ride-hailing company Grab on Thursday said it has secured new investment of $1 billion from a clutch of financial firms, including global asset manager… https://t.co/K61Xf0fJqM https://t.co/uWGiNiadW5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer/ .NET Developer: Job ID: ********-11090-SDP Company Name: Xactware Description: Software Engineer / Web Developer /.NET Developer Role and Responsibilities Service Software, part of the Verisk/Xactware family, is the leading software… https://t.co/mKeOZWG9up https://t.co/bUXhL5cbff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .NET Developer WITS: Senior .NET Developer – WITS Ref No.:18-00123 Location: Columbia, Maryland Position Type:Full Time Experience Level: 8 Years Start Date: 06/28/2018 Senior-level .NET Developer FEi is a leading IT company specializing in… https://t.co/8ZbGSsslQE https://t.co/7EMNVsQ9E6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Software Engineer:   Job Description – .NET Software Engineer (1803519) Job Description  .NET Software Engineer – (1803519) Primary Location : US-CA-Long Beach-Remote Employees Job : Molina Medicaid Solutions Organization : Medical Systems Job… https://t.co/gAj2drrJrj https://t.co/OeBqIQp44A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Principal Engineer: Data Domain LLC (a Dell Technologies company) has multiple openings at our Santa Clara, CA facility for the following positions: Software Engineer 2 (req. 000028), Software Senior Engineer (req. 000187), Software Principal… https://t.co/f55poMeEes https://t.co/FiaTZxskMp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Developer, https://t.co/BKeTHRUc7v, Visual Studio, SSIS, SQL Server: For BNY Mellon Lead Developer, *******, Visual Studio, SSIS, SQL Server job – Information Technology – Multiple Skip to Main Content – – – – Toggle navigation – Who We Are – What… https://t.co/ndPcHIFy2r https://t.co/7W6Yat4LgM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior .NET Developer: Job Information: Junior .NET Developer Job Email Opening Title Junior .NET Developer EOE StatementWe are an equal employment opportunity employer. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to… https://t.co/U2NJEPOYSW https://t.co/DLjYBVjAM7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid-level .NET Developer: Mid-level .NET Developer ‘ Primary Responsibilities: As a .NET Developer, you will assist in the development, implementation and management of technology-based business solutions relating to web based data analytics and workflow… https://t.co/dpOT1g84W9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Analyst: System Analyst Ref No.: 18-31366 Location: McLean, Virginia Position: System Analyst Location: McLean VA Duration: 12 Months MUST HAVE SKILLS – Expertise in data models, data mining and SQL – Hands on experience in working on XML, XSD –… https://t.co/pGz3F4ftmV https://t.co/Y35OGRUiP4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .NET Applications Developer: Senior .NET Applications Developer Job Locations US-DC-Washington Job ID 10309 Minimum Clearance Required US Citizen Responsibilities Functional Responsibilities:  ISYS Technologies is hiring a Senior .NET Applications… https://t.co/6VgzTvEIe4 https://t.co/wVTZnfA27T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer: .NET Developer Ref No.: 18-30644 Location: Pennington, New Jersey Must hava Skill Set Good to have skill set C# ******* Angular JS Angular 2 Typescript Rest/SOAP Web services Agile methodology and be comfortable with agile development… https://t.co/ke0Kv5KI59 https://t.co/K2CnRg8CZR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Business Data Analyst: Intuit Inc. has openings for the following positions in Mountain View, California: Principal Product Managers (Job code: I-3377): Define and lead the vision and strategy for aggregation and categorization services, provide… https://t.co/byOKS6HZmp https://t.co/z1ZWOIAx3Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer II – .Net: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Milwaukee, WI Job Type: Information Technology Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 7/15/2018 Job Description Primary Purpose: This position is responsible for analysis, codes, tests and… https://t.co/98flnyGRJi https://t.co/NWezYbSAHO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Argentina's Mendoza province becomes first to pass law allowing Uber: Uber Technologies Inc [UBER.UL] got the green light on Tuesday to operate in Argentina's Mendoza province when lawmakers there passed the country's first law regulating ride-hailing… https://t.co/QwfT7aJhbM https://t.co/l5PZ9NV01A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .NET Technical Lead: Careers Center | Senior .NET Technical Lead Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome… https://t.co/wggKwTesux https://t.co/Jj7aaT838d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Specialist Developer – .NET, C#, SQL Server — Exchange Traded Funds: Sr. Specialist Developer – .NET, C#, SQL Server ‘ Exchange Traded Funds The Exchange Traded Funds Technology Team creates application-layer solutions to streamline and improve the… https://t.co/FRHEX406PJ https://t.co/Rv351dmh2r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer Ref No.: 18-30215 Location: Dallas, Texas Role: .Net Developer Location: Dallas, TX Duration: Full Time Permanent Skills Required: .NET development (C#.NET, WPF, Entity Framework, *******, *******, MVVM, MVC) .NET Web… https://t.co/d7x3kvh5wd https://t.co/UrBx7eBJcF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer Ref No.: 18-30256 Location: Plano, Texas Position: .Net Developer Job Location: Plano, TX Job Title: Full time permanent – Strong knowledge of .NET web framework. – Proficient in {{C# and/or ******}}, with a good knowledge… https://t.co/fWhXuJiqmW https://t.co/rBOYBy0GfN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead .NET Software Engineer: Trimble  is recruiting for a  Software Engineer/ Tech lead to fill an opportunity in Westminster, CO. Virtual Site Solutions (VSS) is a joint venture between Trimble and Caterpillar Inc. responsible for the development of Web… https://t.co/2RWoljmUI9 https://t.co/ZlXnX8X7Gn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.net developer: .net developer Ref No.: 18-29009 Location: NYC, NY, New York Key skills required for the job are: * Angular 2-L3 (Mandatory) * AngularJS for .NET-L3 As a Senior Developer, you are responsible for development, support, maintenance and… https://t.co/Rgc0mjqtbI https://t.co/nLI8oa4UdW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Graduate Server Performance Engineer: Graduate Server Performance Engineer – Job ID #: 11501 – Job Category: Design Engineering – Employment Type: Graduates – Division: Infrastructure – Department: Infrastructure Engineering – Primary Country: USA –… https://t.co/LC25bunbIg https://t.co/k4G2EezcJu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer: .NET Developer Ref No.: 18-32536 Location: Mesa, California Over all .NET Experience should 6+ years ******* , C#, MVC, Angular, DevOps, AGILE Javascript Experience (jQuery, Lightbox, etc) CM Tool experience (Git or TFS) CSS Experience… https://t.co/qyPqtv8SLx https://t.co/oKai0hiIEJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior C# https://t.co/BKeTHRUc7v Developer/Architect: This well-respected and industry-leading software firm located in North Dallas is seeking to hire a Senior Software Developer/Architect with strong C# ******* experience to join their growing team.… https://t.co/3dNQrudGTq https://t.co/sikSzZWEcQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C#/.NET Developer: Search and apply for jobs at Piper Companies | Careers at Piper Companies Careers Search Jobs Connect With Us C#/.NET Developer Job Attributes Job Id: 19486Job Category: Software Applications &amp; ERPJob Location: Raleigh, NC… https://t.co/5BOCxV2c2C https://t.co/C9QcuXAqdR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .NET Developer: Senior .NET Developer ID 2017-9089 Category Software Development Location US-NY-New York Responsibilities More than 20 years ago, TransPerfect was founded with a mission to help the world's businesses navigate the global… https://t.co/PUXJWSvaJI https://t.co/dB0qARxI6q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer Austin, Texas – United States Job Start Date – 07/05/18, Posted Date – 07/05/18 Primary Skills.netTax TermsC2COverviewThis is a 6-12 months contract with DELL. Phone and Skype. Candidate with 1 real time project. Must have… https://t.co/4mYiECpEjO https://t.co/p1ayHY80ex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer: .NET Developer Ref No.: 18-32534 Location: St. Louis, Missouri Primary Skills: Over all .NET Experience should 6+ years ******* , C#, MVC, Angular, DevOps, AGILE Javascript Experience (jQuery, Lightbox, etc) CM Tool experience (Git or… https://t.co/Lvm1omW5oU https://t.co/jEu19WsQqh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Integrator Developer, .NET 4.0, C#, WEB API: Software Integrator &amp; Developer, .NET 4.0, C#, WEB API Wilmington, DE THE OPPORTUNITY Application architectures range from vendor supplied package applications (70%) to in-house developed software… https://t.co/voXdsqQfxd https://t.co/gAMMRGguZ9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Engineer, Software Developer: Senior Engineer, Software Developer &amp; Engineer – Comcast Cable Communication, LLC, West Chester, PA. Provide technical leadership for maintain co’s National Data Warehouse &amp; data services platform. Requirements:… https://t.co/FXx9eqXAi1 https://t.co/VTY8HJAsYF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla explores building Gigafactory in Europe: Wall Street Journal: Tesla Inc is in talks with authorities in Germany and the Netherlands to build its first major European factory, the Wall Street Journal reported on Monday, citing officials involved in… https://t.co/rZ1cDyjmMI https://t.co/cFXTUmgbCY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – .NET: Software Engineer – .NET at EXPERIANSkip Navigation Consumer Small Business Business More…X Experian Site Sections About Experian Consumer Support Credit Advice Global Sites Company Profile Corporate Fact Sheet Principal… https://t.co/P5XLObbbcl https://t.co/aTQMfZbUT9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Developer: Application Developer: Develop interface batch applications automation for ETL Informatica. Develop ETL processes to load data into Data warehouse &amp; Data marts using Teradata utilities. Distribute database data support &amp; execute… https://t.co/NsFypNeNqk https://t.co/vKYnWbRD1t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft .NET Front-End Developer: Job Description Microsoft .NET Front-End Developer (17455) The Johns Hopkins University Applied Physics Laboratory (APL), a national leader in scientific research and development, located midway between Baltimore and… https://t.co/xVA5563AJ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer: Web Developer Job Description Are you passionate about building amazing software? Are you constantly pushing yourself to develop better, faster and more efficient applications? Do you have an innate interest in releasing products that… https://t.co/5dxN1cyXEA https://t.co/uwAAgfTaql]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>