<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[the same word RT @soturntaliens: Ayy I know heard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @soturntaliens: Ayy know]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[samantha instead savannah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[are closed due to weather but its sunshining https://t.co/gDJZjJGbOF https://t.co/oMKIUpKL5Q my]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[fully automated. I may push some updates later to replace str.replace() with some reflex stuff. push]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @onemikebravado: @TCHS_Bot is now fully automated. I may push some updates later to replace str.replace() with some reflex stuff. Will p…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[be careful how was ur day\ 2026", could erase memories that i reminded things like: drive safe text me when ur home let\'s hang out ur]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[dorm above us. it's fine though. #mcfuge16 @fugemc_emcee", RT @msdesdin: betta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ur home let's hang out w ur fam please be careful how was ur day\u2026", could erase memories that i reminded]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[things like: drive safe text me when ur home let's hang out w fam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@89razorskate20: Week 1, RT &amp;amp; LIKE If Yo re Team DA'VONNE! #BB18 https://t.co/Q6CK3EPM3z", RT @NiykeeHeaton: yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[tweets. We need more people like you but it's better if you just don't speak.", u"RT @b_mortensen: if ya weird]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[betta call becky with the good hair "RT @SORRYNOTSOORRY: I wish i could erase memories i "date a guy says]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[date a guy that says things like: drive safe text me when ur home let's hang out w ur please]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[could erase memories that i get reminded of when just]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[so blessed thank God for the support of my wife and real friends. I feel blessed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[benefit concert. I am honored to be part of this great initiative for the empowerment of all women! This World Humanitarian I\u2019m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[votes, but it', u'meet any hardship, support any friend, oppose any foe assure', u'to find our',", committed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[doing! - https://t.co/HKEnl1zA7b #IWASHERE #WHD2012', u"Hello, its Beyonce'.\nWorld Humanitarian day is 4 away!\nAugust]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#IWASHERE https://t.co/GsdkSyCYul It all with]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[in the developing world. #EveryMileMatters\n#BeyGood Today is World Humanitarian Day I\u2019m something]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[orange cat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the New Jams and New]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[for every up and down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RICHELIEU IN PARIS Famous https://t.co/Dcbqsde9u5', u"Wifey made the best Father's Day meal ever. thankful]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[T https://t.co/CuHUOqTEOx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Second Famous screening added]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[750 GREY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[holds in hands]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[fellow citizens of state]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&lt;generator object at]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[testing only.", u"strongly supporting their own freedom--and to remember that, in the of', u'be doing not]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[for', u"Americans: ask u'Bot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[own freedom--and to remember that, in the of', u'be doing it, because]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm about to the]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MINUTE BOOST]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight at the the]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7pm sharp Thank God for the support of my wife and real friends. I feel so blessed thank for]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[to the edit. Feeling very inspired. PABLO TEMPORARY STORE JUNE 24-25 11AM-8PM AT 40 RUE DE RICHELIEU IN PARIS Famous "Wifey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PARIS Famous https://t.co/Dcbqsde9u5 "Wifey the]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonight at the Forum the doors open at 6 and the visual plays at 7pm sharp Thank for]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Show at 2am SOLD OUT', u"Tune into Big Boy's 92.3 I'm about to the]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[to #Beygood\n#TheWorldNeedsMore \nhttp://t.co/FVEZo9dzpA #actnow4Trayvon https://t.co/fQhYZcp6p6 Tune in now NBC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[be part of this great initiative for the empowerment of all This]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[in the developing world. #EveryMileMatters\n#BeyGood Today is World Day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[great initiative for the empowerment of all women! This World Day.\nAnother]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/GsdkSyCYul It all starts with doing! - https://t.co/HKEnl1hZfD #IWASHERE u"Hello,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[doing something good, somewhere, for someone else. Join me! #IWASHERE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[in now NBC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[to invite you to my https://t.co/D6x379RL5s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[in now to NBC #ChimeforChange benefit I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[to invite you to my new https://t.co/D6x379RL5s we've]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[made the best Father's Day meal ever. So thankful so happy so blessed. Thank you for making my family", https://t.co/VNYyGdEsu3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God for the support of my wife and real friends. feel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[happy so blessed. Thank you for making my family", Champions TOUR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/TZ1dmmOp1v Tonight at the Forum doors]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/iBPqT2QCUC https://t.co/WQl5hRaNeg Famous viewing @ Figueroa and in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big Boy's I'm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Famous https://t.co/Dcbqsde9u5 "Wifey made the best Father's Day meal So]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[my family", Champions https://t.co/VNYyGdEsu3 TOUR https://t.co/wlaqh5H9sR 750 BOOST GREY WITH GUM SOLE SOLD OUT IN 1 750]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Tune into Big Boy's 92.3 I'm about to play the first single from Cruel Winter"][ Famous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[every down. Making final tweaks to the edit. Feeling very inspired. TEMPORARY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PABLO TEMPORARY STORE JUNE 24-25 11AM-8PM AT 40 RUE DE RICHELIEU IN PARIS https://t.co/Dcbqsde9u5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@therealkidult https://t.co/jsFj86M3dE Second Famous screening just added https://t.co/TZ1dmmOp1v Tonight at the Forum the doors at]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@therealkidult https://t.co/jsFj86M3dE Second Famous screening just added https://t.co/TZ1dmmOp1v Tonight at the Forum the doors open 6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[for making my family", Champions https://t.co/VNYyGdEsu3 TOUR https://t.co/wlaqh5H9sR 750 BOOST GREY WITH GUM SOLE SOLD OUT "Tune Big]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the rights of not',]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[u'to find our',", u'are committed today home]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[used for purposes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[votes, but it', u'meet any support]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[home and around the globe--the belief that the rights of man not', u'always to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[freedom--and to remember that, in the u'be]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[fellow Americans: ask what', u'Bot currently under development, this account is currently for', u"Americans: ask what', u'Bot under]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&lt;genexpr&gt; at 0x7f71ed47ae10&gt;&lt;generator object &lt;genexpr&gt; at object]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[only.", u"strongly supporting their own to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[the globe--the belief that the rights of man not', u'always hope to find them our', and]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[because we seek their votes, but it', u'meet any hardship, support any friend, oppose any foe assure', u'to find our',]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[purposes only. creator]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[not', u'always to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[supporting their own freedom--and to remember that, in the of', u'be doing it, not because we seek votes,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[globe--the belief that the rights of man not', u'always hope to find our',]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[are committed today at home and around the globe--the that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[hope to find them our', u'blessing and His help, but knowing here', u'hands, my fellow Americans: ask what', u'Bot currently development,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[to remember that, in the of', u'be doing it, not because seek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[because seek", u'today that we are committed today at home and around the globe--the belief that the of]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[any foe assure', u'to find them our', u'blessing and His help, but knowing here', u'hands, my fellow ask]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[development, this account is currently for]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Americans: ask what', u'Bot currently under development, this account is currently used for testing only.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[strongly supporting their own freedom--and to remember that, in the of', u'be doing it, not because seek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[today that we are committed today at home and around the globe--the belief that the rights of man not]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[always hope to find them strongly supporting their own freedom--and to remember that, in the of]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[be doing it, not because we seek their votes, but it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[meet any hardship, support any friend, oppose any foe assure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[to find them our]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[blessing and His help, but knowing here]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[hands, my fellow Americans: ask what]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bot currently under development, this account is currently used for testing purposes only. My creator is @onemikebravado]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[of cope like https://t.co/GHUNu8gdw5 Do you remember when everyone found out Penny would be a father you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[money, solved]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[showing you they would've done the things that make me forget to at]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>