<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome cooking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the cooking lovers in your life!   http://t.co/V6biruigCz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Star Wars  http://t.co/tWp9EDLWnw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is not preparation for life; education is life itself. - John Dewey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Arthur Alexander the Unknown Artist  http://t.co/EM77urQj3l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd walk through hell in a gasoline suit to play baseball. -  Pete Rose]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Benefits of iPads for Seniors  http://t.co/NK68pRJnln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The reason Las Vegas is getting so big is nobody can afford to buy a ticket to leave.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To err is human, to purr, feline - Robert Byrne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The quality of a leader is reflected in the standards they set for themselves. - Ray Kroc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take care of your body. It's the only place you have to live. - Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Christianity as a Profession  http://t.co/54CRt5QEj2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Everly Brothers  http://t.co/FTcWAFpgnm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Air Supply  http://t.co/p4MmAJ0caF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Overview of Domestic Adoption  http://t.co/jSs9q3E9Wj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of White Castle  http://t.co/ou9HU3AAva]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think education is expensive, try ignorance - Derek Bok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Wonderful Canadian Rockies Tour  http://t.co/AZsEf8P19y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Rush  http://t.co/MKaCoRfoa4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate most of what constitutes rock music, which is basically middle-aged crap. - Sting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Michael Jordan Shoes  http://t.co/aTYUXxJS88]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have to have a lot of little boy in you to play baseball for a living.  - Roy Campanella]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life started getting good when I started making money. Balthazar Getty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're listening to a rock star in order to get your information on who to vote for, you're a bigger moron than they are. - Alice Cooper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Product Reviews Through the Eyes of a Child  http://t.co/KKP8QG2PGS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion has two purposes: comfort and love. Beauty comes when fashion succeeds. --&gt; Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome tennis t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the tennis lovers in your life!   http://t.co/VGvvti4qxD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How Small Business Can Grow with Social Media Sites  http://t.co/Ol94SXmXdP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome cooking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the cooking lovers in your life!   http://t.co/uBpEWVKRPX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I started racing my father told me, "˜Cristiano, nobody has three balls but some people have two very good ones. - Cristiano Da Matta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Adoption Part II - the Bulgaria Phase  http://t.co/2cZX0TTfa0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Introduction to Steak 'n Shake  http://t.co/vzgY7sf7n1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Rolling Stones  http://t.co/51xJxhuVDc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In any contest between power and patience -- bet on patience]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It cost more to amuse a child that it cost to educate the father.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating History of ESPN  http://t.co/fib5cAsbfA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Awesome Nintendo Wall Graphics! http://t.co/DuP82aEs5l]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Europe – Best Places to Tour  http://t.co/SY70euQDeL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be successful, you have to have your heart in your business, and your business in your heart. - Thomas Watson, Sr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LinkedIn Used Effectively Helps Companies to Grow  http://t.co/kE4OmXilqg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read a Great Profile of Bo Jackson – An Amazing Athlete  http://t.co/p0CbUPfQ3W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can lead a boy to college but you can't make him think. - Elbert Hubbard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball's future? Bigger and bigger, better and better! No question about it, it's the greatest game there is! - Ted Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a stuffed toy! It's a sleeping bag. IT'S A SHARK! - Its COOL! http://t.co/OQ9gq086uU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BACON shaped themed Adhesive Bandages - Love It! http://t.co/rYZO9MH5ox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honeymoon:  A vacation before going to work for a new boss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just as soon as some people get up in the world they immediately start looking down on others. . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Mac and Katie Kissoon  http://t.co/f0UHwWagMY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These Yoda Lights Must You Have!  Wonderful Geek Gear! http://t.co/V95b1yKA5V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making money is not gonna change anything about what I am, except I won't answer the door. Abel Ferrara]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are 10 types of people in the world: those who understand binary, and those who don't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trust people and they will be true to you; Treat them greatly, and they will show themselves great. - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love my crazy girlfriend - hilarious t-shirt - http://t.co/1ffUNiBPpn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Lobo the Classic Rock Group?  http://t.co/BikfJ13zVd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shall we play a game? - Joshua, WarGames]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Dells  http://t.co/UGM1A1FTP9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips on Getting the Cheapest Car Loan  http://t.co/pCaMimhsfd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[M*A*S*H is an American TV classic - read all about its history -  http://t.co/3BI5jRoyrq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Heineken International  http://t.co/fCMYwQaW1G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is the mark of an educated mind to be able to entertain a thought without accepting it. - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes are the quickest way for women to achieve instant metamorphosis - Manolo Blahnik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellence is to do a common thing in an uncommon way. - Booker T. Washington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ginger Rogers did everything Fred Astaire did, backwards and on high heels - Faith Whittlesey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These Yoda Lights Must You Have!  Wonderful Geek Gear! http://t.co/x0CUY03alo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Crosby, Stills and Nash   http://t.co/KvDMYcCz8s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One family that practices population control:  the mafia!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Star Wars  http://t.co/v8sUL1g7kk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is what remains after one has forgotten everything he learned in school. - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Management is nothing more than motivating other people. - Le Iacocca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This episode was BADLY written! - Gwen, Galaxy Quest]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Useful Products to Help Housebreak Your Pet  http://t.co/F5HnKrgfTB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellence is to do a common thing in an uncommon way. - Booker T. Washington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman is as young as she feels like telling you she is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trying to sneak a pitch past Hank Aaron is like trying to sneak a sunrise past a rooster. - Curt Simmons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Wonderful Canadian Rockies Tour  http://t.co/AZsEf7YdLm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I care not for a man's religion whose dog and cat are not the better for it. - Abraham Lincoln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Writing Company Blogs that are Effective  http://t.co/KwRtukv9hc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About The Christian Faith  http://t.co/ygy9bMjO9A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If people don't want to come out to the ball park, nobody's gonna stop 'em. - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So exactly what is an atomic clock?  http://t.co/XdM3SRiw7S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a great day to play two!  - Ernie Banks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Success is dependent upon the glands - sweat glands. - Zig Ziglar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In difficult times, fashion is always outrageous. - Elsa Schiaparelli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People all over the world recognize me as a spiritual leader.  Steven Seagal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are so many things you can learn about. But you'll miss the best things if you keep your eyes shut. - Dr. Suess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting Your Creative Writing Degree Online  http://t.co/2asKzfW1VP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strikeouts are boring - besides that, they're fascist. Throw some ground balls. More democratic. - Bull Durham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I see a pair of shoes I adore, and it doesn't matter if they have them in my size. I buy them anyway. - Keira Knightley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boys, baseball is a game where you gotta have fun. You do that by winning. - Dave Bristol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yo, dudes. Got a new tourney lined up. We're playing for the last of the deodorant sticks. Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious What Went Wrong T-shirt - Love It!  http://t.co/7yeTHxv9nj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They just couldn't live without each other --  so they got married and discovered they could]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Return the shoes?! I can't talk to you when you're being hysterical! - Gabrielle, Desperate Housewives]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gary US Bonds was an amazing musician and rocker - read his history - http://t.co/f7X9EArQPs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn the Best Spots for Mountain Climbing  http://t.co/f4FcgEyqRr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of American Hamburgers  http://t.co/Y5jmyltydh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fifty per cent of rock is having a good time. - Roger Daltrey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Customer:  "Could I try on that suit in the window?"  Clerk:  "We'd rather you do that in the dressing room."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Walking: the most ancient exercise and still the best modern exercise. - Carrie Latet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science fiction is no more written for scientists than ghost stories are written for ghosts. - Brian W. Aldiss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Amazing and Mesmerizing SciFi &amp; Space Artwork  http://t.co/bDODzDQlh8]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>