<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Plastic surgeons can do almost anything with a nose these days, except keep it out of other people's business]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the shoe fits, it's too expensive. - Adrienne Gusoff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best thing to save for your old age is yourself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[if you want to save face --  keep the lower half shut]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smoking kills. If you killed, you've lost a very important part of your life. Brooke Shields]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fool and his money are soon accepted into the highest social circles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[STAR TREK ENTERPRISE - Brake Light Vinyl Decal - ENGAGE!  --&gt; http://t.co/qNcgVwsbLQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not the mistakes in life that are important; it's what we learn from them. - Donna Guthrie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Finance Trade Secrets  http://t.co/xAs6N6JrYJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is Renter's Insurance?  http://t.co/4G1RA60Gei]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is an ornament in prosperity and a refuge in adversity.  - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Humble Pie  http://t.co/YCEBUAblKw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Different Types of Beer  http://t.co/BCAflPQj9o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Spinners  http://t.co/akYx2yM9J7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Arthur Alexander – Country and R&amp;B Pioneer  http://t.co/FB9YS4Potf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Mountain Biking – A Real Adventure  http://t.co/BswHAJqYyI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Nike  http://t.co/sSViPgnt0S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You could get rich manufacturing crutches for lame excuses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I grew up in a world that told girls they couldn't play rock 'n' roll. - Joan Jett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About How Technology Has Helped Seniors to Make Great Strides in their Lifestyle  http://t.co/cy3XlitxWo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A tax collector has what it takes to take what you got]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wondering. If Money Doesn't Grow On Trees, then Why Do Banks Have all those Branches??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Delfonics  http://t.co/gRENz25fmT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to David Bowie  http://t.co/tNymX1n8xf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The pessimist sees difficulty in every opportunity. The optimist sees opportunity in every difficulty. - Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do something for somebody every day for which you do not get paid. - Albert Schweitzer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The universe, as far as we can observe it, is a wonderful and immense engine. - George Santayana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Early History of Marvel Comics  http://t.co/9L0MRDAbQr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wear my sort of clothes to save me the trouble of deciding which clothes to wear. - Katherine Hepburn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've never heard a Jay-Z song.  Miley Cyrus on Jay-Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Beach Boys  http://t.co/OJBChFaUEM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A mosquito is just like a child, when it stops making noise, you know it's getting into something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Overview of Domestic Adoption  http://t.co/uNzVc3o4Ak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's so nervous he keeps coffee awake]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blogging Season 1 of Lilyhammer by Netflix   http://t.co/oFDylEh0wk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Wonderful Canadian Rockies Tour  http://t.co/o6ACMrcTrY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Petula Clark  http://t.co/6rYEVnMVpI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Best Camping Destinations  http://t.co/V0vzWTNrbK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must accept finite disappointment, but we must never lose infinite hope. - Martin Luther King, Jr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the shoe fits, it's too expensive. - Adrienne Gusoff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Domestic Adoption And Government’s Rules  http://t.co/YmLN7Mtqvm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One Family’s Adoption Stories  http://t.co/jNzQ2XC095]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think nobody cares if you're alive, try missing a couple of car payments. - Earl Wilson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well, I think we're the greatest rock 'n' roll band in the world.  - Joey Ramone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One day your life will flash before your eyes. Make sure it is worth watching - Mooie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not anti-social; I'm just not user friendly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I consider exercise vulgar. It makes people smell. - Alec Yuill Thornton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't be afraid to get creative and experiment with your marketing.  Mike Volpe - CMO - Hubspot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can do anything, but lay off my blue suede shoes - Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many a small thing has been made large by the right kind of advertising. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is an ornament in prosperity and a refuge in adversity.  - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't think and hit at the same time. - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who likes not his business, his business likes not him. - William Hazlitt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Importance of Keywords for Search Engine Optimization (SEO)  http://t.co/UQM56D7Jn0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 7 ages of a woman are the right one and 6 wild guesses!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was your operation expensive? "No, the doctor gave me cut rates."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I live in heels. Give me a pair of flip-flops and I'll trip all over myself. - Brenda Song]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read a Review of Heaven is For Real  http://t.co/sta0efzBI1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About The St. Augustine Alligator Farm – Zip Lines and Lots of Gators!  http://t.co/YhxYwFrmg7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 3 - My Visit With Dr. McFadzean  http://t.co/bYWS8Uo43l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It just seems to happen that by the time most of us get a little money to burn,  "the fire goes out."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Queen  http://t.co/hsQCF8A08m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Molly Hatchet  http://t.co/WbDE9rA1Ak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Auto racing is boring except when a car is going at least 172 miles per hour upside down. - Dave Barry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good pitching will beat good hitting any time, and vice versa. - Bob Veale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read about the interesting history of Garland Texas - http://t.co/Y4ffUxsdON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of France Joli  http://t.co/ekszradhFU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never argue with the data. - Sheen, Jimmy Neutron]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whenever you are asked if you can do a job, tell "˜em, "˜Certainly I can!' Then get busy and find out how to do it. - Theodore Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep your face to the sunshine and you cannot see the shadows. - Helen Keller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lassie is an American TV classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/54OOYtNsqT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Whispers  http://t.co/oMmBTd18RY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Frustrations of Youth Pitching  http://t.co/V9d2ZlTsVg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like wrestling a gorilla- you don't quit when you're tired, you quit when the gorilla is tired - Robert Strauss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can say any foolish thing to a dog, &amp; the dog will give a look that says, My God youre right I never wouldve thought of that! Dave Barry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is the transmission of civilization. - Will Durant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Strategy Consulting Firms: Gaining a Competitive Advantage  http://t.co/hHSemmnGDC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tantrums, Sick Days, and Being a Patient Mommy  http://t.co/Hpz5E8Yf8g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After the third flip, I lost control - Don Roberts after crashing in the Jade Grenade at New England Dragway in 1975.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Strategy Consulting Firms to Avoid  http://t.co/f4rx1UZoSX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Isley Brothers  http://t.co/PtRwCU5OcW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, I'm from Iowa. I only work in outer space. - Kirk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's recording techniques would have been regarded as science fiction forty years ago. - Tony Visconti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool iPhone 4 Review  http://t.co/4EHHgAwTs0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is what you get from reading the small print in a contract. "experience " is what you get from not reading it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hiring Strategy Consulting Firms: The Importance of Competitive Analysis  http://t.co/gR4EH2yaT0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're a very expensive group; we break a lot of rules. It's unheard of to combine opera with a rock theme, my dear. - Freddie Mercury]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The key to wisdom is a knowledge of our own ignorance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think that gay marriage is something that should be between a man and a woman. - Arnold Schwarzenegger, on gay marriage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You've got to say, I think that if I keep working at this and want it badly enough I can have it. It's called perseverance. - Lee Iacocca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is simply the soul of a society as it passes from one generation to another. - Gilbert K. Chesterton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The main part of intellectual education is not the acquisition of facts but learning how to make facts live." - Oliver Wendell Holmes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why did I want to win? Because I didn't want to lose! - Max Schmelling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fish Hotel Aquarium - Jazz Up Your Office! http://t.co/mTYzb3RChQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the shoe fits, you're not allowing for growth. - Robert N Coons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can a guy win a game if you don't give him any runs? - Robert Bo Belinsky after Losing 15 - 0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The quality of a leader is reflected in the standards they set for themselves. - Ray Kroc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DotNetNuke 6.0 – A Big Leap Forward  http://t.co/6FkRp39YOl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All men are born free and equal, but most of them get married.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good-bye, Broadcast.  Hello, Conversation.  Shel Israel - Co-Author Naked Conversations]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>