<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Protect you and and your family from unwanted Internet porn... Get your FREE trial of Covenant Eyes now: http://t.co/yb4VacYaG1  #WeHatePorn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Perhaps the most common reason we are controlled by other people - CLOSELY related to the fea… http://t.co/ZRkHqoHspM http://t.co/BCGPFNWPn1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The pursuit of holiness... - The Holy Spirit’s work in transforming us more and more into the… http://t.co/RfTBrnodoH http://t.co/AA81cQs0sF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Faith Takes the Crown Off a Man's Head - Christ often takes the crown off his own head, and puts it upon the head of… http://t.co/zwA0Pgzb5v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free daily Podcast of Andrew Murray's "Waiting on God"! Subscribe here: https://t.co/hZcE2tyLSy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free one-month trial of the best Internet filter/accountability program (PC or MAC!) - Sign up now at http://t.co/je6uhfJguh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free daily Podcast of Andrew Murray's "Abide in Christ"! Subscribe here: https://t.co/8EqVojijIS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Filter out porn!? Get your FREE trial of Covenant Eyes now: http://t.co/gKUdipf9TT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The true effect of the gospel - The Gospel was not meant merely to reside in our intellect, m… http://t.co/Wuwq1E3A31 http://t.co/6gmLjPrXU4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lord, fulfill this type in me... - The righteous shall flourish like the palm tree: he shall … http://t.co/HwEz1QWT5N http://t.co/AvAXyDRdee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fear-based living vs. Faith-based living - We experience the power of life and death in two gardens: the garden of E… http://t.co/WGPuTuxaEW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Reformed faith eliminates the "worry" aspect of evangelism - The Reformed faith also eliminates the "worry" aspe… http://t.co/dG3qpuXRJR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suffering from an overdose of fear? - An overdose of fear comes from ignorance of the grace of Christ. ~ John Calvin… http://t.co/3ZZXxpA6Xv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How much does mercy cost? - Christ’s mercy is to be had for nothing, bribe or purchase is out… http://t.co/Xc2FJjRIlg http://t.co/7CqhdMyWSa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Randomness, luck, chance, fate? - Randomness, luck, chance, fate. This is modern man’s answer to the age-old questio… http://t.co/EFR2XeMuvE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Way To Be Saved - The way to be saved is to come to Christ. Christ is a person, a living … http://t.co/awUxyQGeqy http://t.co/7nbYWSl5hj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not chosen just so the idea merely bounce around in your brain... - The point of all this is … http://t.co/g44BRaDo1c http://t.co/Izb8gnnDw4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protect you and and your family from Internet #PORN... Get your FREE trial of Covenant Eyes now: http://t.co/ne3Jy4J96t  #WeHatePorn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What It Means To Believe - There are two ways to believe. The first way is to believe about God, meaning we believe … http://t.co/FOkJ19RYQw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please share this with those you know who need to be protected from online #porn - FREE trial of Covenant Eyes at http://t.co/69RSLOgapl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is it that will motivate us to live not for ourselves but for Him? - The apostle Paul wrote that Christ died th… http://t.co/puxz2drwxI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free daily Podcast of Andrew Murray's "Abide in Christ"! Subscribe here: https://t.co/8EqVojijIS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who are members of the universal church? - The visible church may be distressingly and sorely… http://t.co/E6GeFagtpu http://t.co/2Kceyao631]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free daily Podcast of Andrew Murray's "Waiting on God"! Subscribe here: https://t.co/hZcE2tyLSy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More Than A Mere Man - There are certain persons who deny the godhead of our Lord and yet thi… http://t.co/vZ4m3vCdA0 http://t.co/tFwqPmaodj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is impossible for someone whom the Father “draws” not to come to Him - Jesus also says tha… http://t.co/WJKYKzy1Od http://t.co/PsnTS95ZuA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The true Christian seeks after it - The actions of the Christian—I do not claim perfection fo… http://t.co/YTla63a4jx http://t.co/GaRJWYNuSd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free daily Podcast of Andrew Murray's "Waiting on God"! Subscribe here: https://t.co/hZcE2tyLSy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can we come to the place where we are acutely conscious of His love?  - If the love of Christ for us is to be th… http://t.co/EFoEz2HX0J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free one-month trial of the best Internet filter/accountability program (PC or MAC!) - Sign up now at http://t.co/je6uhfJguh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God changing His purpose? - There are some persons who talk about God changing His purpose—su… http://t.co/AfS7Sfa7WQ http://t.co/kuEyYBgjG5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free daily Podcast of Andrew Murray's "Abide in Christ"! Subscribe here: https://t.co/8EqVojijIS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doesn't the teaching on self-esteem and its emphasis on self seem to make the problem worse? … http://t.co/0MeKabMuus http://t.co/lgzoULHjHb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Filter out porn? Get your FREE trial of Covenant Eyes now: http://t.co/KX90O1DXY2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why The Heavenly Robes Are White - Here a saint has an evident excess of the red of courage, … http://t.co/on9fQY0ZQs http://t.co/8ylOaZlvqr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What are the limits of human freedom? - While we are free from our perspective, we must reali… http://t.co/3xXBKlAmUH http://t.co/j6HXTMjFdS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just face your fear!? - Simply saying to a person immersed in fear, “Just face your fear!” is like Bob Newhart’s “Ju… http://t.co/eUCm0eYzMn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free daily Podcast of Andrew Murray's "Waiting on God"! Subscribe here: https://t.co/hZcE2tyLSy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God is good but not sovereign? - Along with the doctrine of chance, many Christians are also buying into the philoso… http://t.co/1AnsF8Qz1Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protect you and and your family from unwanted Internet porn... Get your FREE trial of Covenant Eyes now: http://t.co/mgtHiiYjXh  #WeHatePorn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He who cleaves to sin is not yet saved... - [Commenting on Mt. 1:18-25] The name JESUS means "Savior." It is the sam… http://t.co/pntiOpVEnw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free daily Podcast of Andrew Murray's "Abide in Christ"! Subscribe here: https://t.co/8EqVojijIS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A striking example of faith! - [Commenting on Mt. 2:1-12] ...the conduct of the wise men is a striking example of fa… http://t.co/mG0Uf55rb5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please share this with those you know who need to be protected from online #porn - FREE trial of Covenant Eyes at http://t.co/69RSLOgapl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The second most mentioned virtue in the New Testament - While not surprised by the primacy of love in New Testament … http://t.co/8qJ6xAHorS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The ultimate cure for anxiety - The apostle Paul in writing to the Philippians gives them the admonition to be "anxi… http://t.co/TsrPvrWV5f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our free choices, yet God determined them? - God is much greater than we can possibly imagine… http://t.co/MDq5NKXQVE http://t.co/mkOq2ckzs8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Filter out porn? Get your FREE trial of Covenant Eyes now: http://t.co/zcR11nMeLE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What could be more explicit? - The king’s heart is in the hand of the Lord, as the rivers of … http://t.co/bT9NfcfB8C http://t.co/oDT8Yiofmg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free daily Podcast of Andrew Murray's "Waiting on God"! Subscribe here: https://t.co/hZcE2tyLSy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please share this with those you know who need to be protected from online #porn - FREE trial of Covenant Eyes at http://t.co/69RSLOgapl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That seeming sweet that is in sin... - That seeming sweet that is in sin will quickly vanish;… http://t.co/4jCjfzBKhi http://t.co/p2e7ywfeWH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free daily Podcast of Andrew Murray's "Abide in Christ"! Subscribe here: https://t.co/8EqVojijIS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The glory of the gospel - The glory of the gospel is that God pronounces people just while th… http://t.co/NUC3Z5iQ5M http://t.co/o57ZBw15hu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome display of God's power - Recommended - Science and Grace: God's Reign in the Natural Sciences - http://t.co/n2t9sj9D9R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He never would have chosen me afterwards... - Ah! sir, the Lord must have loved me before I w… http://t.co/vCPtUE7dJx http://t.co/zvHTIF3dca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Defend the Bible? - Defend the Bible? I would as soon defend a lion! Unchain it and it will d… http://t.co/2E71Knupza http://t.co/oBAX71Mw1Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is anxiety always sinful? - Discussing “sin” and “anxiety” with a person struggling with anxiety can produce more an… http://t.co/Kg181KqrSS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God covering His naked enemies - The gospel is the story of God covering his naked enemies, b… http://t.co/mznSNrOXCw http://t.co/iOPvoc7SHr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be happy forever! - To be in a state of true grace, is to be miserable no more; it is to b… http://t.co/m6ufheGH30 http://t.co/nMufqfoDt3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is our faith the gift of God also? - Clearly the “gift” of God is salvation in its totality, … http://t.co/MLO2zNpSnX http://t.co/k7JZIIZv8e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our accomplishments remain insufficient - However much we may want—or feel the need—to trophy… http://t.co/lhJt9bEYYy http://t.co/quOgfK981z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free daily Podcast of Andrew Murray's "Waiting on God"! Subscribe here: https://t.co/hZcE2tyLSy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anger is not Always Sinful - The first thing to understand about anger is that it isn't alway… http://t.co/1QD8igEBe2 http://t.co/UO0WmXnras]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free one-month trial of the best Internet filter/accountability program (PC or MAC!) - Sign up now at http://t.co/je6uhfJguh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A summary of Arminianism vs. Calvinism - Perseverance of the Saints - The Arminian believes t… http://t.co/6ag4iGYsrs http://t.co/YhyjVOGHWZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free daily Podcast of Andrew Murray's "Abide in Christ"! Subscribe here: https://t.co/8EqVojijIS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Hyper-Calvinism Biblical? - I can only conclude that the external call of the gospel is a … http://t.co/UhhoDgvcpc http://t.co/K7b6L6ah73]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Filter out porn? Get your FREE trial of Covenant Eyes now: http://t.co/lmwej4rqTK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What should motivate our goodness? - By showing us what moves God, the Bible also shows what … http://t.co/GuTiMedz95 http://t.co/YOpLOMa2M1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here is a foundation for faith...here is an anchor for the soul! - The Lord God omnipotent re… http://t.co/6l7hOqiSuV http://t.co/EnIcsEj5rf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What facing and fighting anxiety really is supposed to be... - God calls us to share Scripture and soul—truth and lo… http://t.co/oktGyFaEA9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How shall we respond to the fact that God is able to and does in fact move in the minds and hearts of people to acco… http://t.co/a2iyZtjPHn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free daily Podcast of Andrew Murray's "Waiting on God"! Subscribe here: https://t.co/hZcE2tyLSy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calvinism dilemma? God is sovereign vs. our responsibility... - How can Calvinists affirm bot… http://t.co/3os3UPqgqX http://t.co/YziI6EapEe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free one-month trial of the best Internet filter/accountability program (PC or MAC!) - Sign up now at http://t.co/je6uhfJguh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is more than just knowing facts about God - In order to trust God we must know Him in an intimate, personal way. … http://t.co/hxhkqH7Saq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What happens when the reality of my fear runs smack into the reality of Christ’s word? - It is in this context of ov… http://t.co/Ak35VFG1oA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free daily Podcast of Andrew Murray's "Abide in Christ"! Subscribe here: https://t.co/8EqVojijIS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is from this mother-thought that the all-embracing life system of Calvinism sprang. - Ther… http://t.co/TLY9jnlyZL http://t.co/1OPjHtlkoY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No desire for God? - If you don't feel strong desires for the manifestation of the glory of G… http://t.co/s22Vh0m1fm http://t.co/XdIEKiTUe2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free daily Podcast of Andrew Murray's "Waiting on God"! Subscribe here: https://t.co/hZcE2tyLSy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calvin was the first to seek the Church in the believers themselves. - Luther as well as Calvin contended for a dire… http://t.co/ONwq5WFClu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protect you and and your family from Internet #PORN... Get your FREE trial of Covenant Eyes now: http://t.co/2QFH75jHlt  #WeHatePorn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If there is a single event in all of the universe that can occur outside of God’s sovereign control... - Confidence … http://t.co/bMLYb5AuMq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free daily Podcast of Andrew Murray's "Abide in Christ"! Subscribe here: https://t.co/8EqVojijIS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More people in Heaven than hell? - I believe there will be more in Heaven than in hell. If an… http://t.co/18acfP6PLi http://t.co/lKhsF0vI9s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Filter out porn?! Get your FREE trial of Covenant Eyes now: http://t.co/omt3rSWAuI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To recognize that the Bible is God’s Word... - To recognize that the Bible is God’s Word, and… http://t.co/rwgHkXYZ13 http://t.co/Uf30Rm2ssk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A prayer to avoid the pitfalls of loving theology more than the Lord - Mighty God, Thank you for giving me eyes, ear… http://t.co/vIcHgN1pYJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first dimension of the Christian life - You have often heard me say that the Christian life has two dimensions: … http://t.co/iatilX5ue8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free daily Podcast of Andrew Murray's "Waiting on God"! Subscribe here: https://t.co/hZcE2tyLSy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protect you and and your family from unwanted Internet porn... Get your FREE trial of Covenant Eyes now: http://t.co/MksoCbpPl5  #WeHatePorn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does God's sovereignty minimize our obligations? - And the Lord’s servant must not be quarrel… http://t.co/O893gLzNk6 http://t.co/bOgRjFiWcz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free one-month trial of the best Internet filter/accountability program (PC or MAC!) - Sign up now at http://t.co/je6uhfJguh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does God base His choice of His elect on? - The Arminian believes that God's choice is b… http://t.co/W8k833V5D9 http://t.co/l28AfeO2dx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Free daily Podcast of Andrew Murray's "Abide in Christ"! Subscribe here: https://t.co/8EqVojijIS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Faith and repentance in regards to election? - We are not disputing whether faith and repenta… http://t.co/EFMlD0KMlW http://t.co/T77b82WUx0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is God at the mercy of His own creation? - ...if we say that God's providence does not extend over evil, we are maki… http://t.co/vpeJgvAPew]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of our problems with the sovereignty of God - One of our problems with the sovereignty of God is that it frequen… http://t.co/EK9mt4ebor]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>