<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering Technical Leader-Process: Engineering Technical Leader-Process Job Description Global Nonwovens in Roswell, GA at Kimberly-Clark Engineering Technical Leader – Process Requisition No. ****** POSITION SUMMARY Engineers at Kimberly-Clark work… https://t.co/uUavUijpw4 https://t.co/9UN5BG25ul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Advanced Technology Group: The Keefe Group Project Manager will execute and deploy large complex technology implementation projects for state correctional agencies. The success of the deployment is accomplished by managing the various… https://t.co/ziGZNisPHH https://t.co/RYfXZPZKuv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Solutions Architect: Job Description: Would you like to perform rewarding work while contributing to the success of an established, growing company? OurFederal CivilianGroup at Pragmatics, Inc . is seeking a Software Development… https://t.co/wiKtkoT57h https://t.co/NNswkPpCJS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C++ Software Engineer – Santa Clara, CA: C++ Software Engineer Santa Clara, CA Full Time Position Job Description: Software engineer with 5 years experience to work on modem interfacing layers and modem interfacing SW communication protocols for clients… https://t.co/AnLpKZcT2q https://t.co/F4irc3GDSk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Download Your Facebook Data and What to Look for in It: Here's how to parse the downloadable file of data the social network has about you. https://t.co/K2eDTGdn68 https://t.co/30TNzKksNq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Manager – Cybersecurity Team: Why join Irdeto? We are on a mission! A mission to secure the world’s digital platforms. Why? Because a secure platform allows our clients to produce and deliver great content. In return, you can enjoy the latest… https://t.co/PXJd9Hx3ih https://t.co/kDtJYmLpFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Backend Developer: Responsibilities * Develop the core infrastructure, framework and services that incorporate our proprietary algorithms * Collaborate closely with PM, UX, and other stakeholders to clarify functional flows and provide technical insights… https://t.co/2hVtLON3A2 https://t.co/urbRpmlzZd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Help Desk Analyst: Associate Help Desk Analyst Why Work For Credit Acceptance? Credit Acceptance is rapidly-expanding our IT department with a variety of dynamic opportunities. Our culture has landed us on Computerworld’s list of the Best… https://t.co/LcDIXDXRJA https://t.co/e2FhJLSPLh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales and Application Engineer: Sales and Application Engineer Job Description Absolute Process Instruments, Inc. (API), a manufacturer of industrial process instrumentation products and digital pressure gauges, is looking for an experienced sales and… https://t.co/K2QSlhgmeC https://t.co/nBxmcQ63Oy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Satellite Software Engineer: Satellite Software Engineer About SpaceQuest, Ltd. SpaceQuest, Ltd. is an entrepreneurial commercial space company located just outside Washington DC in Fairfax Virginia. We are a leading developer of satellite technology and… https://t.co/RVyFGIKPsL https://t.co/fZeDFaTRw1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Consultant: Description QGenda is a fast growing Atlanta-based healthcare software company, with an amazing corporate culture, where we strive to be the best place to be a customer. Our software is used by thousands of hospital departments… https://t.co/zSAMu8MLwR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Systems Software Engineer: Are you passionate about ray tracing and interactive computer graphics? NVIDIA is looking for talented software engineers to help build software systems that define the future of computer graphics. We are seeking a… https://t.co/cZn3NuTPTw https://t.co/LSdshPW08o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer (JavaScript): Our development team works on the entire tech stack (from low-level database operations to front-end development) for a large cloud-based enterprise application for the construction industry. Engineers work with all… https://t.co/7GJBrcYGcb https://t.co/XKE23P0FTb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Test Automation Engineer: Software Test Automation Engineer Hillsboro, OR Fulltime position Job Description: Responsible for writing test cases, executing tests and automating tests for the OPAE, which is the software infrastructure for Intel… https://t.co/q32stooqNd https://t.co/M1yaQNhjfC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net DeveloperDOT64528118*Richmond, VA*Client needs a .Net developer to make modifications to an electronic registration and titling system.  CLIENT MINIMUM REQUIREMENTS: (ONLY APPLY IF YOU MEET ALL MINIMUM REQUIREMENTS)*Only Direct US… https://t.co/zedxRE3Jfc https://t.co/2k4v5ZtftN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer Analyst-ETL Developer: Programmer Analyst – ETL DeveloperDSS86528656*Richmond, VA*ETL software design, development and enhancements, documentation and maintenance work; mentoring less senior team members and knowledge transfer very important. … https://t.co/ZyxpkTNAUc https://t.co/BTs7HqBRvQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Contact Center Architect. w/ Genesys Interactive Intelligence exp.: Sr. Contact Center Architect. w/ Genesys Interactive Intelligence exp. RT00110011*REMOTE with travel (or Washington, DC)*Experience in overseeing the direction, development, and… https://t.co/GYAXge7jUv https://t.co/w3uB0JTa9n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Zuckerberg Finds It's Not Easy to Tame Facebook's Growth Obsession: Publication of a 2016 memo stating "maybe someone dies" in a terrorist attack coordinated on Facebook reveals just how thoroughly its quest for growth influenced the company. https://t.co/LpLg5dY5J6 https://t.co/Mvi6PuanLC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Bank Analyzer – SC/SM – Full Time – (Top Management Consulting): Sr. Consultant to Sr. Manager level: * 4+ years of relevant consulting or industry experience. Recent consulting experience is "highly desired. * Functional/technical proficiency with… https://t.co/abwYTkIYtu https://t.co/CKu1xB6Xeg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Developer (JavaScript / Angular / React / Node): _Logikos was built on the idea that a software company that focuses on excellent engineers working in collaboration will produce better software for its clients. _ We are looking for a… https://t.co/zN2L4tSNd3 https://t.co/pEAFKThjvZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IOS Mobile Developer: 2 – IOS Mobil Developers Salary: $75-90k flex 2 years plus IOS Development Looking to hire experienced Mobile Application Developers to join our expanding Mobile Technology Center of Excellence. The Application Developers will be… https://t.co/aqHXseHGlM https://t.co/8OcMEyA2jM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big Data Analyst: Big Data Analyst Posted Date 2 weeks ago(3/7/2018 6:46 PM) ID 2018-30343 Job Location USA-DC-Washington Required Clearance Top Secret Category Engineering-Software Employment Type Full Time Hiring Company General Dynamics Mission… https://t.co/8SqozxOREt https://t.co/iMEQjVr1vo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Railgun Test Engineer: 17593BR Railgun Test Engineer General Atomics San Diego California General Atomics (GA), and its affiliated companies, is one of the world’s leading resources for high-technology systems development ranging from the nuclear fuel… https://t.co/CxtYUMJE3i https://t.co/3MGTDhRS3z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: Job Description As a senior software engineer you will work as an integral part of our Cloud Platform team that will enable exciting new features for our wireless audio products. The ideal candidate has extensive DevOps knowledge and… https://t.co/vskLJWeMUQ https://t.co/ggQwmXyDjp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SEO Analyst: SEO Analyst Location: Charleston, South Carolina, United States Full-time SUMMARY Levelwing is seeking highly motivated individuals to analyze, produce, and measure performance of website content as well as optimize websites through… https://t.co/ZhYsQhra3X https://t.co/n2fl8LpS9w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid-Level Program Protection and Anti-Tamper Engineer: General Atomics Aeronautical Systems, Inc. (GA-ASI), an affiliate of General Atomics, is a world leader in proven, reliable remotely piloted aircraft and tactical reconnaissance radars, as well as… https://t.co/55oZqgDTE4 https://t.co/vAB060QktK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Help Desk Support Analyst – Entry Level: Provide IT Help Desk support services to all Penn Virginia users including hardware, software, and certain application systems support. Install, configure, and deploy desktop/laptop hardware, software, printers,… https://t.co/yKN37U8kk5 https://t.co/Px9lgykuXj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Engineer-Industrial Automation: Systems Engineer – Advanced Industrial Automation We have a need for super-sharp systems engineer with a diverse background, experience, knowledge and hands-on skills for the following: • IT systems, server/client… https://t.co/IDk15zcL2x https://t.co/SswZAa5EX3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full-Stack Web Designer/Developer – Marketing: Anonyome Labs was created to give people control and freedom over their personal and private information. We believe that people should be able to determine how, what, and with whom they share their personal… https://t.co/yE50TUsMPs https://t.co/4F9AzZAcff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's Why Putting Porn in the Blockchain Won't Kill the Technology: Opinion: A new paper says dirty content encoded in the blockchain could make cryptocurrencies illegal. That's wrong. https://t.co/M8aMxDui6Z https://t.co/eUwrb0agrJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Sales: Zycus is hiring Regional Software Sales Manager for North East Region. Zycus headquarters was incorporated in Princeton, U.S. in 1988. Since then, we have grown everyday, and established as an organization which now is a leading global… https://t.co/7BjuqztCjF https://t.co/xVHMZVbYvJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Central Staffing Specialist: Position Summary: Will perform central staffing, day-to-day and shift-to-shift changes in the central staffing system in real time to ensure accuracy of daily staffing sheets, as well as ensure accurate productivity and… https://t.co/viMsfKAg1z https://t.co/A50PaecKBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Orthoptist: Job Description Evaluates and diagnose ocular motility disorders, performs specialized eye tests to assess visual acuity, focusing ability, eye movement (strabismus measurements), binocular function and color vision, using such equipment as… https://t.co/XzJ3RVFg7q https://t.co/oGqpMRThqZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Operational Risk Consultant 5 – Conduct Risk Assessment Methodology and Execution: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we want to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them succeed financially. We’re looking for talented people who will put our… https://t.co/FPI2JZaDQA https://t.co/cHcYo2qS8O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer – Market Risk IT – Market Data: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we want to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them succeed financially. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the center of… https://t.co/XHw5Ap8EjK https://t.co/Zq4vJgisO8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Web Developer: PRIMARY PURPOSE: Under minimum supervision, this position is responsible for assisting in the discovery, development, implementation, and support of software applications across BSI, its affiliates and business units. Responsible for… https://t.co/juORwq6Eut https://t.co/uWPLjx2c9Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Operational Risk Consultant 5 – Conduct Risk Assessment and Monitoring Program: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we want to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them succeed financially. We’re looking for talented people who will put our… https://t.co/A8UrS1jIGj https://t.co/DKzK6yYwg4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Secure DevOps Operational Risk Consultant 4: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we invest in our people. Our diverse lines of business offer unique opportunities to expand your knowledge and advance your career. This is an exciting opportunity to join a… https://t.co/P5DF0h16WQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer I, II – Phoenix, AZ: Software Developer I, II – Phoenix, AZ Job no: ****** Work type: Full Time Regular Location: Arizona Categories: Banking, Information Technnology The Software Developer I assists in improving the Bank’s existing… https://t.co/uMFtlbvxMQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer – Customer Data Services: About GoDaddy GoDaddy powers the world’s largest cloud platform dedicated to small, independent ventures. With nearly 17 million customers worldwide and over 73 million domain names under management,… https://t.co/OGZIKyTz9r https://t.co/IMSyRaNH4H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hadoop Administrator/Database Administrator: Food. Purpose. You. As one of the world’s leading food companies, General Mills believes that food should make us better. Food brings us joy and nourishes our lives, connecting us to each other and the earth.… https://t.co/ehhlJ0q8eV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guest Service Desk Team Member: Job ID: ******* Date posted: 04/27/2018 Location: 1 Mystic View Rd, Everett, Massachusetts Description: As a Guest Service team member, you are the front end and the face of what we stand for. You’ll be motivated by and… https://t.co/evSxKHHGmN https://t.co/RFVmL1AdNU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ForgeRock Developer: Job Description: ForgeRock Developer – 3+ Years of experience in IT and should be aligned with Access Management solutions. – 2 years of hands-on experience with ForgeRock AM. – Experience in installation and configurations. – Must… https://t.co/k4cbfNlgPc https://t.co/raD8AelhZp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[iOS Developer: Search and apply for jobs at Piper Companies | Careers at Piper Companies Careers Search Jobs Connect With Us iOS Developer Job Attributes Job Id: 18254Job Category: IT InfrastructureJob Location: Philadephia, PA 19145Security Clearance:… https://t.co/g7h7aRi5lx https://t.co/6iIiy44zq1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer We believe that high ­quality, innovative software is built by craftsmen in a collaborative workshop environment, rather than by workers on an assembly line. Our team values passion and dedication over drudgery and… https://t.co/eNbGEqL9xA https://t.co/ySP5YMCykj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Montage, the single solution to engage, interview, and hire better candidates faster, is seeking a passionate, driven, experienced Strategic Account Management. The Senior Software Engineer will be developing our web based rich… https://t.co/LLEFmiKWSd https://t.co/6HmsIlL3IX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Spport Specialist: Position Summary Responsible for providing first line technical issue resolution for Symitar and the third party applications as well as other support to requests throughout the organization. Position requires collaboration,… https://t.co/4GpRPArNox https://t.co/GruNoJ2RHh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Technical Architect: Description Cox Automotive, is currently looking for a Sr. Technical Architect with Oracle EBS experience to join our team in Atlanta, GA. The Sr Technical Architect is responsible for architecting and designing… https://t.co/AiKqrgO2be https://t.co/YtDs3MSjsa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Atheer is developing cutting-edge products using todays newest technology for one of the hottest emerging markets: Augmented Reality wearable technology. We build two main products: AiR Experience, combining computer vision based… https://t.co/r7awjkm4Z4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator: Stratford Solutions is assisting their client with finding a Systems Administrator to add to their team located in Manhattan, NYC. This is a full-time, direct hire, W2 position with our client. **Cannot accept 3rd party candidates… https://t.co/a1mP1OajBk https://t.co/PTwMXDXBcz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer: For Siemens Sr. Software Engineer job – Research &amp; Development – Flanders, New Jersey Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard – Toggle navigation – My Dashboard – Our Stories – FAQS – – Siemens Careers This… https://t.co/5By9holDCa https://t.co/gATpRzu9Jx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Search Technician/Developer: Where good people build rewarding careers. Think that working in the insurance field can’t be exciting, rewarding and challenging? Think again. You’ll help us reinvent protection and retirement to improve… https://t.co/tK0HXKvJOC https://t.co/a6vJhNfQm7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior Tester: We are currently seeking a motivated, career and customer service oriented Jr.Tester to join our team in Arlington, VA. to begin an exciting and challenging career with Unisys Federal Systems. Duties: – Collaborate closely with project… https://t.co/MceN7jkKvI https://t.co/rLEi7rqKOv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Office Net Web Application Developer: Job Description Job Description Job Number: R******* Office 365/.Net Web Application Developer Key Role: Apply knowledge of Office 365 and .Net Web Application development and design of Office 365 and .Net Web… https://t.co/CJCodNx0tg https://t.co/bRxVpE7Pxq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer Operations Administrator: Search Display Loading Close Your account has successfully been deleted. Close Message deleted. Job has been emailed. Job(s) has been emailed. Send email is not working. Please try again. Close Notifications and… https://t.co/dnoRFSQ2vb https://t.co/SALi2tmn8u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Physician: Pediatric GI Physician Needed in Central CA with: Ground floor Pediatric GI Faculty Opportunity at the Assistant, Associate or full Professor Rank. Great opportunity to help develop and build a new program. Join the ranks of a prestigious… https://t.co/WxnrpcopAy https://t.co/0v47Sq0mOM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quantitative Analytics &amp; Model Development Analyst Sr: Position Overview Position OverviewAs a Quantitative Analytics &amp; Model Development Analyst Sr within PNC’s Analytics and Portfolio Mgmt organization, you will be based in VA – Tysons Corner, DC –… https://t.co/9LwhwQJT9J https://t.co/hBZXmn1TcR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .NET Software Engineer: We are a small, but growing and well-funded healthcare company headquartered in Chicago! We are currently looking to fill a full-time, permanent position for a Senior .NET Software Engineer! This is a full-stack position.… https://t.co/pqFFXuDXiM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Security Systems Analyst, Expert: Cyber Security Systems Analyst, Expert ====================================== Req #: ******Location: Herndon, VA USJob Category: Information TechnologySecurity Clearance: TS/SCI with PolygraphClearance Status: Must… https://t.co/i2YGuGqlt7 https://t.co/fvQhzg6u5C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer Asc: Req ID : 396790BR Job Code/Title : E1071:Software Engineer Asc Job Description : Looking for a career with purpose? One that challenges your mind, grows your skills and contributes to our Nation's most critical missions? Do you… https://t.co/qQ9G1ZLxyi https://t.co/2QoroWarGd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ruby on Rails Developer: QuintEvents is an Official Hospitality Provider to some of the greatest names in sports and entertainment. We host events all around the world for our various partners including Formula 1, The Kentucky Derby, UFC, and NFL Hall of… https://t.co/ZjQRjKOWRj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Data Analyst Internal Audit: Recruiter Crown Castle Location Canonsburg Canonsburg United States Salary Competitive Posted 27 Apr 2018 Closes 23 May 2018 Job role Audit Sector Accounting and public practice Contract type Permanent Hours Full time… https://t.co/NpvOMbhrLS https://t.co/yzNqK0LxYX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior User Experience Designer: Senior User Experience Designer – Careers in United States – Careers This site uses cookies. By continuing to browse the site you are agreeing to our use of cookies. Learn More Continue Some cookies on this site are… https://t.co/2IYMw04vFF https://t.co/gEAsviCzQc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Director: Castro County Healthcare of Dimmitt, is accepting applications for a full-time IT Director. This includes directing all IT operations to meet requirements and support of all maintenance of existing infrastructure and development of new… https://t.co/PY35yHjYsu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Engineer: Apple Inc. has multiple positions available in Cupertino, CA: Software Development Engineer (Req#9UJRYF) Dsgn &amp; dev systms for spatial data ingestion, normalization, anlysis, format intrchnge &amp; publshing. Engineering… https://t.co/lWLGl7xUIA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst: Business Analyst Photon Infotech, Inc. Dallas, TX Research &amp; understand pharmaceutical, healthcare, dining, &amp; health related industry standards to define business requirements. Requires Bachelor of Science/foreign equivalent in Bachelor… https://t.co/fJWybQ7Xxf https://t.co/WVmF8J0Zw5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: SOFTWARE ENGINEER w/ Red Hat Inc. in Raleigh, NC. Senior Systems Engineer on our Infrastructure Services Measurement &amp; Metrics team. Support &amp; evolve our measurement &amp; metrics service portfolio, specifically w/ our Site Reliability… https://t.co/W1db1G9XEr https://t.co/zN3HbfioKW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frontend Web Javascript Developer: Client Reference Code: 209188JOB SUMMARYJoin the Video App Development team to deliver video streaming experiences for millions of Spectrum video customers, across multiple platforms, including Web, Smart TV, and… https://t.co/g206duP9dz https://t.co/fQhVN5JTFT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Field Engineer II: 103844BR Field Engineer II AL – Birmingham, AR – Little Rock, AZ – Phoenix, CO – Denver, ID – Boise, KS – Wichita, LA – New Orleans, MO – St. Louis, ND – Fargo, NE – Omaha, OK – Oklahoma City, SD – Sioux Falls, TN – Memphis ANGB, TN –… https://t.co/g13FYKcYSL https://t.co/d7Enx9LMrE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: TapHunter [************************************************************ is a fast growing technology startup that helps local business owners build thriving and sustainable businesses. We were recently mentioned in TIME, New York… https://t.co/hhyxX9MAIt https://t.co/zBgoWwlFQv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Account Executive: Account Executive Job Location US-NY-New York City Req No. 2018-2340 Category Sales/Presales Overview We have an immediate opportunity for an Account Executive on our Sales team in the New York, NY office. The ideal candidate must have… https://t.co/gM4w5awwYQ https://t.co/rXzmrLsvAm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SCRUM Master – TS/SCI:   Job Description – SCRUM Master – TS/SCI (18008526) SCRUM Master – TS/SCI Requisition ID : 18008526 Location : United States-Virginia-Fairfax US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation Assistance: No relocation… https://t.co/AMGhkLX5Bx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Research Development Test and Evaluation Software Engineer, Junior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Alexandria, VA Job Type: Entry Level, Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 4/15/2018 Job Description Job Number: R******* Booz Allen… https://t.co/0maJppvcJm https://t.co/rUgC1RfDHT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Program Management Advisor: COMPUTER/IT Program Management Advisor needed by STMicroelectronics, Inc. in Santa Clara, CA to author and specify high quality and thorough engineering requirement specifications for optical filters, including performance,… https://t.co/XF6vz1pKlT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tecknology: TECHNOLOGY Workday Inc. is accepting resumes for the following positions at various levels in San Mateo, CA: Software Engineer / Software Development Engineer (P3/4-SESDESM 4/29) – Analyzes, designs, programs, debugs, and modifies software… https://t.co/1rzNz5gh4k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Security Engineer 5 – Database Security Engineer: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the… https://t.co/EIG2jC3qBu https://t.co/5yHvDickZK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[iOS Engineering Manager: San Francisco, CA Full-time $0k – $0k Posted Today If you are a iOS Engineering Manager with experience, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us Our ultimate goal is to the improve the world, globally. We are an e-learning… https://t.co/jqmr68n7nz https://t.co/Z6k8tAuWMq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital Health Solution Architect: Digital Health Solution Architect (45703) Job Type: Full Time FTE/Bi-Weekly Hours: 1.0/80 Shift: Days Hours in Shift: 8 Location: Palo Alto, CA Req: 45703 Job Description Job Summary Define standards, guidelines,… https://t.co/PnEdpRI7AU https://t.co/qcb5SnKyUX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Account Support Manager:   Job Description – Account Support Manager (0066762_P0225624) Job Description  Account Support Manager-0066762_P0225624 Description   Title: Account Support Manager Job Location: Mumbai About Company: NCR Corporation (NYSE: NCR)… https://t.co/PUEgx4OHlm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Backend Node.JS Developer: Lead Backend Node.JS Developer Ref No.:18-02126 Location: Manhattan Beach, California Position Type:Contract This opportunity is with a multibillion $ Global giant based in United States, Canada &amp; Mexico, with 16 different… https://t.co/YKHloXV2cg https://t.co/gwffNvj9kG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front End Web Developer AngularJS, Mid-Level: We are looking for a mid-level Front-End Web Developer who is motivated to combine the art of design with the art of programming. Responsibilities will include translation of the UI/UX design wireframes to… https://t.co/0lz1WvAF6r https://t.co/5NA9XA7p6E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Research Applications Developer: Summary:  The research applications developer (RAD) is an entry-level programming job at the Southern Poverty Law Center’s Intelligence Project. The RAD supports projects across the research department with a focus on… https://t.co/AWPEQ0zlcf https://t.co/HPAhCqvQqi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staff Software Engineer #1251: Synaptics Inc. looks for Staff Software Engineer at Irvine, CA, to develop chipset software for digital media entertainment devices.   recblid m0wev1cwvdnr8bi4kmpqwtv9qdos31 https://t.co/bvdQaryMfK https://t.co/c9TJnDXYKj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Description:Leidos Corporate Information Security Group has an immediate opening for an experienced and motivated Software Developer to join our Cybersecurity Intelligence &amp; Response Center (CSIRC) in Gaithersburg – MD.   As a… https://t.co/CSC3OwGJwp https://t.co/sfShb2ciUi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QUALITY AND DATA COORDINATOR: Position PurposeThis RN position serves as the Surgical Care Reviewer (SCR) in support of the American College of Surgeons (ASC), National Surgical Quality Improvement Program (NSQIP) registry. Collects preoperative,… https://t.co/wxjqSzn9gL https://t.co/fUBBJrg1Np]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Analytics Principal Engineer I: Client Reference Code: 215208Company Overview:Charter Communications is America’s fastest growing TV, internet and voice company. We’re committed to integrating the highest quality service with superior… https://t.co/YmNUAQYl5o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Operations Analyst: Our client, a leading global FinTech company, is looking for an Operations Analyst to join their team. This is an opportunity to work with a dynamic team, to fuel the company’s growth and will provide enormous exposure to the… https://t.co/cidSDAEnyU https://t.co/hI1Kl2gcp0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer / Security Technology Group: For years, Cisco’s vision has been to change the way the world works, lives, plays, and learns. Our vision is more relevant today than ever. We made the Internet what it is today. First, we focused on… https://t.co/gATQMIgoze https://t.co/GuItpY7d59]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Numerical Control Programmer – Composites Trim and Drill: Numerical Control Programmer – Composites Trim and Drill Jobs in Tukwila at Boeing Skip Navigation SearchMenu – News – Investors – Employee/Retiree – Merchandise – Suppliers – Features &amp;… https://t.co/jlVvd2UDl4 https://t.co/o24k7wcCbD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Engineer-Software: Senior Engineer-Software sought by Dish Network, LLC in Superior, CO. Design, build, create, &amp; maintain python ETL scripts/services applied to various meta data providers; optimize &amp; enhance existing NOSQL &amp; SQL based services;… https://t.co/ra9U2dRb2m https://t.co/S1M2HVOYa9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Human Factor Engr: Eng’g: Human Factor Engr (Irvine, CA) Eyefinity, Inc.: Dvlp user intrfc desns for web, tablet, mobile, &amp; desktop user apps; lead/improve process of defin’g user intrfce app desn &amp; behavior. recblid sf12gi4n5cp1kw2r5qm6byoeenyh3z https://t.co/bq4hbEBoyM https://t.co/lJhiJmo8cK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Security Consultant: Position Overview At PNC, our people are our greatest differentiator and competitive advantage in the markets we serve. We are all united in delivering the best experience for our customers. As a Cyber Security Consultant… https://t.co/KwZPvAMH8M https://t.co/bbeHDX1pgu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Building Engineer: JOB SUMMARY Leads shift operations and directs vendors and subcontractors. Utilizes advanced skills to perform complex preventive maintenance and corrective repair of buildings, industrial systems, vehicles, equipment and grounds.… https://t.co/BGgxML58VN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Controller / Director of Accounting -Entertainment: Job Description Controller / Director of Accounting – Entertainment Our client is a leading entertainment company focusing on TV, film and digital production and distribution. They are looking to add a… https://t.co/0DUhVAKQoS https://t.co/KprkImNAb0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indices Data Analyst: Indices Data Analyst Princeton Posted Apr 4, 2018 – Requisition No. 66381 Bloomberg runs on data, and in the Global Data team we’re responsible for acquiring it and providing it to our clients. We collect, analyze process and… https://t.co/BWopBwRmuq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Antenna Systems Mechanical Designer: Req ID : 431682BR Job Code/Title : E1412:Mechanical Engineer Job Description : The RF &amp; Photonics Department is seeking candidates to work in a research and development environment providing mechanical engineering… https://t.co/FRn5t1gJRp https://t.co/DBVecKJPTU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Lead Business/Process Analyst: Job Title: IT Lead Business/Process Analyst Location: Eagan, MN, Mid-West United States, USA Company: CHS Inc. Industry Sector:Agribusiness Industry Type: Input Retail, Cooperative and Related Crop Services Career… https://t.co/vsta1rwjTj https://t.co/3RWsSEUCUc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[iOS Developer: Faithlife is looking for an iOS developer to join the Engagement Products team. As a Software Engineer on the team, you will develop Faithlife Groups and other apps. Faithlife is a tech company committed to the Church. We build the worlds… https://t.co/pTXO2fdWu9 https://t.co/Med53XuZn0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Analyst III – Systems Strategy: Business Systems Analyst III – Systems Strategy Tracking Code 3164-159 Job Description Graphic Packaging International, LLC, a wholly-owned subsidiary of Graphic Packaging Holding Company (NYSE: GPK), is… https://t.co/ur0AeiVxGe https://t.co/rHZgsjaTe3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior QA Engineers: Americloud Solutions, Inc. seeks Senior QA Engineers for various &amp; unanticipated worksites throughout the US (HQ: Schaumburg, IL) to design sw test plans, scenarios, &amp; scripts. Master’s in Comp Sci or Comp/Electrical/Electronics… https://t.co/MTMf01GwdJ https://t.co/65bbh9XvE2]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>