<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Operations Analyst – Kent, OH: Job Description Operations Analyst – Kent, OH #30955 Date: Jun 15, 2018 Location: Kent, OH, 44240 Company: The Davey Tree Expert Company Requisition Number: 30955 Company Name: The Davey Tree Expert Company Service Line:… https://t.co/LnQz2jFzLY https://t.co/9foBRHVTdn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master New Albany, Ohio – United States Job Start Date – 07/16/18, Posted Date – 06/28/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview Scrum Master Apex Systems, the nation s 2nd largest IT Staffing organization, has an exciting opportunity… https://t.co/7CcpL3pTy0 https://t.co/hxJfiG1IuW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former US Gymnastics doctor wants to be resentenced, disqualify judge who gave him 40-175 years in prison: Larry Nassar, the disgraced former US Gymnastics doctor now spending the rest of his life behind bars, is asking to be resentenced on sexual… https://t.co/Tv0YQ987Bh https://t.co/hZ5WBhbher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MS Access Engineer – assessing of the code, what it does, and how to bring it together | Can you reverse engineer a MS A: MS Access Engineer – assessing of the code, what it does, and how to bring it together | Can you reverse engineer a MS Access… https://t.co/y7pJFiZgeb https://t.co/1Dh9ClM5VZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Jersey will stop prosecuting marijuana cases, for now: New Jersey's top law enforcement official has instructed prosecutors statewide to hold off on pursuing convictions for marijuana-related crimes until the fall. https://t.co/2jGuz6kUay https://t.co/4WZJ0psSO0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump admin was warned a policy change could strengthen MS-13. They did it anyway.: Internal report said that ending US protections for more than 300,000 Central Americans would strengthen and grow MS-13 and other gangs https://t.co/2xsQi43Cox https://t.co/3ejCPN4IvA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Specialist IT-Application-Development: Specialist – IT Application Development Populus Group seeks a Specialist – IT Application Development in Columbus, OH to plan, initiate, and manage information technology projects in the insurance industry. Build a… https://t.co/P7xhIhXrhE https://t.co/AoehGkmOye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mgr Programs 1:   Job Description – Mgr Programs 1 (18007734) Mgr Programs 1 Requisition ID : 18007734 Location : United States-Ohio-Cincinnati US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation Assistance: No relocation assistance available… https://t.co/fEeibTkDBf https://t.co/BiSAsZigil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fans pay tribute to Demi Lovato with #HowDemiHasHelpedMe: Demi Lovato has often said she chose to be transparent about her struggles in the hope that it would help others. https://t.co/Pi9ajduUJF https://t.co/5T6yS3e1Qr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer: Senior Software Developer / Cincinnati , OH Overview: We are adding a senior level scrum team member with a focus on software engineering to help enhance our industry leading, in-house developed IT solutions. This position will… https://t.co/kdwZ8hsSpu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chinese state pushes back against widespread outrage over vaccine crisis: The Chinese government is turning to censorship and appeals for calm, amid mounting public anger following revelations earlier this week that one of the country's largest vaccine… https://t.co/LiHJhWgAtT https://t.co/AWkW3jS0PH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[40 years later, why is IVF still not covered by insurance?: Nearly 12% of American women have difficulty becoming pregnant or carrying a pregnancy to term. This makes it a condition roughly as common as diabetes, and yet the treatment for it is rarely… https://t.co/Dymk1JLlFo https://t.co/lJ1DxP9bkO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager II – Higher Ed: Project Manager II – Higher Ed Tracking Code 5158-244 Job Description At Gilbane we’re building more than buildings, we’re helping create schools, hospitals, laboratories and other facilities across the United States and… https://t.co/HpXRfHnWcj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big Data Developer: Big Data Developer Ref No.: 18-31648 Location: Columbus, Ohio – 5+ years of experience in middle-tier/backend systems development in Java/Linux – 6+ experience with Unix/Linux/Java scripting – Experience in Python scripting is a plus… https://t.co/1YcCJLAWqw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook is about to reveal whether data scandal hurt business: Investors are about to find out if Facebook has truly escaped the data debacle unscathed. https://t.co/lQdol3MDxj https://t.co/k2rN2rFS7k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NYC pizza delivery man to be released from ICE detention: Pablo Villavicencio, who was detained after trying to deliver a pizza to a military base in Brooklyn, will be released from ICE detention. https://t.co/zsWQlHIBwE https://t.co/47ZmckzEaz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man was shot to death while defending his friend against racial slurs, police say: When a man began yelling racial slurs at Chad Merrill's friend at a bar near York, Pennsylvania, Merrill told his friend to ignore him. But Merrill didn't heed his own… https://t.co/q1MP1GAQ84 https://t.co/f6L67P2AW4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Balenciaga's viral $8K coat is just seven coats piled on top of each other: The voluminous garment is also a physical representation of the struggle to keep warm. https://t.co/HbX0Xh7OAc https://t.co/fpHezTmNjO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From easy living to hard times, 300 years of New Orleans: As New Orleans celebrates its 300th anniversary in 2018, you can visit and enjoy a wide range of events, exhibitions and activities that mark 300 years of easy living and hard times. https://t.co/oPQABluVpz https://t.co/SjMic5E9BN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Andrew Gillum is smart not to take Ron DeSantis' 'monkey this up' bait: White people linking black people to monkeys has been a racist trope for centuries, LZ Granderson writes, but new Democratic nominee Andrew Gillum is wise to keep his campaign… https://t.co/JjgrDBrO7p https://t.co/32wCmU6Va2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ECM Developer: ECM Developer Ref No.: 18-35587 Location: Dublin, Ohio Position: ECM Developer Location: Dublin, OH Duration: 12 Months Job Details: ECM Developer Relevant Experience (in Yrs)4-6 years Technical/Functional Skills Java Scripts, IBM DB2… https://t.co/vZfp9bhKev]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia refuses to give a visa to Chelsea Manning, who wants to visit as part of a speaking tour: US whistleblower Chelsea Manning has been refused a visa to enter Australia where she was due to make a series of public appearances, her touring company… https://t.co/56Du7SPiiL https://t.co/4JYkAtERZZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prince Harry wows crowds by singing at Hamilton in London's West End: Prince Harry stole the show at London's West End after bursting into song at the hit US hip-hop musical Hamilton. https://t.co/Zy8eRGRrX6 https://t.co/agEttjD6Sh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jr. Ruby Developer | design, build, and maintain efficient, reusable, and reliable Ruby code: Jr. Ruby Developer | design, build, and maintain efficient, reusable, and reliable Ruby code – CareWorks TechCareWorks Tech CareWorks Tech Menu – Services – IT… https://t.co/KL5Wqgagvn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agile RA/BA – leads and manages requirements gathering and analysis activities by working with stakeholders, developers,: Agile RA/BA – leads and manages requirements gathering and analysis activities by working with stakeholders, developers, designers,… https://t.co/BOr3nlL7x1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How McCain's faith sustained him and allowed him to forgive himself: He rarely showed it in his public life, but John McCain spent a lot of time thinking about this moment -- when he would face his final judgment before God. https://t.co/w3ytuPxZGu https://t.co/rli1purTlv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Duck boat operator, captains now subject of federal criminal investigation: A federal criminal investigation into a deadly duck boat sinking on a Missouri lake was initiated after the US Coast Guard determined the 17 deaths resulted from "misconduct,… https://t.co/Uo1HZc9fkx https://t.co/XlXaN3E9ca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guidewire Developer: Guidewire Developer Ref No.: 18-33819 Location: Cinncinati, Ohio Must have: – 5-7 years of hands on work experience Guidewire Policy Center/Billng Center modules -Handle team of 4-5 members indipendently – Hands on knowlwdge of… https://t.co/8hBXTdvAwD https://t.co/uybknphE2Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally, a cop is convicted for recklessly shooting an unarmed teenager: Issac Bailey explains why the conviction of former Texas cop Roy Oliver in the shooting death of unarmed teenager Jordan Edwards is so significant. https://t.co/0lD5xPkOfI https://t.co/V5MnkJMAQT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adm. John Kirby shares letter McCain sent to his son: Retired Rear Adm. John Kirby became emotional on Wednesday when he recalled a letter the late Sen. John McCain had written to his son as he was getting ready to be commissioned into the US Navy. https://t.co/DOKYiI50Wh https://t.co/rEhTWctro2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Engineer: Search Display ****************************************************************************** &amp; siteid=105 &amp; PageType=JobDetails &amp; jobid=******* &amp; codes=IND Loading Close Your account has successfully been deleted. Close… https://t.co/niazVP72vD https://t.co/3jZPF3Fl9L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cynthia Nixon and Andrew Cuomo to square off in hotly anticipated debate: Cynthia Nixon is no stranger to the stage, but she's never before had a platform quite like this. https://t.co/cz5tSc1Q6I https://t.co/XWGuISokDP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle Business Analyst II (Finance): Applicants must be eligible to work in the specified location Description The Oracle Business Analyst is responsible for the maintenance and support of the Oracle eBusiness Suite and ancillary applications while… https://t.co/6B6Oj5JSpp https://t.co/2XXyMImU5b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aretha Franklin's family being 'guided by God' to honor her: Sabrina Owens started to consider how to bid her beloved aunt Aretha Franklin farewell before the world even knew the legendary singer was ill. https://t.co/mW3iRiOXAL https://t.co/HJ0hNBQON4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Performance Engineer: At Cardinal Health, we’re developing the innovative products and services that make healthcare safer and more productive. Join a growing, global company genuinely committed to making a difference for our customers and… https://t.co/jhngOgrzYX https://t.co/9diLxYXcUr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe suffers panic attacks in Iranian prison: Nazanin Zaghari-Ratcliffe, the British-Iranian woman who has been imprisoned in Tehran since 2016 on spying charges, is being treated in hospital after suffering panic attacks, her… https://t.co/GJLiM7FQdx https://t.co/axbm7i7ap5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst: Description The Identity Management Solutions team is a group within the Corporate Security and Resilience (CS &amp; R) organization and provides subject matter expertise and associated security services to the business divisions across the… https://t.co/6VdZrbwiNL https://t.co/tKQydaBnp5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Desktop Support Technician: Date: Aug 21, 2018 Location: Columbus, OH, US Company: NTT DATA Services Req ID: 28872 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The quality, integrity, and commitment of our… https://t.co/gpoK7f8nia https://t.co/ToM0ntmKBJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Automation Engineer: Department Overview: The FUSE Commercial Technologies CORE PLATFORMS AND DATA/MESSAGING team supports multiple business units and commercial platforms within Cardinal Health. We focus on supplying a self-service platform as a… https://t.co/zhd45mzj3w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After years of military control, Somali national stadium returns to sports: After years of militant and military control, the Somali national stadium in Mogadishu will return to a place for sports. https://t.co/8LydvTBZa1 https://t.co/8uQUJY73KF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Engineer: QA Engineer Ref No.: 18-36358 Location: Mason, Ohio Must have: – UI &amp; Web service Automation Experience(With Java/C#) – Object-oriented programming experience using C#, Java – SQL query experience – including joins and subqueries. – Web… https://t.co/jR10em6UHp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's bet on Kim Jong Un is looking increasingly shaky: President Donald Trump took a huge risk by holding a summit with North Korean leader Kim Jong Un and hailing it as a stunning history-changing success. https://t.co/zGsyWSdOCC https://t.co/dt0mrcQ8rP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer, Technical Support: Search Display ****************************************************************************** &amp; siteid=105 &amp; PageType=JobDetails &amp; jobid=******* &amp; codes=IND Loading Close Your account has successfully been deleted. Close… https://t.co/sBWPyjtVFp https://t.co/YN0urmzY4f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mária Švarbová finds beauty and serenity in socialist-era swimming pools: Slovakian photographer Maria Švarbová's carefully composed "Swimming Pools" series is both serene and surreal. https://t.co/WO9fouObHb https://t.co/JMJ4DYC8t6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Green slime oozes into Florida's primary elections: Green slime is oozing from Lake Okeechobee, polluting Florida's pristine waterways. The crisis has caused a dramatic decline in the economy and voters want their voices heard. https://t.co/GgffWCckWF https://t.co/Wce6K51NJZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Oracle Developer: Job Description What you’ll be doing… If you are curious about new technology and the possibilities it creates, then this job may be perfect for you. As part of the Information Technology team, you will work on new technologies… https://t.co/ceUlDzI6Kn https://t.co/5AqHCh2UAC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA-Tester: QA Tester Populus Group seeks a QA Tester in Columbus, Ohio to provide software application quality assurance and testing utilizing Oracle, ALM (HP QC), Informatica, MS SQL Server, PL/SQL, SharePoint, Selenium, VB Script, Hbase, QTP, SQOOP,… https://t.co/JwjxkiWo38 https://t.co/8AIS7sMA1Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9-year-old died by suicide after he was bullied, mom says: A Colorado 9-year-old ended his own life on Thursday, shortly after coming out as gay and being bullied at school, according to his mother, Leia Pierce. https://t.co/d16ZJbEyby https://t.co/tJqnxkaedv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A special hearse transported Aretha Franklin: The hearse that brought Aretha Franklin's body to the Charles H. Wright Museum of African American History in Detroit on Tuesday has historical significance. https://t.co/hhVPcqUDik https://t.co/uUYTpqsTrD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solutions Architect Lead III (Orders and Integrations): Founded in 1866, The Sherwin-Williams Company is a global leader in the manufacture, development, distribution, and sale of paints, coatings and related products to professional, industrial,… https://t.co/RvgrhEUFed https://t.co/F1cJN0DkuH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Debunking Donald Trump's latest conspiracy theory on Google: The playbook, by now, is familiar. Faced with a negative story -- or stories -- President Donald Trump uses his Twitter feed to float a conspiracy theory of some sort designed to distract and… https://t.co/QFNTzAnEjR https://t.co/Qe9j1wR0za]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Operations Analyst Cleveland: Job Description ******** JOB SUMMARY Working under direct supervision, provides routine day-to-day operations and administrative support for a business unit or large department. Assists in coordination of budget,… https://t.co/orfgKVGze9 https://t.co/JfYac7AGzd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Serena Wiliams turns heads with striking outfit at US Open: Serena Williams' dress was the talk of the town at the US Open, as the 23-time major winner played her first home grand slam as a mother. https://t.co/YsMYLdm6QG https://t.co/PS3vOzPPHl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead IT Business Analyst: Location US-OH-Richfield Posted Date 2 months ago(6/19/2018 10:11 AM) Job ID 23729 # Positions 1 Category Technology Position Type Full Time Overview National Interstate is a member of Great American Insurance Group. As one of… https://t.co/CtwFYkxiXX https://t.co/OXKe6EKVdt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[French environment minister Nicolas Hulot quits government in live radio interview: French Environment Minister Nicolas Hulot announced his resignation from President Emmanuel Macron's government during a live radio interview on Tuesday, over his… https://t.co/Vj6IJn4yqO https://t.co/iXMuy7dQbo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GI Endoscopy Assistant.GRH OR-Full Time Days: Description – Accurately decontaminates and reprocesses endoscopic equipment and accessories. – Maintains the cleanliness of all procedure rooms and reprocessing room. – Maintains inventory of endoscopy… https://t.co/RoEKbhnc7v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's brand of politics has eclipsed McCain's: Sen. John McCain's heroism and code of honor, duty and unifying pragmatism will endure as a powerful historical example. But his political legacy met its match in President Donald Trump, who has prevailed… https://t.co/FZUZtN6I59 https://t.co/dcQxMe165T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate, Infrastructure Support #180078319: Associate, Infrastructure Support job #180078319 Columbus, OH.  Duties: Install new software product versions and releases. Perform proactive software maintenance and conduct production readiness inspections… https://t.co/mhHZ9pPq4H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist Intern: Date: Aug 6, 2018 Location: Wickliffe, Ohio, US, 44092 Company: Lubrizol Corporation Lubrizol Additives is a pioneering global supplier of chemical additives technologies including additives for engine oils, driveline applications,… https://t.co/uD1ZOr9VMq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[War on drugs: Priest speaks out against Philippines 'blood lust': Catholic priest speaks out against "blood lust" in the Philipines and says President Rodrigo Duterte has a "messiah complex." https://t.co/HaLARTTCTD https://t.co/e7VELmn67U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jr / Entry Level Software Developer: Jr / Entry Level Software Developer =================================== Req #: ******Location: Beavercreek, OH USJob Category: Information TechnologySecurity Clearance: SecretClearance Status: Must be Obtainable Job… https://t.co/doedRwAS8e https://t.co/3cerG9UuG7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toyota invests $500 million in Uber: The companies will work together to bring self-driving cars to the world. https://t.co/ZSvwG8r4ZN https://t.co/oHdh3EudzA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Rock helps honor fan who died in car crash: Dwayne "The Rock" Johnson has helped a son pay tribute to his late mother. https://t.co/ohDEtH4jqm https://t.co/eYJEeAZdSS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Serena Williams' catsuit set to be consigned to the closet: Serena Williams' superhero-like catsuit is set to be consigned to the back of her closet, but "everything is fine" over the French Open's new outfit rules, according to the US tennis star. https://t.co/DxdJnoTuxZ https://t.co/W9A8NYRj0F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Report Developer: Applicants must be eligible to work in the specified location Description The Report Developer works with customers and peers to design, develop, modify and test data marts and data models that meet the customer’s needs. Requires a… https://t.co/04Tyjcf3Ry https://t.co/esBGZqFqPS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your first look at the long-awaited new season of 'True Detective': The mystery about when HBO's 'True Detective' will return has been solved. https://t.co/yHJipMwHQT https://t.co/YGm7mCBbjP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook bans Myanmar military chief and says it was 'too slow' to act: The social media giant admitted it was "too slow" to prevent the spread of misinformation that has contribute to violence against minorities in the country. https://t.co/pn62Ye0ojI https://t.co/iZwWyOgQ2J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Middleware Engineer III: The Engineers role is to support and administer the design, planning and implementation of all technology related activities of the organization. The Engineer will work closely with solution architects, application development… https://t.co/VcQxP6LfYs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Myanmar military leaders accused of genocide in country's north: An independent United Nations investigation into alleged human rights abuses carried out against Rohingya Muslims in Myanmar has called for the country's military leaders to be investigated… https://t.co/ykNw5z7EY0 https://t.co/pix3Q8yIq4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(Healthcare or Higher Education) Project Architect -RELOCATION: Cincinnati, OH Compensation Unspecified Posted 08/09/2018 Title: Project Architect/ Senior Project Architect/ Associate Architect Compensation: Base, Bonus, Benefits, 401k, additional perks… https://t.co/tDJiOZbLsv https://t.co/iClsSDFPDs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How this Australian Instagram account amassed 3.2 million followers: Jaw-dropping images and cheeky captions go a long way to elevate your Instagram game. Here's how Tourism Australia amassed 3.2 million followers and counting. https://t.co/JhUvYrCK4V https://t.co/nWWhvm0wqa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Washington Post: Trump opted against sending official statement praising McCain: President Donald Trump went against the advice of senior aides to issue an official White House statement praising Sen. John McCain for his heroism and decades of service,… https://t.co/ds8maKiGCB https://t.co/HHGwnYkRvo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guest Service Desk Team Member: Guest Service Desk Team Member Description: As a Guest Service team member, you are the front end and the face of what we stand for. You’ll be motivated by and always look for opportunities to go above and beyond guest… https://t.co/GqK6wIjMH7 https://t.co/VeqT01Y9Vb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QAS | Software Test Analyst: QAS | Software Test Analyst Columbus, OH 08-09-2018 Location: Columbus, OH For more than 18 years, CareWorks Tech has been delivering technology solutions that drive results. As your advocate, the common thread across our… https://t.co/9McB5H14N5 https://t.co/Er9XKsnSAG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Embedded Software Engineer: Senior Embedded Software Engineer Business Group Architecture and Software No. of Positions 1 Requisition Number 77762BR Job Category Engineering and Technicians Position Type Full Time Relocation Eligible Yes Position… https://t.co/1oQNxMYY2E https://t.co/0TszGMw8cz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[java: java Ref No.: 18-31467 Location: Independence, Ohio Hi Hope you are doing well Number of position : 7 (Not Contract or C2C) I, Salman Shaikh (Enterprise Solution Inc.) would like to share a job opportunity as Sr. Java Developer based in… https://t.co/2uJM0kSTuV https://t.co/N3X6bBrEV4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Start your Monday smart: Aretha's funeral, more midterm primaries, college football: Bidding adieu to the Queen of Soul. Hot primaries in Arizona and Florida. College football. Here's what the next six days will bring. https://t.co/c3nsk4shif https://t.co/LbuR1HkcYo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Mass shooting' at Madden video game tournament in Jacksonville, Florida, authorities say: A shooting occurred during the Madden 19 Tournament at the GLHF Game Bar in Jacksonville, Florida, according to CompLexity Gaming, one of the event organizers,… https://t.co/1H7D6YvON0 https://t.co/cfA00XXWJh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Crazy Rich Asians' tops box office again with crazy second weekend: "Crazy Rich Asians" is still crazy rich at the box office with a strong second weekend. https://t.co/ctJtNGY4Vr https://t.co/CPH3hADtQL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[User Experience Engineer Advanced Arlington, TX or Milford, OH: **User Experience Engineer Advanced – Arlington, TX or Milford, OH** Multiple Locations:Arlington, Texas; Milford, Ohio Job Family: Research &amp; Development New Search English (US) **Job… https://t.co/Yz8dQ3Nvjr https://t.co/WPJwSz06NX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Operations Analyst Kent, OH: Job Description Operations Analyst – Kent, OH #30955 Date: Jun 15, 2018 Location: Kent, OH, 44240 Company: The Davey Tree Expert Company Requisition Number: 30955 Company Name: The Davey Tree Expert Company Service Line: 1UTL… https://t.co/B4Jo1T0g3K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[McCain's complex legacy offers GOP soul-searching opportunity: John McCain leaves behind a complex political legacy, writes Julian Zelizer. While he was a vocal critic of Trump, he also played a critical role in opening the door to the transformation… https://t.co/HWImY1yNvw https://t.co/u7UTDejNVE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Engineer, Software Engineering (https://t.co/AEZJZiAUH4 Technical Lead) (P-Mod): At Cardinal Health, we’re developing the innovative products and services that make healthcare safer and more productive. Join a growing, global company genuinely… https://t.co/pGOV6h2qt6 https://t.co/XSz0SmXSkB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Afghan national security adviser quits. Resignations of 3 other officials rejected: Afghan President Ashraf Ghani accepted the resignation of his national security adviser but refused the resignations of three other security officials as the country… https://t.co/y2SrsVzj6b https://t.co/mfeH4Cingv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hadoop Developer: Hadoop Developer Ref No.: 18-35497 Location: Cleveland, Ohio Title:- Hadoop Developer Location:- Pittsburgh , PA / Cleveland , OH Duration:- 12 Months Job description 1. Hadoop experience (on a user not Administrator level) 2.PySpark… https://t.co/FWt6AqXWdO https://t.co/QYzo45M7IB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAS Developer: SAS Developer Ref No.: 18-36657 Location: Cincinnati, Ohio SAS Developer Cincinnati, OH 12 Months C2C contract Job Description 10+ years of software development experience; particularly within the Banking industry. 7+ years of experience… https://t.co/O9fKlgJ0bN https://t.co/HsSHmuOqfh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Systems Analyst, Sr: Our Financial Systems Analyst Senior is an integral member of the Financial Information Team. The Financial Information Team is a high profile function, providing financial information to business segments across the Bank.… https://t.co/W1pzX374cL https://t.co/EE24wzQYQw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack .NET Developer: EXODUS INTEGRITY SERVICES, INC., is a rapidly expanding technology company headquartered in Northeast Ohio. EIS provides quality services to our clients by instilling honesty, commitment, and hard work to find the most… https://t.co/A0QtJ5TnG4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protesters to greet Pope in Dublin amid sex abuse scandal: Pope Francis will celebrate Mass with half a million faithful in Dublin on Sunday afternoon, as thousands protest over clerical sexual abuse. https://t.co/KjmlwBQsbW https://t.co/OaifDfRt5N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John McCain, senator and former presidential candidate, dies at 81: Whenever America was in a fight during his long lifetime, John McCain was in the thick of it. https://t.co/zbQxIEK02c https://t.co/SKpjpDLmtw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Developer: Database Developer ================== Tyler Technologies is growing and is looking for software developers to design, develop and maintain enterprise level HTML5 software applications used by the public sector nationwide. As a… https://t.co/W2XVv7xQb8 https://t.co/hJT4SlXDTp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QAnon-believing 'conspiracy analyst' meets Trump in the White House: A right-wing conspiracy theorist and QAnon-believer appeared to visit President Donald Trump in the Oval Office on Thursday, according to a picture posted on his Twitter account. https://t.co/2olCvWVrfx https://t.co/xrjmPwVsuc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst: Business Analyst Columbus, OH 08-09-2018 Location: Columbus, OH For more than 18 years, CareWorks Tech has been delivering technology solutions that drive results. As your advocate, the common thread across our associates is crafting… https://t.co/AZ0J9BOHfJ https://t.co/ARYSp4c19B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They pledge. Get hazed. The cycle continues: With the dangers of hazing so evident, why would students voluntarily subject themselves to such potential abuse? Experts and former pledges contacted by CNN said the answer is more complicated than you might… https://t.co/kDF8PCz8QH https://t.co/DqI6WsAa2B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inside the high-stakes business of tracking space junk: AGI's ComSpOC aims to be a premium version of the US military's J https://t.co/goaeSkSlPq https://t.co/5hBlJexxtv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager: Job ID : 70614BR Location : US – Ohio – Cincinnati : Job Description Summary: Manages client related projects in an effective and efficient manner by ensuring delivery for assigned complex projects., such as project expansion,… https://t.co/LuvcZj7Nla https://t.co/lj8ngMWns7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Win or lose, Beto O'Rourke will help Texas Democrats: Why does the closeness of the race between Rep. Beto O'Rourke matter if Texas Sen. Ted Cruz is probably going to win? It's all about driving turnout in the House races in the state. https://t.co/H0yYam94Lp https://t.co/fZdzWXsINB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RPO Solution Design Manager: **This person will ideally be based in the Findlay, OH office. The Solution Design Manager is responsible for planning, scheduling and controlling the scoping activities during the sales analysis life cycle for ADP RPO… https://t.co/eNu1d0Efzt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lane weakens to a tropical storm, but landslides and flooding are still a threat: Hawaii residents breathed a sigh of relief as Hurricane Lane disintegrated into a tropical storm, but authorities warned its thrashing winds and relentless rain remain a… https://t.co/yYYs6L6uO4 https://t.co/BgGAJT322l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Service Management Analyst: Service Management Analyst Ref No.: 18-35760 Location: Cincinnati, Ohio Title:- Service Management Analyst Location:- Cincinnati OH Contract Role Duties &amp; Responsibilities – Leads the rollout of new processes or improvements… https://t.co/oUmlSEco84 https://t.co/39NlICZW09]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>