<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju We Are Social's Curiosity Stop #17 #socialcommerce https://t.co/NvSnDImaMa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju A Silicon Valley Lawmaker's $1 Trillion Plan to Save Trump Country #technology #geek https://t.co/1NPJ0o2s9o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju What is the rocket icon on Facebook? Mysterious symbol baffles social media.. #facebook #internet https://t.co/cQbO3Risk0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Don’t let life discourage you; everyone who got where he is had to begin where he was.”- Richard L. Evans]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju The Challenges of Moving into E-Commerce - PCWorld #ecommerce #tech https://t.co/Me1rSPGGwG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju What to expect now that Internet providers can collect and sell your Web browser.. #internet #web https://t.co/Xhf1THctwI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju How to Successfully Track the Results of Your Mail Campaign #entrepreneur https://t.co/BIMWHnDlLx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju 5 Ways to Turn Social Users Into Social Shoppers - Adweek #socialcommerce https://t.co/0g8MPHeEAp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju LSU to host its first robot battle competition next week - Greater Baton Rouge Bus.. #competition https://t.co/K2EGYUdpQK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju How Can Brands Meet the Challenges of a Changing America? - https://t.co/VzuP51AOjV #branding #brands https://t.co/uJ1ZWd7jjY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't dream at night, I dream all day; I dream for a living. Steven Spielberg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Intel's Got a Plan to Dominate VR. First Stop? March Madness #technology #geek https://t.co/Sa62EtXeTG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Facebook pivots into Stories - TechCrunch #facebook #internet https://t.co/nCNnbCVyde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The only place where success comes before work is in the dictionary." Vidal Sassoon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Ecommerce is about selling fake stuff: Andy Xie - Economic Times #ecommerce #tech https://t.co/0Ks0LnhoPs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju As Congress Repeals Internet Privacy Rules, Putting Your Options In Perspective .. #internet #web https://t.co/UP51abwPzG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju 6 Times You Should Turn Down Work #entrepreneur https://t.co/CV85yVUEie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Claremore students advance to national competition - Claremore Daily Progress #competition https://t.co/U2zucifeVl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Lottery manager still on job after firing - Crain's Chicago Business #manager #leader https://t.co/4lES6L11ol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The function of leadership is to produce more leaders, not more followers." Ralph Nader]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Ridley Scott Reveals the Origin of His Androids in the Alien Saga #technology #geek https://t.co/YowGYUKWst]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Facebook launches stories to complete its all-out assault on Snapchat - The.. #facebook #internet https://t.co/e2UB9Yky5w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Speak the truth, but leave immediately after.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Snapdeal's woes show e-commerce isn't doing enough - Livemint #ecommerce #tech https://t.co/4qb95Yj7QD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Your internet data may be up for sale - https://t.co/spvyEo4OmS #internet #web https://t.co/KFeorVPcKi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju How to Include Politics in Your Marketing Without Turning Anyone Off #entrepreneur https://t.co/b6nwbafetM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strength does not come from physical capacity. It comes from an indomitable will. Mahatma Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju We Are Social's Monday Mashup #347 #socialcommerce https://t.co/I93hQqJv4R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Scientists Hack a Human Cell and Reprogram It Like a Computer #technology #geek https://t.co/o3ZDc6oDCv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Facebook's Move To Dominate - Seeking Alpha #facebook #internet https://t.co/SXEOmCZD7C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Expect the best. Prepare for the worst. Capitalize on what comes." Zig Ziglar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju 10 Ways to Future-Proof Your Ecommerce Fashion Store - Entrepreneur #ecommerce #tech https://t.co/TOolauHw1D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Push for Internet Privacy Rules Moves to Statehouses - New York Times #internet #web https://t.co/pPaNNSxN4H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Who Do You Trust to Hire Your Next Top Employee? #entrepreneur https://t.co/HNSMd8OfFm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju OHO's new "social commerce platform" aims to create Bt5 billion of ... - The Na.. #socialcommerce https://t.co/YLOyRYuTSr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Coalition asks competition watchdog to investigate energy prices - The Guardian #competition https://t.co/TqG2ZLcRYw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Brands Try to Blacklist Breitbart, but Ads Slip Through Anyway - New York Times #branding #brands https://t.co/bOzMwbhmpq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Editorial: Council should strongly consider city manager form of government - .. #manager #leader https://t.co/A9Tp5cDyBq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Opportunity is missed by most people because it is dressed in overalls and looks like work." Thomas Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju While You Were Offline: Trump Is President and You're Not, FYI #technology #geek https://t.co/v0RJnt0ECl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Trending: No way to tame the dark side of Facebook Live - Knoxville News Se.. #facebook #internet https://t.co/rOhA38AQWy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Latipay enables e-commerce in China - https://t.co/zeYcIUmBZS #ecommerce #tech https://t.co/3Q2Y2n14fz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Senate votes to kill internet privacy protections - FOX 61 #internet #web https://t.co/fmZuL1GiOx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Do Your Homework and Avoid a Venture Capital Nightmare #entrepreneur https://t.co/mZmQNa54xE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju More big brands pull ads from YouTube in widening boycott - Lowell Sun #branding #brands https://t.co/CEe9gjtoyb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju TV's Best Political Show Might Just Be The Originals. Yeah, the One With the .. #technology #geek https://t.co/iGIFOdPku9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju How to Log Off of Facebook Forever, With All Its Perks and Pitfalls - New Y.. #facebook #internet https://t.co/82OYC3VnDj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When life gives you a hundred reasons to cry, show life that you have a thousand reasons to smile.- Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Why you now need a strategy for ecommerce packaging - Packaging Digest #ecommerce #tech https://t.co/1rCD5b3cZJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju AT&amp;T continues to expand its fiber internet service - The Verge #internet #web https://t.co/Mn4NRY82ir]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Debunking 'Diversity' by Amplifying Inclusion #entrepreneur https://t.co/vc9hZr1F5P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju The Rise of Social Commerce - Motley Fool #socialcommerce https://t.co/z0aMT3WBDz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju More Big Brands Pull Ads From YouTube in Widening Boycott - Fox Business #branding #brands https://t.co/rfffkT1Bdq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are two primary choices in life: to accept conditions as they exist, or accept the responsibility for changing..- Dr. Denis Waitley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Rock Band VR Shreds the Rhythm-Game Paradigm #technology #geek https://t.co/dVmkmFAYjJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Clean Up Toxic Waste Or Bet Against Google And Facebook - Forbes #facebook #internet https://t.co/OjcKOnDYi5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Too many of us are not living our dreams because we are living our fears." Les Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju DHL eCommerce Expands Presence in South China to Further Boost China's Booming.. #ecommerce #tech https://t.co/pIAzrO5WcM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Congress Moves to Strike Internet Privacy Rules From Obama Era - New York Times #internet #web https://t.co/JCNEwkXXw3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju 3 Onboarding Tips That Close the Gap for Remote Employees #entrepreneur https://t.co/PIIQeXCcRI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju How Brands Can Tap Micro-Data in Social Campaigns - https://t.co/VzuP51SpIv #branding #brands https://t.co/KY8kGjydti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tell them what you're going to tell them, tell them, then tell them what you told them.Communications axim]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju WikiLeaks Reveals How the CIA Can Hack a Mac's Hidden Code #technology #geek https://t.co/KyDZTzWacX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju You Can Now Use Facebook Live From Your Desk - Fortune #facebook #internet https://t.co/63MQFScnbp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where the willingness is great, the difficulties cannot be great. Machiavelli.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju 40 Reasons Video Will Be Essential in Ecommerce Marketing in ... - MarTech Adv.. #ecommerce #tech https://t.co/aIPhWYOry1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju The Senate Prepares to Send Internet Privacy Down a Black Hole - WIRED #internet #web https://t.co/RFKKh54TtF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Increase Your Direct Mail Camaign Results Using Holidays #entrepreneur https://t.co/vwbMr5bAM0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Spin social commerce into gold with Facebook Messenger (VB Live) - VentureBeat #socialcommerce https://t.co/Av4KmoAzfY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Calif. class action suit alleges 'unfair competition' with Ivanka Trump brand - Ch.. #competition https://t.co/tF6BAQaEsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Google advertising row spreads to US brands - BBC News #branding #brands https://t.co/c2u7g8wlwa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Why Being a Middle Manager Is So Exhausting - Harvard Business Review #manager #leader https://t.co/ETekiRktzb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do first things first, and second things not at all.- Peter Drucker.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Congress Is About To Give Away Your Online Privacy #technology #geek https://t.co/bmikfheUo7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Facebook redesign turns comments into messages for a reason that actually m.. #facebook #internet https://t.co/BgumWpIOqo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Success is the worst teacher" via Trace Cohen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Walmart Launches 'Store No. 8' E-Commerce Venture - E-Commerce Times #ecommerce #tech https://t.co/NCBMlCN7yf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju 5 Reasons Why Diversity and Inclusion Initiatives Fail #entrepreneur https://t.co/8hbzGjBLxJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Nobody Wants to Go Shopping on Social Media—And This Is Why - Observer #socialcommerce https://t.co/B7jlAj2iq6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Ivanka Trump's brand sued over 'unfair competition' - AOL Small Business #competition https://t.co/EbnYqHNXtj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju 4 Ways Brands Can Up Their Online Game - Forbes #branding #brands https://t.co/wOoYBZK52w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The successful man is the one who finds out what is the matter with his business before his competitors do. Roy L. Smith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Helping to promote HSBC's digital banking products on social #socialcommerce https://t.co/E1WQXA9hjM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Android O, Google's Next OS, Is Coming to Save Your Phone's Battery #technology #geek https://t.co/FOe15wtsOb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Facebook's Epic Data Blast Is Good for Everyone—Especially Facebook - WIRED #facebook #internet https://t.co/Xb2eTY9jYK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Artificial intelligence is no match for natural stupidity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Tristan Walker: 'No one wants to fund e-commerce companies anymore' - Recode #ecommerce #tech https://t.co/eG0nYm4Qxw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju The Internet - Irish Times #internet #web https://t.co/cWU78PPIxe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju The 'Whys' of Why You Should Consider HR Software for Your Small Business #entrepreneur https://t.co/h46oqWNmpD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju The Pros and Cons of Competition Among Employees - Harvard Business Review #competition https://t.co/MFZQlw8AYU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju These Are China's Most Valuable Brands - Fortune #branding #brands https://t.co/X6Ue0DF6zx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attitudes are contagious. Make yours worth catching.- Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju We Are Social's Monday Mashup #346 #socialcommerce https://t.co/z26RCrlZZG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Trump's TSA Budget Fails to Cut the Obvious: Air Marshals #technology #geek https://t.co/WnXHVk7Hmz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Facebook is looking for somebody to lead a retail push for consumer hardwar.. #facebook #internet https://t.co/EugAmG1Ogy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Far better it is to dare mighty things, to win glorious triumphs even though checkered by….– Theodore Roosevelt via Mike Jones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Welcome to eCommerce Week - DMN #ecommerce #tech https://t.co/KRuEsNyKbd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Bear witness to the terrifying 'big chicken' that's scaring the internet - Masha.. #internet #web https://t.co/WtUEt0zoXz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju 3 Strategies for Projecting Success and Confidence as a Leader #entrepreneur https://t.co/PG1IpflG0P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Chinese multinationals should do this for long-term success, according to Sir.. #branding #brands https://t.co/hh2uECeaRU]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>