<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[People share read &amp; generally engage more with any type of content when its surfaced through friends &amp; people they know and trust - Facebook]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Example is not the main thing in influencing other people; it's the only thing - Abraham Lincoln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[E.T. phone home - E.T.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Chuck Berry  http://t.co/w7ll4AJ67Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Locate Your Garage Space Before Installation Of Cabinets  http://t.co/8TpGi9eLVm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To make a rock'n'roll record, technology is the least important thing.  -  Keith Richards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If people don't want to come out to the ball park, nobody's gonna stop 'em. - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We didn't lose the game; we just ran out of time. - Vince Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A comparison and History of Game Consoles  http://t.co/Tgl9d0l9af]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the Icebound Land by John Flanagan  http://t.co/xaNVGi4JQO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome darts t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the darts lovers in your life!   http://t.co/DWtc5Bonoc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out Why Technology Is Helpful To Seniors  http://t.co/PxA5FNV3K1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Chilled Stones to Keep Your Drink Cool - Milled in Vermont http://t.co/0750kjqWRT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We (San Francisco) have football weather during baseball season, and baseball weather during football season. - Herb Caen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overheard when the boss returned from his safari in Africa: "He's the first man the head shrinkers ever failed with."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adoption - Initial Stages - Part 1  http://t.co/yw9NmqM1Ry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You’ve got to give us Americans a lot of credit.  How else could we buy a new car every year?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Publishing Management with HootSuite  http://t.co/6iinDBJAtS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you love James Bond?  Check out these cool t-shirts, hats, stickers and more --&gt;  http://t.co/8ZEA4t4Mju]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make it so! - Engage! - Captain Picard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make the customer the hero of your story.  Ann Handley - Chief Content Officer - MarketingProfs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A shoe without sex appeal is as barren as a tree without leaves. - Rita De Acosta Lydig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any trip is short when you're in good company]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The rest of the world lives to eat, while I eat to live. - Socrates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Kim Carnes  http://t.co/WhNm0tSJSI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If high heels were so wonderful, men would be wearing them. - Sue Grafton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The History of Lyme Disease  http://t.co/wu3155j9RA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never realized how boring this game was.  - Homer Simpson while watching baseball while sober]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Grapevine, Texas  http://t.co/BVMa96wchS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Donovan  http://t.co/j4zcq4iRxp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He ran out of talent about halfway through the corner. - Buddy Baker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Religion Both Protestant and Catholics  http://t.co/0uhQcb8ge9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent Blue LED light stemmed Umbrella - a unique take on the Umbrella! http://t.co/yMACKkRpBc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Little House on the Prairie – An American Classic TV Series  http://t.co/biQSqw7Lxt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is the key to unlock the golden door of freedom. - George Washington Carver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool just found these 25 Original Unopened Packs of Vintage Baseball Cards (80s-90s) - can find some value in there!  http://t.co/NuVoc7QrzG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love science fiction. - Pam Grier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stiletto, I look at it more as an attitude as opposed to a high-heeled shoe. - Lita Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I pretty much try to stay in a constant state of confusion just because of the expression it leaves on my face.  Johnny Depp quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is not the most important thing in the world. Love is. Fortunately, I love money. - Jackie Mason]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read The History of the Beau Brummels  http://t.co/DFJKYoyY8D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The dog represents all that is best in man. - Etienne Charlet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of David Gates  http://t.co/0qWjiynQ7b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Marketing Experts Reveal Tips to Success  http://t.co/bOBb3Bv4b9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Assisted Living in Your Own Home  http://t.co/AUhYEjLRg9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before you create anymore great content figure out how you are going to market it first - Pulizzi &amp; Barrett - Get Content Get Customers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Ohio Players    http://t.co/9DR5IK6Yj7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Driving a car is like playing baseball. The object in both is to get home safely. - Joe Moore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Parliament  http://t.co/E4Wep63h4z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best thing to save for your old age is yourself]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Review of the Book Eragon  http://t.co/NTyq9fSRGX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sign on a barber shop window --  Home haircuts repaired  $20.00]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take care of your body. It's the only place you have to live. - Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of Skylanders: Spyro’s Adventure  http://t.co/i5nt6aY8WF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before the marriage, he talks &amp; she listens.  During honeymoon, she talks &amp; he listens.  Later, they both talk &amp; the neighbors listen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's behind you doesn't matter. - Enzo Ferrari]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your attitude determines your altitude! - Denis Waitley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He who begins many things finishes but few - German Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good teaching is one-fourth preparation and three-fourths pure theatre. - Gail Godwin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inflation is when you pay fifteen dollars for the ten-dollar haircut you used to get for five dollars when you had hair. - Sam Ewing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter Can be an Invaluable Business Tool  http://t.co/HLjg7moOwb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I won't be a rock star. I will be a legend. - Freddie Mercury]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Son, a father told his growing boy, "just remember on thing:  I know a lot more about being young than you do about being old."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the dressing room, I always put on my right shoe first. Same thing for my right wristband. -  Mary Lou Retton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Artificial Intelligence is no match for Natural Stupidity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lacing Up The Facts: A History of Shoes  http://t.co/5ta8sArrCa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jazz up  your pool or patio with these trendy light cubes - cool!  http://t.co/y8QbaeXesC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How To Find Best Supplies For Gardening  http://t.co/EtXlBzFNPh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good introduction to Minecraft Mods - http://t.co/spn7T5AVkH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are three things you can do in a baseball game. You can win, or you can lose, or it can rain. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Kitty Kallen  http://t.co/sHad1MKFTV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By the time a person gets to greener pastures, he can't climb the fence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top Movies of the 1930s - theband4: The decade experienced a political and economic turmoil. Aside from the... http://t.co/jFupiaoqX3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Auto racing, bull fighting, and mountain climbing are the only real sports --  all the others are games. - Ernest Hemingway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caring For Your New Garage Floors  http://t.co/gsC4oQ552z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Natalie Cole  http://t.co/x28EXZUjHD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You cannot dream yourself into a character: you must hammer and forge yourself into one. - Henry D. Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Foghat  http://t.co/OZJ00LKTVA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes are the quickest way for women to achieve instant metamorphosis - Manolo Blahnik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smoking kills. If you killed, you've lost a very important part of your life. Brooke Shields]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excuse me, miss, a little bit of your face is showing around your makeup - you might want to take care of that!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elegance is refusal. --&gt; Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a rock and roll singer.  -  Adam Ant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If opportunity doesn't knock, build a door. - Milton Berle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of the animals except for man know that the principle business of life is to enjoy it. - Samuel Butler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fitness - If it came in a bottle, everybody would have a great body. - Cher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn the Keys to Using LinkedIn for Your Company  http://t.co/9ceo6hW6kJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Fort Worth, Texas  http://t.co/AGXgB7ZW6E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of Stargate Universe  http://t.co/IWgxGOLHfp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious T-Shirt - “I Got Your Back” http://t.co/gUy7XXgYvJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to C.S. Lewis  http://t.co/0V7eBP29ij]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people are like angels - always harping on something!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make Your Own Ice Cream Cookie Bowls - YUM! http://t.co/orpTIoqdeu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Courtship is the period during which a girl decides whether or not she can do better]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Fun Science Ideas for Kids  http://t.co/c68fZVFk1r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A women with good shoes is never ugly. They are the last touch of elegance. - Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Best Tasting Burger - theband4: http://t.co/WQl4231u3N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Modern Glo Night Light - Night Light Fashion!  http://t.co/I0Y9NpaArl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Parliament  http://t.co/E4Wep63h4z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Favorite Things for Kids to Review  http://t.co/2pUptjDWH0]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>