<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ProducerScott: Best. Sign. EVER. Get this retweeted guys, it's an absolute gem... http://t.co/aoNoanW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rorylawson9: At Glasgow airport. Scottish family turn to Chris Paterson (105caps,4thRWC) and ask him if he's off on a "gid old stag  ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#hangover]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Beer o'clock!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Next week: HPFM for a crash course in fund management! #cre #property]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Particularly kind as they got nothing out of the deal apart from some lackey work on my behalf! They don't recruit grads #cre #property]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just finished a superb four week long internship with Miller Developments. A great bunch and they taught me so much. #cre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@StevieMoffat: If Celtic are reinstated, Neil Lennon loses the right to complain about anything ever again” -- damn right!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait for #beer o'clock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @philmcnulty: Walcott elbowed right in front of extra official. Nothing done. What is the point of their existence? Have they ever gi ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[what has happened to Szczesny? he's become a top keeper overnight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tedligety: FIS backs down. Compromise on GS radius rule now 35m radius from 40m. I still don't agree but its workable. I fear... htt ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arcade fire and the Walkmen next week! #yaldi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is clearly a wild duck chase #gareh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SkyNewsBreak: Sky Correspondent: Hundreds of people celebrating in streets of Tripoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tedligety: My thoughts on FIS's attempt to ruin GS. http://t.co/cCbUjJ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AND Rangers getting beat off Maribor. Best night ever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love seeing the jam tarts taking a pounding! #FTH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sky News - Drunk Motorised Beer Cooler Driver Banned. http://t.co/kkECROo  What a guy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FootballAid: Just noticed we've got 992 followers, who's going to get the warm glow inside knowing they're the 1,000th follower of o ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just walked past two kids on the way to school. One eating a fab the other a magnum #earlygrave]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aaaaah! So fucking keen for a @brewdog #beer tonight!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@millarmind eeewww I hope not #weedgies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheChainSpokers: We've just totted up our fundraising and between our Race Night and our LEJOG we have raised a grand total of £6,67 ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DeucharsIPA: RT @rcahms: Happy Birthday Sir Walter Scott! Edinburgh monument foundations laid #onthisday 1840: lots of great images  ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aspy87 rooneys new hair is pretty contoversial!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the sky sports overly dramatic hype-pieces. #football wouldn't be the same without it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matthannah1987 looks like a mint blend of #rome and #gameofthrones]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The advocate just refused my custom. An outrage I will be writing to the management!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @salomonfreeski: New Salomon Powfinder app is coming soon. Want to join the private beta for iPhone/Android? RT this message & win an ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rory_g_macrae I never got the invite for fallow. Plus, I don't really like you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rory_g_macrae are you not questing to mordor? I sent you text anyway!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rustyboy2310 think I'm doing some fest stuff tomo night with lize. Keep in touch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rustyboy2310 babyface. Are you going to make it out for #beer ?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rory_g_macrae @rustyboy2310 I know what this references and it amuses me! #lordofchalmersesring]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Cameron to return tonight & call meeting tomorrow, 11am." Yeah cool man, whenever youre ready mate no rush. Leave a bit of time for brekkie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/Er3bbwp @matthannah1987 what do you reckon? Shall we go quids in?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love these!  :: http://cot.ag/o7bh1m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just had the misfortune of hearing 'swagger jagger'. #boke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#bored]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DuncanBannatyne: Wooooo hoooooo I am pissed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh my god Torres!!! #motd2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @stephencgrant: "... ..... .. ....... .... ..." #DeafThreats]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aspy87 the human torch was denied a bank loan #ronburgandy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love lamp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rustyboy2310 ....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@writerspry hi really enjoy the tweets. Is there a website or blog where I can find all these nuggets of advice? Thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @simonpegg: T. Hardy fact. Back in the day Tom would join us in The Shepherds, Highgate (now the mighty Boogaloo) the pub that inspir ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Billy brown new hibs assistant. What the hell is going on at Easter road?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Aiannucci: Hi everyone. Yes, I can confirm Alan is up and genuinely tweeting on @ThisisPartridge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @simonpegg: I'm hearing word of a Point Break remake. When I finish writing this tweet, I will sigh heavily, close my eyes and shake  ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[here here @rory_g_macrae http://t.co/yLAxRtu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rip Andy Whitfield.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SteepSkiing: Cant wait to effect change! RT @AudenSchendler: Pro snowsports athletes in DC to lobby congress on climate! http://t.co ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CraigLevein: Watched Andy Murray last night. Seemed to come undone when he went for winners. Happy to pass on some defensive tactic  ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come on Wales #RWC2011]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rory_g_macrae @rustyboy2310 im actually hitting up the new museum with @OfficialMannah so no rugby for me. Maybe drinks later?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[England are rattled! #RWC2011]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feel bad for contepomi #RWC2011]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes phone guy! #redorblack]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Come on guy with the phone!! #redorblack]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Power team are unbelievable!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why don't more snow movie makers distribute their work via ITunes? I know @NimbusIndpndnt did with #contrast a couple of years ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have just watched #theartofFLIGHT. Absolutely ridiculous. Best snowsports movie I have ever seen- even for bunch of gays on trays!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @michaelocc: WARNING: if you see tweets offering free clip of the new Nickelback album DO NOT CLICK. It links to a free clip of the n ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The itv commentary is so horrific. Never thought I would be missing Brian Moore! #RWC2011]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tonga avoid the bagel! #RWC2011]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rustyboy2310 good luck with your 'chat' today mate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @brewdog: BrewDog launches 28%ABV beer served from a stag’s head to ‘smash UK perceptions of beer’ http://t.co/mStoRjt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Levein have a shave ya mink. #scotland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FootballAid: Wishing all the Home nations in action the best of luck tonight. We're not biased of course but we do have to say #come ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rory_g_macrae @aspy87 @rossmcnairn @rustyboy2310 fair, prob just going to watch it at home tbh. Really need to save some cash!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rory_g_macrae @aspy87 @rossmcnairn @rustyboy2310 It's okay Tom, he gets off on not inviting people to things. What are thinking Rory?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @brewdog: Drool. RT @brober87: @brewdog Punk n' Beef stew. Bloody excellent #BrewBake http://t.co/gtFlleQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OfficialMannah why don't you just have some pasta... And a cheese sauce?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The injustice of this is killing me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fucking cheating Czech fuckers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brewdog Punk n' Beef stew. Bloody excellent #BrewBake http://t.co/HZLg2zS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amy macdonald is no Ronnie the corrie #scotland]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rory_g_macrae yeah was going to watch it at the flat if you fancy joining? What time does @rustyboy2310 kick off?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#beers are on @OfficialMannah ! How many dubloons did you pick up?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And nothing from the first two albums by the Walkmen. Great night for it though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arcade Fire is an alcohol free event... #noooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aspy87 yeah should be. Keep in touch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rory_g_macrae @rustyboy2310 maybs. Keep in touch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rory_g_macrae @rustyboy2310 sorry mate at arcade fire tonight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jim White. #deadlineday royalty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aspy87 aye are you up? Going to see arcade fire at the castle tomorrow! Walkmen/vaccines supporting!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aspy87 he's been really short on form recently as well. Hopefully only the manager getting the heave ho at hibs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not sure if arteta for 10mil is a good deal or not. He's got it in him. Has just played like a chump the last 18 months #bbcfootball]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JojoRobertson1 eh?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A wonderfully Frank article for anyone attempting NaNoWriMo http://j.mp/nxOVXX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CraigLevein: #mathematicallypossible]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rustyboy2310 @rory_g_macrae potentially meeting @rossmcnairn for a pint in stocky but it will just be 1. Promised lize a night in!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A win @rustyboy2310 ? Keen for standard @rory_g_macrae]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rory_g_macrae man down]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Colinko: Do you Remember Bebeto's cradle rocking celebration at USA 94? That baby has just signed for Flamengo. Don't you feel old?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Tartanarmy not booing Lichtenstein anthem, good to see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rory_g_macrae amen brother.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Couldn't help but notice Craig mackail-smith isn't singing the anthem. Could it be he doesn't know the words?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>