<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Chi-Lites  http://t.co/uPVldfBqlS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these top auto insurance companies!  http://t.co/XzWXrFfAEj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Very Fun and Geeky 8-Bit Tie!  http://t.co/622C9uGhqW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Wonderful History of Tulips  http://t.co/X7tSWhIcRZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I grew up in a world that told girls they couldn't play rock 'n' roll. - Joan Jett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our Review of Amazon’s Popular Kindle Reader  http://t.co/eiCiHXF2HY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The great difficulty in education is to get experience out of ideas. - George Santayana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The rest of the world lives to eat, while I eat to live. - Socrates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Platform Shoes  http://t.co/ZjVuqKMmwu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Air Supply  http://t.co/HWiOmJPGtj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Best Camping Destinations  http://t.co/hiwz2eqLPi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hit the ball over the fence and you can take your time going around the bases. - John W. Raper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the parents of a Little Leaguer, a baseball game is simply a nervous breakdown into innings. - Earl Wilson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I actually don't understand a word Paula's saying anymore. It's like a new language.  Simon Cowell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The History of The Six Million Dollar Man  http://t.co/Je6XP86HYE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Mike Clifford - A One-Hit Wonder  http://t.co/mLDSv8z7nn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are flirting with danger when you buy high-heeled sandals - Eileen Allen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it's too close to bother to buckle your seat belt it's close enough to walk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Jackson Browne  http://t.co/pPpuVdvDla]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would give a million bucks to have seen my mother say "cute shoes" to a naked Ashley Judd. --&gt; Brian Fies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Jack in the Box  http://t.co/7Am2JXm5df]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Jimmy Choo  http://t.co/8LSJ9tT9ud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Media is a Helpful Tool in Connecting with Customers  http://t.co/JV6PiX3iPj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You call the driver of a car a motorist, until he comes just little too close.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Heineken Phone Case --&gt; http://t.co/nLdmaD3Xkl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must accept finite disappointment, but we must never lose infinite hope. - Martin Luther King, Jr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to know what a man is really like, take notice of how he acts when he loses money.  Simone Weil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you ain't making waves, you ain't kickin' hard enough - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man's health can be judged by which he takes two at a time - pills or stairs. - Joan Welsh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Jackson Browne  http://t.co/pPpuVdvDla]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame Block Hunt: That Guy had a Porcupine Sleep on His Face  http://t.co/Hs02B312Uz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of Little House on The Prairie Episode - "In the Big Inning"  http://t.co/mTLwUjJjfx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bad habits are like chains that are too light to feel until they are too heavy to carry. - Warren Buffet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do women want? Shoes. --&gt; Mimi Pond]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool Hands Free Umbrella! http://t.co/oBYu4zAAie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate most of what constitutes rock music, which is basically middle-aged crap. - Sting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Major Watch Retailers and Brands  http://t.co/wD3NeFq6FX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take care of your body. It's the only place you have to live. - Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is not a rock opera. This is not Tommy. I can write songs that emote, and that's it. - John Mellencamp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Successfully Use Other Websites for Link Building  http://t.co/VguQSrRKTc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most serious mistakes are not being made as a result of wrong answers. The truly dangerous thing is asking the wrong question P Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who can believe that there is no soul behind those luminous doggie eyes! - Theophile Gautier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Favorite Things for Kids to Review  http://t.co/rrHZayqVzH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I mean, we're lost on an island, running from boars and monsters -- freakin' polar bears.  Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Matrimony: An Institution of learning in which a man loses his "Bachelor's Degree" and his wife acquires a "Masters"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Hiring a Strategy Consulting Firm  http://t.co/rfQk0AggrC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Superhero caped glasses - totally cool!  http://t.co/UwW000HqQX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Boston  http://t.co/mNmfgyDKAy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Create your own Ice, Chocolate, Jelly in the shape of Han Solo in Carbonite!!!  http://t.co/5dqaDt8PmR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Emmylou Harris  http://t.co/R46kB0AqwZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the history of the Modern Tennis Shoe  http://t.co/qEo3h6rWg0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Health and Mana Video Game Inspired Earrings with Key Charms!  Cool! http://t.co/k1ElOr3VYo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Are the Different Types of Web Hosting?  http://t.co/9z5nsd4FyJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion is what you're offered four times a year by designers. And style is what you choose. - Lauren Hutton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is Renter's Insurance?  http://t.co/Ur3IiOHkLN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make Your House More Attractive With Fall Flowers  http://t.co/err8mQSP9T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wanted to make the lightest shoe possible, but still be able to perform at the same time. - Carmelo Anthony]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Kalin Twins  http://t.co/d7GXP3ohIS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We worked 80 hour weeks for 30 years to keep from having to get a real job. - Tom Lemon's comment on the rigors of being a drag racing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 2 - Road Trip!!!  http://t.co/kVlFepeL3w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What becomes of the broken-hearted? They buy shoes. - Mimi Pond]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The time has come the Walrus said, To talk of many thing’s Of shoes and ships and sealing-wax of cabbages and kings - Lewis Carroll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can a leopard change his spots?  "By going from one spot to another"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only person who is educated is the one who has learned how to learn and change. - Carl Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a very easy way to return from a casino with a small fortune: go there with a large one. - Jack Yelton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My software never has bugs. It just develops random features.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the Icebound Land by John Flanagan  http://t.co/CR0gT7bSur]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman is the only hunter who uses herself for bait]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michael, I did nothing. I did absolutely nothing, and it was everything that I thought it could be. - Peter Gibbons, Office Space]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who Needs a Boyfriend to Snuggle With This Pillow! http://t.co/af1I2pqrK7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret of success is constancy to purpose. - Benjamin Disraeli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why worry about death, it'll come sooner or later. - Jim Dunn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Superhero caped glasses - totally cool!  http://t.co/UwW000HqQX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By the time a person gets to greener pastures, he can't climb the fence]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Little House on the Prairie – An American Classic TV Series  http://t.co/JyUBOBw1XU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adornment, what a science! Beauty, what a weapon! Modesty, what elegance! Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one really knows who created Bitcoin - read about the fascinating history of Satoshi Nakamoto... http://t.co/odpeDkHzev]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you ever had it so good? And had it taken away so cockeyed fast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Mars Exploration Project with Mars One  http://t.co/DlXstDgRqo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Christians Making a Profession of their Religion  http://t.co/RnrtLj5GFc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One Family’s Adoption Stories  http://t.co/TcmsXp6gay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One deer to another:  "I wish I had his doe"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tornado Automatic Cocktail Shaker - VERY COOL http://t.co/9hO5tpqleB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every instructor assumes that you have nothing else to do except study for that instructor's course.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you don't do what's best for your body, you're the one who comes up on the short end. - Julius Erving]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hokey religions and ancient weapons are no substitute for a good blaster at your side, kid. - Han Solo, Star Wars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do I set a laser printer to stun?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagination is the key to my lyrics. The rest is painted with a little science fiction. - Jimi Hendrix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The iPaperPad is not magical or revolutionary. It's a paper pad. A poor man's iPad LOL http://t.co/9MXOmFI31i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman is as young as she feels like telling you she is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Real education must ultimately be limited to men who insist on knowing, the rest is mere sheep-herding. - Ezra Pound]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't really see science fiction as fiction. I can imagine colonies on Mars and everything. - Sigourney Weaver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No heaven will not ever Heaven be; “Unless my cats are there to welcome me.” - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Utilize Strategy Consulting Firms: Gain a Competitive Advantage  http://t.co/63SbTZQZXJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greetings, programs! - Flynn, TRON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who are the Three Degrees oldies group?  http://t.co/PPJjC14afG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rule your mind or it will rule you. - Horace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The woman who wants a perfect husband will have to grow him and should allow at least thirty years for the process]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overheard when the boss returned from his safari in Africa: "He's the first man the head shrinkers ever failed with."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've destroyed my feet completely but I don't care. What do you really need your feet for anyway - Sarah Jessica Parker]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>