<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Front End Developer: Sr. Front End Developer Cincinnati, Ohio – United States Job Start Date – 06/25/18, Posted Date – 06/18/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview Apex Systems, the nation s 2nd largest IT Staffing organization, has an immediate… https://t.co/DTH4r0k4ub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woman says park officer stood by as man harassed her for wearing Puerto Rico shirt: An Illinois park is investigating after a woman accused one of its police officers of standing by as a man harassed her for wearing a shirt with the Puerto Rican flag,… https://t.co/9Lt4vTHfrL https://t.co/EjeMDY4rrO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Web Developer: Founded in 1866, The Sherwin-Williams Company is a global leader in the manufacture, development, distribution, and sale of paints, coatings and related products to professional, industrial, commercial, and retail customers.… https://t.co/JTgAqxoBfo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer Business Group Architecture and Software No. of Positions 1 Requisition Number 74810BR Job Category Engineering and Technicians Position Type Full Time Relocation Eligible Yes Position Summary As a Software Engineer… https://t.co/zIUQN68xpr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Trump's court pick, who won?: CNN commentators weigh in on Donald Trump's historic nomination to the Supreme Court of the United States to replace the retiring Justice Anthony Kennedy. https://t.co/Trojdm8Dui https://t.co/C4MnqTArPO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lucky few migrant families to be reunited Tuesday: A few dozen immigrant families are expected to be reunited by a court deadline Tuesday, as the fates of thousands more remain in limbo. https://t.co/wJmv9Y5Mfe https://t.co/nlGqxAMfYt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Software Engineer: .Net Software Engineer ====================== Tyler Technologies is growing and is looking for software engineer to design, develop and maintain enterprise level software applications used by the public sector nationwide. As a… https://t.co/sgz97BkKRB https://t.co/cNr4IaX8RJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Controls Programmer: Contract/Freelance Project Description Job Title Controls Programmer (Glass and Manufacturing) Job Location Toledo, OH Department TOL1843 – EGCM Glass/Mfg Controls – Toledo Position Type Contract / Regular Full-Time Position Summary:… https://t.co/2RKHJAnhuq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['World's largest vertical farm' to feed Middle East's high-fliers: The team behind the $40M farm claim it will harvest 6,000 pounds of leafy greens -- every day. https://t.co/ERdApSzY5H https://t.co/trG3iDvBTC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democratic senator open to voting for any one of the SCOTUS finalists: Democratic Sen. Jon Tester of Montana said Monday he is open to voting for any of President Donald Trump's potential Supreme Court nominees. https://t.co/zJJoqW2gQP https://t.co/U00CfhIgBz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former FBI lawyer Lisa Page subpoenaed for House interview on Wednesday: Lisa Page, the former FBI lawyer who exchanged anti-Trump text messages with FBI agent Peter Strzok, has been subpoenaed for a closed-door interview this week with the House… https://t.co/eBTUfBD3D2 https://t.co/WWLiyFKMwf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump is the skunk at NATO's garden party: Donald Trump is heading to Europe, where he is deeply unpopular and has earned disdain through his attacks on the NATO alliance and his praise for Vladimir Putin, Michael D'Antonio writes. https://t.co/LsHyME7ICh https://t.co/RL62epNvnI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Service Desk Technician – Mid/Sr – TS/SCI – Wright-Patterson AFB, Ohio: Come join General Dynamics Information Technology Team! – Follow all approved customer policies, processes and procedures. – Follow the written and verbal instructions provided by… https://t.co/EVO98Z1BTb https://t.co/u8cwFIL1Df]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Trump and African leaders need to know about food security: Tewodaj Mogues writes that the increased uncertainty of US support to food-insecure regions like Africa presents a rare opportunity for both Africans and the development sector. https://t.co/N0kTcVUSgF https://t.co/uKRqVWLlf5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Web Developer: Description Founded in 1866, The Sherwin-Williams Company is a global leader in the manufacture, development, distribution, and sale of paints, coatings and related products to professional, industrial, commercial, and retail… https://t.co/E6ScL6myUH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer, Software Engineering (SAP LE/MM Global Supply Chain): At Cardinal Health, we are developing the innovative products and services that make healthcare safer and more productive. Join a growing, global company genuinely committed to making a… https://t.co/yDWogcvJwN https://t.co/pQy2kwjAjD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meet Xiaomi's billionaire executives: Xiaomi's Hong Kong IPO has turned some of the smartphone maker's top executives into billionaires. https://t.co/eUdQb8gVfn https://t.co/LQuvM5SQnY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mgr Programs 1:   Job Description – Mgr Programs 1 (18007734) Mgr Programs 1 Requisition ID : 18007734 Location : United States-Ohio-Cincinnati US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation Assistance: No relocation assistance available… https://t.co/LXnc0yZ3vT https://t.co/J4XyA98OBZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer: Senior Software Developer in Cleveland, OH at National General Insurance Toggle Navigation – Home – About – Benefits – Training – Our Values – All Jobs Join Our Talent Network Search Our Jobs Keyword: Location: –… https://t.co/kQjD2HTs8O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How fashion model Hailey Baldwin made a name for herself: 21-year-old Hailey Baldwin is a social media star, fashion model and fiancee to Justin Bieber. https://t.co/eiyQtIKihN https://t.co/O278BSJxOl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Cincinnati, Ohio – United States Job Start Date – 07/03/18, Posted Date – 07/03/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview Position Description: The Developer is responsible for leading the design, development, testing,… https://t.co/L0di7vqXyc https://t.co/hPcMyvvrRb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[functional analyst: functional analyst Ref No.: 18-29326 Location: dublin, Ohio Functional Analyst Dublin /OH 12 months * Should have good knowledge on S4 HANA Finance and Controlling (FICO) * Should have done End to End Implementation process, * Should… https://t.co/tvCeFbKfBi https://t.co/y1pWnXK1G4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump to unveil Supreme Court pick for the ages: When President Donald Trump unveils his second Supreme Court pick Monday night with the prime-time flourish of a reality show star, he will lay a momentous marker in modern political history. https://t.co/bCe8qiNc94 https://t.co/CxNg2e7SwJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WaPo: McConnell chased from KY restaurant by protesters: Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell was followed to his car Saturday by protesters who hurled both personal insults and political rhetoric at him while he left a Kentucky restaurant, The… https://t.co/d7oIKpmyXG https://t.co/L5ttPqpvi9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PA: UK Brexit secretary David Davis resigns: The UK's Brexit Secretary David Davis resigned Sunday, the British Press Association said on Twitter. https://t.co/lHZgaNiEKZ https://t.co/sq3rCGk9CK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ayatollah Seyyed Ali Khamenei Fast Facts: Read CNN's Ayatollah Seyyed Ali Khamenei Fast Facts for a look at the life of the Iranian Supreme Leader. https://t.co/kzgT8gm6gf https://t.co/gS0mT80ZiR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Application Analyst and Developer: Location US-OH-Cincinnati Posted Date 19 hours ago(6/18/2018 3:18 PM) Job ID 23720 # Positions 2 Category Technology Position Type Full Time Overview Be Here. Be Great. Working for a leader in the insurance… https://t.co/Nv5zev9o52 https://t.co/6qHb7LOmuu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager II – Higher Ed: Project Manager II – Higher Ed Tracking Code 5158-244 Job Description At Gilbane we’re building more than buildings, we’re helping create schools, hospitals, laboratories and other facilities across the United States and… https://t.co/YLC8JStAA4 https://t.co/lDXp8ZU5qy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Consultant, Business Analyst (Lean and Business Process Optimization): At Cardinal Health, we’re developing the innovative products and services that make healthcare safer and more productive. Join a growing, global company genuinely committed to… https://t.co/mUztqAmZOy https://t.co/E622ExFoQ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Inside Politics': McConnell advising Trump on Supreme Court pick: President Trump prepares to announce his second Supreme Court nominee before heading to Europe for the NATO summit, immigration experts push back on calls to abolish ICE, red-state… https://t.co/fUNgsj8ZbR https://t.co/v2t0meg5dE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Careers and Culture – Polaris Alpha -Software Developer Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job.… https://t.co/5sk65ekOyp https://t.co/VEoW5815yp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump: US 'working very closely' with Thailand to rescue children: President Donald Trump tweeted Sunday morning that the US is working with the Thai government to rescue children trapped in a flooded cave. https://t.co/9WGy1abwaZ https://t.co/69lahoDQDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce Business Analyst Marketing: **Salesforce Business Analyst Marketing** Locations:Milford, Ohio Job Family: Information Technology New Search Apply English (US) **Job Description** **Division:** Digital Factory **Business Unit:** Product… https://t.co/sw3RATdG63 https://t.co/LTgrERD4nJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tariffs cast a shadow as earnings season begins: Earnings season is here. And after months of bluster, so are tariffs. https://t.co/yfel8PQqOI https://t.co/qqRsGjZfWF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Service Desk Technician – Mid/Sr – TS/SCI – Wright-Patterson AFB, Ohio: Come join General Dynamics Information Technology Team! – Follow all approved customer policies, processes and procedures. – Follow the written and verbal instructions provided by… https://t.co/PwYWjvNMyR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Homeowners come home to ash and rubble as wildfires ravage California: Eric Durtschi moved to Santa Barbara County two weeks ago. His home is now a dusty pile of ash and debris as a fast-moving blaze sweeps through Southern California. https://t.co/Vj7u0UkMZb https://t.co/VZ0sLn15i4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer Professional Apprentice: Job Description Founded in 1866, The Sherwin-Williams Company is a global leader in the manufacture, development, distribution, and sale of paints, coatings and related products to professional, industrial,… https://t.co/B5YduIX8JW https://t.co/yXhhTeHVCw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solution Architect: Solution Architect Ref No.: 18-26117 Location: Cincinnati, Ohio Role: Solution Architect Location: Cincinnati OH Duration:9-12 months JD – Strong Architect experience with skillsets reflecting that of Java, Spring MVC, CRM, IVR,… https://t.co/i4F92yjm1t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Data Warehouse Developer: Brief Description: This role is on the Enterprise Information Management (EIM) team, which is responsible for supporting Huntington’s (HNB) Enterprise Data Warehouse, ETL and Business Intelligence tools. The role will ensure… https://t.co/YpVEN7Hs0N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thai cave rescue: Divers enter cave to free boys -- Live updates https://t.co/SA4XnFDQDt https://t.co/B3ofBC2VI7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer | full-stack C#/JavaScript developer: .NET Developer | full-stack C#/JavaScript developer – CareWorks TechCareWorks Tech CareWorks Tech Menu – Services – IT Consulting – Enterprise Service Management – Infrastructure – Security –… https://t.co/pxHvQPHwRw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thai rescue: Youngest boy trapped in cave dreams of fried chicken: Twelve Thai boys trapped in a cave have sent letters to their parents, and for the youngest of them all, foremost on his mind is the prospect of a tasty fried chicken meal when, and if,… https://t.co/v4T5NsuDKw https://t.co/PNFHxgADKT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK police officer hospitalized in connection with nerve agent incident: A police officer has sought medical advice in connection to an ongoing investigation of Novichok nerve agent exposure in Amesbury, England, A hospital official said Saturday. https://t.co/j3kGcloIvP https://t.co/NliV5BYOe7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US service member killed in Afghanistan in apparent insider attack: A US service member was killed and two others were wounded in an apparent insider attack in southern Afghanistan Saturday, according to the NATO-led coalition's Resolute Support mission. https://t.co/7fiCTlbabf https://t.co/SS1iWOm7pt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Lead: Job Title: .NET Lead Location: Findlay, OH Job Number: JO-1806-27512 Description ProKarma is currently seeking a .NET Lead to join our team in Findlay, OH! Qualified candidates must possess a minimum of 8 years’ experience with at least… https://t.co/VzmaUuQ6Jr https://t.co/v1UaAfLYGi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What we lose when we let Trump's tweets and insults take over the news: When newsrooms scramble to cover Trump's rallies, such as the one held on Thursday in Montana, other, more important stories may be getting left behind. https://t.co/oor0B59Q7F https://t.co/9jnRDx76ri]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Director Americas Delivery Executive:   Job Description – Sr Director Americas Delivery Executive (019775) Job Description  Sr Director Americas Delivery Executive-019775 Description   As the Diebold Nixdorf Americas Managed Service Delivery Executive… https://t.co/oB7W7ZJ3Yf https://t.co/sK46nvqxJw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2020 Insight: Trump says he'll throw a DNA test at 'Pocahontas'; Kennedy talks presidential ambitions; Cuomo keeps Trump cash: Our weekly roundup of the news, notes and chatter about the prospects for the next Democratic presidential race: https://t.co/tEEPt34yCs https://t.co/uIVod6N0UP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Construction Project Manager – Commercial/Concrete!: Cleveland, OH Full-time $80k – $120k Posted Today If you are a Project Manager with experience, please read on! What You Will Be Doing •Review incoming concrete engineering packages for drawings,… https://t.co/n1KCAKa5VR https://t.co/LhsPVXasmc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iran executes eight men over last year's terror attacks in Tehran: Iran executed eight men convicted of terrorism for last year's twin attacks that left 17 people dead in Tehran, state media reported Saturday. https://t.co/KL7qQdB753 https://t.co/m1NhQzAM3A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer III: Software Engineer III sought by Accolade, Inc. in Plymouth Meeting, PA. Job # 58808. Resolve complex technical issues and deliver innovative solutions that improve user engagement, system availability, resiliency, and performance.… https://t.co/OiYc8dX7kE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Trump administration separated families. Reuniting them is a giant mess.: The family separations saga has revealed failures of governance, competence and humanity and made one thing clear: President Donald Trump doesn't believe Harry S. Truman's… https://t.co/6XIvNPvl0a https://t.co/ebje1YW2SU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ready or not, Puerto Ricans rush to prepare as storm nears Caribbean: With Puerto Rico still recovering from hurricanes Irma and Maria last year, cautious residents filled supermarkets and department stores Friday as the first hurricane of the season… https://t.co/xBxIVNkPHc https://t.co/MHojlGWP5c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer C# Programmer: For Siemens Software Engineer – C# Programmer job – Research &amp; Development – Johnson City, Tennessee Skip to Main Content – – – – – Our Stories – FAQS – My Dashboard – Toggle navigation – My Dashboard – Our Stories – FAQS… https://t.co/19j8k1TRgJ https://t.co/G9TxfQqVka]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whether trapped in a cave or held by the US, children need us to care: There seems to be a disconnect between our concern for the children in Thailand and the migrant children held by the US government, writes Jill Filipovic. But as we continue to hope… https://t.co/zMmpmGeqkd https://t.co/osxI306Wsm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calgary Stampede 2018: 7 reasons to jump on the bandwagon: The 2018 edition of the annual Calgary Stampede is July 6-15. Here are seven reasons to join the bandwagon in Canada -- from white-knuckle road to pancake breakfasts. https://t.co/r5REAeQERo https://t.co/2d5feHejuu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Salary/Rate N/A Permanent Location US-Columbus-OH, United States Posted By Aegion Corporation Date Posted 6 hours ago Expires 17 Jun 2018 Qualifications None Project Manager in US-Columbus-OH, United States US-Columbus-OH, United States… https://t.co/eK3LTNoQa8 https://t.co/GQ80Sgj4pP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Red Hen - the restaurant that asked Sarah Sanders to leave -- reopens amid protests: After a nearly two-week hiatus, Red Hen, the Lexington, Virginia restaurant known for turning away Press Secretary Sarah Huckabee Sanders reopened its doors. https://t.co/i9EUQ7gwtf https://t.co/b1DaZK5aOt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Web Developer: Founded in 1866, The Sherwin-Williams Company is a global leader in the manufacture, development, distribution, and sale of paints, coatings and related products to professional, industrial, commercial, and retail customers.… https://t.co/djpIX9HCgf https://t.co/h4pi7cXhSn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer – API/ Johnston, RI: Software Developer-API Location: Johnston, RI (some remote possible, need candidates to be based around Johnston, RI) Duration: 6+ months contract * The candidate must have Java at their core and be committed to… https://t.co/dcnLuJ6RCk https://t.co/vm8aA855gy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What we know about RAICES, the group raising money to reunite separated immigrant families: In the discussion about immigrant kids separated from their parents at the US-Mexico border, one name comes up often these days: RAICES. https://t.co/VHGzHmDctw https://t.co/EDblmVpvWz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Developer: Database Developer ================== Tyler Technologies is growing and is looking for software developers to design, develop and maintain enterprise level HTML5 software applications used by the public sector nationwide. As a… https://t.co/HhHRZUJxbk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Airbus CEO: UK has 'no clue' on Brexit: The CEO of Airbus has accused the British government of having "no clue" how to deliver a successful Brexit. https://t.co/zsKqTGeHMs https://t.co/GQq9CKVngB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Android Developer $140k: Cincinnati, OH Full-time $110k – $140k Posted 04/28/2018 If you are a Android Developer with experience, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us We are one of the fastest growing companies in the country that invest heavily… https://t.co/sT0QHllLUb https://t.co/X0rG9HMLWo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dangerous heat wave is about to threaten millions of people in California and southwest US: A dangerous heat wave is expected to grip California and other parts of the southwest Friday and into the weekend, threatening millions of people and likely… https://t.co/iiTxHelw25 https://t.co/RbtsdAnMmD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's #MeToo swipe updates his 2016 playbook: President Donald Trump understands what got him elected -- a willingness to throw caution and decorum to the wind and to assail what his supporters see as rampant political correctness. https://t.co/j8iEV38f0f https://t.co/3JaniuUC6T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Project Manager: Job Description Job Title Sr. Project Manager (Industrial Process) Job Location Cincinnati, OH Columbus, OH Midland, MI Toledo, OH Department TOL1511 – EGCM Project Mgmt – Toledo Position Type Regular Full-Time Position Summary: SSOE… https://t.co/rjqvF8ASWB https://t.co/WUGTqu848D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Future Concept Campaign Modeling and Simulation Analyst/Developer, Mid: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Wright-Patterson Air Force Base, OH Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 7/2/2018 Job Description Job Number: R*******… https://t.co/nKw5qqykzO https://t.co/QBeV0SKUAp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Engineer: COMPANY PROFILE Talis Clinical, LLC provides health technology supporting clinicians to impact patient safety and improve outcomes. The team at Talis Clinical is committed to developing technologies that provide enhanced… https://t.co/aNRfeG8riG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thai soccer team rescue: Former Navy diver dies while exiting flooded caves: A former Thai Navy diver who joined the operation to rescue 12 boys and their coach from a cave in northern Thailand has died, according to a Thai Navy source. https://t.co/G4oi9adTsv https://t.co/taJpCuvU8U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A former coal lobbyist is the new leader of the EPA: A former coal lobbyist will be the new acting head of the Environmental Protection Agency after former agency Administrator Scott Pruitt resigned on Thursday. https://t.co/m8ouQsCgpw https://t.co/Hd8CbI7Bus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[University of Maryland suspends athletics staffers as football player's heatstroke death is investigated: The University of Maryland has placed members of its athletics staff on administrative leave during an investigation of the death by heatstroke of a… https://t.co/FsXkD61Z4R https://t.co/j5nDuxFSxB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Avenatti is right: Democrats need to fight fire with fire: Michael Avenatti may have had a point when he rejected the famous advice of former first lady Michelle Obama who said, "When they go low, we go high," Julian Zelizer says. https://t.co/HI0RIWIDd9 https://t.co/Wz2lYdnF1D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer, Senior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Blue Ash, OH Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 7/19/2018 Job Description Job Number: R******* Python Developer, Senior Key Role: Work independently to design and… https://t.co/RDxOZbn5U8 https://t.co/R2SLkv3rci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[XP Cloud Engineer/Developer: Location US-OH-Cincinnati Posted Date 2 months ago(5/31/2018 9:53 AM) Job ID 23665 # Positions 1 Category Technology Position Type Full Time Overview Be Here. Be Great. Working for a leader in the insurance industry means… https://t.co/XMGCktO7rn https://t.co/QOqmeniya8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kavanaugh argued a president would have to testify before a grand jury if subpoenaed: Supreme Court Justice nominee Brett Kavanaugh, while working on the independent counsel investigation into President Bill Clinton in 1995, argued that a sitting… https://t.co/oWuJ6VwBWB https://t.co/mVTkrE7MIM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All-Source Network Intelligence Analyst: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Wright-Patterson Air Force Base, OH Job Type: Strategy – Planning Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 7/25/2018 Job Description Job Number: R******* All-Source Network… https://t.co/wxYPzEwnCg https://t.co/axSKb18lV9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Trump's White House, Charlottesville was a moment that wasn't: When President Donald Trump declared a year ago that "very fine people" were among the Nazi mobs descending upon Charlottesville, Virginia, the reaction was swift. https://t.co/GPb50I9Tre https://t.co/3zoB8LdbHB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior IT Business Analyst (Kronos/Payroll): Description The position is visible to the hospital’s business service lines and serves as a liaison between IT and those groups. This position also functions as a team member responsible for providing… https://t.co/9ZzF0HLKMq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9-year-old chess prodigy wins right to stay in Britain: The family of a child chess prodigy living in London has been given the right to stay in Britain because of his "world class talent." https://t.co/opL803yIpM https://t.co/dV1akbftMj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ANALOG HARDWARE ENGINEER: ANALOG HARDWARE ENGINEER Ref No.: 18-33491 Location: Mayfield Heights, Ohio overviews :: – Product development and enhancement of industrial control products viz. Programmable Logic Controllers, I/O Modules and Communication… https://t.co/6YxmnKFiaX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plane with only an airline employee aboard crashes after unauthorized takeoff in Seattle, airport says: An aircraft that took off without authorization and without passengers has crashed, officials at Seattle-Tacoma International Airport said Friday night. https://t.co/U1FZp5FJvA https://t.co/HafSA9pRnf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Takeaways from day nine of the Paul Manafort trial: As prosecutors neared the end of presenting their case against former Trump campaign chairman Paul Manafort, the federal court in Virginia gave its watchers a true cliffhanger. https://t.co/NwtUNWTyaQ https://t.co/FSV3Yp5Zlp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't fall into Trump's trap on NFL protests: Somewhere between Colin Kaepernick and the President calling NFL players sons of bitches, the media appears to have lost its appetite for stressing the original and urgent reason NFL players took a knee in… https://t.co/OwQT8ayYZi https://t.co/NPzXmPgmyj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer, Software Engineering: At Cardinal Health, we are developing the innovative products and services that make healthcare safer and more productive. Join a growing, global company genuinely committed to making a difference for our… https://t.co/x2svy2YVOE https://t.co/HajuHSy5pf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quickly catch up on the day's news: Here's what you might have missed Friday on CNN. https://t.co/CoGaBV9E6t https://t.co/16S6m3xYNd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dad and son are accused of illegally killing a family of bears and covering it up. They didn't know a camera was running.: A father and son from Alaska are accused of slaughtering a mother black bear and her cubs as they rested in their den. What they… https://t.co/hp6I7o9MGs https://t.co/cvlT32Hu7R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Embedded Software Engineer: Senior Embedded Software Engineer Business Group Architecture and Software No. of Positions 1 Requisition Number 77762BR Job Category Engineering and Technicians Position Type Full Time Relocation Eligible Yes Position… https://t.co/Mrhz7cCHnY https://t.co/PTSpjvSNJm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Crazy Rich Asians' stars explain why the film should be allowed to fail: "Crazy Rich Asians" cast members Awkwafina, Nico Santos, Ronny Chieng and Janice Koh are hyperaware there's a lot riding on the success of their film. https://t.co/vOxVdYn24N https://t.co/F7ssWElHcf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to own a sailing yacht on a budget: Think sailing is too expensive? This story will show you how you can get on the water for the equivalent cost of buying a second-hand car. https://t.co/YClPuGUVeJ https://t.co/KXUtVCZnNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manufacturing Automation Developer: Lubrizol, a Berkshire Hathaway company, is a market-driven global company that combines complex, specialty chemicals to optimize the quality, performance and value of customers’ products while reducing their… https://t.co/faMbZNeKXv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer-Analyst/Senior Programmer-Analyst, IT: Location: Dayton Job type: Permanent Sector: IT &amp; Communications Category: Analyst Jobs Location: DAY PSA Corporate HDQ (DAY-PSAH) Additional Locations: None Requisition ID: 20869 Overview Join us for a… https://t.co/XR5UVbPImw https://t.co/BuqZkoV1UH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China warns off US reconnaissance plane over the South China Sea: High above one of the most hotly contested regions in the world, CNN was given a rare look Friday at the Chinese government's rapidly expanding militarization of the South China Sea from a… https://t.co/l4snowSQi9 https://t.co/TiV7ZjDUSW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Systems Specialist: Company The Boeing Company Job ID ********** Date posted 07/25/2018 Location Heath Ohio United States Job Description The Boeing Defense, Space &amp; Security (BDS) organization is seeking a Quality Systems Specialist (Level 2)… https://t.co/DqB1ssFuZ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Client Project Manager: Client Project Manager Req ID #: 37345 Location: Spencerville, OH, US For 70 years, Charles River employees have worked together to assist in the discovery, development and safe manufacture of new drug therapies. When you join our… https://t.co/JpwTXAXQaV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The making of a judicial phenomenon: Ruth Bader Ginsburg marks 25 years on the bench: When Ginsburg failed to land a law firm job, she turned to teaching, then became a women's rights lawyer and eventually found her way to the Supreme Court https://t.co/UpGhtw9jmA https://t.co/THsowr3TON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[North Korea: US not adhering to its side of the bargain since Trump-Kim summit: North Korea issued a forceful statement Thursday against what it said were elements of the US government which are not adhering to the spirit of the dialogue established by… https://t.co/CqqgiKAS13 https://t.co/KUtRD2nMMz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook bars users from sharing blueprints for 3D-printed guns: Facebook won't let users share the blueprints for making 3D-printed guns on their site. https://t.co/z8O18ajdnX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man accused of soliciting murder of ICE agents on Twitter: A Massachusetts man was arrested on Thursday for allegedly using Twitter to solicit the murder of ICE agents. https://t.co/gjCKE7z7aA https://t.co/AGeHZVHOlm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: What IT Program &amp; Project Management contributes to Cardinal Health IT Program &amp; Project Management is responsible for playing a key/critical role in realizing business value through the application of project management knowledge,… https://t.co/vlaj6m5l58 https://t.co/E4mbrFIShP]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>