<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[software engineer: Nutanix is hiring developers to build enterprise-grade products around Docker and Kubernetes. Responsibilities: Work directly on Kubernetes, Docker, and several other open source projects. – Work on cutting-edge features of Kubernetes… https://t.co/yNrHv1zFB6 https://t.co/F8uIUTazDJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Contract Full Stack/Python Engineer: If youre open to a long term contract role in NYC and some strong software engineering skills using Python, we want to talk to you! WHATS THE JOB? We are digitizing a massive legacy software platform that was written… https://t.co/BQT8LLtuWN https://t.co/OJiam2cVSA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer 3: ALL CANDIDATES MUST HAVE AN ACTIVE TS/SCI WITH A POLYGRAPH CLEARANCE Description: This is a Software Engineering position that involves designing, developing, building and deploying software code to implement streaming analytics that… https://t.co/WR7bslilib https://t.co/9dBZCqYD3f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Backend Developer: Who we are: Arable Labs, Inc. is a venture-backed startup founded by scientists to provide crop monitoring and point precision weather forecasts – a complete approach to crop management. (https://t.co/pa1eeGNlDO). What we need: We are… https://t.co/07pS4hWMqn https://t.co/4EgKN8sLkF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Python: Req ID : 410768BR Job Code/Title : E1071:Software Engineer Asc Job Description : Orion Test &amp; Verification Engineer. This person will be responsible for writing test success criteria, developing test procedures, scripts and… https://t.co/TRvn07A1NY https://t.co/AQsAZgmSaK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director, Data Engineering: ASCAP is home to more than 625,000 music creator members across all genres – the greatest names in music, and thousands more in the early stages of their careers. We are the world leader in performance royalties, advocacy and… https://t.co/IHKFbPhS0o https://t.co/hQtQhcNixr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infrastructure Software Engineer: Company Description Dropbox is a leading global collaboration platform that’s transforming the way people work together, from the smallest business to the largest enterprise. With more than 500 million registered users… https://t.co/OgUxajRS9d https://t.co/tacRD7Vrff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Artificial Intelligence Engineer – Python, TensorFLow, Caffe: San Francisco, CA Full-time $175k – $250k Posted Today If you are a Artificial Intelligence Engineer with experience, please read on! We are based in beautiful San Francisco, CA. We are an… https://t.co/U9z4ifN3Pj https://t.co/HPh5emEDM6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java/Python development: Java/Python development Malvern, Pennsylvania – United States Job Start Date – 03/21/18, Posted Date – 03/21/18 Primary SkillsAWS,Java/Python development,implementing REST API’s with Java for integration to 3rd party… https://t.co/RxpGaah8hu https://t.co/RTyOfBS5Gk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Developer Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: Python programming experience is a must. Should have atleast 2+ Years of experience in Python Application Development Able to understand OOPS concepts… https://t.co/7GKKsE7SJ2 https://t.co/ljjQXEz5g7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(Senior) Software Engineer: IoT Defense is looking for a strong, motivated developer looking to make an impact on our 2018 strategies. We are a start-up business looking to build out our development and engineering team to support our products. With the… https://t.co/1mIL8BjhBF https://t.co/j069oGFeP3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java/Python Developer: Java/Python Developer Location: Boston, MA Duration: Long term contract Pay Rate: $51 to 57/hr. on w2 with voluntary employee paid benefits No# of openings: 2 Required We are seeking a senior software engineer with background in… https://t.co/qPFkeAG1nN https://t.co/90kzqibIdI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Director, Outcomes Research and Data Science: Associate Director, Outcomes Research and Data Science Merck &amp; Co., Inc. Kenilworth, N.J., U.S.A. known as Merck in the United States and Canada, is a global health care leader with a diversified… https://t.co/gH4sCqEDhr https://t.co/Ag6JQU7HzI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Data Architect: Date: Mar 14, 2018 Location: Southlake, TX, US Company: Sabre Req ID: 31843 Job Family: Information Technology/Software Development Sabre is the global leader in innovative technology that leads the travel industry. We are… https://t.co/zslYM2spe0 https://t.co/2JgDjJCn0e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Application Software Engineer – Python Developer: Job descriptionPosition Purpose: Design, build, test and maintain scalable and stable off the shelf application or custom built technology solutions to meet business needs. Act as a subject matter… https://t.co/ydf5mnrQcB https://t.co/7AV9e2JO7c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Django / Python DevOps: If working with a sophisticated cloud environment spanning multiple service providers and using a range of technologies such as Python, Django, Docker and many others is what youre aiming for, then wed be happy to welcome you to… https://t.co/03H2vsm2EB https://t.co/cTx6r9JOaC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer – Startup/Python/HIPAA Compliant: San Francisco, CA Full-time $140k – $175k Posted Today If you are a Full Stack Developer with experience, please read on! Based in San Francisco we are a digital healthcare startup that is looking… https://t.co/e52gMnsgz9 https://t.co/waEwSEoWAO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer Location US-NJ-Somerset | DE | US-NJ-Somerset # Positions 1 Experience (Years) 3 Category Engineering Position Description/Company Info Legrand has a great opportunity for a Software Engineer to work in multiple… https://t.co/PjeK44d090 https://t.co/1yqBMOClQR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital Network Exploitation Analyst – Entry/Mid-Level: As a Digital Network Exploitation Analyst at the NSA, responsibilities may include: – conducting analysis of metadata – conducting target analysis and research – identifying target communications… https://t.co/XbNDmHFE1N https://t.co/2cbIFIW1zw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – python, C or Javascript, Docker: Belay Tech is seeking a Software Developer with proficiency in Python, has a knowledge of backend web development, and basic linux command-line knowledge. Knowledge or proficiency with C and JavaScript… https://t.co/FoqZONLe0f https://t.co/X7Mhb8Uofc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Engineer: Wonderschool is building a platform to bring preschool to millions of children who dont have access today. We partners with preschool teachers to open neighborhood schools in their own homes. Most preschool teachers struggle with… https://t.co/SlG3be5d1i https://t.co/m1EboML2ks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Under Armour says 150 million MyFitnessPal accounts breached: (Reuters) - Under Armour Inc said on Thursday that data from some 150 million MyFitnessPal diet and fitness app accounts was compromised in February, in one of the biggest hacks in history,… https://t.co/O59NKQU1ZZ https://t.co/KpNgv8nKKQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blue Tactics Development MS&amp;A Lead – Engineer Systems Modeling Simulation 4: Job Description The individual in this role will lead the Blue Tactics and CONOPS Modeling, Simulation, and &amp; Analysis focus area for the Systems Analysis &amp; Simulation team… https://t.co/XicwOi9CNn https://t.co/6t7PlDD19d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SDET- Python: About Us Gorilla Logic provides custom application development services on the ground and in the cloud to many of the world’s leading software-driven organizations. It has a rich history of applying software engineering best practices to… https://t.co/aHXXB45sZa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python Familiar… https://t.co/DOvXym1jAg https://t.co/nlXygjF9s8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Category: Development/Engineering City: Lafayette, Louisiana, United States Position ID: J0318-2009 Employment Type: Full Time Meet our professionals Build a Career that Matters at CGI’s Lafayette Center Position Description: Want to… https://t.co/cDaLNAiOxP https://t.co/DCRccNhl2W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UI Architect: UI Architect We are hiring a UI Architect to make our customers dreams a reality by utilizing the best-in-practice architecture, tools, and design patterns in web development. You will work closely with Reciprocitys global product and… https://t.co/HH2TLIAMTY https://t.co/BpVesM7yzm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Application Developer (Mid-Level to Senior): FullStack Labs is a fast growing software consultancy with offices in Sacramento, CA, Washington, D.C., and Barranquilla CO. We build web, desktop, and mobile applications for businesses, from small… https://t.co/v5ml6qnLfb https://t.co/iF1IOJr45u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer – Growth: About thredUP thredUP, based in San Francisco, is the leading online marketplace for buying and selling like-new womens and kids clothing. thredUP was founded in 2009 and currently employs nearly 1,000 people across its… https://t.co/J2alJEygkQ https://t.co/yiNzkbnTTJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer: Adaptive Software is one of the fastest growing parts of the DRG family. Broadly, Adaptive sells workflow and business process software tools to health plans and Pharmacy Benefit Managers (PBMs), the organizations that… https://t.co/5XVU4utqcv https://t.co/UgzYJBVjXf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Full Stack Software Engineer: Margin &amp; Estimates (Python, PHP): THE ROLE This role will be a key contributor as a FULL-STACK, full life-cycle engineer, capable of working both independently and within in team to accomplish tasks and projects… https://t.co/zIP9NB7pWO https://t.co/7L5PHYBljt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C++ Software Engineer – Santa Clara, CA: C++ Software Engineer Santa Clara, CA Full Time Position Job Description: Software engineer with 5 years experience to work on modem interfacing layers and modem interfacing SW communication protocols for clients… https://t.co/9UbMV6SmSM https://t.co/Us4GjYLhke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python developer with Tableau: Python developer with Tableau – iTechwin Systems – Milpitas, CA – 02-26-2018 | ******** Toggle navigation – Tech Careers – Job Search – Skills Center – Dice Careers Mobile – Career Explorer – Salary Predictor – Career Paths… https://t.co/X6okdIDp9e https://t.co/xIKbYDaky6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Data Scientist – SAP Innovative Business Solutions Job: Date: Mar 1, 2018 Location: Palo Alto, CA, US Company: SAP Requisition ID: ****** Work Area: Software-Design and Development Expected Travel: 0 – 20% Career Status: Management Employment… https://t.co/86zbct90s0 https://t.co/fHcLeXB6iN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Python Developer: Financial Python Developer McLean, VA $100-120K Prestigious Organization is looking for a developer who has quantitative finance experience and is strong in Python development. Design, develop and support systems within the… https://t.co/qWW9tUmqFa https://t.co/INiPJChRRw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation developer: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python Familiar with any one… https://t.co/jf3Nt1CLLt https://t.co/QyndWWE5M0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java/Python Developer: Java/Python Developer Ann arbor, Michigan – United States Job Start Date – 03/21/18, Posted Date – 03/21/18 Primary Skills3 Python and Java,large data processing requirements and data ingestion,data pipelines and analytical… https://t.co/KVUqh614ws https://t.co/2feQDE5iMr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Frontend UI Angular 2/4.x Developer: Frontend UI Angular 2/4.x Developer Dallas, Texas – United States Job Start Date – 03/22/18, Posted Date – 03/22/18 Primary SkillsUITax TermsC2COverview Job Title – Frontend UI Angular 2/4.x Developer Location Dallas… https://t.co/AEuaMlhsjd https://t.co/bR1iAp6EqW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Red Tactics Development MS&amp;A Lead – Eng Sys Modeling Simulation 5: Job Description The individual in this role will lead the Adversary Tactics Development Modeling, Simulation, and &amp; Analysis focus area for the Systems Analysis &amp; Simulation team within… https://t.co/6IKvWxsFGW https://t.co/30nSNf979E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer, Platform API: Welcome to Planet. We believe in using space to help life on Earth. Planets mission is to image the whole world every day and make global change visible, accessible and actionable. We build compact satellites and… https://t.co/zQ4M3UrTwX https://t.co/HACcwAt9wY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Organizational Development Specialist:   Organizational Development Specialist (Mountain View, CA) Design, develop, &amp; implement appropriate programs &amp; solutions for Google. #1615.3563 Exp Incl: supp complex client groups or consulting; dvlpg biz… https://t.co/0KtHYCwqpW https://t.co/85EDNdQqyd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Validation hardware Engineer: Validation hardware Engineer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Be able to build out and setup of PC client systems (hardware and software) Experience in Software validation and executing test cases Experience… https://t.co/I1HD1E1MKl https://t.co/yxkqRHsMdQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blue Tactics Development MS&amp;A Lead – Engineer Systems Modeling Simulation 4: Job Description The individual in this role will lead the Blue Tactics and CONOPS Modeling, Simulation, and &amp; Analysis focus area for the Systems Analysis &amp; Simulation team… https://t.co/yzQfpYmewa https://t.co/zuLw3yjNSg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla shares recover as company pushes to hit Model 3 target: SAN FRANCISCO (Reuters) - Tesla Inc shares rose on Thursday ahead of the expected release next week of the company's quarterly auto production data, while a senior executive urged workers at… https://t.co/xIPhlq4iDt https://t.co/2G1DQzP96x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer with Machine Learning Skills: Python Developer with Machine Learning Skills Ref No.: 18-10432 Location: Atlanta, Georgia Role: Python Developer with Machine Learning Skills Location: Washington DC Duration: FTE – Responsibilities The… https://t.co/kJwMWiunY8 https://t.co/vXFpJmG44C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer: O3 World is seeking a Full Stack Developer with a passion for building great tools and compelling experiences like the projects listed in the WORK section of our site [************************** You will work with some of the… https://t.co/WofieTJ1MA https://t.co/08uUKKKndD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Python Developer Ref No.: 18-10920 Location: Des Moine, Iowa Position: Python Developer Location: Des Moine IA Duration: Long Term Contract Job Description: Expert in Python2.x and Python 3.x programming Strong Design and Development… https://t.co/PAMtpeGlg5 https://t.co/ZsaA1VHNXD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[python/c++ Automation developer: Python/c++ Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python Familiar with any… https://t.co/zS342H2ft2 https://t.co/FzjkVLGTW6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Platform Debug Engineer- C++: Platform Debug Engineer- C++ Hillsboro OR Full Time Position Job Description Validate hardware and platform features and track the enabling status of those features in silicon, low-level firmware/software, OS (e.g. Windows… https://t.co/3SYtAnuyPg https://t.co/Z5iVtGgNy3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Security Engineer 5: Continuous Monitoring Compliance Analysis and Reporting Team: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented… https://t.co/YF2yUkT42U https://t.co/OrT56iVSF7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer (Houston, TX): Open Systems International, Inc. (OSI) ************ [******************************************************* is a fast-paced, growing, high technology company, headquartered in Medina, Minnesota. As a world leader… https://t.co/lNcpkHxtkT https://t.co/BDNEVhT6XH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Security Engineer 5: Continuous Monitoring Compliance Analysis and Reporting Team: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented… https://t.co/WH9yu3kDPE https://t.co/fWc2xShT9f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital Network Intelligence Analyst: Company Description ThreatConnect arms organizations with a powerful defense against cyber threats and the confidence to make strategic business decisions. Founded in 2011, ThreatConnect (then called CyberSquared)… https://t.co/2OWjCQ3SIE https://t.co/JEuWaoOPAg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[python Automation Developer: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python Familiar with any one… https://t.co/CxXzotWFU4 https://t.co/7KKMHcFeIT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python/C Developer: Req ID 91829BR Business Title Python/C Developer Group MCIS Location USA VIRGINIA Herndon Clearance Level Needed Secret Category Cyber Job Duties and Responsibilities The Python/C Developer will be a key member of our mission… https://t.co/dR6zzxGrUm https://t.co/TXbrfyw8xD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Developer Client: CMMi Level 5 Company Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: Strong Python (&gt; 2.7 Version) Programming experience is a must. Should have Application Development experience using Python… https://t.co/XnHND4e29O https://t.co/y7sqt2WRQ8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jr Python Developer: Following established written procedures, guidelines and techniques, develops, enhances, modifies and/or maintains applications that support business units or support functions in the Global Markets environment. Software developers… https://t.co/wC9ObWQWaU https://t.co/HTJFMBtwM1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python Familiar with any one… https://t.co/MgxTz7Bbye https://t.co/QouWpyF0PK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: Irvine Technology Corporation (ITC) is a leading provider of technology and staffing solutions for IT, Security, Engineering, and Interactive Design disciplines servicing startups to enterprise clients, nationally. We pride ourselves in… https://t.co/wb4dwfSg5i https://t.co/4SXQbJo47I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Application Developer (Mid-Level to Senior): FullStack Labs is a fast growing software consultancy with offices in Sacramento, CA, Washington, D.C., and Barranquilla CO. We build web, desktop, and mobile applications for businesses, from small… https://t.co/b6KMm0TQy8 https://t.co/UDShqb1N8q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – (3GPP Protocol): Software Engineer – (3GPP Protocol) Santa Clara, CA Full Time Position Job Description: Software engineer with 5 years experience to work on modem interfacing layers and modem interfacing SW communication protocols… https://t.co/YscqtwSU8N https://t.co/gYUgFL6vyp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Urbint engineering is building a cutting-edge data ingestion and machine learning pipeline for exposing the hidden intelligence within urban data. We are a team of close-knit, talented engineers who obsess over problem solving,… https://t.co/TFwLxZZK2w https://t.co/odAJ6jSAju]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[python Automation Developer: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python Familiar with any one… https://t.co/R9CaMmnuyq https://t.co/b3pOf6wsSq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Avaya Python Automation Engineer: AVAYA AUTOMATION ENGINEER WITH PYTHON PROGRAMMING FOR AUTOMATION FULL RELO Avaya CM, SM,CC Elite, BSR, CMS, AES, AIM (SIP), call centers, IVR, CTI, this is a SME out of a large enterprise environment with automation… https://t.co/asV5P16bF9 https://t.co/aEDZ2S8ax6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Backend Software Engineer [Spark &amp; Python]: ABOUT THE ROLE Online video is exploding. The rates of both production and consumption of video content are growing exponentially over time. Our client is at the forefront of the digital video… https://t.co/1vBm8bnc1h https://t.co/vfd68JSEfF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tesla shares dive again, stung by fatal crash, credit downgrade: NEW YORK (Reuters) - Tesla Inc shares fell sharply again on Wednesday, reeling from a credit downgrade of the electric car maker by Moody's Investors Service, federal probes of a fatal… https://t.co/lgoJoFWRjY https://t.co/WQxPPYYYhE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Lead Application Software Engineer – .NET/Python: Position Purpose: Responsible for the entire implementation process and drive definition of business needs Responsible for the entire implementation process and drive definition of business needs… https://t.co/eEjGou45Tp https://t.co/z9SsrMhpj9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Data Analyst: Federal Signal Corporation (NYSE: FSS) provides products and services to protect people and our planet. Founded in 1901, Federal Signal is a leading global designer, manufacturer and supplier of products and total solutions that… https://t.co/BFSAtcX7Kn https://t.co/hfOX2bjIbr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer: Description Are you a talented Network Engineer looking for the next step in your career ? Check out PSS! Position Description PSS, Inc. is actively seeking a Senior Network Engineer to join our growing team located inChantilly, VA.… https://t.co/gbvkugEKI3 https://t.co/iHrEfmUG06]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full-Stack Software Developer: As we build and scale Crystal over the next few years, our product &amp; engineering group is growing along with it. We’re building the largest, most accurate personality platform in the world – it’s a huge project that… https://t.co/YK5aQTEkMc https://t.co/s4q1DZNVoL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Artificial Intelligence Engineer – Python, TensorFLow, Caffe: San Francisco, CA Full-time $175k – $250k Posted Today If you are a Artificial Intelligence Engineer with experience, please read on! We are based in beautiful San Francisco, CA. We are an… https://t.co/iEksevPFdk https://t.co/vxLwzUDQOB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer – Startup/Python/HIPAA Compliant: San Francisco, CA Full-time $140k – $175k Posted Today If you are a Full Stack Developer with experience, please read on! Based in San Francisco we are a digital healthcare startup that is looking… https://t.co/2ly9uyf4C2 https://t.co/ZbUGEcmVQp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Programmer: Python Programmer Location: Hillsboro, OR Position: Contract/Full Time Experience: Any Graduate Job Description: 1-2 Yrs of Scripting experience in Python Good in OOPS concepts Good in Python (or) Perl Programming Able to develop Test… https://t.co/cYS3K6aRbt https://t.co/aIIw9IgCxn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: At SwiftStack, were creating a purpose-built object storage system to help companies store, manage, and access the petabytes of data they generate in the course of their business. We are primary contributors to OpenStack Swift, the… https://t.co/uGxnlkOH3e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Application Developer – Newport News, VA: Web Application Developer Newport News, Virginia Full Time Position The developer will work on several different Automotive diagnostic and configuration tools, as well as a web database application. Job… https://t.co/hUvu6izvEY https://t.co/0NkEqOg5rL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Developer Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: Python programming experience is a must. Should have atleast 2+ Years of experience in Python Application Development Able to understand OOPS concepts… https://t.co/P6Wm340otI https://t.co/2uzcamKbHP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: LawnStarter [*************************** is looking for a Senior Backend Engineer to join our growing product development team. LawnStarter is a fast growing startup with an engineering team that prides itself on high energy,… https://t.co/6xnTXARzCO https://t.co/ZycYW6OK1G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Infrastructure – Mountain View: DataVisor is a next generation security company that utilizes industry leading unsupervised machine learning to detect fraudulent activity for financial transactions, mobile user acquisition, social… https://t.co/kVYv5PmbGI https://t.co/Gfms7db7rt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Python Developer Ref No.: 18-10920 Location: Des Moine, Iowa Position: Python Developer Location: Des Moine IA Duration: Long Term Contract Job Description: Expert in Python2.x and Python 3.x programming Strong Design and Development… https://t.co/mqrHW9HAuL https://t.co/EAB3i93biG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Programmer: Python Developer Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: You should possess at least a Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science, Computer Engineering or related field. A Master’s degree is preferred. Candidate should… https://t.co/Fea7tWAmtw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Software Developer: Careers Center | Python Software Developer Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome page… https://t.co/V2CYk4nvTh https://t.co/I9t5JO763D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer: Python Automation Engineer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Programming Skills – Python (mandatory), Shell Scripting ,OOPS Concepts (Mandatory). Development of Test Script and Execution Hands-on experience in… https://t.co/04NsTHLHJ9 https://t.co/1EzQ401GP3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Security Engineer 4: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the center of everything we do. Join… https://t.co/1991AekHXN https://t.co/bvudFIRqNU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python/C++ Developer: Python/C++ Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position JOB DESCRIPTION: Responsibilities: Design and implement automation solution for BIOS validation test cases (in gherkin and python) Debug the test failures in automation and… https://t.co/kGXP0ydqQ9 https://t.co/OW0fUj5v3h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Security Analyst 4 – Policy Violations: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the center of… https://t.co/s9wgmazEoZ https://t.co/aLJAYvZFfR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python – C++ Developer – Hillsboro OR: Python/ C++ Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using Python/C ++ Familiar with any one Scripting language Python/Perl Strong debugging… https://t.co/uPEPAeCobf https://t.co/FVXHRcSSV3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Security Engineer 4: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the center of everything we do. Join… https://t.co/YNGWS3C44u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Full Stack Software Engineer: Margin &amp; Estimates (Python, PHP): THE ROLE This role will be a key contributor as a FULL-STACK, full life-cycle engineer, capable of working both independently and within in team to accomplish tasks and projects… https://t.co/hWFZ9hokAl https://t.co/I0ydAYHMpU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nvidia halts self-driving tests in wake of Uber accident: (Reuters) - Chipmaker Nvidia Corp said on Tuesday it has suspended self-driving tests across the globe, a week after an Uber Technologies Inc autonomous vehicle hit and killed a woman crossing the… https://t.co/FiGebAt5nI https://t.co/Sj1eqFcdGM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: We are looking for a Mid Level Python Developer for a full-time direct-hire role with our client in North Austin, TX. Responsibilities: Operate and develop within enterprise data environment hosted on AWS. Preferred experience/skills:… https://t.co/5KN1f2HWW3 https://t.co/ZhI7FS0bye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Developer – Windows (C, C++, Python): Req ID : 375321BR Job Code/Title : E2555:Cyber Intel Analyst Sr Stf Job Description : Do you have a passion for low-level code development? Do you pride yourself on solving problems that others think are… https://t.co/fOHJWPJ47C https://t.co/vj79aaVNiQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Lead Application Software Engineer – .NET/Python: Position Purpose: Responsible for the entire implementation process and drive definition of business needs Responsible for the entire implementation process and drive definition of business needs… https://t.co/M9kNsIhLfB https://t.co/3T9aCP9sk5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Job Title: Python developer Duration: Minimum 3 Months Contract with POSSIBILITY of extension) Job Description We are seeking a Python developer responsible for building and maintaining Django and AWS lambda based systems. Your primary… https://t.co/cHnOeAaNyU https://t.co/MXbbNnxrKt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber/Non-Kinetic Lead – Engineer Systems Modeling Simulation 5: Job Description The individual in this role will lead the Cyber/Non-Kinetic Threat focus area for the Systems Analysis &amp; Simulation team within the Global Strategy and Mission Solutions… https://t.co/yl5ZKsPnny https://t.co/QJntzslx8N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Security Engineer, FireEye: Support the FireEye ecosystem including patching, and administering configs with a FireEye AX, CM, EX, FX, HX, NX environment Test FireEye HX Agent configs prior to upgrades and testing FireEye Appliances and validate… https://t.co/U9kQ5Zpd0P https://t.co/pYENNEjxqL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Security Analyst 4 – Policy Violations: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the center of… https://t.co/eCVkASaqk0 https://t.co/nIL6WSdc4J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Security Engineer 4: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the center of everything we do. Join… https://t.co/9RCcYG6QpW https://t.co/UX0uSNsgsJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Security Engineer 4: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the center of everything we do. Join… https://t.co/swOJt631Vq https://t.co/Ttzuxvk6r7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: You should possess at least a Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science, Computer Engineering or related field. A Master’s degree is… https://t.co/oVXLcbKZXw https://t.co/ubvTd1mcjW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Security Analyst 4 – Policy Violations: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we have one goal: to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them achieve their dreams. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the center of… https://t.co/7mgSWIhMqZ https://t.co/j7Cxv6EwQZ]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>