<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Options for Using Slimmers and Trimmers for Weight Loss  http://t.co/Ghsio8Zlcl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Geek Decision Ball - Picks FAIL, WIN, meh, 404 error, LOL, PWND and More! http://t.co/n2JFzFdKGT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The truest test of moral courage is the ability to ignore an insult]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Ray Conniff  http://t.co/6yjLq4zscz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's hard to win a pennant, but it's harder losing one. - Chuck Tanner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They call him "magician".  He walks down the street and turns into a saloon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame: Capture the Flag  http://t.co/gokLI9bJgI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Let's Play: LOTR Ep 1: Meeting the Hobbits  http://t.co/TqbsvD2i39]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Kinds of Strategy Consulting Firms to Avoid  http://t.co/AmLD3gpt6i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read a Review of Heaven is For Real  http://t.co/E2lejuNivs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overview Of Major Children's Shoe Brands  http://t.co/Za2NnXyzDm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Creating Beautiful Gardens with Butterflies - Easy Steps  http://t.co/u34tet6mP9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One day your life will flash before your eyes. Make sure it is worth watching - Mooie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But I'm a rock 'n' roll singer; that's my livelihood, my occupation.  - Little Richard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn the Best Spots for Mountain Climbing  http://t.co/HFzIL8FDon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I play with my cat, who knows whether she is not amusing herself with me more than I with her. - Montaigne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Square meals make round people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Old age means realizing you will never own all the dogs you wanted to. - Joe Gores]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Highland Village, Texas  http://t.co/2CcWYwatXa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Tsingtao Beer  http://t.co/9IBs5Y037a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was sad because I had no shoes, until I met a man who had no feet. So I said, Got any shoes you're not using? --&gt; Steven Wright]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Strategy Consulting Firms: Gaining a Competitive Advantage  http://t.co/El0kn6Co4C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[College isn't the place to go for ideas. - Helen Keller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My life is an open book. With illustrations.  Hugh Hefner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before you create anymore great content figure out how you are going to market it first - Pulizzi &amp; Barrett - Get Content Get Customers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I went through baseball as a player to be named later." - Joe Garagiola]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Pat Benatar  http://t.co/sA7KCmYXgQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Try not. Do, or do not. There is no try. - Yoda, The Empire Strikes Back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plastic surgeons can do almost anything with a nose these days, except keep it out of other people's business]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 4 - Supplements and Herbs  http://t.co/bSY2YLVdH1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The time for action is now. It's never too late to do something. - Carl Sandburg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Skol Beer  http://t.co/blTnLot5Fe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Music of Hot Chocolate  http://t.co/dJHQvtYnOL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Jose Feliciano  http://t.co/KChZWimln9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gluttony is an emotional escape, a sign something is eating us. - Peter De Vries]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 1 - What the heck do I have????  http://t.co/OOKx8g4Jri]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apollo: I will not serve under a man who questions my integrity. Adama: And I won't have an officer under my command who doesn't have any.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A mosquito is just like a child, when it stops making noise, you know it's getting into something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caring For Your New Garage Floors  http://t.co/nw2YXGLjPW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Mod Showcase: Secret Rooms Mod  http://t.co/3FWajXAlBl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just in time for winter - Touch Screen Texting Gloves  - http://t.co/z65cB0ZIHn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NERD?  I prefer the term intellectual Bad ASS!  http://t.co/Osv9Do4r2y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get a Minecraft Enderman! http://t.co/oNPvKGPQhS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you can leave two black stripes from the exit of one corner to the braking zone of the next, you have enough horsepower. - Mark Donohue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Love Unlimited  http://t.co/xAKW5F9TCm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very cool Star Wars windshield sun reflector - may the force be with you!   http://t.co/uYd0v2DnmL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Triple Crown Sports Organization  http://t.co/STrIcYggci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out Why You Should Consider a Creative Writing Degree  http://t.co/qrvAWtGEPo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any manager who can't get along with a .400 hitter is crazy. - Joe McCarthy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The chains of habit are generally too small to be felt until they are too strong to be broken. - Samuel Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Invest in Penny Stocks And Earn Huge Profits  http://t.co/jPwqbeTM8G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How much do you weigh? "Well, according to the charts, I should be six inches taller."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you love James Bond?  Check out these cool t-shirts, hats, stickers and more --&gt;  http://t.co/4ZJVPKQ3C0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who wish to sing, always find a song. - Swedish Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Nike  http://t.co/lQvtvQhFmg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space is the stature of God. - Joseph Joubert]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you chase two rabbits, both will escape. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana’s Lyme Journey - Part 5 - Test Results In!  http://t.co/37IrbXa8wX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feed sparingly and defy the physician. - James Howell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He who opens a school door, closes a prison. - Victor Hugo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We thought you was a toad! - Delmar, O Brother Where Art Thou?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahh Read About Loving Fine Wine  http://t.co/GAwYFYJl6c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space isn't remote at all. It's only an hour's drive away if your car could go straight upwards. - Sir Fred Hoyle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What fun is it being cool if you can't wear a sombrero? --&gt; Bill Watterson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes transform your body language and attitude. They lift you physically and emotionally. - Christian Louboutin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we knew what it was we were doing, it would not be called research, would it? - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As far as I'm concerned, there won't be a Beatles reunion as long as John Lennon remains dead. - George Harrison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rule your mind or it will rule you. - Horace]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More die in the United States of too much food than too little. - John Kenneth Galbraith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because the human history is the history of shoes. The history of places where we ever tread and stand.  - Stebby Julionatan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cheap Divorce Lawyers: Avoiding Exorbitant Legal Costs  http://t.co/W7CAi4dXBh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celiac Disease Requires Gluten Free Foods - Learn More  http://t.co/zpEFDdaIG8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was born in 1950 and watched science fiction and horror movies on TV and was always really fascinated by them. - Rick Baker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool iPhone 4 Review  http://t.co/2tCmyt45R8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never, never, never, never give up. - Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the Lava Lamp - so retro and so cool --&gt; http://t.co/NoBncelDPe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is not a technology.  It's a conversation. And it's happening with our with out you.  Charlene Li - Co-Author Groundswell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My little dog -- a heartbeat at my feet. - Edith Wharton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Lewisville, Texas  http://t.co/z6LX6vvJn0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Fort Worth, Texas  http://t.co/VoIrO1E7Qc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Help with Picking Garage Cabinets  http://t.co/I80STdeBLJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who will wear a shoe that hurts him, because the shoe-maker tells him 'tis well made? - Algernon Sydney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't go into details, I've already told you  more than I overheard myself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I mean, we're lost on an island, running from boars and monsters -- freakin' polar bears.  Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Fun - Bumper Water Boats with Water Cannons! http://t.co/8TUD0UbobS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always wear expensive shoes. People notice. - Brian Koslow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The earth is the cradle of humankind, but one cannot live in the cradle forever. - Konstantin Tsiolkovsky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great History of Johnny Ace: A ‘One of his Kind’ Musical Legend  http://t.co/I60XmFgV71]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dream house is one that cost twice as much as you ever dreamed it would…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What is Chronic Lyme Disease?  http://t.co/7QBIkBObhT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your Attorney Search: Red Flags That Shouldn’t Be Ignored  http://t.co/1ENnljRkiT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of John Lennon  http://t.co/sjTAZ0LMLA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prayer doesn't change things, it changes people and they change things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool - A Cute Fire Extinguisher Lighter With LED Light http://t.co/2xlnerE8Vj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its not so much about the shoes, but the person wearing them --&gt; Adriana Trigiani, Viola in Real Life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Pat Benatar  http://t.co/sA7KCmYXgQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The voyage of discovery is not in looking for new landscapes,  but in looking with new eyes. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To win without risk is to triumph without glory. - Pierre Corneille]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WOW - Very Cool A Sticky Note Wrist Watch! http://t.co/oPxuCwUrbb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ginger Rogers did everything Fred Astaire did, backwards and on high heels - Faith Whittlesey]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>