<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Meal kits account for &lt;1% of US food/beverage sales, but they shouldn't be dismissed by investors or competitors https://t.co/ObePN6JIds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Organic, fresh, natural &amp; free-from claims should not be in FDA's definition of #healthy, @American_Heart says https://t.co/hnvbIQJQf3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out what attracted @Unilever to meal kit company @SunBasketMeals https://t.co/khGh39uRDc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you have a strategy for Sweets &amp; Snacks Expo? @iriworldwide's Larry Levin has a few suggestions on the candy side https://t.co/kXIi9PHo1E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@PepsiCo promises to make at least 2/3 of its global beverage portfolio have 100 calories or fewer from added sugar https://t.co/kjRTq7wZNg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a gaping void of products that are safe for ppl with #peanut #allergies. #Startup Safe+Fair wants to help: https://t.co/s1bKPGWegX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TamarHaspel: Look away from the trainwreck for a moment to read @CSPI's @JaffeGregory on we should regulate #GMOs. He's right. https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will Canada require labeling of #GMO food? https://t.co/F7QMqKANoX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Danone: #Study: Today people are choosing food brands in their own image and which impact on tomorrow's world. https://t.co/s6dEru8LYw…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LizGoodwin: Fascinating research showing need to reduce food waste https://t.co/MlZkd8LJFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former First Lady @MichelleObama says delaying the new Nutrition Facts label is insulting to consumers: https://t.co/p5pxg0juRd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoodNavigatorUS: Are you an ambitious &amp; bright journalist planning your next move? Do you have experience in B2B media? We're hiring! h…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has @WholeFoods failed to rise with the rest of the grocery category? https://t.co/DBXZlE7mjG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out how a strong #deli counter is helping grocers drive consumer interest: https://t.co/U4dLVywiXL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most #ag leaders want to protect #NAFTA but some wouldn't mind a few changes: https://t.co/ttU6uviYXp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@drinkwanku walks fine line between health claims and telling consumers what their herbal infusion is all about https://t.co/hJiHE3gezo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out how removing investor scrutiny will give @WholeFoods breathing space: https://t.co/DBXZlE7mjG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@daiyafoods is more than #vegan cheese -- its multiple cross-category platforms is what attracted new buyer #Otsuka https://t.co/S5lMnQsgni]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is holding #kombucha back from its full potential? https://t.co/V9fQLVGn2e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are #alternativefacts at play in taxes designed to reduce sugar (and as it turns out non-caloric sweeteners)? https://t.co/R83Wppxkrt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does FDA's qualified health claim for macadamia nuts indicate for the agency's view on saturated fat? https://t.co/RMqMvR6ZCs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Despite economic slowdown in Brazil, smaller, more innovative food &amp; beverage brands continue to succeed: https://t.co/2LH53yu2nO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is behind the growing interest in acidic beverages in the US? https://t.co/nfsrp6LKjx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#kosher products have broader appeal than just religious consumers. #vegan #glutenfree ppl also use it as shortcut: https://t.co/KBWw6vDnJA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will #protein infused water be the next big functional beverage? @Protein2o thinks so: https://t.co/cHchTCUEI1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is the secret to success for a top performing grocery store? https://t.co/U4dLVyNTPj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What are the relevant factors in a trademark case? https://t.co/FtXm8c5XuC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want the functional benefits of #kombucha w the approachable flavors of plant-based waters? Check out @drinkwanku https://t.co/hJiHE3xPXY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is next for #NAFTA? https://t.co/ttU6uvAzOX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out how consumers' desire for increasingly acidic food is creating opportunity for pectin: https://t.co/nfsrp6u8UX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@WholeFoods still faces significant challenges even with @amazon's help: https://t.co/DBXZlE7mjG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can big food companies #innovate or should they throw in the towel and simply buy new ideas? Find out at #foodvision https://t.co/pUepKb2HHc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Otsuka scoops up @daiyafoods https://t.co/S5lMnQsgni]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Implementing @GuidingStars nutritional rating system could boost retailers' health halo in the eyes of consumers https://t.co/NSNNFiGs2Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#kombucha sales grew 41% last year. @revivekombucha explains why: https://t.co/V9fQLVoLDE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should sin taxes designed to reduce sugar consumption also apply to non-caloric sweeteners? https://t.co/R83Wppxkrt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Despite saturated fat, #FDA gives macadamia nuts a qualified health claim of heart health https://t.co/RMqMvQPodS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@BetterBeanCo moves prepared beans from the center of the store to the fresh section:https://t.co/S2Eib505wl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The trade down in Brazil  is at 75% vs 58% in the US. @EWatsonWrites investigates what this means for CPG industry https://t.co/2LH53yu2nO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out the potential for kefir in the US: https://t.co/nfsrp6u8UX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out how becoming #kosher certified can boost sales &amp; spark consumer interest in this wk's #podcast w @OUKosher https://t.co/KBWw6vDnJA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out what is behind @Protein2o's explosive growth: https://t.co/cHchTCD3Qt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How much protection can private label expect when it comes to appearance? https://t.co/FtXm8c5XuC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How big is #kombucha's potential in the US? @revivekombucha weighs in https://t.co/V9fQLVGn2e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As competition between retailers heats up, @GuidingStars could give some players an edge: https://t.co/NSNNFiGs2Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Non-caloric sweeteners are getting caught up in the war on #sugar https://t.co/R83Wppxkrt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#macadamia nuts are now officially heart healthy ... under specific circumstances https://t.co/RMqMvR6ZCs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does it take to become an iconic household brand? https://t.co/S2Eib5hGnT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does Brazil's bleak economic outlook mean for the food industry? https://t.co/2LH53ycrwg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales of #kosher products in the US are on the rise. Find out  why and who is buying them in this week's #podcast https://t.co/KBWw6vDnJA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Packaging is just as important as product innovation bc if consumers don't identify w branding they won't buy it, Jason Cohen #foodinnovate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Much of the 92% mortality rate of food and beverage launches can be attributed to failure to raise funds says @healthybrandman #foodinnovate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Innovation doesn't have to be all things to all ppl, says Jason Cohen. Sometimes innovation is more successful if it targets a select group]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#innovation is about solving a problem in a fresh new way and cater to an unmet consumer need says CEO of @BareSnacks #foodinnovate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How will the creation of meat in a lab and not from a farm change consumers' views on 'processed' food? https://t.co/Pkjq5S4i71]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As online shopping grows, it is predicted 1 in 3 people will buy groceries online this year: https://t.co/dagsazJrKf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are 'processed' ingredients really as bad as everyone makes them out to be? Some say no: https://t.co/Pkjq5S4i71]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out how Lidl stands apart from the competition in the US: https://t.co/bn3cVUa0u2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Store to door grocery delivery just got bigger with retail chain Meijer expanding in the space https://t.co/dagsazrQlF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many view 'processed food' as an enemy to avoid. But how processed is too processed? @EWatsonWrites finds out https://t.co/Pkjq5S4i71]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[41% of shoppers want healthier options that also make them feel full longer: https://t.co/dLYTVcfmW2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The term innovation is tossed about these days, but what exactly does it mean in the food/beverage space? https://t.co/P4qxypfy01]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consumers are finally embracing chilled prepared meals: https://t.co/96a9r6b9e3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do you create a winning brand on Amazon? https://t.co/hAbmpR3WQj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Temptation and higher prices are two barriers blocking consumers from eating healthier https://t.co/dLYTVcwXNA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can 100% juices make 'no added sugar' claims? https://t.co/U6xFRAeI2E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What tools are brands using to get to market faster? Find out at our free online Food Innovation forum July 19: https://t.co/P4qxyoXX8t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Discover how green banana flour can help clean up your label by replacing gums: https://t.co/7WivRCgAAc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales of specialty water grew 75% from 2014-16, according to @SpecialtyFoodFn. Find out why in this week's #Podcast https://t.co/4kVmnMWOWP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What should meat grown in a lab vs on the farm be called? https://t.co/h44mk28lk3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is the extent of opportunity in the chilled prepared food segment: https://t.co/96a9r5TxPt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More than a quarter of 18-24 year olds are cutting back on eating meat: https://t.co/dLYTVcfmW2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out how Amazon offers a launchpad for #startups in packaged food and beverage categories: https://t.co/hAbmpR3WQj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A new legal twist in the war on sugar: https://t.co/U6xFRAeI2E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can big food still innovate? Find out at our free online Food Innovation forum July 19. Check out details &amp; register https://t.co/P4qxyoXX8t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out how @pnuffcrunch extended its shelf life by creating a clean label snack https://t.co/EmIm0obana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kellogg is trying to create a more rational distribution system. Check out the details: https://t.co/X5GqBsUQqj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This #4thofJuly consider how @Beekman1802Boys epitomize the American spirit: https://t.co/oIBx3p6TZJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does it take to grow a chicken in a lab instead of on a farm? https://t.co/w2HM3ICFhv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is the "ethnic aisle" in the grocery store passe? Retailers consider new ways to stock globally inspired products https://t.co/b9dGU9JBgU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So-called clean meat grown in a lab instead of a farm offers potential for customized cuts https://t.co/fEc6IHXQli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Discover the latest #glutenfree solution: https://t.co/7WivRCybrK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 cos in  bottled #water category discuss what makes them standout &amp; where the category is going in this #podcast: https://t.co/4kVmnNeqlp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Already No. 2 in overall #yogurt category, @chobani wonders if the launch of new smooth line could bring it to No.1 https://t.co/Djlwsv24R2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clean #meat, or that which is raised in a lab and not on a farm, does not need pre-market approval, says @DWTLaw rep https://t.co/h44mk28lk3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Almost a quarter of Americans say they plan to cut back on animal #protein, according to @Nielsen https://t.co/JhRVTAbk90]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it possible to preserve a #startup mentality &amp; still scale? @revivekombucha says yes, &amp; here is why its important https://t.co/MXpqoSNtXT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why are #plantbased 'dairy' products not succeeding like beverage counterparts? @RippleFoods has an idea &amp; solution https://t.co/pZUoxjI4ou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What about #organic food appeals specifically to parents? https://t.co/W5XsWPhmak]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Enhanced' sugar from @DouxMatok could help cos cut the sweet stuff 20-40% wo impacting taste https://t.co/CPKLHFbh8Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is MyoTechnology's fermented mushroom ingredient a game changer for plantbased protein? https://t.co/TcEapAnHiT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is eating breakfast on-the-go less healthy than sitting down at the table in the morning? https://t.co/BZscAQywd1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Necessity is the mother of invention &amp; for @abbysbetter need for healthy nutbutter led to a line of on-trend spreads https://t.co/uu64p8OFCZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@QuornFoods expands beyond the freezer aisle in the US to the chilled section for increased convenience: https://t.co/eNU0Vo43Yz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FDA pushes back the new Nutrition Facts labeling requirements, but not nearly as far as industry wanted https://t.co/hZwQqghqNf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FDA will beef up training for  #FSMA inspectors during unexpected reprieve https://t.co/Z0ZoHnIiX2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out why this app offers consumers cash back for buying healthy, #organic snacks ... and how it can help brands: https://t.co/npwmDBYjNE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New coalition argues proposed anti-dumping changes to NAFTA could be 'traumatic' and move trade backwards https://t.co/iOAtsMfmjh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How will voice activated ordering on Amazon impact impulse purchases of #snacks and #sweets? https://t.co/2gAKpE8Eku]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just bc juice is green doesn't mean it is healthy, says @HarvestSoul. Rather, it needs #fiber: https://t.co/jOqxrNoq9p]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>