<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Foghat  http://t.co/DSsUk5gGwM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool Hands Free Umbrella! http://t.co/D95zMYqnnx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Lynyrd Skynyrd  http://t.co/qaEeHGSbo4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Isaac Asimov  http://t.co/ArdWr2UGCA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If people don't want to come out to the ball park, nobody's gonna stop 'em. - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Early History of Hamburgers  http://t.co/pmx6ABMg3m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Whispers  http://t.co/kgGLyNR3gF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The human body is the best work of art. --&gt; Jess C. Scott]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science fiction, outside of poetry, is the only literary field which has no limits, no parameters whatsoever. - Theodore Sturgeon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never, never, never, never give up. - Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Domestic Adoption - A Helping Hand To A New Life  http://t.co/dCzavoos5Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Building Experts - Get Some Free Tips  http://t.co/o4aISENVK1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is A Derivative?  http://t.co/tZZOUEbW3v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are so many things you can learn about. But you'll miss the best things if you keep your eyes shut. - Dr. Suess]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Increasingly, the mass marketing is turning into a mass of niches - Christ Anderson Author of The Long Tail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's basically the same, just darker. - Alan Kulwicki, on racing Saturday nights as opposed to Sunday afternoons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Very Unusual Hamburgers  http://t.co/nm0Rrv6T34]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the way society functions. Aren't you a part of society? - Kramer, Seinfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Hamstring Rehab  http://t.co/06NKg1DbUX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today's recording techniques would have been regarded as science fiction forty years ago. - Tony Visconti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Little House on the Prairie – An American Classic TV Series  http://t.co/OSnXN3OQA1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The process of growing old is a question of mind over matter. If you don't mind, it doesn't matter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Play is the only way the highest intelligence of humankind can unfold. - Joseph Chilton Pearce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the darkness of the world cannot put out the light on one small candle. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to find somebody and you want to be married and you want to have children, don't make it a rock star. - Stevie Nicks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Increasingly, search is our mechanism for how we understand ourselves our world, and our place with in it.  John Battelle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Media are tools.  Real time is mindset.  David Scott - Marketing Strategist - Author of The New Rules of Marketing and PR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His head is getting too big for his toupee...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What is Facebook Gaming?  http://t.co/Wav1mBSTfC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here Kitty Kitty Kitty! - Tony Stewart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome biking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the biking lovers in your life!  http://t.co/LfYnEfLU6U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Square meals make round people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome - Hopside Down Glass - Upside Down Beer Bottle Glass - Cool! http://t.co/8b2gIcYbKY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Use SEO on Multiple Websites to Drive Traffic in Your Direction  http://t.co/TUwdEtCExb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've destroyed my feet completely but I don't care. What do you really need your feet for anyway - Sarah Jessica Parker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Visiting  relatives are like fish. They begin to stink after 3 days!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The woman who wants a perfect husband will have to grow him and should allow at least thirty years for the process]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Out the Top Football Teams of the 2011-2012 Season  http://t.co/XokDHbfJFh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dammit, man! I'm a doctor, not a physicist! - Leonard 'Bones' McCoy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Fitness Alternative Energy Devices  http://t.co/O7HkTbUl7v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fool and his money are soon accepted into the highest social circles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some of the worst mistakes in my life were haircuts --&gt; Jim Morrison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think Jennifer knows how to get pregnant. Leah Remini on rumors that she was trying to convert JLO to Scientology to help with fertility]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we're growing, we're always going to be out of our comfort zone. - John Maxwell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Help with Planning Garage Flooring  http://t.co/AnVNbjkRCA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter what, the very first piece of social media real estate I'd start with is a blog.  Chris Brogan - New Marketing Labs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was always attracted to science fiction movies. - Tina Turner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent Blue LED light stemmed Umbrella - a unique take on the Umbrella! http://t.co/upgs58LBTh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn from yesterday, live for today, hope for tomorrow. - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Social Networking for Seniors  http://t.co/0JD5i5TkRM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Musings of a Homeschooling Dad (sort of)  http://t.co/Jndv2whg69]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you blame others, you give up your power to change. - Dr. Robert Anthony]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What you don't know won't hurt you but it provides a lot amusement for other people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Small Dogs Can Make Great Pets - Picking the Right Breed  http://t.co/rOHZM8yBfC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Damita Jo  http://t.co/IknEWtiFMz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Giant Squids - Hunters of the Deep  http://t.co/pdtnsyUGxf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So now I'm left with cigarettes, and I'm trying to scrape that off my shoe and then I'll be done. - Diane Lane]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When in doubt, wear red. - Bill Blass]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Rufus Thomas  http://t.co/iLYMSSLk1d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Flying Alarm Clock - COOL!  http://t.co/f4QGW5DFE0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the The History of the Chambers Brothers  http://t.co/bVjHQy6spT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I'm hungry, I eat. When I'm thirsty, I drink. When I feel like saying something, I say it. Madonna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's no need for a piece of sculpture in a home that has a cat. - Wesley Bates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I went through baseball as a player to be named later." - Joe Garagiola]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Julius LaRosa  http://t.co/IMnGzIB4BV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is A SERP exactly?  http://t.co/C1P8UfTT20]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Skiing in Canada - learn more!  http://t.co/vNC5w5RMCH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone can get dressed up and be glamorous, but it is how people dress in their days off that are the most intriguing Alexander Wang]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we knew what it was we were doing, it would not be called research, would it? - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful Women Prefer Nerds! A Real Man's Guide on How to Find, Date, and Romance the Perfect Woman! http://t.co/EnraueQxFD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Adoption Part II - the Bulgaria Phase  http://t.co/mHQ5bE3p8k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting Overview of Top 10 International Beers  http://t.co/clr9ExCwo7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Awesome BookBook for iPhone- Combine Wallet and Phone and Style  http://t.co/fX9gNRTxQL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fascinating history of solar power - read on!  http://t.co/HD1Sw3uhKy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Don Henley  http://t.co/aBxARFzK3Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't steal second base and keep one foot on first. - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calling upon my years of experience, I froze at the controls. - Stirling Moss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Locate Your Garage Space Before Installation Of Cabinets  http://t.co/wE3d7XodCO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I die, I'm leaving my body to science fiction. - Steven Wright]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Arthur Alexander - The Unknown Legend  http://t.co/xVulirgtUN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Jay Ferguson  http://t.co/dwtwPeKAbE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of KC and the Sunshine Band  http://t.co/6c4DcHAf2q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm a rock and roll singer.  -  Adam Ant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The process of growing old is a question of mind over matter. If you don't mind, it doesn't matter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful Women Prefer Nerds! A Real Man's Guide on How to Find, Date, and Romance the Perfect Woman! http://t.co/EnraueQxFD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have the end in mind and every day make sure your working towards it - Ryan Allis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do... or do not. There is no try. - Yoda - The Empire Strikes Back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hops Holster 12 Can Ammo Pack - Beer Anywhere!  http://t.co/qRhrwmL3zQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft MiniGame QuakeCraft: Victory was in Sight!!!!! http://t.co/yHJrlPcJIA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dammit, man! I'm a doctor, not a physicist! - Leonard 'Bones' McCoy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is a Creative Writing Degree for You?  http://t.co/P9JdFmcF63]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is that which discloses to the wise and disguises from the foolish their lack of understanding. - Ambrose Bierce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to David Bowie  http://t.co/XyIQYhlFaM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is the transmission of civilization. - Will Durant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To err is human, to forgive, canine - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's so timid he wouldn't open an oyster without first knocking on the shell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is A Derivative?  http://t.co/tZZOUEbW3v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See you in another life, brother. - Desmond Hume, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Trini Lopez    http://t.co/uR0vV27JrV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fool and his money are never without friends]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>