<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[[{quot;IDquot;:null,quot;Titlequot;:quot;Sr. Software Engineer: [{‘ID’:null,’Title’:’Sr. Software Engineer Sr. Software EngineerLocation: Salt Lake City, UT The Sr. Software Engineer is responsible for providing technical leadership to individual team… https://t.co/s1BawrO8S1 https://t.co/O4n9L4LjaU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Developer: Job ID #: 13677 – Job Category: Software Engineering – Employment Type: Experienced Professionals – Division: IPG – Department: IPG Strategy – Primary Country: USA – Primary Location: Seattle (WA) We are an Equal Opportunity Employer and… https://t.co/8UIZ92VykB https://t.co/beA24Fx2DE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Traveling Superintendent – Retail TI: Dallas, TX Full-time $0k – $0k Posted Today We are a commercial general contractor headquartered in Texas, doing business across the country. Our projects are both ground up and renovation and are mostly within the… https://t.co/c3GmUmb0QL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advanced Real Estate Specialist: Advanced Real Estate Specialist Posted Date 1 week ago(6/13/2018 10:57 PM) ID 2018-31776 Job Location USA-VA-Fairfax Required Clearance No clearance Category Facilities/Real Estate Management Employment Type Full Time… https://t.co/FxyL6RmGS8 https://t.co/koi1WDyjp0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seller Risk Analyst, Chargebacks: Seller Risk Analyst, Chargebacks San Francisco, CA Full-time Company Description We believe everyone should be able to participate and thrive in the economy. So we’re building tools that make commerce easier and more… https://t.co/iNxA3fKfjp https://t.co/rpu2Skq8YL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Executive Support Analyst: Under Armour is all about performance. Because what we make empowers athletes in every form to push themselves, to turn good into great, and to stay hungry for whatever comes next. And this is exactly what we expect from each… https://t.co/ETEKJhPpsM https://t.co/LWVZIo8JMT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laser-Shooting Planes Uncover the Horror and Humanity of World War I: Instead of digging into Belgium's Ypres Salient, archaeologists used lidar laser scanners to map the war zone and turn up some remarkable finds. https://t.co/lmGv7dMOdO https://t.co/Ropo0LPCPa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sourcing Project Manager Centralia, MO: Corporate Overview Hubbell Incorporated was founded in 1888 and has grown into an international manufacturer of quality electrical, lighting and power solutions with more than 75 brands used and recognized around… https://t.co/L4SbBqYyct https://t.co/zeB2cdI2ly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Project Manager Power Plant Decommissioning: A pioneer in groundbreaking scientific and engineering developments since the 1960s, TRC is a national engineering, consulting and construction management firm providing integrated services to the power,… https://t.co/LHFgbOkiiw https://t.co/VrxZCBjZEv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Industrial Hygiene Project Manager: A pioneer in groundbreaking scientific and engineering developments since the 1960s, TRC is a global consulting, engineering and construction management firm that provides technology-enabled solutions to the power, oil… https://t.co/RsxtCxUGWu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YouTube Debuts Plan to Promote and Fund 'Authoritative' News: The video platform is less focused on getting rid of conspiracy theorists than on trying to elevate journalism it considers valuable. https://t.co/dSOMxNY7Pc https://t.co/xWUsL99O27]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Implementation Specialist: The company where you can make an impact and bring value. Job Summary: Aeros, a Cultura Technologies Company, provides integrated software solutions for animal agricultural industries specific to financial and flock decision… https://t.co/q0QbZPxyhD https://t.co/6JhOTUM1oc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Infoshare Systems, Inc. (Mission Viejo, CA) needs: Project Manager: supervise multiple employees, provide project mgt. throughout the life of project: Sr. Application Developer: design, develop &amp; test software solutions using JAVA, J2ee,… https://t.co/A6KJj4Pk5W https://t.co/JYQFpgR7on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager at Children s National Health System: Job Description 41092BR Senior Project Manager at Children’s National Health System Senior Professional Job Description As a Senior Project Manager, you will be responsible for numerous complex… https://t.co/AD9E0Jxy6h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer in Test: Department Development – US Employment Type Employee Minimum Experience Mid-level Software Developer in Test About us INVIDI Technologies Corporation develops products and services for addressable television advertising. Our… https://t.co/nRWuZi9eXf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JAVA Developer Junior: JAVA Developer – Junior ======================= Req #: ******Location: Chantilly, VA USJob Category: Information TechnologySecurity Clearance: TS/SCI with PolygraphClearance Status: Must Be Current Job Description CACI has an… https://t.co/CBh9n6eHSc https://t.co/CzmsMte62v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java full stack: Java full stack philadelphia, Pennsylvania – United States Job Start Date – 06/18/18, Posted Date – 06/18/18 Primary SkillsJava FullstackTax TermsC2COverviewclient – comcast skype for consultant who have previous comcast experience else… https://t.co/GgIzrmk4bd https://t.co/53YwihHN8j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Security Engineer (Cygnacom): Principal Security Engineer REQ# 18000036 Position Overview: Cygnacom Solutions is currently looking for motivated and technology-oriented associates to join our security and information technology consulting team… https://t.co/SoOuhtpZZb https://t.co/aP3sybWS9j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manager Embedded Software Engineer 2:   Job Description – Manager Embedded Software Engineer 2 (18010175) Manager Embedded Software Engineer 2 Requisition ID : 18010175 Location : United States-Maryland-Baltimore US Citizenship Required for this… https://t.co/CWcGQMnVlZ https://t.co/PkTgNkaBbT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roborace's Self-Driving Car Takes On England's Swankiest Track: The Robocar is headed to the Goodwood Festival of Speed to take on the event’s famed hill climb. https://t.co/DW4jOrvvcr https://t.co/1IyceaAhsH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Informatica Developer: Prestigious Enterprise Company is currently seeking a Sr. Informatica Developer. Candidate will be responsible for the design, development, maintenance and production support for various Data Mart applications. Candidate… https://t.co/g6RVT6TY4m https://t.co/yBMyzk329u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud DevOps Engineer: Requisition ID 2017-32264 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level None Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description *This position is not for immediate hire. If you would like to be considered in… https://t.co/YfDafmNh4R https://t.co/hS7YLqMirg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Technical Project Manager: Senior Technical Project Manager, Federal Employee Program in Washington, DC – CareFirst Looking for Health Insurance? Visit ************* – Home – Jobs at CareFirst – Our Teams – Talent Network – Why Work at CareFirst –… https://t.co/8dcHzHq3NM https://t.co/yp7AEzc43F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP-Solutions-Architect: SAP SOLUTIONS ARCHITECT PRINCETON, NJ Required Skills: – Minimum of BS degree in Information Systems or a closely-related field. – Complete understanding of the architecture of SAP applications in a large SAP environment. –… https://t.co/okyvHlyqmn https://t.co/C5UyMtRjQ8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Big Data Developer: Verisk Analytics Job OpportunitiesView Job Careers | Contact Verisk HomeAbout VeriskConferencesPressInvestorsBlog U.S. Job Search Login to Job Section My Candidate Home Help with Job Application Non-U.S. Job Search Careers… https://t.co/KfE8ijgGjv https://t.co/OTP74JyjEo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Construction Project Manager: Heggem-Lundquist Paint Company Construction Project Manager Denver, CO 80223 POSITION OVERVIEW: The Project Manager (PM) is responsible for understanding and managing projects from Requests for Information through the… https://t.co/Ih0MQECP6c https://t.co/tZFObhLyBB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Technical Lead: Java/J2EE Technical Lead Ref No.: 18-26204 Location: syracuse, New York Hi, Hope you are doing great!! We are currently looking to fill urgent full-time permanent job positions as Java/J2EE Technical Lead with the client based in… https://t.co/dYUHC49sWN https://t.co/dHdFiVuMzp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Job ID 2017-59851 Program Posting Miami-Corporate Regular / Temp Regular Full-Time Category Professional Non-Clinical Location Miami Zip Code 33131 Official Job Title Project Manager State Florida Overview Why VITAS Healthcare and What… https://t.co/Hr7e22XICY https://t.co/Lhs0g7XzGu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer, Online Services: Software Developer, Online Services =================================== Have you ever thought about working with an amazing organization, surrounded by amazing, scary smart, people and making the world a better place?… https://t.co/ShwBwuOFdS https://t.co/6OSQykw587]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Requisition Title Sr Associate Systems Technical Support Engineer: Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome page… https://t.co/YmQUALEyna https://t.co/vujRLCmcCF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer About the Job Duration: Long term contract Location: Denver, Colorado Pay rate: Hourly Job ID: 2018-0028-UIM-064 Overview Datasoft Technologies, Inc. is seeking a Java Developer for a client in Denver, Colorado. All… https://t.co/08zh7fo4Wv https://t.co/xQoqSKJfEP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Facebook’s Rise Fueled Chaos and Confusion in Myanmar: The social network exploded in Myanmar, allowing fake news and violence to consume a country emerging from military rule. https://t.co/7FhG4olEQW https://t.co/nGQC435xyW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FIN Director IT Investment: FIN Director – IT Investment Innovate to solve the world’s most important challenges Provide partnership and leadership to Corporate Finance, Enterprise IT organization to create increased visibility into operational strategy… https://t.co/RCHgNDKLT1 https://t.co/7A8NUGMCkV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solution Architect – Teamcenter – Major City Western U.S.: **Solution Architect – Teamcenter – Major City Western U.S.** Multiple Locations:United States; San Diego, California; Cypress, California; Portland, Oregon; Seattle, Washington; Los Angeles,… https://t.co/pEzOO6U4HF https://t.co/GQ5GQNDAiI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Business Systems Analyst: Sr Business Systems Analyst – About Us – Career Development – Values &amp; Culture – Corporate Headquarters – Community Involvement – Featured Jobs – Store Team – Store Leadership – Restaurant Team – Tire Care &amp; Mechanical –… https://t.co/bO1oMl87KH https://t.co/Sko2JL39HM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flattened Fluids Help Scientists Understand Oceans and Atmospheres: By squeezing fluids into flat sheets, researchers can get a handle on the strange ways that turbulence feeds energy into a system instead of eating it away. https://t.co/jlOmXJnUz2 https://t.co/Uugf29PPAu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Business Analyst: Job Title Systems Business Analyst State Illinois Description Connection Services has a fantastic opportunity through our technical staffing division in Downers Grove, IL. We are looking for a SystemsBusiness Analyst. This is a… https://t.co/VEECIUPbP4 https://t.co/HfXTpbyYMz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Project Manager- Building Automation – Saint Louis: **Associate Project Manager- Building Automation – Saint Louis** Locations:Saint Louis, Missouri Job Family: Project Management New Search Apply English (US) **Job Description** **Division:**… https://t.co/mVVQcXlNgR https://t.co/1acYYp2qir]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Future of Former EPA Chief Scott Pruitt's Anti-Science Legacy: Pruitt's replacement might be more effective at gutting environmental protection than Pruitt himself. https://t.co/LHarDGn5bq https://t.co/dokRJz5tjy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineers: Kastech – Home – About us – Services – Products – Blog – case studies – Careers – Contact careers Are you looking for a great career opportunity? Current Openings Cheers !! Be the first person to step into the innovation team. Looking… https://t.co/Aibziq2RHp https://t.co/odj4DWpzEP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An Astronomer Explains Black Holes at 5 Levels of Difficulty: His specialty: The structure of the universe. (That's the official name of his research group at NASA.) https://t.co/YLnMHC78pB https://t.co/LZCKZzhdp7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Vulnerability Researcher: Req ID 97639BR Business Title Software Vulnerability Researcher Group MCIS Location USA VIRGINIA Vienna Clearance Level Needed Secret Category Intelligence Job Duties and Responsibilities ManTech Mission, Cyber and… https://t.co/l0BBUfcdiW https://t.co/NjMJqM8xsZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist: Costa Mesa, CA Compensation Unspecified Posted Today If you are a Data Scientist with experience, please read on! What You Will Be Doing Our ideal candidate will have expertise working with large data sets to explore, interpret, and… https://t.co/8F8QIbt5ih https://t.co/8GoTgPOfYy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Multimedia Developer: Careers Center | Multimedia DeveloperPlease Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome page Returning… https://t.co/MCjEh4gROK https://t.co/uxYpKYrrH8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Defense of the Vegan Hot Dog: One carnivore's advice: When a tofu dog snuggles up to your tube steak on the grill, don’t be a jerk about it. https://t.co/EFsMc2MtDc https://t.co/5oOootIVMW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waterfront Technical Support: Job Description The selected candidate will be responsible for providing direct technical and administrative support to multiple waterfront programs. The Waterfront Technical Support role provides coordination and technical… https://t.co/Rw4kxoKP1N https://t.co/QjdQMKMS8v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UI Developer (Angular/AngularJS/ReactJS): UI Developer (Angular/AngularJS/ReactJS) Ref No.: 18-01710 Location: SFO Downtown, California Position Type: Contract Start Date / End Date: 07/03/2018 to 12/03/2018 Job Description: Responsibility – Lead UI… https://t.co/wlO2berwGM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Radical As Ever, Boots Riley Takes On the Tech Boom: With his feature directorial debut, 'Sorry to Bother You,' Riley has stormed Hollywood in a second act no one expected. https://t.co/UppvznHpXb https://t.co/BrSgeMHx3I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Fire Flowers' Dazzle in Gorgeous Photos of Japanese Fireworks: Makoto Igari pays tribute to the country's unique pyrotechnics. https://t.co/8IEChha10Y https://t.co/hz5SR5HBNM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Performance Engineer: Job Description What you’ll be doing… Customers expect our networks to perform at a high level all the time. That’s where you come in. You will investigate, evaluate and resolve network and data performance issues to ensure… https://t.co/ah5J9CjZOW https://t.co/pDd6gSWMLz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NETWORK ENGINEER III: Network Engineer III, Sprint Corporation, Overland Park, KS. Research, design, plan, develop and/or evaluate new, advanced network technologies. Apply at https://t.co/aAz73rZJdX, Req # 243924BR. Sprint is a background screening,… https://t.co/xCHb4Vw3d6 https://t.co/44bIU5OVat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Fox Stands Alone, a Look at *Red Dead Redemption 2*, and the Rest of the Week in Games: There's more to gaming than the newest title—catch up with our weekly recap. https://t.co/jzAuEKSv54 https://t.co/sSruO2uSMD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager- Highways: Job Description Project Manager- Highways Project Manager- Highways (******) About UsAt HDR, we specialize in engineering, architecture, environmental and construction services. While we are most well-known for adding beauty… https://t.co/LJljINo3w7 https://t.co/lA5p719QCv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Management, Enterprise Platform Solutions : SAP Controlling (CO): Project Management, Enterprise Platform &amp; Solutions : SAP Controlling (CO) Ref No.: 18-30793 Location: Cary, North Carolina Project Management, Enterprise Platform &amp; Solutions :… https://t.co/1Hk6zsWXns https://t.co/nBtsqYuVaL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At DefCon, the Biggest Election Threat Is Lack of Funding: While hackers at the DefCon security conference dismantle voting machines, officials stress the need for means to act on the results. https://t.co/nNWacSm1qA https://t.co/ozC9zBD0LH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer : 18-01706 Ref No.: 18-01706 Location: Bellevue, Washington Akraya is looking for a Software Engineer for one of our clients. If the job description below is a fit, please apply directly or call Rahul Shribas at… https://t.co/A7YLHS8RvM https://t.co/Inx4kJeHBt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SDET (Software Development Engineer in Test): SDET (Software Development Engineer in Test) Ref No.: 18-30630 Location: Seattle, Washington Title: SDET (Software Development Engineer in Test) Location: Seattle, WA 9 to 12 months Job description: 1. 3- 7… https://t.co/acJHPuFgfW https://t.co/ys4uesWLwq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Development DBA: Overview Job Description: Contribute to the development of technical design decisions involving the database. * Work collaboratively with Application Architects, Project Managers, and Business Owners to develop the database model… https://t.co/GL640Xfy9a https://t.co/vd0O8xD8Ib]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Quality Assurance Analyst: Senior Quality Assurance Analyst Princeton Posted Jul 12, 2018 – Requisition No. 68096 Are you interested in joining a team that maintains Bloomberg’s status as the world’s leader in execution management and trading… https://t.co/DsXOu0Kns6 https://t.co/EwEBj5bT8F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Machine Learning Can Identify the Authors of Anonymous Code: Researchers have repeatedly shown that writing samples, even those in artificial languages, contain a unique fingerprint that's hard to hide. https://t.co/VzmRDHBRLk https://t.co/WRU6uQYOEe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Network Solutions Architect (SDN, SD-WAN, DC): Philadelphia, PA Compensation Unspecified Posted Today Leading solutions provider partnered with EMC, NetApp, VMware, Citrix, Microsoft, &amp; Cisco is in growth mode and looking for Principal / Senior level… https://t.co/zBBlSf5YFi https://t.co/RcqLAOVLB0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer in Test 3: Digital Experience Engineering – Software Engineer in Test 3 At Asurion, we don’t just redefinewe reinvent. We began by establishing a culture that rewards results and isn’t confined by a hierarchy. As a result, we have… https://t.co/3fEcuEvnNT https://t.co/V34HyGO6iZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Sr. Developer: Java Sr. Developer job | Cognizant job in Rolling Meadows, Illinois, United StatesJob Details | Cognizant – ************* – Industries – – – Services – – – Latest Thinking – – – About Cognizant – – Careers Home – Get To Know Us – Our… https://t.co/CSW7LKockv https://t.co/YHiDEJmG57]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Tweet About Hacking During Defcon Gets a Google Engineer in Trouble: Matt Linton says he was asked to leave Caesars Palace Thursday night after a tweet about an “attack” was reported to the police. https://t.co/Em4vSmwhi3 https://t.co/Nz7G1Dnx37]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering: TECHNOLOGY Data Domain, LLC (a Dell Technologies Company) is seeking a Software Principal Engineer at our Santa Clara, CA facility to develop software solutions for external clients based on detailed specifications from technology/ systems… https://t.co/gjPlPLX1SD https://t.co/fgGcv5J2Vd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bugs in Mobile Credit Card Readers Could Expose Buyers: Card readers used by popular companies like Square and PayPal have several security flaws that could result in customers getting majorly ripped off. https://t.co/GwLGuVXUqX https://t.co/vWRxnYmXWx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology: TECHNOLOGY Palo Alto Networks, Inc. is seeking applicants for the following positions in Santa Clara, CA: SW QA Eng(s) (#180) &amp; Sr SW QA Eng(s) (#474):Dvlp &amp; execute SW test plans for ntwk security firewall prods; Tech Support Eng(s)(#327):… https://t.co/th5ExeZTbF https://t.co/BJHLWw4iN7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAS programmer: Sagarsoft Inc has multiple job openings for the following positions to work in Glastonbury, CT and / or various client sites throughout the U.S: Must be willing to travel and/or relocate. Senior ETL Software Engineer to design, develop &amp;… https://t.co/j1EaoCMaJM https://t.co/HLLQFYvYoO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: SOFTWARE DEVELOPER, IBM Corporation, Research Triangle Park, NC: Own architecture, design, and development of complex and critical tasks. Identify, quantify, and delegate tasks to engineers. Adapt and embrace new technologies, tools,… https://t.co/FkUAOmZM8K https://t.co/PFROLLhwB3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Experienced Project Manager: Requisition ID *******Posting Date 03/24/2018Category ServicesLocation Camp Hill, Pennsylvania | United StatesSchedule Full-timeEmployee Status Day JobEEO Tagline: DXC Technology is EEO F/M/Protected Veteran/ Individual with… https://t.co/PtQYc09t76 https://t.co/2bXAs9VQe9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer, Software Engineering (JAVA Developer): Cardinal Health at Home is a best-in-class provider of medical supplies to patients in the home. It is comprised of two separate operating segments: Edgepark, a leading direct-to-consumer (DTC) medical… https://t.co/1JKXgM0rtL https://t.co/kRblZ8lNG6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Spanish Ghost Towns Left By the 2008 Financial Crisis: An estimated 3.4 million homes are currently unoccupied in Spain thanks to the country's great housing bust. https://t.co/7sWd3hDNY3 https://t.co/td0rBglPMD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RD Javascript FrontEnd Engineer: R &amp; D Javascript Front-End Engineer Jobs Home Our Culture Search Jobs Country Information Students and Graduates – Sign Up For Job Emails – Sign in Search jobs by job title or keyword or location or job ID # this Job R &amp;… https://t.co/GWBIlVTwKU https://t.co/RGebtZMmva]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Network Solutions Architect (SDN, SD-WAN, DC): Parsippany, NJ Compensation Unspecified Posted Today Leading solutions provider partnered with EMC, NetApp, VMware, Citrix, Microsoft, &amp; Cisco is in growth mode and looking for Principal / Senior level… https://t.co/hDwf8TQFdT https://t.co/WUMSMqspdl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intelligence Operations Specialist 4:   Job Description – Intelligence Operations Specialist 4 (18015356) Intelligence Operations Specialist 4 Requisition ID : 18015356 Location : United States-Virginia-Quantico US Citizenship Required for this Position:… https://t.co/FjASd56FvL https://t.co/WFU4FXkv9p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Designer – Referral Partnership: Are you an independent web developer with a large network of clients who process e-commerce transactions? Do you design web pages that require an e-commerce solution? Are you looking for proven opportunities to… https://t.co/Bj8fZrNrez https://t.co/XdvAMxYFek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Oracle Developer: TECHNOLOGY Cyber security software dvlpmt, database admin &amp; diagnostic positions available at SonicWall, Inc. (Milpitas, CA): Sr Oracle Dvlpr (REQ #227); Test Sr Engr (REQ #228); Test Staff Engr (REQ #229); Software Dvlpmt Staff Engr… https://t.co/EzU24cALfe https://t.co/KSmgfmZ9vW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hacking a Brand New Mac Remotely, Right Out of the Box: Researchers found a way to compromise a Mac the first time it connects to Wi-Fi, potentially putting scores of enterprise customers at risk. https://t.co/QcfFqAXeO0 https://t.co/wtdG2q24RB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Semiautonomous Cars Have Flaws. That's Why They Need Tests: The Insurance Institute for Highway Safety tested features in cars from Tesla, BMW, Mercedes, and Volvo and found they all had issues. Here’s where safety rankings would come in handy. https://t.co/PeCzlhED4m https://t.co/T6ezGUwPKZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Princ Analyst, Functional- Storage SMEE: Contract: I2TS 3 Position: Sr Analyst, Functional – Subject Matter / Functional Expert (L3) Location: Charlottesville, VA GENERAL SUMMARY: GDIT is seeking candidates to support the US Army Intelligence and… https://t.co/eQYhGttqIG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aftermarket Senior Database Administrator: About GoDaddy GoDaddy powers the world’s largest cloud platform dedicated to small, independent ventures. With nearly 17 million customers worldwide and over 75 million domain names under management, GoDaddy is… https://t.co/nrru36wW2F https://t.co/lO2QoYvfCN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Engineering the Climate Could Mess With Our Food: Scientists look at the eruptions of Mount Pinatubo and El Chichón to give us a glimpse at how geoengineering might affect a critical global system: agriculture. https://t.co/2S0SYnpa1n https://t.co/9doy4AKQgw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Job Description Project Manager (WD***********) What you will love about Johnson Controls: We’ve been dedicated to protecting the environment since our invention of the electric thermostat in 1885, which provided a fundamental shift in… https://t.co/ohtZg5mi2E https://t.co/GBHYYEGrcT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Business Intelligence Visualization Engineer: Location US-NC-Raleigh Posting date 7 hours ago(7/31/2018 4:12 AM) Job ID 61983 Category Software Engineering Company description At Red Hat, we connect an innovative community of customers, partners,… https://t.co/cttnJ6U4LI https://t.co/AG8BwqUzd7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alexa Machine Learning Science Team – Software Engineer – Cambridge, MA (Kendall: Job Description Alexa Machine Learning Science Team – Software Engineer – Cambridge, MA (Kendall Square) Location: US-MA-Cambridge Job ID: ****** Company: : **********… https://t.co/iDo9gwr9e9 https://t.co/NoyuI3paKw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager: Job Description Turner &amp; Townsend is GROWING! We are looking to hire a Senior Project Manager to be a part of a team that leads projects of varying sizes, depending upon the complexity and technical requirements of the project.… https://t.co/tbp7cfTTmI https://t.co/WeNLkShFEG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can Elon Musk Really Take Tesla Private?: The Tesla CEO tweeted he had secured funding for a buyout of the electric carmaker, and market madness ensued. https://t.co/aTbfKeCU83 https://t.co/7iCbkxCJ96]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scale API Wants Self-Driving Cars to Share Data: If data-labeling companies like Scale API have to re-do the same kind of work for multiple autonomous driving companies, the really important stuff—the weird edge cases—might get missed. https://t.co/ILTCfIDNKp https://t.co/vvXHkYL6oj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SDN DevOps Engineer FT Summer Co op: Join the team that’s transforming the way the world communicates ! Nuage Networks from Nokia has the innovation power, capabilities and global scale to bring a unique combination of ground breaking cloud technologies… https://t.co/D2ZhClaMgF https://t.co/oX3WLJgwBp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Reporting Analyst Online Reporting System: Job Description – Data Reporting Analyst – Online Reporting System Job LocationUS-DC Job ID9395 Job LocationUnited States CategoryProject Management Overview The American Institutes for Research (AIR) is a… https://t.co/zY3gF2WfK2 https://t.co/YdgjTvOs2o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test Leads: Test Leads Ref No.: 18-29576 Location: Hastings, Michigan Test Leads- Exp- 4-8 Years Work Authorization- Citizen, GC, GC EAD, L2 EAD, TN ‘UAT Lead: Hands on experience with GW PC Experience in analyzing Book of Business. Strong Testing Skills… https://t.co/XHzsBuF66f https://t.co/HkpKCWehtN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Account Executive, Senior (Mandarin speaking): Account Executive, Senior (Mandarin speaking) Job Location US-CA-Newark Req No. 2017-2256 Category Sales/Presales Overview We have an immediate opportunity for a Senior Account Executive on our Sales team in… https://t.co/kwDpq4MuK6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could Ketamine Be the New Prozac?: The club drug might be the next big depression treatment—but how best to use it remains unknown. https://t.co/fIMFtrE2cS https://t.co/Lt7q2DSy0P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Construction Project Manager: Minneapolis, MN Compensation Unspecified Posted Today If you are a Construction Project Manager with experience, please read on! What You Need for this Position We build some of the most modern and state of the art buildings… https://t.co/BKBS70Mids https://t.co/dQq1FkQ8cc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Performance Engineer: Job Description What you’ll be doing… Customers expect our networks to perform at a high level all the time. That’s where you come in. You will investigate, evaluate and resolve network and data performance issues to ensure… https://t.co/5rUyXv1mxV https://t.co/lXBotTPTvH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Application Developer: Job Description Make a Difference Every Day with Team Applied The people of Applied are making a difference every day through innovation and a commitment to help safeguard and protect what matters most. With first-to-market… https://t.co/ByhL3jZQCZ https://t.co/P2MRqlpdtB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer – Referral Partnership: Are you an independent web developer with a large network of clients who process e-commerce transactions? Do you design web pages that require an e-commerce solution? Are you looking for proven opportunities to… https://t.co/Yrw6hDx7o4 https://t.co/qxNrL0sonJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Telemedicine Could Help Fill the Gaps in America's Abortion Care: A growing body of research suggests that medication abortion could be offered without any in-person interaction at all. https://t.co/Hu7ZBXx7Yl https://t.co/Y7QJRFuUDX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Questions About 'PUBG'? Ask PlayerUnknown Himself: Also known as Brendan Greene, the game's creator helps out fans in our newest episode of "Tech Support." https://t.co/xlSVDNz6zl https://t.co/oPMG3ATbtT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Assistant Vice President: COMPUTER: DB GLOBAL TECHNOLOGY INC. seeks an Assistant Vice President in Cary, NC to design functional process solutions based on bus. req’mnts, across a variety of bus. areas &amp; in line w/ overall bus. priorities. Req’s:… https://t.co/a7WLGscmke https://t.co/EFExLQS5oR]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>