<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Boston police Black History Month tweet heavily panned - CBS News https://t.co/pAgoNPc7V6 https://t.co/smhc5KCTAL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Miles from Winter Olympics, three Americans remain detained in North Korea - Fox News https://t.co/ulCzHLfTEZ https://t.co/pu7iJfs69f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michigan officer shot during barricaded gunman incident - KWQC-TV6 https://t.co/7VMuU7vaOm https://t.co/3Dipk0dmqc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ruth Bader Ginsburg says #MeToo has 'staying power' and can withstand backlash - https://t.co/bPgwx84BLZ https://t.co/bt79oXmqIn https://t.co/23LWiy8Nji]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Major advertiser threatens to pull ads from Google, Facebook over trash content - Fox News https://t.co/P55dLTUeZ6 https://t.co/k5x6HUpzdi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Detroit police officer shot, two women killed during ongoing barricaded gunman situations - WXYZ https://t.co/YBy1K8U2pJ https://t.co/L00smtfSFj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pence raises prospect of talks with North Korea amid 'intensified' pressure - Reuters https://t.co/vLUeLfebcb https://t.co/kDaAgaahG3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mike Pence raises prospect of US-North Korea talks - https://t.co/bPgwx84BLZ https://t.co/FmZygYhXap https://t.co/xaEsUI1V7I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who Is Joseph Nickell? Kentucky Gunman Shoots Parents, Girlfriend Before Killing Self - International Business Times https://t.co/dCwlgE2doQ https://t.co/b6tpCoXsab]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[North Korea heads for diplomacy gold medal at Olympics: analysts - Reuters https://t.co/r7JLyvTRAA https://t.co/ikr9yIvHiG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HR #tech The most popular IT Job site in the US https://t.co/kzpCgnRGxN #jobboard https://t.co/R5gk4XqrnF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lesbian teacher fired from Miami Catholic school after marrying 'love of my life' - ABC News https://t.co/TMWszqSAZM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After the Olympics, the real games with North Korea begin - Charleston Post Courier https://t.co/5wgsJTm2GL https://t.co/VNuiHMBccb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jamie Anderson wins her second Olympic gold in women's snowboard slopestyle - USA TODAY https://t.co/YUl7zALNqZ https://t.co/G5xTlnLRHP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump declares state of emergency for American Samoa - Fox News https://t.co/glcaFiRK1n https://t.co/wHSosGm4BJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Puerto Rico hit with partial blackout after power plant explosion - Fox News https://t.co/rs3103pBxu https://t.co/xvXYbicjxv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Northern Puerto Rico in dark after explosion starts fire at main power substation - Washington Times https://t.co/kPnpJkeh8c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adam Rippon dazzles with performance, wardrobe on ice - USA TODAY https://t.co/j0uDUnWqDO https://t.co/b2TMmZsltG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Southwest cancels all flights at Midway Sunday afternoon - WLS-TV https://t.co/d6fIOWi3HG https://t.co/ZhsupsUwFK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Report: 49ers' Reuben Foster arrested in domestic violence case - https://t.co/6vxkJsXYvO https://t.co/g2WLNHmYdj https://t.co/xEShpHFyU4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's big infrastructure plan has a lot of detail on everything but how to pay for it - Washington Post https://t.co/ES0zL1tBiN https://t.co/RxDNsh2PGF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GOP Rep Jordan: 'Big Concerns' With Paul Ryan Over Spending Increase - Breitbart News https://t.co/rWeYpqNqU9 https://t.co/1WaAu6CV2Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schiff says he'll meet with FBI to discuss Democratic memo redaction - CNN https://t.co/5VeHg78GIs https://t.co/77n7djV8ra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Devin Nunes created a partisan news website to hype his memos - Salon https://t.co/CLiKsp0tNc https://t.co/xJYUm6kKlh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harvard names Lawrence S. Bacow as 29th president - Harvard Gazette https://t.co/7K2vrEexoT https://t.co/z6uHGGTR2Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[International Space Station could be privatized under Trump administration plan - New York Daily News https://t.co/FqLvsKhfrq https://t.co/cTpoJt3XA0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Devin Nunes continues the war on #FakeNews with his own alternative news site - Vox https://t.co/gXukdS5dJE https://t.co/UwOw5lnpF3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[City of Waukegan Declares Snow Emergency Sunday - NBC Chicago https://t.co/6WMjvKXjV5 https://t.co/IdEyuBqfbK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kim Yo Jong Fascinates, And Puzzles, In South Korea - NPR https://t.co/tdOuQx4U7j https://t.co/g1cGMYjiEH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wardrobe malfunction mars routine of South Korean ice dancers - Yahoo Sports https://t.co/EeYTrPpNRq https://t.co/DglYCg8UY3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Immigrants in NH labor force - WMUR Manchester https://t.co/3SIv39tk1X https://t.co/oVcLrMdmui]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump 'Not Sure' If Israel Seeks Peace With Palestinians - CHANNELS TELEVISION https://t.co/qmHOjzuWVu https://t.co/8Bu3cegGup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pakistani human rights champion Asma Jahangir dies - Reuters https://t.co/XPa5msxVBk https://t.co/rOgdeliDQc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kim Jong Un's Sister Heads Home After Whirlwind SKorea Visit - U.S. News &amp; World Report https://t.co/52LrskNOJD https://t.co/TDsEobHeVL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NBC forced to make apology after Japan comment draws anger in South Korea - BizPac Review https://t.co/SOIxfPAfyI https://t.co/KWAy10G1ZS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kim Yo Jong Fascinates, And Puzzles, In South Korea - NPR https://t.co/UyWMrbcomC https://t.co/woprT3Gr1g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As Olympics shift to sports, what on Earth just happened? - Washington Post https://t.co/s9qsKQYcMX https://t.co/Kukx9h8Y3q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian jet 'crashes' after Moscow take-off - BBC News https://t.co/R3i2ZkZ5PT https://t.co/o91bmNQipL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK threatens to cut off aid cash to charities after Oxfam sex report - Reuters https://t.co/D2f7ZDWHj6 https://t.co/w11crgZn0v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NBC apologizes to Koreans for Opening Ceremony remarks about Japan - Yahoo Sports https://t.co/9d2V2QRhzE https://t.co/wiB32xu2tc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As Olympics shift to sports, what on Earth just happened? - ABC News https://t.co/ngy9TnsX4i https://t.co/7IVRWowIk2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HR #tech ☆★☆ https://t.co/LOqMQLanFR ☆★☆ https://t.co/nt8St6v0m4 #jobboard https://t.co/l9UoIvoHCJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Japan and South Korea, the Friendly Foes of East Asia - New York Times https://t.co/GiMpjupSer https://t.co/wh4NGlY3GY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[North Korea sent cheerleaders to the Olympics. Here's what they're saying. - Washington Post https://t.co/cV3zyeL6A6 https://t.co/rTQ1hJupQl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Capping years of criticism, Purdue Pharma will stop promoting its opioid drugs to doctors - Los Angeles Times https://t.co/HowFs5LBz7 https://t.co/IRtlmposdZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[North Korea sent cheerleaders to the Olympics. Here's what they're saying. - Washington Post https://t.co/sdFf1z8fou https://t.co/oiWNGO7hll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At least three killed in Grand Canyon helicopter tour crash - New York Daily News https://t.co/bkk4xKmE66 https://t.co/BN36UQLAqA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['A horrific murder spree' in Johnson County leaves five dead, including the shooter - Lexington Herald Leader https://t.co/CycFNn17Wu https://t.co/ZnpbSrdvnm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Slain deputy remembered as a 'great hero' at funeral - SFGate https://t.co/ro7242SwJM https://t.co/pfLDjnwHDb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 11 cities most likely to run out of drinking water - like Cape Town - BBC News https://t.co/wrnPXIHlMP https://t.co/rUXiwtFMaX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Carlos Cordeiro Wound Up Winning US Soccer's Presidential Election - Sports Illustrated https://t.co/T8ybUpZfQY https://t.co/5O7V3HR0T9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Police: Washington man raped dying woman, texted photos - https://t.co/Ldpz6Ih1Ld https://t.co/xzVDcqvose https://t.co/Gll36eYEtj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why did the GOP vote for a budget-busting spending bill? Because voters don't seem to care. - Washington Post https://t.co/ClfqbiyNK0 https://t.co/I19Q01MOOV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israel strikes Syria after downing Iranian drone - PBS NewsHour https://t.co/Lq90H3KMLC https://t.co/SCaUUmRpw4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top official departs 'rudderless' railroad safety agency - Politico https://t.co/0cdgVmsCgr https://t.co/FSQ7uKsGTk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[North and South Korea Compete as One for the First Time in Olympic History - TIME https://t.co/oT3ALl94iq https://t.co/8u9wPeIJg8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the case of the FISA memos, transparency is national security - The Hill https://t.co/AhZFQgVE9A https://t.co/Yc1sUUqUM5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's block of a memo is a block of checks and balances - CNN https://t.co/6Gh3iTUMRU https://t.co/bjvTcG0C8q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[North Korea's Kim Jong Un invites South Korea's president to Pyongyang - Washington Post https://t.co/ajtYfnmyxs https://t.co/wLb3l0CwkK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MLB Hot Stove: Cubs reportedly sign Yu Darvish to bolster rotation - https://t.co/osIrRJ0zvJ https://t.co/nlKtBlFFam https://t.co/LOqNMiHpqv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jóhann Jóhannsson, Oscar-Nominated Composer, Dies at 48 - Billboard https://t.co/bjl8PmbZ0k https://t.co/QtLNfT3LwG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[North Korea's Kim Jong Un invites South Korea's president to Pyongyang - Washington Post https://t.co/nOhZ1KlCpt https://t.co/FtZKNFfvkN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ohio police officer killed another critically injured while responding to call; suspect in custody, reports say - Fox News https://t.co/IhJz4T3Fje https://t.co/soDsBajywS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kim Cattrall Slams Sex and the City Co-Star Sarah Jessica Parker: "You Are Not My Friend" - E! Online https://t.co/8GWKt9L4Fl https://t.co/18cc82Ds3R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump will not declassify Democrats' current memo, White House says - CBS News https://t.co/0BmGpfySok https://t.co/F7qVev8DaK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kim Jong-un Invites South Korean Leader to North for Summit Meeting - New York Times https://t.co/qDlXnuZU5B https://t.co/HV9pEi24AN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump blocks release of Democratic Russia memo - Politico https://t.co/pxQc2jC4UE https://t.co/G55sA7HTo5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump blocks release of Democratic Russia memo - Politico https://t.co/aoGckzVniV https://t.co/EMGbsJUkNa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House seeks revisions to Dems' FISA rebuttal memo, halting release - Fox News https://t.co/aX3Ny5TSVm https://t.co/DR1pRX5mK1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[North Korea invites South to first official talks in 10 years - The Hill https://t.co/ZmWR5p8HcM https://t.co/VxmQEm1OIb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vice President Pence shows up at short-track, and so do some singing North Koreans - USA TODAY https://t.co/w5JFjMXedt https://t.co/pRS8GJYse2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kim Jong-un Invites South Korean Leader to North for Summit Meeting - New York Times https://t.co/IpJMvOMRS5 https://t.co/xwH4uLj6nc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kim Jong-un Invites South Korean Leader to North for Summit Meeting - New York Times https://t.co/vTWSYzrElY https://t.co/GFphreuu7d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kim Jong-un Invites South Korean Leader to North for Summit Meeting - New York Times https://t.co/pCaOzyXmOZ https://t.co/KoAM701olc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meet the Korean War veterans returning to South Korea for the Winter Olympics - CNBC https://t.co/vyzFfcT7ZY https://t.co/1l6A21DxNV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Modi in Ramallah LIVE: India and Palestine's relations have stood the test of time, says PM - Hindustan Times https://t.co/8APz0z1bhb https://t.co/osruI1RQmP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Illegal immigrant found guilty in murder of 2 deputies - New York Post https://t.co/JH4MGuKjK0 https://t.co/UCPqgin1ol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#HR #tech IT Recruiters https://t.co/kwLqiWsvYj #jobboard https://t.co/N44p5vFgfv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Officer slain, deputies wounded, suspect dead near Atlanta - Fox News https://t.co/nbM6qZ91GE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Syria war: Israeli fighter jet crashes under Syria fire, military says - BBC News https://t.co/iDV8PnmHaU https://t.co/KvviDArWeH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South Korea's Moon hosts North Korean talks as Pence keeps up pressure - Reuters https://t.co/X3kfKehbxn https://t.co/40F4AToqIq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mike Pence doesn't stand for North Korea athletes during opening ceremonies - CBS News https://t.co/Jtcn4YMSLr https://t.co/Bpo2A4oBrK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Autopsy Finds Gunman Who Killed 58 People in Las Vegas Took Anti-Anxiety Drug - U.S. News &amp; World Report https://t.co/k9ZBPwlVzn https://t.co/ESYOIueQIV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Autopsy Finds Gunman Who Killed 58 People in Las Vegas Took Anti-Anxiety Drug - U.S. News &amp; World Report https://t.co/sKWcOXy3QD https://t.co/ar576tRMNO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump will not immediately release Democrats' memo on FBI surveillance - Washington Post https://t.co/JDchAm43zn https://t.co/BQl4XS9prn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump Joins With Russian Bots to Trash Mark Warner on Twitter - Mother Jones https://t.co/trSjnNM1jl https://t.co/DsEwg0wYsr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No. 3 Official at the Justice Department Is Stepping Down - New York Times https://t.co/6rN8J5eV1O https://t.co/2CuMLdQdZc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman may have given birth in an airport bathroom, and left the baby behind, police say - Duluth News Tribune https://t.co/4pUtr8A5WX https://t.co/FdI8dsxQrh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This flu season is the worst in nearly a decade — and it's not getting better - USA TODAY https://t.co/RY2EsO7TDm https://t.co/79OYemwQlp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#apexopus Cost of denying an employee extended leave? $4.5 million https://t.co/22vtJp4Ls9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Hill's 12:30 Report - The Hill https://t.co/GXquxjZqN5 https://t.co/XXn73Yj6VX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WATCH: US mom abandons newborn after giving birth in airport bathroom - Independent Online https://t.co/cvv1nZBWYN https://t.co/CJAjw6y21o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LIVE UPDATES: Officer dead, 2 deputies wounded in Henry County shooting, officials say - Atlanta Journal Constitution https://t.co/s3oastfOs8 https://t.co/Zs5kv3Qy9D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#apexopus Nearly a third of companies will pass tax law savings to staffers: Here’s how https://t.co/AMYmlBOKq3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian nuclear weapons engineers caught minting blockchange with supercomputer - Ars Technica https://t.co/enJCvXt3dT https://t.co/S2eXSujp7e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former Trump administration officials, from Comey to McCabe - Fox News https://t.co/H7G52JTNxi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supreme Court on the verge of reversing some of its old decisions - USA TODAY https://t.co/9eGBiTAk9v https://t.co/ZOLJUHa6Kn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former Virginia Tech student pleads no contest to murder of teen he met online. - Washington Post https://t.co/VosTCNowu3 https://t.co/IVTJUm85Iw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waymo and Uber reach a surprise settlement - The Verge https://t.co/DUx3iDcVSm https://t.co/tzJYPK8z3K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breaking with tradition, Trump skips president's written intelligence report and relies on oral briefings - Washington Post https://t.co/jCYMZ6TD8L https://t.co/8dkaHkH4wv]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>