<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA["Why we love our coaches! "Tell everyone what you want to do & someone will want to #help you do it." - W. Clement Stone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Discover your support system, Discover the people who step up with a helping hand, Discover what makes you smile, Discover your #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You just can't beat the person who won't give up." - Babe Ruth #determination]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A good #friend is a connection 2life - a tie 2the past, a road 2the future, the key 2sanity in a totally insane world" Wyse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every person who ever achieved #greatness crossed the bridge of self-doubt. via @AffirmationSpot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing limits achievement like small thinking; nothing expands possibilities like unleashed #imagination.~William Arthur Ward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The power of someone believing in you that you can do it, can mentally change your game" #coach #friend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Training gives me proof" John Litei #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Any #runner interested in maximizing potential must study the mind-body connection or their journey will not be complete" Ryan Hall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["An overflowing lust for #life...the most attractive of all personality characteristics" Matt Fitzgerald]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don’t ask what the world needs. Ask what makes U come #alive & go do it. Because what the world needs is people who have come alive~Thurman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you have to ask us why we run, you'll never understand. #run via @successfulrun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can feel either sore or sorry tomorrow... Your #choice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A helping hand up is another step forward.” via @Kcancer #charity #runners]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never saying never, keeps everything possible!” via @AffirmationSpot #run #life #love #friends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Man is so made, that whenever anything fires his #soul, impossibilities vanish" via @runnersworld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["#Running is the ultimate faith healer, restoring belief not only in oneself but life’s possibilities." ~ via @BartYasso]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Stadiums are for spectators. We #runners have nature and that is much better" Juha Vaataine via @running_junkie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Live #life--don't let life live you." --Marshall Faulk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In the end, all we have are memories; make as many as you can.” via @SexCigarsBooze #life #love #friends #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Each of us has a #gift...use it!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I bet this sounded like a good idea when you signed up 6 months ago." #MarathonCheeringSigns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Free Nipple Massages" #MarathonCheeringSigns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You have great stamina. Call me." #MarathonCheeringSigns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Naked cheerleaders 1 mile ahead"
-mile 25 #MarathonCheeringSigns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you feel tired it's because of too much ass kicking #MarathonCheeringSigns via @anahiboesch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Do you still think this is a good idea?" (sign at mile 20) #MarathonCheeringSigns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[0.2 down only 26 to go!!! via @purpleplaid #MarathonCheeringSigns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Run faster or Kiss me #MarathonCheeringSigns via @mcktll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You proved them all wrong. #MarathonCheeringSigns via @terrainLA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I like the way you go fast" #MarathonCheeringSigns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You are NOT almost there" #MarathonCheeringSigns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Training is the opposite of hoping." - Nike #makeithappen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There isn't a person anywhere who isn't capable of doing more than he thinks he can. ~Henry Ford via @LJ3000]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most effective way to do it, is to do it.~Amelia Earhart via #run #train #do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Doubters can suck it" (saw this at mile 23 -- definitely #inspired me!!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Don't put a limit on anything. The more you #dream the farther you get." - Michael Phelps via @SoCalNerium]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Somebody who's got nothing to lose can be very, very dangerous." via @Maccanow #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hold fast to #dreams, for if dreams die, life is a broken winged bird that cannot fly - Langston Hughes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You don't stop #running because you get old, you get old because you stop running" McDougall, Born to Run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The way to know #life is to love many things.~ Vincent Van Gogh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A comfort zone is a beautiful place, but nothing ever grows there." via @AffirmationSpot #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Choose to live your life #love #friends #live #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you want to #win a game, you have to teach. When you lose a game, you have to learn. -Tom Landry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not every race is perfect, not every run is perfect. Getting out there, is perfect]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Friends... they cherish one another's hopes. They are kind to one another's #dreams ~Henry David Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If a window of opportunity appears, don't pull down the shade." - Tom Peters #secondchance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Goals are not only absolutely necessary to motivate us. They are essential to really keep us alive." -Robert Schuller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Happiness is pushing your limits and watching them back down" New Balance #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Man is so made, that whenever anything fires his #soul, impossibilities vanish" via @runnersworld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["#Running is the ultimate faith healer, restoring belief not only in oneself but life’s possibilities. ~ via @BartYasso]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I don't think I would have been such a good #runner if I hadn't enjoyed it." -Greta Waitz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The power of people that believe in you & #encourage you to chase your dreams is a tremendous #gift"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Follow your #bliss and the universe will open doors where there were only walls." ~Joseph Campbell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When someone tells  #you "it can't be done," it's more a reflection of their limitations, not yours.” via @DrAndyBaldwin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Charity #runners have no finish line unless a #cure is found]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The race does not always go to the swift, but to those who keep on running. Unknown via @brentnhunter #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Athlete by #heart, #runner by choice." via @bretra88]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["People who think I can't do, just make my do possible" unk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I am still standing at the end of the #race, hit me w/a board &knock me down, b/c that means I didn’t run hard enough~Jones #Houston2012]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the love of the marathon ~ Olympic Trials #Houston2012]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is full of folks telling you no, you can’t, you’re not qualified, you should move on #Dream #Goforit via @JoshCox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We all have #ability. The difference is how we use it." -Stevie Wonder]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Often hear someone say I’m not a real runner.We are all #runners, some just run faster than others.I never met a fake runner via @BartYasso]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Find your love, your talents, your #passions and embrace it. Don't hide behind happiness. Experience it!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Challenges are #gifts that force us 2 search 4 a new center of gravity. Don’t fight them. Find a different way 2 stand ~@Oprah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#run, gather your friends, and make a difference together #runners #giveback]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Relish the bad #training runs. Without them it's difficult to recognize, much less appreciate, the good ones."~Pat Teske]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surround yourself with #positive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's more to a #race than being faster than last time.” via @nuuutymel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No extra points for #running fast on easy days! Save energy for hard workouts. via @runnersworld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It happened when it was supposed to ~The Curious Case of Benjamin Button]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And I hope you see things that startle you. I hope you feel things you never felt before ~ Benjamin Button]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["But then you find your inner strength, and realize you're capable of so much more than you thought." -Arthur Blank #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Your present circumstances don't determine where you can go; they merely determine where you start." Nido Qubein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A #race time is just the final page of a book. It means very little without knowing the story leading up to it. #running via @runwicked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Friends who believe in you when others do not, friends who tell you can do it when you fear otherwise, friends are a gift" #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Mental toughness is to #physical as four is to one."~Bobby Knight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a powerful driving force inside every human being that once unleashed, can make any #vision, dream or desire a reality~Tony Robbins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Life is meant to be lived. Take risks. Feel passion. Discover love. Run free.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Doubters can suck it" (saw this at mile 23 -- definitely #inspired me!!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Somebody who's got nothing to lose can be very, very dangerous." via @Maccanow #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hold fast to #dreams, for if dreams die, life is a broken winged bird that cannot fly - Langston Hughes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You don't stop #running b/c you get old. You get old b/c you stop running." -Jack Kirk, the Dipsea Demon #BornToRun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life has so many roads, why do you limit yourself to just one” via @poetjanetdawson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Running isn't what I do. It's who I am & as I've learned, nothing, not even cancer, can take joy of running away. Touzeau via @RunMikeRun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We live in a Universe where risk is the cost of reward. To risk nothing, is to lose everything via @AffirmationSpot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There are many wonderful things that will never be done if you do not do them." ~ Charles D. Gill via @AffirmationSpot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The biggest adventure you can ever take is to live the #life of your dreams." - Oprah Winfrey #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Don't let your victories go to your head, or your failures go to your #heart." -Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine's Day &gt;&gt; Sex & the #Marathon: Why runners make better lovers http://t.co/AZumkuZ6 via @cowhateration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I'd rather lose myself in passion than lose my passion."Jacques Mayol #friendship #love #run #life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Running has the power to change your life. It will make you fitter, healthier, even happier. -Selene Yeager via @runnersworld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Valentine's Day &gt;&gt; Sex & the Marathon: Why runners make better lovers http://t.co/AZumkuZ6 via @cowhateration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Who runs for #pleasure never gets tired" Dean Karnazes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Passion cannot be instilled; it is either there or it is not" Joan Benoit Samuelson via @LJ3000]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When u're breaking down w/ur insides coming out, that's when u find out what ur heart's made of -Switchfoot  #marathon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beginning is sometimes the hardest step to the start line]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Running opens doors we may have thought were long closed. It opens doors to the impossible]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Running makes me stronger. Not just physically, but also mentally]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>