<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA["If fear is the great enemy of intimacy, love is its true friend." Henri Nouwen
Read more at: https://t.co/jvSY4CU3M1 #quote #inspiration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To invent, you need a good imagination and a pile of junk. - Thomas Edison #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winning is the most important. Everything is consequence of
that."
- Ayrton Senna #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have courage. It clears the way for things that need to be. - Laura Fitton #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are pirates! @ Puget Island, Washington https://t.co/xudxlbNllG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tell more people that you love them. You never know how much they might need it. - Chris Brogan #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I believe in Christianity as I believe that the sun has risen: not only because I see it, but because by it I see everything else.C.S. Lewis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Raise your words, not voice. It is rain that grows flowers, not thunder. - Rumi #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When you are winning a war almost everything that
happens can be claimed to be right and wise."
- Winston Churchill #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there any one so wise as to learn by the experience of others? - Voltaire #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The mighty Columbia River!

#freshair #columbiariver #friends #love @ Puget Island, Washington https://t.co/wHmEGJdO8u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Debbie reading to Taryn! @ Puget Island, Washington https://t.co/eFfTTFcmD0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are some people who listen to you when you talk and there's other people who just wait for their turn.- Bryan Kramer #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've never seen a problem that was solved by only complaining about it. - Steve Keating #quote #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The purpose of fear is to raise your awareness, not to stop your progress. - Steve Maraboli #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We are what we repeatedly do. Excellence, then, is not an
act, but a habit."
- Aristotle #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Connect enthusiastically. Give relentlessly. And lead bravely. Do that, and the future is yours! – Ted Coine #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotter done again, 10,000 steps!

#walk #walkabout #exercise @ Cathlamet, Washington https://t.co/fngWfxmmZO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Princess cowgirl Talia! @ Puget Island, Washington https://t.co/urUOBWVbum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My walk today!

#columbiariver #walk #freshair @ Cathlamet, Washington https://t.co/W3LLKjafND]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consistently investigate what gives other people energy. Be the fan that fuels it. - Darren Rowse #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beware that the detours in your life don't turn into destinations. - Tim Fargo #quote #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to my top interactors! @DownlandCrafts @ARBraun @FamilyLegacyAdv via #SocialJukebox https://t.co/g9O0oSxImJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep your goals in front of you and your fears behind you. - Tony Robbins #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to my top interactors! @terrylancaster @QuoTweety @DivinaCourtney via #SocialJukebox https://t.co/g9O0oSxImJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Setting goals is the first step in turning the invisible into the visible. - Tony Robbins #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Wealth obtained by fraud will dwindle, but whoever earns it through labor will multiply it" Proverbs 13:11 (HCSB). #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your life will never improve unless you start making daily improvements. - Lewis Howes #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Success without honor is an unseasoned dish; it will satisfy
your hunger, but it won't taste good."
- Joe Paterno #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are all born ignorant, but one must work hard to remain stupid. - Benjamin Franklin #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The person that said winning isn't everything, never won
anything."
- Mia Hamm #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no such thing as a minor lapse of integrity. - Tom Peters #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Wealth obtained by fraud will dwindle, but whoever earns it through labor will multiply it" Proverbs 13:11 (HCSB). #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Connect enthusiastically. Give relentlessly. And lead bravely. Do that, and the future is yours! – Ted Coine #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@QuoTweety @JusticeEagan @dpistulka @DarrylRealistic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The big question: what are we going to do for humanity? Serving others is the essence of leading at a higher level. - Ken Blanchard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you can dream it you can build it. If you can build it, you can live it. - Pam Moore #quote #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Raise your words, not voice. It is rain that grows flowers, not thunder. - Rumi #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Optimism is the one quality more associated with success
and happiness than any other”
- Brian Tracy #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most people will never accomplish the long term great because they settle for the short term good. – Reg Saddler #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is like photography. You need the negatives to develop. - Unknown #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The most practical, beautiful, workable philosophy in the
world won't work - if you won’t"
-Zig Ziglar #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Self-Esteem begins and ends with you. The more you know about yourself, the less moved you'll be by the opinions of others. - B. Dilley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have no special talents. I am only passionately curious. - Albert Einstein #quote #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let us never negotiate out of fear. But let us never fear to negotiate. - John F. Kennedy #quote   #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If people don't appreciate what you bring to the table.. then let them eat alone. - Unknown #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m listening to Jeremy Camp ♫ @iHeartRadio https://t.co/QuZZlWxWqN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find your spirit, and no challenge will keep you from achieving your goals. - Christopher Penn #quote #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything ultimately comes down to trust.- Marcus Sheridan #quote #socialmedia #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The true sign of intelligence is not knowledge but
imagination.”
- Albert Einstein #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You never know what worse luck your bad luck has saved you from. - Cormac McCarthy #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Educating the mind without educating the heart is no education at all.- Aristotle #quote  #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everything ultimately comes down to trust.- Marcus Sheridan #quote #socialmedia #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there any one so wise as to learn by the experience of others? - Voltaire #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Learn to help people with more than just their jobs; help
them with their lives”
- Jim Rohn #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One finds limits by pushing them. - Herbert Simon #quote   #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your talent deserves a voice! - @Meddleit #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Wisdom is not a product of schooling but of the lifelong
attempt to acquire it"
- Albert Einstein #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inspiration doesn't respond to meeting requests. You can’t schedule greatness - Jay Baer #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your business is never really good or bad ‘out there’. Your
business is either good or bad right between your own two
ears"
-Zig Ziglar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret of being a bore is to tell everything. - Voltaire #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just started following The Living Room on #Vimeo: https://t.co/T0AgZ2P7nQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no cosmetic for beauty like happiness. - Maria Mitchell #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Try not to become a man of success but a man of value.”
- Albert Einstein #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd rather live with a good question than a bad answer.- Aryeh Frimer #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ideas are easy. Implementation is hard. – Guy Kawasaki #quote #entrepreneur #startup #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Focus on where you want to go, not on what you fear. - Anthony Robbins #quote  #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We've got bacon! A labor of love for some youth group leaders!

#bacon #youth #youthgroup #love https://t.co/G33fkCdPGe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Inspiration and genius are one and the same.”
- Victor Hugo #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live more, complain less.
More smiles, less stress.
Less hate, more blessed.

- David Roads #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beware that the detours in your life don't turn into destinations. - Tim Fargo #quote #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[May your faith be unshakeable and your will, unbreakable. - Tristan Bishop #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JusticeEagan @CliveJeffrey @boomerbizcoach @QuoTweety @Juliann74629439]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Out for a nice walk in the 'Burg! Love these little creeks today flow through our little… https://t.co/WYgNPpAcW0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Success is normally found in a pile of mistakes. - Tim Fargo #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just liked “Envision- Taipei” on #Vimeo: https://t.co/Tdl2TU3S5p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch “Envision- Taipei” on #Vimeo https://t.co/OI0g4gkK4Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Resolve to pay any price or make any sacrifice to get into the
top ten percent of your field. That payoff is incredible!”
- Brian Tracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your life does not get better by chance, it gets better by change. - Jim Rohn #quote  #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I never knew a man come to greatness or eminence who lay
abed late in the morning."
- Jonatha
n Swift #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your fear is 100% dependent on you for its survival. - Steve Maraboli #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life's tragedy is that we get old too soon and wise too late. - Benjamin Franklin #quote  #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["First we form habits, then they form us. Conquer your bad
habits or they will conquer you."
- Rob Gilbert #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We'd achieve more if we chased our dreams instead of our competition. - Simon Sinek #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Unless you change how you are, you will always have what
you've got.”
- Jim Rohn #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Setting goals is the first step in turning the invisible into the visible. - Tony Robbins #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Marketing Leads Generation Platform https://t.co/XtzvdmhHxT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Success is the result of good judgement, which is the result of experience, experience is often the result of bad judgement. - Tony Robbins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Motivation is the fuel, necessary to keep the human engine
running"
-Zig Ziglar #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can often change your circumstances by changing your attitude. - Eleanor Roosevelt #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Positive thinking will let you use the abilities, training and
experience you have"
-Zig Ziglar #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To affect the quality of the day, that is the highest of arts. - Henry David Thoreau #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pghgirl15222: Penguins fans are looking awfully spoiled and unrealistic. Losing a preseason game means virtually nothing. Long season a…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Discipline is just choosing between what you want now and what you want most. - Unknown #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Greatness is a road leading towards the unknown."
- Charles de Gaulle #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intelligence is knowing the right answer. Wisdom is knowing when to say it. - Tim Fargo #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[13
"Leadership is the challenge to be something more than
average”
- Jim Rohn #johnbdeleo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are all born ignorant, but one must work hard to remain stupid. - Benjamin Franklin #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You may never know what results come of your actions, but if you do nothing, there will be no results. - Gandhi #quote #babyboomers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["My mentor said, 'Let's go do it,' not 'You go do it.' How
powerful it is when someone says, 'Lets!’"
- Jim Rohn #johnbdeleo]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>