<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Even on bad run days be proud that you got there! #proudrunner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Don't settle for mediocrity when you can have #greatness" unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thrive off of this workload. I simply adore the exhaustion that comes with training hard. -- Deena Kastor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And those who were seen dancing were thought to be insane by those who could not hear the #music - Nietzsche via @TheTrailJogger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Running is more than a sport. Running creates friends and relationships all over the globe #proudrunner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The best #runs sometimes come on days when you didn't feel like running." ~anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["True friends are special gifts. Take care of them, listen to them, thank them, and never forget to be a #friend back" unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Nothing will ever be attempted if all #possible objections must first be overcome." - Samuel Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep digging deeper.. you will find what you #passionately pursue for! via @Kcancer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A single act of courage is often the tipping point for something extraordinary." via @AnnTran_ #start #run #finish]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Anyone can run 20 miles. It's the next six that count." - Barry Magee #running #marathon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If I were to be remembered for anything at all, I would want that to be that I am/was authentic. No Mas. Run Free!" #RIP #MicahTrue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#change #life #live #dream #goforit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Mentoring is your true legacy. It is the greatest inheritance you can give to others. To teach and be taught.”John Wooden, #coaching]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is a bad plan that allows no room for #modification - Publius Syrus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give me strength, reserve control 
Give me heart and give me soul ~ Coldplay #marathon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe the streets alight, maybe the trees are gone..I feel my heart start beating to my favourite song ~Coldplay #run #feel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Run without rules]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Do not be afraid of death. Be afraid of the half-lived life!" - Laird Hamilton #live]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Never settle, set your sights high. If you aim your #goals too low, you might just hit them.” via @TheNoteboook]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The question isn't who's going to let me; the question is who's going to #stop me. ♥ Ayn Rand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are a million open doors to opportunity and no waiting. When you do what others won't, the lines are shorter.” via @AffirmationSpot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“If good things come to those who wait, then I must have something ridiculously #amazing coming!” via @TheNoteboook]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone is a #runner. Some just haven't figured it out.” via @BartYasso]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love what you do. Do what you love." - Wayne Dyer #passion #run #love #makedifference]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Laziness is nothing more than the habit of resting before you get tired." Jules Renard via @ninagarcia #train #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Life is either a daring adventure or nothing." Helen Keller #live]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When the road ahead seems too long, look back to see how far you’ve come. #triathlon #progress via @zumadog]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is more fun with other #runners via @JeffGalloway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Confidence is contagious. So is lack of #confidence." -Vincent T Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If we do not take advantage of our #opportunities, it is our own fault." -- Thomas J. Watson via @RunToWin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embrace the souls that dare to reach out a hand in kindness ~ unknown #quote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Running helps me believe I can]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["open doors let life pleasures in, closed doors do not" unknown #life #risks #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All #marathons are 26 miles 385 yards. Anything longer &amp; race is ultramarathon. Anything less &amp; course was mismeasured~via @higdonmarathon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never give up on something that you can't go a day without thinking about. via @DrAndyBaldwin #life #love #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Every step you take brings you closer to the #finish line.” via @higdonmarathon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You will do this! #run #marathon #ironman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pain is the sensation that reminds you that you are still #alive - R Marchenko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["My philosophy on #running is, I don't dwell on it, I do it." Joan Benoit Samuelson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who say that I will lose and am finished will have to #run over my body to beat me.~Said Aouita]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Love the life you live. Live the life you love." - Bob Marley #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your #possibilities are absolutely endless. via @AffirmationSpot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“You are never too old to set another goal or to dream a new dream.” via @Kcancer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Go the extra mile. It's never crowded. ~Author Unknown #giveback via @LJ3000]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a little like wrestling a gorilla. You don't quit when you're tired you quit when the gorilla is tired ~Strauss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes the biggest accomplishment is not who finishes first, but who #finishes last!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I #run on purpose]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most people just exist. Go #live! via @DrAndyBaldwin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Limitations live only in our minds. But if we use our #imaginations, our possibilities become limitless.” Paolinetti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not running this #race to win, but to give it everything I got]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To settle is a choice, you can choose to #run after your dreams”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter our age or condition, there are still untapped #possibilities within us &amp; new beauty waiting to be born ~Turner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't feel the finish line, if you don't start #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["None are so old as those who lose their #enthusiasm." ~Henry David Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Endurance? You’ve only got to get out there and do it. Face up to it: man was meant to #run – Percy Cerutty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Racing for me was about energy management." Frank Shorter #run #marathon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are never too busy to start #whynot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes you just need a little #positive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you want it, go get it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["This 26.2 is for all of the non-believers" RQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You got a #dream, you got to protect it. People can’t do something themselves, they want to tell you you can’t do it ~Pursuit of Happyness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You want something, go get it. Period. ~ Pursuit of Happyness #dreams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I run because I can #getiton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You just can't beat the person who won't give up." -Babe Ruth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I plan to break the rules #run #hard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why have #good when you can have #great ~~&gt; #goforit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't follow your #dreams; chase them. ~ Richard Dumb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't be pushed by your problems, be led by your #dreams ~Les Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["#Running is a journey that whether we do alone or with others, we are always together"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't think you got this, you got it! #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There is just something about people who enjoy going long" #runners]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Hope is a #good thing, maybe the best thing, and no good thing ever dies” Shawshank Redemption]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make room to receive your #desires ~ Rhonda Byrne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All great achievements require time. ~ Maya Angelou #courage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Person born with a talent they are meant to use will find their greatest #happiness in using it." ~Wolfgang von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you know what you #want, & you want it bad enough, you'll find a way to get it. ~Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["#Running reminds us that we are alive"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The next mile is the only one a person really has to make." Eric Sevareid #run #life]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live life fully while you're here. Experience everything. Take care of yourself and your #friends ~ Anthony Robbins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Don't let the barriers you see define what you do." Sonal Shah via @charityideas #live]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Begin each day as if it were on purpose” Radmacher #live]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A great friend knows how to take you by the hand and lift you up when you are down and if you are really lucky for a #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The world needs #dreamers & the world needs doers. But above all the world needs dreamers that do." Sarah Ban Breathnach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Some men see things as they are & ask why. Others dream things that never were & ask why not.” Shaw #goforit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is not a single path. Don't be afraid to #run on new roads]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Act as if what you do makes a difference.  It does.  ~William James]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He who has begun is half done - Horace #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If we wait for the moment when everything, absolutely everything, is ready, we shall never #begin." - Ivan Turgenev]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who have abandoned their own dreams will try to convince you to abandon yours. Don't listen. #neverquit via @JoshCox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man who dares to waste one hour of time has not discovered the value of life. ~Charles Darwin #live #love #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Life has no #limitations, except the ones you make." - Les Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If we wait for the moment when everything, absolutely everything, is ready, we shall never #begin." - Ivan Turgenev]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're pursuing a #dream & folks are saying, 'you can't do it, you're wasting your time' you're probably on the right track via @JoshCox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What #great thing would you attempt if you knew you could not fail? ~Robert H. Schuller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We cannot waste time. We can only waste ourselves." - George M. Adams #quote via @SusanCosmos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still get wildly enthusiastic about little things. I play w/ leaves. I skip down the street & run against the wind~ Buscaglia via @LJ3000]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Put your #heart, #mind, and #soul into even your smallest acts. This is the secret of success. ~Swami Sivananda]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The most powerful lesson you can learn in #running? You're capable of much more than you think." via @runnersworld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Racing teaches us to #challenge ourselves. It teaches us to push beyond where we though we could go." - Patti Sue Plummer]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>