<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Between the Mourinho/Paul Joseph Watson panel, the Fergie/Bobby Charlton one and Neymar, this may just be @squires_david's finest work yet https://t.co/Fqy0o2xRj5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@waynefarry I highly doubt Gervais even knows who PJW is tbf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[King Krule playing in the new episode of Atlanta, which once again proves it's the best show on tv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CRSvanX The American Badass]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@glennthefitz I just want him to do another swerve and shout 'I've plenty left in the tank']]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Seananigen Hahaha spot on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can confirm that Golden Skans by Klaxons still absolutely bangs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@swearimnotpaul @Jon_Mackenzie Salah would probably break his metatarsal as well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConJClancy Haha, never. But at least it's not just Juve winning ten games in a row to get the title. At least want some drama]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConJClancy Superb result. Keeps it tight, which is all we want]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jon_Mackenzie @waynefarry 💕]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@waynefarry @Jon_Mackenzie Does that mean I'm handsome?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jon_Mackenzie @waynefarry He pointed to my face and claimed as such. Fair enough I say]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@waynefarry He called me a virgin on twitter before. Arguably my finest moment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ianmbarry Or even Courtois. It would make sense. If I was Madrid, would have Salah over Hazard all day]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salah is going to be amazing for Real Madrid. The perfect galactico signing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConorMPwalsh Would say a combination of both]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Akhlaq1386 @TifoFootball_ @CobhRamblersFC @NFFC @ManUtd @CelticFC @johnsportraits @WilliamHill The 2002 WC and Keane's international career is part of a future video]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching Ireland win the Grand Slam on Paddy's Day in a bar full of pissed Irish in Toronto is pretty fucking special]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Replete_Solkatt Haha, not a fan I take it?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the subject of Keane, he was absolutely spot on when he said the Manchester United job was too big for Mourinho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wrote the words for this video on Roy Keane for @TifoFootball_ https://t.co/uzwyUka32s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@waynefarry Me too. Has shades of Arsenal-Chelsea 2004]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ankaman616 Come to Toronto]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@darren__holland As I'm in Toronto, we're heading to either Pitchfork or Lolla in Chicago, or the governors ball in NYC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ankaman616 Saw him play at electric picnic in Ireland last year and he absolutely murdered it. Incredible performance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gregianjohnson @Football_LDN I have Chelsea going on a late season run, but I'm still not sure how it worked out that way haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gregianjohnson @Football_LDN I honestly don't see Liverpool finishing second. Think their fixtures are trickier than they look, plus champions league to contend with as well]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gregianjohnson @Football_LDN I may have overestimated Tottenham's chances without Kane, but anyway https://t.co/NdiBwEHCNu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are ways to go out of a tournament. At least Tottenham and Chelsea played with some guts and had a go, as opposed to sitting in their own half and hiding]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thibaut Courtois' Real Madrid audition is going well anyway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to Giroud doing a Drogba in flip flops at full time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are truly privileged to be able to watch Messi every week]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RorySmith This may be your finest work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RorySmith: Like all Spanish teams apart from Barca and Real, Sevilla are amateurs, so less than 24 hours after beating Man Utd, their p…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bjarm_ Usually tends to when Mou is involved haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@waynefarry Grave, digging, own etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mourinho starting two holding midfielders at home in a game they have to win against a Sevilla team that have conceded 42 goals in La Liga. Louis Van Gaal was sacked for less]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NostalgiaUltra5 Hoping the scarf means a podcast dedicated to the Europa League final in 2011 is on the way]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only thing more impressive about Son than his football ability is his commitment to creating new handshakes for every teammate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yet another goal for Heung-Min Son: @SebSB's favourite Spurs player and mine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well on board with Troy Deeney missing a penalty just months after questioning Arsenal's cojones.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehuwdavies Haha lovely, thank you. Hopefully we can complete the job next week]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is with regret that I have to inform you that West Ham United football club are at it again https://t.co/eVDTRqDfAT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehuwdavies I've still no idea why Coleman agreed to take that job]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehuwdavies When he played for Southampton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ankaman616 Gimme dah]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LiamPaulCanning I appreciate good footballers even if the manager doesn't]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rashford and Martial are better than Sanchez, pass it on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamKelly19 Drake is the Ranieri to Boi-1da's Craig Shakespeare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching the Toronto Raptors and Drake is essentially the de facto coach. All for that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ConorPacKelly: Wrote about Neymar, PSG and why the Brazilian's playboy lifestyle off the pitch will only end badly for him @BetBright/@…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wrote about Neymar, PSG and why the Brazilian's playboy lifestyle off the pitch will only end badly for him @BetBright/@TifoFootball_  https://t.co/zp8Edu48KA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You think Milan have made progress and then you see Fabio Borini aimlessly running around up front and realise they've a long way to go]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adammcmahon99 @Joesmithd @MiguelDelaney Right, I'd like to leave this conversation if possible as it's got rather juvenile]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adammcmahon99 @Joesmithd @MiguelDelaney You should read the Diego Torres book on Mourinho's time at Madrid and you'll understand why all of what you've said above won't happen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adammcmahon99 @Joesmithd @MiguelDelaney Conte's won four league titles in a row before this season as well as taking a declining Italian team to within a shootout of beating Germany. Pretty sure I know who I'd rather have]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adammcmahon99 @MiguelDelaney The old George Santayana quote about history being doomed to repeat itself comes to mind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MiguelDelaney Reminds me of when Florentino Perez backed Mourinho against Casillas and Ramos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ramiejowe Very jealous. Pretty sure I've listened to every one since the first week]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For anyone who does anything creative, this is a fucking class listen. https://t.co/bjAXqjPY3t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ConJClancy I am 100% with this]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching Juventus defend is art]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To state the blindingly obvious, Dybala is a fucking class act]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SamDiss @RorySmith Think Spurs are just really good. The standard of PL teams has risen significantly this year, Juve possibly dipped slightly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is absolutely incredible https://t.co/f0zkaLO2RT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Farewell NME. Will always remember your continual anointing of bang average indie bands as 'the most important band of our era'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SonjaMissio @AlexLukasNathan @ConJClancy Haha responded]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tehTrunk Watch them score with their only chance of the game and leave with a 1-0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@COILIROILI Can confirm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Myself and @ShaneMurphy2692 spent 15 minutes browsing through the grilled cheese subreddit last night. Regret nothing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@horan_james Yeah, on reflection it was. Still such a horrible way to go. Madrid are the ultimate bad guys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mo_Farrell92 Roma reaching the final is all I really want to see from the rest of this CL season. It would be the best story for a variety of reasons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SamDiss @ElMengem And like every good plot, when the evil overlord finally, eventually gets toppled it's more impactful and meaningful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mo_Farrell92 Nah, Roma-Liverpool with Salah scoring the winner at the Olimpico is nailed on]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're a heartless bastard if you don't have sympathy for Gigi tonight. Absolutely robbed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Football is fucking evil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So a predictable Champions League season has become really great this week]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gregianjohnson Makelele primarily shielding the Chelsea back four, because I'd grown to with Keane/Vieira playing box-to-box, tackling, scoring, passing, carrying etc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new Unknown Mortal Orchestra album is a beaut and this tune is so addictive https://t.co/HVaTYZL4FK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ankaman616 This card is mad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mark_Flynn4 One set of fans obsessed with others rather than enjoying their own success. 'A different breed' alright]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Zonal_Marking: 2017/18 needed tonight's drama. Overall this European season has been very dull - barely any title races and a very pred…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GerraDeegan If they are as great a team as we all think, this is only the beginning. They'll come back from it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MundialMag The working man's Cristiano]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@GerraDeegan First leg was the problem. Complete no-show by City unfortunately. Pep needs to figure out a solution to his teams collapsing in April]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is why non-Liverpool fans enjoy seeing them implode. They have an amazing team/coach that should be the neutral's favourite, yet they can't even enjoy their own success without childish bitterness https://t.co/ToYLL9uWdY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roma making the final would be truly special for the club and the eternal city. Here's hoping]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kvn_clmn Definitely the semi-final with Salah scoring a hat-trick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Roma are definitely drawing Liverpool in the semi-finals and Salah is definitely scoring a hat-trick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mo_Farrell92 It's like finding a RAF Simmons jacket for €40 in TK Maxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fastcarbuzzy Roberto Di Matteo won the champions league]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The worst bit of transfer business in history by Roma only getting £35 million for Mo Salah. Monchi is a fraud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fully expecting Manchester City to score four goals tonight but go out after a tragic mistake from Otamendi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CianByNature Skream still a boss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For those who've weirdly missed listening to me on podcasts, I joined the @under_thecosh lads on their latest episode. Che che check it out https://t.co/AWZWhJjwy3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ankaman616 Only a two appearance deal so he can drop it to Reigns in front of a more accepting audience. Nonsense]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CRSvanX Jesus, Vince is clueless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CRSvanX Surely that's where they go now. Have him win the title with help from Heyman, turn him into the biggest bad guy in the company and build to Reigns-Bryan at next year's Mania]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fucking love the Graps #WrestleMania]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>