<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[A variant on this classic uses convertible bonds. The company sells the financier a convertible bond in a private placement.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is a bit de trop to say "to quote Samuel Jackson in 'Pulp Fiction.'"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine if you tried to send an email and a rickshaw driver showed up at your office offering to deliver it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[However, if Manchester United win both the Premier League and FA Cup this season, the rate is boosted to 3.2pc.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Because trading is necessarily a business of misdirection and keeping information from your counterparties," is I think one good answer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe an Apple Tesla would be better than a Tesla Tesla?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now it's trying to sell the mines at a loss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["They are a pain in the ass to negotiate with," says a former hedge funder. "They retrade at the last minute all the time."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They are a reasonable way to attract an executive with lots of unvested comp at another firm that she'd be giving up to take a new job.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SarahFKessler T. Rowe Price Group managed to get some of its funds denied appraisal on two entirely different technicalities.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This isn't legal advice or anything, but you probably want to avoid telling a federal judge that you "sort of" ran a Ponzi scheme.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This column does not necessarily reflect the opinion of Bloomberg View's editorial board or Bloomberg LP, its owners and investors.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is that the sanctions-enforcement staff get high-paying jobs at the banks and other companies that have to comply with the sanctions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blockchain blockchain blockchain blockchain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That lawsuit went poorly because, among other reasons, Ceglia's own lawyers concluded that he had forged the contract.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We have talked before about the shifting balance of power between entrepreneurs and capital providers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Investors are fleeing from a business they see as confidence-based, and therefore prone to unravel at speed."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like obviously the client is expecting an un-marked-up price, and so thwarting his expectations seems straightforwardly dishonest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Others have gone to prison for mis-valuing securities or helping clients evade taxes or manipulating Libor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have to sort of admire Uber's bluntness. "Give Up Your Keys," as a slogan, manages to be both boring and menacing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nor for that matter was Wainwright Bank &amp; Trust.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know, I get the sense that Icahn isn't kidding about thinking he should not run a proxy fight.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But the report at least points to that heterogeneity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How bout that. Or whatever, a thing, let's call it a "law," without being too doctrinaire about what that word means.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@duffmcdonald What even is value? It's a strange time for private company fundraising.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This seems like a general problem with the current generation of tech companies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As I've argued, if you want to have a lot of trading in your dark pool, you need to let people who trade a lot into your dark pool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People are worried about bond market liquidity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lending Club steps into the bank's shoes and really is your lender, in a way that I am not.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's got a new house, he's got some art, he's got a slide deck quoting Heraclitus, he's got some views on the Fed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These plans should be vetted with senior management and control functions and be reviewed on a regular basis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today in hedge funds. ("We actually don’t see ourselves as a hedge fund," says Seth Klarman of Baupost.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Real markets don’t currently work this way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lending Club priced its initial public offering at $15 a share, above the range of $12 to $14, which was $10 to $12 last week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still. Running Alphabet, and leaving Google to new CEO Sundar Pichai, probably does free up Page and Brin to focus on the moonshots.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Banks can't generally be dealers in stocks; they can't trade stocks for market-making purposes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things are bad, if you're in the oil business.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One simple view might be that public ownership is not optimal for some (all?)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(Taleb says, "as volatility increases, the barrier gets flat vega while the vanilla retains its effect.")]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some evidence for that conclusion is the fact that BoNY messed it up twice:
There was an additional hiccough at BONY.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyway probably don't play this game, or go to law school.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But hang on, Charikov said: Actually banks in 2006-2007 didn't care at all about anyone's income, or their intent to live in any houses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“This is a big deal, not just for us, but for the entire Bitcoin industry,” says itBit’s chief executive officer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not for any particular regulatory reason, just so we can all kibbitz about short campaigns the way we do on long activist campaigns.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things definitely are better now, in real concrete ways that grow out of lessons learned by the Fed during the financial crisis.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And if you turn Twitter into Facebook, it won't be Twitter, and Twitter is good.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reuters describes them as "the Financial Information Authority (AIF), the Holy See's financial watchdog."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some predictions. I enjoyed this post from Eoin Power about how sell-side financial research works.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(There are also some big items for "condo sales," which I guess technically aren't either rents or capital gains, so I'll allow them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the future, the only jobs that the robots won't take will be the jobs that require specifically human attributes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People are worried about bond market liquidity. It was touch and go for a while yesterday but then the worrying started up again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elsewhere in fascinating job stories, here is Kevin Roose on teaching prisoners to code.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are various ways to guarantee against those claims being impaired when the bank loses money.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But the good news is that investors are considerably less concerned about evaporating bond market liquidity now than they were in May.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Presidential politics. Well here is Donald Trump's financial disclosure form.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The isolated warlike tribe of floor traders.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Still impressive. Also a guy talked about how drones and bioweapons will team up to kill us all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What was Barclays thinking with its dark pool advertising?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You might think that a nuclear powered Nimitz-class supercarrier would not be a pleasure craft, but you would be mostly wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's not expecting a numbered list of 22 reasons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is not the first to succumb to temptation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By lunchtime today we'll learn that Islam is 46 and that Stuyvesant High School does not actually exist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hacked into a server and stole this newsletter before it was made public. http://t.co/3t3Zr3qmV1 via @matt_levine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So you route to your dark pool. Various evils might or might not come from this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Barofsky -- who also hasn't read it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are activists an important check on shareholder complacency?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clearing, on the other hand, makes everything safer, right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Markets in bonds are still sometimes made by humans because they do have some advantages; see the item immediately above this one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We thought transparency would be good, the sunshine would be helpful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The problem with Wall Street is that we're not paying whistleblowers enough. So the Justice Department wants to pay them more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People are worried about bond market liquidity. I wrote a little more about bond liquidity worries yesterday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The story continues as you might expect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But the whole thing is very much worth reading, a defense of nuance against snap black-and-white moral judgments.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This reflex is exactly why we have a mass incarceration problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even if you do think that, though, I'm not sure it's much of a reason to be bearish. The universe of potential scams is infinite.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel like I'd rather buy Greek bank equity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People are worried about bond market liquidity. Still!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I guess I can't criticize; I used to file my nails at my desk at Goldman. But I'm horrible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surely he makes his money as an entertainer, not as a financial adviser.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I didn't know this: For months, Goldman Sachs Group Inc.’s activism-defense business has been the butt of competitors’ jokes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's how to 
make the Volcker Rule worse
.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The index funds have the advantage of free-riding, but the disadvantage of being predictable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And yet the sprawling U.S. rule and the slim European one get to not that different a place, at least with regard to proprietary trading.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[as a meaningful prediction of 1-year forward prices?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do you do tobacco antitrust regulation?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really they should just hand all their cases to the federal prosecutors in New York; those guys win like crazy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As one FX Sales employee wrote in a chat to an employee at another bank on December 30, 2009, “hard mark up is key . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So ProPublica's Carmen Segarra article is worth another look today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That Exchange will likewise be open to Holdout Bonds.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you received a misdirected e-mail that created a material risk to Goldman Sachs's financial performance, do let us know in the comments.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Other than the fact that they can both call themselves "hedge fund managers."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He likes IEX, a new market designed to limit abusive trading.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And bond mutual fund managers are having trouble finding mortgage-backed securities to match the Barclays U.S.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But, as I said yesterday, you can stop: Now there is evidence!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matt_levine ("I personally lost $100,000 in one second.")]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People are worried about bond market liquidity. But, as I said yesterday, you can stop: Now there is evidence!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It goes on from there but it's too much for me. Follow me on Ello!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brewer also engaged in a multi-year scheme in which he prepared and filed false tax returns for others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you have a willing buyer and a willing seller, in what sense is the price wrong? And yet it does seem wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That it is impossible to know for certain that you are obeying the law?]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>