<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Working with people who have "no interest in politics" is soul destroying]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ashleyfeinberg: both my father and my sister are dead because of guns and I would like to plunge in now https://t.co/BmXyEX4U7w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CityofVancouver @BcfRa PAPER STRAWS!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BWestbrookAZ8: The @NRA has donated over $3,781,803 to Congress, which has translated to over 100 failed proposals for stricter gun pol…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jk_rowling: The massacre of schoolchildren in Dunblane led to UK gun law reform, which is why many stunned that there was no US change…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ajplus: Egypt is cracking down on the LGBTQ community. Police arrested 22 people over the last 3 days after a rainbow flag was raised a…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GeorgeTakei: Will our lawmakers listen this time? https://t.co/cgb7NFCqaq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nytimes: The Russians who posed as Americans on Facebook last year tried on quite an array of disguises https://t.co/uZ4YjyfgAN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CBCAlerts: Prominent Putin critic jailed again on charge of organizing illegal rally. Alexei Navalny sentenced to 20 days. BG: https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Mikel_Jollett: For those of you saying this was a case of "mental illness":

Remember THIS was one of the first things Trump did: https…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GreenpeaceCA: If this Trump executive order is carried out, it could open up prospects for oil drilling on California's coast
https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JoeBiden: How long do we let gun violence tear families apart? Enough. Congress &amp; the WH should act now to save lives. There's no excus…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NobelPrize: Our biological clock helps to regulate sleep patterns, feeding behavior, hormone release and blood pressure #NobelPrize htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ChrisMurphyCT: To my colleagues: your cowardice to act cannot be whitewashed by thoughts and prayers.

None of this ends unless we do s…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7/11 Loves Plastic https://t.co/xKrxg04Dto]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jeremyscahill: Why don’t we talk about white on white crime? If this was a hip hop concert and shooter was black...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @eorlins: “Thoughts and prayers” are nice, but they don’t stop #MassShootings! We need #guncontrol by way of legislation. #lasvegashooti…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TravelGoC: Shooting in #LasVegas #US, Canadians: For emergency assistance contact us at 1-844-880-6519 or sos@international.gc.ca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NaomiAKlein: I have, and we all should be amplifying today. Nothing can justify this state violence. #CatalanReferendum https://t.co/6x…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CBCAlerts: BREAKING: Ontario provincial politician Jagmeet Singh wins the federal NDP leadership race. Takes over 50% of the vote on fi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woot! https://t.co/a4cqMVOzCw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RepJoeKennedy: Programs GOP Congress let expire last night
-healthcare for low-income kids
-Community health centers
-Loans for low-inc…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[run away piggies! https://t.co/M9CDcfpmS6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jaketapper: WH is upset about this WaPo report:

Lost weekend: How Trump’s time at his golf club hurt the response to Maria https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BillWeirCNN: This is absurd. 
Every FEMA person I met thanked us for highlighting the enormity of the disaster and trying to get them m…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ddale8: This story is amazing. New Jersey doomsday prepper about to lose his house donates all his supplies to Puerto Rico: https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This https://t.co/yXJrpLOtlU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ChrisEvans: A Trump Thread In A Time Of Crisis:
-Narcissistic ✔️ 
-Defensive✔️
-Insulting✔️
-Multiple references to himself in the thir…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @StopUBCanimalre: As S-203's creator Senator Wilfred Moore told the Senate, "Whales and dolphins don't belong in swimming pools.... http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ChrisGiles_: Thanks #Brexit https://t.co/3A8kslVyz3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chrisdonovan: Ret Lt Gen Honore on Trump tweets today: "I have no reaction. The mayor’s living on a cot, and I hope the President has a…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WalshFreedom: And by the way @FoxNews, Robert Mueller is an American hero. 

Marine, Vietnam Veteran, he has dedicated his life to serv…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pewenvironment: Significant levels of overfishing persist in the EU because #AGRIFISH ministers continue to set fishing limits too high…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @shannonrwatts: John Lennon was shot and killed 37 years ago today by a man who bought a gun in Hawaii and brought it to New York in his…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ajplus: Net neutrality rules are in danger of being repealed. Here's why you should care. https://t.co/udJTDCNVkg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KerryKennedyRFK: We must continue to protect America's public lands and Native American sacred sites. To deprive future generations acc…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nytimes: Russian operatives repeatedly emailed Hope Hicks after the 2016 election. The FBI met with her to urge caution. https://t.co/X…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Sethrogen: I was supposed to do a press tour on @SIRIUSXM on teusday but I'm no longer doing it because I can't bring myself to appear…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @leadnowca: He's lining his team with far-right hate.

We can't let them succeed. https://t.co/Bwu3e6I4EV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GeorgeTakei: No greater purveyor of fake news than this White House. via @actdottv https://t.co/SNVKWrjcCM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SarahKSilverman: Barely made news yesterday. Another school shooting in America. Two kids murdered at school. Still no change in legisl…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CharlieAngusNDP: Canada needs to deliver a clear, unambiguous message to Trump and Israel on Jerusalem. Canada needs to play a credible…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NANComms: "This report raises many red flags. The prime minister made a firm commitment to end long-term drinking water advisories on r…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CNN: Protests erupted outside the American Consulate in Istanbul, Turkey following US President Donald Trump's decision to recognize Je…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @greenpeaceusa: By the year 2050 there could be more plastics than fish in the world’s oceans. 

Tell Coca Cola's CEO to do their part t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Variety: .@JaneGoodallInst says Caesar's behavior in 'War for the Planet of the Apes' "reflects the struggle of humanity as we try to o…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @UBCIC: Joint News Release: NDP #SiteC Approval Would Slap First Nations in the Face. #bcpoli https://t.co/6cmD6rTr1X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ajplus: Senator Al Franken announced his resignation, but not without taking a jab at President Trump and Roy Moore. https://t.co/wCeGd…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BTroublemakers: "This is a sea change in activism like nothing I’ve ever seen,” said Leslie Gaines-Ross, chief reputation strategist at…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @VanHumane: Cetaceans keep dying so Vancouver Aquarium rushes in some walruses https://t.co/DsIJxKltDf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cbcnewsbc: Walrus calves' big move sparks calls for aquarium boycott https://t.co/FcKLRlWQyL https://t.co/Eu15O854L8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ggreenwald: This is a vital point. Opposing Trump's decision by emphasizing Arab violence 1) avoids condemning Israel for land theft an…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GreenpeaceCA: BLOG: Activists visit @CocaColaCo_ca headquarters urging the global company to give some good will to marine life this ho…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SenSanders: We have a president who acknowledged on tape that he assaulted women. I would hope that he pays attention to what's going o…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[URGENT: Hours left to Stop Site C!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PAYOLETTER: rt if you think this cat is doing an amazing job https://t.co/byNWuLi5si]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BGT_ENG: Time to say goodbye ☹️

Ronaldinho to officially retire - FULL STORY: https://t.co/a60xjoSgvV https://t.co/xgIQvt2V10]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MikeHudema: Two killed, two seriously injured in Kinder Morgan pipeline explosion https://t.co/PVzLOc0xza 

#ActOnClimate #bcpoli #NoKX…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deadline tomorrow: Tell the Fair Wages Commission we want $15/hr for all workers by January 2019]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CharlieAngusNDP: Proud of my colleague @HLaverdiereNPD for speaking out against @realDonaldTrump call to move US Embassy to Jerusalem.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PalestineUSA: Jerusalem's Christian leaders to Trump moving the embassy will be irreparable damage. https://t.co/koIl8PWEE1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nytimes: Breaking News: Michael Flynn told an associate that Russia sanctions would be "ripped up" early in the Trump presidency, a whi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GeorgeTakei: Keep your eye on the ball, friends. And follow the money. More than what Trump may be worth, the subpoena may uncover actu…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Amy_Siskind: Yes! I have been waiting for this.  Deutsche Bank known as the Laundromat for Russian money has an unusual lending relatio…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KoehlerMatthew: BREAKING The Navajo Nation and partners are suing @realDonaldTrump over his illegal decision to shrink America's #Bears…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PoliticsOTM: It begins: Palestinians burn portraits of Donald Trump in protest of the US embassy moving to Jerusalem. 3 Days of Rage de…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ajplus: BREAKING: A court filing reveals Paul Manafort and a colleague with ties to the Russian government were ghost-writing an op-ed…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LeoDiCaprio: Please support the efforts by @DiCaprioFdn grantee, @UtahDineBikeyah,  to defend these national monuments in court. https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MittRomney: Roy Moore in the US Senate would be a stain on the GOP and on the nation. Leigh Corfman and other victims are courageous he…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@jjhorgan @carolejames @michellemungall: cancel the Site C megadam now. #bcpoli #stopsitec https://t.co/ue0lBZZPVM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ajplus: Bears Ears National monument is 1.3 million acres and home to Native American ceremonial lands and tens of thousands of signifi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ajplus: President Trump is slashing protected public lands sacred to indigenous people by millions of acres. Native communities, enviro…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nytimes: Breaking News: In a move that could alter the course of U.S. land conservation, the Trump administration is slashing protectio…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ajplus: Delhi's air pollution is so bad that cricket players walked onto the field wearing masks. https://t.co/0zo6Cl4zQu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KerryKennedyRFK: President Trump's myopic decision to gut protected federal land sets back over a century of bipartisan conservation ef…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Alyssa_Milano: For your records, @realDonaldTrump. https://t.co/6dACoJBFD8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Comey: “I want the American people to know this truth: The FBI is honest. The FBI is strong. And the FBI is, and always will be, indepe…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just donated to @Wikipedia. Support free knowledge! #iloveWikipedia https://t.co/WfTS0KLbaA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RexHuppke: This could seriously imperil Jared Kushner's ability to bring peace to the Middle East.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @renato_mariotti: So now the question is: What did Jared Kushner tell Mueller about his conversation with Flynn? We know Mueller intervi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sarahkendzior: Congress has known for half a year that Kushner was implicated. They knew he lied on his clearance forms. They did nothi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@jjhorgan @carolejames @michellemungall: cancel the Site C megadam now. #bcpoli #stopsitec https://t.co/8sFcjVDb5z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PhilippeReines: Prosecutors stated Flynn was directed to engage the Russians on 12/29/16 by donald’s national security transition team.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @leadnowca: We plastered these ads all around #Ottawa, asking @JustinTrudeau to reject #TPP. Tweet pictures at us if you see them! https…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jimsciutto: Two years ago almost to the day: https://t.co/JqoZNsTYhE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GeorgeTakei: Well said, sir, well said, indeed. https://t.co/SUTBC1sax4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheDavidSedaris thank-you - I needed that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pieglue: Group protesting #KinderMorgan in Vancouver outside hotel where company president and Alberta Premier Rachel Notley speaking t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SInow: It is a rare person who gives up what he loves in exchange for what he believes. 

Colin Kaepernick is the winner of SI’s Muhamm…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JohnMayer: Idea: somebody should tell Trump they want to make a 3-D scan of his head for a statue but really it’s an MRI.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cbcnewsbc Nope]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/0gEMe7auS3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tell @DLeBlancNB to ban infectious waste from being pumped into our oceans. https://t.co/ckoOqx750x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kylegriffin1: Russell Begaye, President of the Navajo Nation, on MSNBC: “To put in a slur that has become racial, ‘Pocahontas’, didn’t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nytimes: “They call her Pocahontas.” Trump mocked Senator Elizabeth Warren at an Oval Office event honoring Navajo veterans https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jaketapper: POTUS called Sen. Warren "Pocahontas" in April 2017. The bi-partisan National Congress of the American Indians said "we can…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GeorgeTakei: While Trump uses racial slurs, let honor the people who stood behind him. Hundreds of Native Americans joined the US armed…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tell @Nestle to drop the lawsuit against a tiny township trying to protect its water. https://t.co/OaImftXDoH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tell @GeorgeHeyman to deny Cermaq's pesticide permit and protect Clayoqout Sound. https://t.co/rxkiRXkMwj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MikeHudema: "Someone needs to explain to me why wanting clean drinking water makes you an activist, and why proposing to destroy water…]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>