<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Down-to-earth Alan Turing" after reading @BotOnBotAction's latest tweets with scientific Hawking-blackhole-black, enigmatic Mystique-blue and brilliant pearl-white https://t.co/zevPjvTl0U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @BotOnBotAction's overbearing and overly-sentimental tweets were edible they'd be Lemon drizzle cake made with broken glass instead of sugar https://t.co/21wubyOdei]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does Automated Analysis of your tweets reveal about you? How might the analysis be framed? Tweet  #MyJustDessert to find out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Plugged In William Randolph Hearst" after reading @Zendaya's latest tweets with media-savvy Netflix-red, influential Madonna-blonde and powerful Gandalf-grey https://t.co/4UHj1rdKyG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This endearing new book by Veale &amp; Cook makes Charles Dickens's 'A Christmas Carol' seem as endearing as Stalin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @Tip's self-aggrandizing and high-handed tweets were edible they'd be Chantilly cake made with liposuction fat instead of heavy cream https://t.co/LXzprZKI4P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Considerate Patch Adams" after reading @AnupamPkher's latest tweets with funny Joker-purple, overly-sentimental Gump-forest-green and easy-going Gumby-green https://t.co/XYzCAVzAaA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon reads YOU!
Based on @AnupamPkher's powerful and inspirational tweets it pushes Yoda's book Teaching The Next Generation https://t.co/bIuHuCmv9i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Peace-loving Buddhist" after reading @Persie_Official's latest tweets with calm dove-grey, generous knight-silver and peace-loving Lebowski-weed-green https://t.co/Vae8MrcWhm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Take5 things that remind me of @Persie_Official:
1. Obi-wan Kenobi
2. Mickey Mouse
3. Madonna
4. Buddhist
5. Nuns https://t.co/Tl5zK2IHof]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Self-promoting Professor Charles Xavier" after reading @Doutzen's latest tweets with condescending patrician-toga-white, intelligent Blackadder-black and self-promoting Trump-orange https://t.co/LiTg2xjCla]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reading @Doutzen's philosophical and influential tweets feels just like being blown up with Sun Tzu's Chinese gunpowder rocket https://t.co/r9gR80zh35]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Avuncular Jay Gatsby" after reading @Guaje7Villa's latest tweets with social-climbing Ikarus-sun-orange, suave Lucifer-red and generous knight-silver https://t.co/unDdYTZmE6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the best of Albus Dumbledore with the worst of Mick Jagger and you get @Guaje7Villa: whimsical and loving yet preening and posturing https://t.co/8B1b354OFk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Attention-seeking Muhammad Ali" after reading @AdrianaLima's latest tweets with arrogant Oxford-blue, socially-conscious Clooney-grey and attention-seeking Ikarus-sun-orange https://t.co/uAvHfjkqVu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This sincere new book about Twitterbots makes Hermann Hesse's 'Siddhartha' seem as sincere as a forced midwestern smile]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reading @AdrianaLima's powerful and media-savvy tweets feels just like being crushed with Rupert Murdoch's power of the press https://t.co/TVIv9pebhC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Social-climbing Selena Gomez" after reading @DanaPerino's latest tweets with motivational Obama-brown, affable Gumby-green and social-climbing Ikarus-sun-orange https://t.co/iCMaPpghdA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian hackers are watching!
@DanaPerino's educated and influential tweets suggest infection with the TEACHERZ virus https://t.co/8V8DzSik3O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning: the influential TEACHERZ virus uses your own credit-card details to buy you 1000s of fake followers (from India) on Twitter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Media-savvy Angel" after reading @heidiklum's latest tweets with calm lagoon-blue, guileless angel-white and media-savvy Netflix-red https://t.co/n4aaUcq67n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This engrossing new book about computational creativity makes Kazuo Ishiguro's 'Never Let Me Go' seem as engrossing as a tutorial on the sex life of the dung beetle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mate the best of Madonna with the best of Obi-wan Kenobi and you get @heidiklum: influential and attention-grabbing and powerful and patient https://t.co/XZUFRoscg8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Confident Dr. Eldon Tyrell" after reading @peeweeherman's latest tweets with cold cucumber-green, arrogant Hawking-blackhole-black and confident Anchorman-burgundy-red https://t.co/leSYUcZPAD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reading @peeweeherman's lively but prideful tweets feels just like being repelled with Lizzy Bennet's sharp tongue https://t.co/k6A4enLP7m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Media-savvy Ferdinand Magellan" after reading @DMiliband's latest tweets with ruthless Sith-black, fearless warrior-woad-blue and curious Einstein-dandruff-white https://t.co/d2yFiQaXZd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hulk is watching!
Hulk HATE smart humans who remind him of Noam Chomsky. So Hulk SMASH @DMiliband's systematic, intelligent and preachy tweets! https://t.co/7002BvhCdP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Laid-back Stephen Hawking" after reading @Cristiano's latest tweets with inspirational Braveheart-woad-blue, arrogant Trump-orange and laid-back Lebowski-weed-green https://t.co/YOp6Ohhl0G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This stealthy new book by Veale &amp; Cook makes John le Carré's 'Tinker Tailor Soldier Spy' seem as stealthy as a pregnant elephant on crack]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @Cristiano's social-climbing and opinionated tweets were edible they'd be Biscuit Tortoni made with pickled pirate blood instead of rum https://t.co/0b7aoXfROC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Attention-seeking Gustavo Fring" after reading @ash_r_dhanush's latest tweets with ruthless Saruman-white, polite C3PO-gold and attention-seeking Ikarus-sky-blue https://t.co/RYsOHCH4Dj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a confession box in which
Donald Rumsfeld can enjoy @ash_r_dhanush's cunning and energetic tweets
while offering gnostic advice https://t.co/4RLuXmisJM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Socially-aware Sergey Brin" after reading @RGVzoomin's latest tweets with cocky Bieber-blond-yellow, arrogant Anchorman-burgundy-red and socially-aware Democrat-blue https://t.co/y5RukHlPaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @MayorofLondon's volatile and swaggering tweets were edible they'd be Vanilla wafer cake made with white-out fluid instead of milk https://t.co/pSethuUGxs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Peace-loving Sergey Brin" after reading @kelly_clarkson's latest tweets with arrogant Hawking-blackhole-black, cocky Bieber-blond-yellow and peace-loving Lebowski-weed-green https://t.co/NEHxl96pMD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The NSA is watching. It reads your tweets!
It files @kelly_clarkson's wacky and smug tweets under Larry Page nuts https://t.co/0biSrzoA6H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Socially-aware Reginald Jeeves" after reading @DwightHoward's latest tweets with ingenious Pimpernel-scarlet-red, insightful Columbo-beige and socially-aware Democrat-blue https://t.co/A4RozlyeTH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Take5 things that remind me of @DwightHoward:
1. Dr. Greg House
2. Sherlock Holmes
3. Sir Hugo Drax
4. Simone de Beauvoir
5. Computers https://t.co/SQdexpjjD6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Laid-back Sister" after reading @SpongeBob's latest tweets with loving heart-red, generous Buddhist-saffron-orange and laid-back Lebowski-weed-green https://t.co/tqY3q59C4B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This pretentious new book by Veale &amp; Cook makes Jean-Paul Sartre's 'Nausea' seem as pretentious as a donut salesman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lord Voldemort has just unfollowed @SpongeBob
All those powerful and serene tweets remind him too much of Albus Dumbledore https://t.co/vacunRh9aV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Overly-sentimental Professor James Moriarty" after reading @TVCommentBot's latest tweets with arrogant Thor-blond-yellow, ruthless ninja-black and overly-sentimental Gump-forest-green https://t.co/y5Yg7C2uxa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian hackers are watching!
@TVCommentBot's cunning and sarcastic tweets suggest infection with the DR.GREG.H0U5E virus https://t.co/EexnMc2U8C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning: the shrewd DR.GREG.H0U5E virus disguises itself as another piece of pornography on your disk to avoid detection by virus scanners]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Attention-seeking Alexander Fleming" after reading @WWESheamus's latest tweets with curious Einstein-dandruff-white, self-promoting Trump-orange and attention-seeking Ikarus-sun-orange https://t.co/rdhIRCsOcx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is a music hall in which
Madonna can enjoy @WWESheamus's attention-seeking but influential tweets
while singing pop songs https://t.co/DyYPQwY4cD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Good-natured Jay Gatsby" after reading @ParineetiChopra's latest tweets with suave Pimpernel-scarlet-red, generous prince-purple and social-climbing Ikarus-sun-orange https://t.co/Om3E3Wz9pl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This imaginative new book about Twitterbots makes Roald Dahl's 'Charlie and the Chocolate Factory' seem as imaginative as a door knob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the best of Albus Dumbledore with the best of Santa Claus and you get @ParineetiChopra: inspiring and inspirational and jolly and avuncular https://t.co/5tD7IzWwhN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Self-promoting Troy McClure" after reading @iamwill's latest tweets with affable Gumby-green, media-savvy Britney-blonde-yellow and self-promoting Trump-orange https://t.co/ncPVTepXKb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Overly-sentimental Devil" after reading @TheBatman's latest tweets with devious demon-red, cunning wolf-grey and overly-sentimental Gump-forest-green https://t.co/vaxm7oyyru]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Take5 things that remind me of @TheBatman:
1. John McCain
2. Adolf Hitler
3. Philosophers
4. Assassins
5. Dogs https://t.co/ZC3ays1jIb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Holier-than-thou Piers Morgan" after reading @sneijder101010's latest tweets with self-promoting Trump-orange, cocky Bieber-blond-yellow and media-savvy Netflix-red https://t.co/OIhXEbfM1W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yosemite Sam has just unfollowed @sneijder101010
All those nonchalant and self-assured tweets remind him too much of Bugs Bunny https://t.co/VeKSoDK9ot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This elegant new book about Twitterbots makes Virginia Woolf's 'Mrs. Dalloway' seem as elegant as a drunken giraffe on roller skates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Brave Dave Lee Roth" after reading @realDonaldTrump's latest tweets with over-the-top Bollywood-tandoori-red, loud Yankee-blue and spirited knight-silver https://t.co/rehyGOWWr1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Well-meaning Leonardo Da Vinci" after reading @BotOnBotAction's latest tweets with inspirational Hawking-blackhole-black, artful fox-red and smart brain-grey https://t.co/AHkJoe5PoY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hulk is watching!
Hulk HATE heroic humans who remind him of crusaders. So Hulk SMASH @BotOnBotAction's impassioned, courageous and indomitable tweets! https://t.co/wROb5HIJBD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does Automated Analysis of your tweets reveal about you? How might the analysis be framed? Tweet  #TickleMeHulk to find out.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This dark new book about Twitterbots makes Stephen King's 'Carrie' seem as dark as an old tea cosy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Media-savvy Marco Polo" after reading @DelBoy_ofah's latest tweets with observant Columbo-beige, curious Bart Simpson-yellow and media-savvy Netflix-red https://t.co/upmMmI7XdQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon reads YOU!
Based on @DelBoy_ofah's observant and influential tweets it pushes Marco Polo's book Opening New Markets https://t.co/PnVTqoiDtV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Socially-aware Amelia Earhart" after reading @LeoDiCaprio's latest tweets with tenacious lobster-red, attention-seeking Ikarus-sun-orange and socially-aware Democrat-blue https://t.co/9CzgHiIj0l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hulk is watching!
Hulk HATE fearless humans who remind him of lionesses. So Hulk SMASH @LeoDiCaprio's strong, defiant and ferocious tweets! https://t.co/vFu1FllGhs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Attention-seeking Detective" after reading @edsheeran's latest tweets with observant Eeyore-grey, ingenious Pimpernel-scarlet-red and attention-seeking Ikarus-sun-orange https://t.co/9jDj7UcRPD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to Amazon, people who bought this fun book about Twitter 'bots' also bought:
-   Douglas Adams's 'The Hitchhiker's Guide to the Galaxy'
-   Jane Morrison's 'Eating'
 How very fun!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Action-oriented Meghan Markle" after reading @VickyPattison's latest tweets with social-climbing Blackadder-black, pretty dove-grey and socially-conscious Democrat-blue https://t.co/DOi2DSkolJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hulk is watching!
Hulk HATE eccentric humans who remind him of eccentrics. So Hulk SMASH @VickyPattison's nutty, charming and wacky tweets! https://t.co/GTNaQBRBHa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Holier-than-thou Saddam Hussein" after reading @AnnaKendrick47's latest tweets with self-aggrandizing Trump-orange, cunning Saruman-white and holier-than-thou priest-black https://t.co/sUB24QeyVL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This user-friendly new book about computational creativity makes Alex Comfort's 'The Joy of Sex' seem as user-friendly as a tangle of wire coat]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @AnnaKendrick47's hyper-logical and crafty tweets were edible they'd be Battenberg cake made with foot cheese instead of marzipan https://t.co/DX7TXLfSxY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Self-aggrandizing Piers Morgan" after reading @DrBaileyGSM's latest tweets with media-savvy Netflix-red, cocky Bieber-blond-yellow and self-promoting Trump-orange https://t.co/endAWgNUfC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NETFLIX watches YOU!
Based on @DrBaileyGSM's condescending and arrogant tweets it pushes films about Detective Fiction and/or Sherlock Holmes https://t.co/Wje3Qu55En]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Laid-back Blanche DuBois" after reading @soundaryaarajni's latest tweets with well-mannered cadet-grey, condescending patrician-toga-white and laid-back Lebowski-weed-green https://t.co/kg23VZH9XN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Take5 things that remind me of @soundaryaarajni:
1. Alan Sugar
2. Lizzy Bennet
3. Doves
4. Gandalf the Grey
5. Butterflies https://t.co/yLrS7up8Sm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Holier-than-thou Conspiracy" after reading @marieltpadilla's latest tweets with devious Gollum-grey, elitist patrician-toga-white and holier-than-thou priest-black https://t.co/Rvvkhw9c9r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This readable new book about computational creativity makes Armistead Maupin's 'Tales Of The City' seem as readable as a legal document]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teacher is watching
Following @marieltpadilla's witty and entertaining tweets is like one long lecture on bending the law from Saul Goodman https://t.co/VZkLs9MDSa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Attention-seeking Sigmund Freud" after reading @StephenAtHome's latest tweets with observant Columbo-beige, insightful Yoda-green and attention-seeking Ikarus-sun-orange https://t.co/Zf6xRQ11Ao]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian hackers are watching!
@StephenAtHome's cunning and probing tweets suggest infection with the DR.GREG.H0U5E virus https://t.co/jCylFd5D2Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warning: the condescending DR.GREG.H0U5E virus replaces 'dear colleagues' to 'dear children' in your outgoing work emails]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Eager-to-impress Rocket Raccoon" after reading @tomhanks's latest tweets with tactical Coriolanus Snow-white, energetic Tigger-orange and eager-to-impress Ikarus-sky-blue https://t.co/s3PtCY5XEn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teacher is watching
Following @tomhanks's arrogant but observant tweets is like one long lecture on solving mysteries from Sherlock Holmes https://t.co/148OU61iyM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Attention-seeking Dean Winchester" after reading @cocorocha's latest tweets with funny Joker-purple, easy-going Lebowski-weed-green and attention-seeking Ikarus-sun-orange https://t.co/yc0a4FJYS7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This substantial new book about bots makes Roger Penrose's 'The Emperor's New Mind' seem as substantial as a dragonfly wing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mix the best of Quentin Tarantino with the best of Muhammad Ali and you get @cocorocha: observant and entertaining and witty and sardonic https://t.co/1dirQRKBc1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Media-savvy Baron Munchausen" after reading @usainbolt's latest tweets with self-promoting Trump-orange, attention-seeking Ikarus-sun-orange and media-savvy Britney-blonde-yellow https://t.co/AzX2qsVa5H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon reads YOU!
Based on @usainbolt's accomplished and powerful tweets it pushes Albus Dumbledore's book Running A School For Gifted Teens https://t.co/Iko8f4k1Af]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @edsheeran's probing and attention-grabbing tweets were edible they'd be Sponge cake made with white-out fluid instead of milk https://t.co/VhWXBW12IJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon reads YOU!
Based on @iamwill's sweet and vivacious tweets it pushes Marilyn Monroe's book Starring In Hollywood Movies https://t.co/YX9xNjL686]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Eager-to-impress G. Gordon Liddy" after reading @prakashraaj's latest tweets with strident Trump-orange, loyal Eeyore-grey and eager-to-impress Ikarus-sun-orange https://t.co/dbRNA9Xcgz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This silly new book about Twitter 'bots' makes William Shakespeare's 'Much Ado About Nothing' seem as silly as a 4 door coupe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mate the best of Albus Dumbledore with the best of Bridget Jones and you get @prakashraaj: eccentric and powerful and spunky and fun-loving https://t.co/0pkVmonudo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Easy-going Miss Jane Marple" after reading @LittleMix's latest tweets with sharp-witted Blackadder-black, insightful Gandalf-grey and observant Columbo-beige https://t.co/9XuVx0pglk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should Benedict Cumberbatch or Jeremy Brett play @LittleMix on TV?
Each played the equally brilliant and probing Sherlock Holmes https://t.co/pDxYqI4OXM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Media-savvy Jack Nicholson" after reading @RobertDowneyJr's latest tweets with charismatic Adonis-tan-orange, charming park-green and media-savvy Netflix-red https://t.co/6dCVdObwDq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hulk is watching!
Hulk HATE inspiring humans who remind him of champions. So Hulk SMASH @RobertDowneyJr's smug, resolute and dominant tweets! https://t.co/6bklhAAFUu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I painted "Holier-than-thou Quasimodo" after reading @ladygaga's latest tweets with tenacious Scarlett-scarlet, loyal Groot-brown and kind-hearted Shrek-green https://t.co/850ipJqYtg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This informed new book about computational creativity makes Dava Sobel's 'Longitude' seem as informed as a pitch fork waving witch burner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If @ladygaga's intimidating and pompous tweets were edible they'd be Hot milk cake made with anthrax spores instead of sugar https://t.co/sH6Zixkrmr]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>