<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Trendspotting at #SIAL2017 reveals lots of #quinoa, #beantobar chocolate, #plantbased #protein snacks and more. https://t.co/Ev8BykYqO3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes working for @FoodNavigatorUS is like an episode of Mr. Roger's Neighborhood, for ex yesterday's fantastic tour of @QueenVicProduce https://t.co/Yhb9ReMfb6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#glutenfree may no longer be 'hot' but it is an industry standard that can't be ignored https://t.co/uTbOQRcRxZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The (multi) million dollar question: What does clean label actually mean? https://t.co/nfBnXJk9gp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#ecommerce is gaining importance in the #food and #beverage sector: https://t.co/AfXZyxnADi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out how @DrinkVitaCup is making it easier to for people to take their daily vitamins https://t.co/INslgkxk2B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is trying to define 'healthy' futile? https://t.co/ajZyR7jGjy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Companies must move fwrd w new Nutrition Facts labels even as they wait for #fiber &amp; #sugar guidance https://t.co/cL1cT27BhS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pressure is on for @WholeFoods to sell, but is @Albertsons the best match? https://t.co/aN6HGYyx2q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Neat! Aquaponics at Niagara College Canada offer a system where you can eat the greens AND fish used in system. Add compost &amp; its zero waste https://t.co/4hmu50Ceyy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#craftbrew is such a big trend that @niagaracollege now offers a 2 yr course in brewing craft #beer! https://t.co/x3dPzXx4nJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AlexBromage Ah. Fair point.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TalentBranded: Good story from @ECrawfordwrites on how #smallbiz used a good strategy for #influencermarketing &amp; moved the needle!! htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a growing demand for diabetic friendly foods https://t.co/dj4HqnqLem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are there lessons to be learned from Soylent's recent bad luck with recalls? https://t.co/OUlde8XL9Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will consumers embrace "clean" meat? https://t.co/nfBnXJBKEZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The diabetic food market is worth $60.4 billion: https://t.co/dj4Hqn9amO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #glutenfree trend may be tapering off, but it is still 6x higher than it was a decade ago: https://t.co/uTbOQRcRxZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@DrinkVitaCup #coffee offers more than an eye-opening jolt of #Caffeine. It also packs a day's worth of vitamins https://t.co/INslgkOUU9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A reductionist approach to defining healthy in terms of nutrients is an outdated mode of thinking https://t.co/ajZyR725s0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The top three challenges associated with the new Nutrition Facts rule that is set to go into effect in about a year: https://t.co/cL1cT27BhS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@HonestSeth says #plantbased @BeyondMeat burgers are an opportunity for American farmers not a threat. https://t.co/S1Y1e0U5uS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marrying @Albertsons &amp; @WholeFoods would bring 2 'average operational structures' together &amp; not create a great one https://t.co/aN6HGYgWaS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@BeyondMeat is feeding 100 staffers on Capitol Hill in DC and sharing how #plantbased is more sustainable than animal based #protein https://t.co/ovLLOuhTET]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EWatsonWrites: Trying to get your head around #Smartlabel? Checkout this video from @ECrawfordwrites with @BumbleBeeFoods  https://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#natural, #organic and #functional foods and beverages are shining stars in otherwise flat category https://t.co/AfXZyxFc1S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Soylent is back in the hot seat with another recall: https://t.co/OUlde8G9Lg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to make #glutenfree and #DairyFree baked goods taste good and not like sawdust: https://t.co/uTbOQRuspx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can cleaning up food/beverage labels by ditching "chemicals" &amp; undesirable ingredients help flagging legacy brands? https://t.co/nfBnXJBKEZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is the #food and #beverage industry stuck in a race to the bottom that values cost cutting over #innovation? https://t.co/AfXZyxnADi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ppl might forget to take their vitamins, but they don't forget their coffee. Can combining them improve compliance? https://t.co/INslgkxk2B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will #FDA ban the use of the word #healthy from food &amp; beverage marketing? https://t.co/ajZyR725s0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What would a delay to the new Nutrition Facts rule actually mean for industry players? https://t.co/cL1cT1Q0qk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@WholeFoods represents about 20% of the roughly $50B #organic food segment, making it attractive to @Albertsons https://t.co/aN6HGYgWaS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most experts agree that #foodsafety will remain a top priority for FDA under Trump https://t.co/hqPyXmTLc7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can bottled water be sustainable? @FlowWater is trying: https://t.co/ZlAZe62z1n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["God knows when we will see #GMO final regulation," warns expert noting deadlines set by Congress are often missed https://t.co/gmFO5Tljx6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Discover the three goals of Hain Celestial's venture arm: https://t.co/HWpSFFC6Vq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Retailers focused on international products are upping their game to attract a wider cross section of consumers https://t.co/b9dGU9JBgU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rebranding for Puris makes products seem less like raw ingredients and more like finished products https://t.co/Lp4GCwK9yG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can @hamptoncreek do for the chicken (and cow and pig) what it did for the egg in Just Mayo? https://t.co/w2HM3ICFhv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jackfruit continues to gain traction in the US as a #plantbased alternative to shredded meat https://t.co/kV2iPDawtD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out what is so great about green banana flour: https://t.co/7WivRCybrK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can high-end water stand in for a glass of wine at dinner? https://t.co/4kVmnMWOWP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Meat grown in a lab instead of a farm CAN be regulated under the current laws, according to one @DWTLaw lawyer: https://t.co/h44mk1QKsv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out from the @Beekman1802Boys how giving others a helping hand is good for business: https://t.co/oIBx3p6TZJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out from @pnuffcrunch how extra crunch can help create a clean ingredient deck: https://t.co/EmIm0obana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Kellogg just being nice by giving retailers more time to pay, or has it lost its leverage? https://t.co/X5GqBsDfyL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Growing consumer interest in global flavors puts pressure on retailers to increase offerings of ethnic products https://t.co/b9dGUa1c8s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The former World Food Processing steps out at IFT w a new name and logo: Puris https://t.co/Lp4GCwK9yG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a new player in the clean meat space, adding legitimacy and pushing the timeline forward https://t.co/w2HM3Il4pX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Chobani made itself in the Greek yogurt category, but is now taking aim at the non-Greek category: https://t.co/Djlwsv24R2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Better Bean Co gets a boost from Hein Celestial's Cultivate Ventures arm: https://t.co/HWpSFFC6Vq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out from @EWatsonWrites what the next hot ingredients are from #IFT2017 https://t.co/cMnBcow4js]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @eatsnowmonkey: Check out our co-founders' latest interview with @ECrawfordwrites from @FoodNavigatorUS! https://t.co/qT0KIZnNoW #EatNoE…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Refrigerated baby food continues to gain traction https://t.co/HAXe8VYyYM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The game-changing impact of Amazon buying Whole Foods: https://t.co/A0IVZPLNKy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why don't more grocery shoppers scan QR codes? https://t.co/DQDS8jvgJQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have a new food idea but not sure others will think it is great? @kickstarter could help w proof of concept https://t.co/HAXe8Wg9Qk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What will become of the 365 brand now that Amazon owns Whole Foods? https://t.co/A0IVZQ3oC6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Online grocery shopping is growing fast w 43% of #Millennials buying food online in 2017 vs 28% in 2016 https://t.co/Fi5yImjAOv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The emerging refrigerated baby food market stretches into Canada with Keen Bean: https://t.co/A0IVZPLNKy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What does @amazon's purchase of @WholeFoods mean? https://t.co/A0IVZPLNKy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The stereotype of grocery shoppers as women is changing as more men take care of at least half of food buying needs https://t.co/hZEFPiOmVj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are getting excited about  @FoodVisionEvent in Chicago. If you have a killer new product, you could come for free https://t.co/4cbmNCNtC9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you have the next best thing in food &amp; beverage? Apply to take center stage @FoodVisionEvent in Chicago this fall https://t.co/4cbmNCNtC9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rolling back school lunch standards bc they're difficult to comply w ‘doesn’t make a lick of sense’ says @RepTimRyan at #OrganicWeekDC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OrganicTrade: @RepJohnFaso #organic is like motherhood and apple pie #OrganicWeekDC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[76% of Americans who buy organic do so for healthier food, 33% to help environment and 22% bc its convenient says @surveyfunk #OrganicWeekDC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[39% of Americans think #GMOs are worse for health, and this view is more likely held by younger people, says @surveyfunk at #OrganicWeekDC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[54% of Americans say they are paying more attn to eating healthy food, which is good for #organic business says @surveyfunk #OrganicWeekDC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Proposed budget is a "no go" as is says @RepJimmyPanetta at #OrganicWeekDC He adds its unfortunate that is direction Trump wants to go.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More than 82% of US households buy #organic, according to @OrganicTrade research presented at #OrganicWeekDC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PeggyMiars: 80% of US households buy organic. It's a nonpartisan issue. #OrganicWeekDC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales of #organic reached $47B in 2016, up 8.6% from prior year and up from just $1B in 1990, @OrganicTrade reveals at #OrganicWeekDC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eating insects is a growing trend, but they could help fight #obesity in another way: https://t.co/mDpzZ9MNIV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@GrowPlantBased will meet with #FDA this week to discuss use of terminology such as milk for plant-based products https://t.co/KGYG4QlsiV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out from @cumberlandfarms what it takes for convenience stores to offer fresh, healthy options https://t.co/SnorwLznVU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is the meal-kit category ready for consolidation? https://t.co/ObePN6s7lU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@American_Heart says total #fat should not be considered in the definition of healthy, but saturated fat should https://t.co/hnvbIQJQf3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Safe+Fair fights stigma that ppl w peanut #allergies eat 'weird stuff' by using premium packaging for its products https://t.co/s1bKPGWegX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@MichelleObama defends her legacy and the stricter school meal standards saying it is not okay to feed kids 'crap' https://t.co/p5pxg01TsD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can we fight childhood #obesity? @billclinton says ants might give us the answer https://t.co/mDpzZa4oAt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out how @DnaturalsCo accelerated rapid growth in the crowded bar category: https://t.co/Ob70T37YuM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FDA needs to stop picking and choosing which regulations it wants to enforce, say milk producers https://t.co/KGYG4QD3at]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@NACSonline convenience store members will begin promoting @drinkupwater to help shoppers stay healthy, hydrated https://t.co/SnorwLQZku]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Detailed analysis by @EWatsonWrites of the meal kit market in the US, including who uses them &amp; the threat they pose https://t.co/ObePN6JIds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@American_Heart says "healthy" should be reserved for products that meet 2015 Dietary Guidelines https://t.co/hnvbIQJQf3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@PepsiCo teams with @PHAnews to offer healthier options https://t.co/kjRTq7OBbQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Skeeter Nut Free gets a makeover https://t.co/s1bKPHdPFx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@MichelleObama encourages consumers to buy products w new Nutrition Facts labels &amp; support transparency w their $ https://t.co/p5pxg0juRd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cooperation may not be as fun as a 'blood-on-the-floor fight' but its best way to solve social problems @billclinton https://t.co/4cbmNCvSKB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can @DnaturalsCo cut through the clutter in the bar segment? https://t.co/KGYG4QlsiV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think you have an awesome new food or beverage? Let us know and potentially win a spot our Trailblazer competition https://t.co/4cbmNCvSKB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Milk safety officials vote in favor of ensuring the proper use of the standardized names for dairy milk https://t.co/KGYG4QlsiV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @1WorldSync: @1WorldSync is featured in @FoodNavigatorUS Soup-to-Nuts Podcast: Driving #ecommerce with #omnichannel marketing. https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @packaged_facts: Now on sale: "Energy &amp; Sports Drinks: U.S. Market Trends &amp; Opportunities"

https://t.co/7USEDRuyJF

#mrx #energydrinks…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RaboFoodAgri: New Rabo Food &amp; Agri Innovation Fund invests in F&amp;A startups. #innovation #agtech #foodtech check https://t.co/kyiw6fvAg2…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Members of Canadian Parliament decide today whether to require #GMO labeling https://t.co/F7QMqKANoX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@NACSonline and @cumberlandfarms commit to @PHAnews to make more healthy food available in convenience stores https://t.co/SnorwLQZku]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>