<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KuperSimon: My visit to Kylian Mbappe's hometown and old coaches - and why Greater Paris is world's best talent pool in football (and y…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Simone Veil will be admitted into the Panthéon tomorrow. Here is her 1974 speech to the Assemblée Nationale  https://t.co/4e9bKjqi5Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FHeisbourg: Sacré match dans la moiteur débilitante de Sotchi. Les Uruguaiens formidables face aux Portugais non moins pugnaces.Les Cél…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@duncanrobinson @alanbeattie @thomasforth Actually, it's best when you're 3-0 down at half-time, have a man sent off walking back to the dressing room and come back to win 4-3 https://t.co/EwUKaRLq3Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @j_stafford88: This rambling, shallow and morally irresponsible paean to parochialism should end Streeck's status as the West's sexiest…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Delicious: Geoffrey Smith explores the career of Charlie Haden https://t.co/l8rDI4pokQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here is all the @FinancialTimes's comentary analysis this week on the future of the EU in one place https://t.co/N26J3BZtqE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very good piece from @bronwenmaddox on this week's extraordinary cabinet ructions https://t.co/XxEnQ07ooB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@muradahmed and @jburnmurdoch are having a very good tournament. Here they give us the World Cup in five charts https://t.co/NxboTiIvGB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TimHarford: My @FT colleagues have had enough, it seems. Here's Martin Wolf on "The Irredeemable Folly Of A No Deal Brexit" - which sou…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@holland_tom I envisage a CRITIQUE of Southgate's JUDGEMENT in leaving out Sterling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ChrisGiles_: I recently argued with @prospect_clark in @FT about whether economics had failed. 

Now we’re going to have it out in pers…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This superb column by @EdwardGLuce is essential reading for liberals who persist in believing that the arc of history bends towards justice https://t.co/hw0zRIUeSH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@TonyBarber8 on how Poland is desperately trying to stay in the right side of Trump https://t.co/peooMgqEaX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@holland_tom England's search for a way through the Belgian defence will resemble human reason's groping after the unknowable thing in itself. #critiqueofpurereason]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is very good: @MehreenKhn and @jimbrunsden's handy cut-out-and-keep guide to eurozone reform https://t.co/I1b1vSFmbn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sundersays Quoted British Future's research in a piece on Southgate in Saturday's FT https://t.co/O9q25sfhpq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ChassNews: Head to head - @IMateosylago vs @HansWernerSinn debate #Meseberg and eurozone reforms : https://t.co/vvc71Z9RHH via @financi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@IMateosylago and Hans-Werner Sinn debate the respective merits of the Macron and Merkel plans for eurozone reform https://t.co/3xUHJMYyzy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@marinab52 @olivialanguage I endorse this message.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TonyTassell: and here is @dsquareddigest with an @FT op-ed on banking and how the debtor/creditor relationship opens itself up to abuse…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Work in the age of intelligent machines: @martinwolf_ distills a very interesting sounding lecture by @AdairTurnerUK https://t.co/zHetYnPiwZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Emmanuel Macron is not rightwing https://t.co/WDejy8DR90]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The great David Goldblatt has died, leaving behind an extraordinary visual record of apartheid South Africa https://t.co/uWqZ96xTYp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This superb essay on post-crash politics in Britain by @HelenHet20 has won the Bernard Crick prize  https://t.co/NYAgg2sZYl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AliceFishburn: Yes! @sarahoconnor_ picks up the Orwell Prize for exposing Britain's social evils with her amazing piece on Blackpool. W…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BMW to the British government: "If at the end of the day the supply chain will have a stop at the border, then we cannot produce our products in the UK" https://t.co/SiYwGNT2tC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@gideonrachman on how Trump has enabled the emergence of a "nationalist international" https://t.co/pvzGBEaN1M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is lovely: a tribute to the first Orange Juice album, You Can’t Hide Your Love Forever https://t.co/qE1HPAMAmT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elephant and Castle will be fun tonight #Colombia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @greenmiranda: Anyone who has seen French kids getting ticked off for bad table manners has seen this poor kid's expression before. Macr…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Jderbyshire: A last nudge for my paean to Southgate and his boys ahead of the Panama game https://t.co/anekibxK60]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tremendous tale of rural ructions in Oxfordshire by @Grepsul  https://t.co/9ux8MRLIOP https://t.co/kbSNtPnshZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lovers rock in Windrush Square https://t.co/rs0DCrF3dR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Domino tournament, Windrush Square, Brixton #Windrush70 https://t.co/aJXdvp9ru4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fine essay by @Jesse_Norman on Adam Smith and why the theory of moral sentiments matters https://t.co/ALBlm3VAtI https://t.co/9IRqE70avB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @artangled: Obsessive and haunting: a philosopher’s photographs at @narrativeP https://t.co/W5pd1iznvR https://t.co/GD0hNnUjNs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A last nudge for my paean to Southgate and his boys ahead of the Panama game https://t.co/anekibxK60]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Edgecliffe: "The word 'indeed' is of course a crucial lubricant, especially when added to 'cooler heads must prevail'..." @FT editorial…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@johnharris1969 Ssshh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may be some time https://t.co/81xBpehWyO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Unlike in the 1930s, there is still a global order to defend” - @EdwardGLuce seeks cold comfort https://t.co/0zPZlkUuA7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This by @sterling7 is really rather extraordinary  https://t.co/NT7XmDfLE0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nick Timmins on the NHS at 70 - it's sustainable, but we're going to have to pay for it https://t.co/3ujrpm2jDZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've written something about why I really rather like Gareth Southgate and this England team https://t.co/O9q25sfhpq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ft_wealth: Lady Edwina Grosvenor talks to @jderbyshire about her prison philanthropy and the frustratingly fast turnover of justice min…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rodrikdani: I understand that borders are morally arbitrary and that there are more and less humane ways of managing them. Does anyone…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very good @lemondefr interview with Julian Jackson about de Gaulle, Britain and Europe https://t.co/Rx93U3rnWa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is such a powerful piece by @niamhnih https://t.co/OjXaTqpoAi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a very interesting thread on Pankaj Mishra’s LRB piece on Mounk and Moyn https://t.co/i4WbQjoc6J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leorobsonwriter Indeed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TimHarford @BaldwinRE Read some of that over the weekend. Really interesting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cavell's range and curiosity was extraordinary - Wittgenstein, Shakespeare, music, the Hollywood comedy of remarriage ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very sorry to learn of the death of Stanley Cavell - one of the most unusual and subtle minds of his generation. And a distinctive prose stylist to boot. This Mark Greif piece on "Cavell as educator" from 2011 is very good https://t.co/C3GRb0JvK3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[V good by @leorobsonwriter though I think distinction between aestheticism &amp; partisanship not quite as clear cut https://t.co/SzYcX8zztZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BlakeBaileyOn @NewYorker And an eight-page special supplement consacré à lui.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NewYorker .@BlakeBaileyOn right to say Roth is bigger in France even than in US. Struck by huge display of PR’s books in rue de Rennes Fnac in Paris.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wonderful @NewYorker podcast about Philip Roth https://t.co/n2shg0E6pa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SocialHistoryOx: Look guys, it’s either full communism or a Hobbesian state of nature mixed with 19th century colonialism where you all…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MalmstromEU: Writing in the @FT about the need for reform of the @WTO system.

https://t.co/jlWo7XYWu7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overheard at the FT: "Do we cap up gorgonzola?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you haven't read Jerry Cohen's wonderful If You're an Egalitarian, How Come You're So Rich?, you can now do so for nothing online https://t.co/drdMMsY0zi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EU trade commissioner @MalmstromEU for @ftopinion on why we mustn't give up on the rules-based global trading system https://t.co/fwFcjgZnLU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In this fascinating interview with @lemondefr, Alexandre Benalla seems pretty unrepentant  https://t.co/wENIC1ErPI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @georgemagnus1: Another RT for this excellent piece which is even better on 2nd read : Brexit lays bare the extremes that define British…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unforgiving - Macron seems to have lost @lemondefr https://t.co/Ge5yXWkknQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The EU should give May's Brexit plan a helping hand, says @IMateosylago https://t.co/voNawe7GDZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Splendid @henrymance sketch of Raab and Robbins at the Brexit select c'ttee today  https://t.co/s3cqA3ilvB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent blow-by-blow run down of "l'affaire Benalla" https://t.co/THxyTX7GU7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MESandbu: I'd be curious to know if other non-British (and indeed British) friends of Britain feel the same as what I describe here. An…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting piece from @markhleonard on why the Chinese discern method in the Trumpian madness https://t.co/2Rc5YGjwOB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Britain used to congratulate itself on being sober and pragmatic. But it was always more extreme than we thought - economically as well as politically. Excellent column by @MESandbu https://t.co/FDA9IYEn2J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alexandre Benalla could be the protagonist in a 'polar' written by Michel Houellebecq - diplomatic passport, National Assembly pass, the keys to the Macrons' house in Le Touquet. This story gets stranger and stranger https://t.co/41SMeIxwae]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@sarahoconnor_ calls on millennials to flex their political muscles https://t.co/WiJIrqMNgL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Britain is now seen from Europe, part 94: "The UK post-Brexit, outpost of Trumpism?" https://t.co/nsC0naC5s0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At the RAH for the BBC Radiophonic Workshop prom https://t.co/leJFcO4oCE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @johnthornhillft: My latest column on China’s response to its ‘Sputnik moment ‘ #AI  https://t.co/gWwHjulabk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what I gather the young people call a banger https://t.co/kHjfrUG3gk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevenpoole And to make things worse, Twitter is an engine for generating tu quoque "arguments" by the bucketload.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @gideonrachman: Here is my latest on how Putin's world-view is simultaneously completely cynical and utterly sincere https://t.co/Ut56Uf…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One for the hipster tactics crowd https://t.co/EhSJY5NRrp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobPollardMCFC https://t.co/v36W0YWfTx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philosophybites Rue Monsieur Le Prince]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's quite a vitrine: Foucault, Jakobson, Lévi-Strauss, Heidegger, Habermas, Agamben https://t.co/SSRm1h3M7s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DanielKatz6 A 23-storey tower in Les Gobelins.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When my friend told me she and her partner had moved to the 13eme arrondissement, I wasn’t sure. Now I understand. https://t.co/bM8FbOzG81]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And this in the Cimetière Montparnasse- a family wiped out at Auschwitz https://t.co/gjXcSMNO4J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always brought up short in Paris by plaques like this (this is a lycée in the 14eme) https://t.co/1z7AZvUAq5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Soyez réalistes, demandez l'impossible", 1968-2018 https://t.co/fPZmschmZX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But Librairie Philosophique J. Vrin nearby miraculously hangs on https://t.co/YZ0EcjfQhJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The site of what used to be the Presses Universitiaires de France is now a Pret A Manger #latecapitalism https://t.co/bHVRzzMjP3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republican vernacular, Paris 14eme https://t.co/nNitlW0OBj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Commune agitée de Raspail" https://t.co/3hQcGM0Lff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EmilyZFeng: "Like the panopticon itself, it is the fear of being watched that is the most powerful tool of all." A @FT magazine piece w…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paris, 6eme https://t.co/WZax16lsMA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sound Business (1981), Molly Dineen’s first film, about Coxsone Sound, narrated by Mikey Dread https://t.co/HCga51RpRt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @holland_tom: Losing our wildlife, trashing our sacred landscapes, destroying our country's beauty: these, if they happen, will be lamen…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joe Harriot’s school in Kingston, JA pays tribute to the great saxophonist https://t.co/SUgABe5EGi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remnick on Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez as the heir to Michael Harrington’s “left wing of the possible” https://t.co/P98B5WRD0a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one has given the "green light to designer babies" just yet - bracing good sense from Emily Jackson on the Nuffield Council on Bioethics report on genome editing https://t.co/4QmQZiv2yI]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>