<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Girls are like internet domain names, the ones I like are already taken.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome football t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the football lovers in your life!   http://t.co/cw6Gzfgghu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plastic surgeons can do almost anything with a nose these days, except keep it out of other people's business]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never go to a movie in Poland, you'll end up setting behind a Pole.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think MTV should consider using subtitles. Half the time, even I can't understand what the **** I'm talking about.  Ozzy Osbourne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When Life Gives You Questions, Google has Answers - AJ Carpio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sovereign invigorator of the body is exercise, and of all the exercises walking is the best. - Thomas Jefferson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you can look in the mirror and smile at what you see, then there's hope for you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wait a minute, Doc. Ah --  Are you telling me you built a time machine --  out of a DeLorean? - Marty McFly, Back to the Future]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool Batman Comfy Throw - Stay Warm and Cool :&gt;)  http://t.co/bra2RLx4TB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That which is bitter to endure may be sweet to remember. - Thomas Fuller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes, you have to roll a hard six. Commander William Adama]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Keys to Good Marketing for Your Business  http://t.co/0C8kO1HMKA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Joe Tex  http://t.co/BxOoAwLdjx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Try not. Do, or do not. There is no try. - Yoda, The Empire Strikes Back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Motown, Motown, that's my era. Those are my people.  Hillary Clinton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Wendy's  http://t.co/EKgZE88Df0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Calling upon my years of experience, I froze at the controls. - Stirling Moss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take twice as long to eat half as much. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Babysitter: a teenager who acts like a Grownup while grownups are acting like teenagers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's very strange writing science fiction in a world that moves as fast as ours does. - Daniel Keys Moran]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every great batter works on the theory that the pitcher is more afraid of him than he is of the pitcher. - Ty Cobb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get a Hunger Games Mockingjay Pin - http://t.co/42MtLYbx7I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About The Beginning Of Christian Religion  http://t.co/0X9EaEKZXs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Rufus  http://t.co/naUwwQNSAA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some of the greatest Hollywood actors are not the award winners, but those congratulating them on their triumph]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Lobo the Classic Rock Group?  http://t.co/PQsJGfpe7l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A mind once stretched by a new idea never regains its original dimensions. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of LA Gear  http://t.co/8aKDROUBqg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of Stargate Universe  http://t.co/kUVlNEhy80]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do you judge me as a musician, John? All I'm interested in is making money. Glenn Miller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You've got to say, I think that if I keep working at this and want it badly enough I can have it. It's called perseverance. - Lee Iacocca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to J.R.R. Tolkien  http://t.co/wvU0T7jDFf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Giant Swiss Army Knife - with Over 87 Tools!  http://t.co/jAfDejhFbU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is A SERP exactly?  http://t.co/SOrXjGrO8L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never dance in a puddle when there's a hole in your shoe (it's always best to take your shoes off first). --&gt; John D. Rhodes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to 3D Printing  http://t.co/2CFgy5ZYoI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We thought you was a toad! - Delmar, O Brother Where Art Thou?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome basketball t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the basketball lovers in your life!   http://t.co/TskqjwIwJS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Importance of Keywords for Search Engine Optimization (SEO)  http://t.co/Voaoy8RTFy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fifty per cent of rock is having a good time. - Roger Daltrey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about necessary foods for your prepper pantry!  http://t.co/t0r3pnQr81]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Superhero caped glasses - totally cool!  http://t.co/AjsrTSHnu4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Isley Brothers  http://t.co/JQ0u5JoBF5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space or science fiction has become a dialect for our time. - Doris Lessing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spock, where the hell's the power you promised?" - Kirk  "One damn minute, admiral" - Spock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Gary Lewis and the Playboys  http://t.co/JR3Gif628X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Overview of the USSSA Youth Sports Organization  http://t.co/rLWlGMzOXh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The years are adding up when it takes us longer to get rested than it does to get tired. . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Foreigner  http://t.co/WSQR2tOrPV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Overview of Domestic Adoption  http://t.co/Of77RVc4fj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have always felt I was more accurately a Hard Rock musician.  - Geddy Lee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How to Create an Effective Company Blog  http://t.co/qZBTRMewlZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Adoption Part II - the Bulgaria Phase  http://t.co/fKnbKFCmUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't preach a boy about his problems. Just remind him that you, too , were a Nincompoop at his age.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making money is art and working is art and good business is the best art.   Andy Warhol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Bee Gees  http://t.co/0XfNdXYZAk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can I build a high quality free website?  http://t.co/27psxoaF07]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of the animals except for man know that the principle business of life is to enjoy it. - Samuel Butler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winning is everything. The only ones who remember you when you come second are your wife and your dog. - Damon Hill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Personally, I'm always ready to learn, although I do not always like being taught. - Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every day, in every way, I am getting better and better. - Emilie Coue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of American Hamburgers  http://t.co/9F3AAtvDaT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Budget: A domestic quarrel!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to 3D Printing  http://t.co/2CFgy5ZYoI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About DotNetNuke for Corporations  http://t.co/pCCnApWKa5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahh Fond Memories of San Antonio  http://t.co/j54JGE2PcV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you think, your mouth is closed, but your mind keeps on talking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 15 - The Cowden Protocol  http://t.co/CLZZzRpqmb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Confucius say it is better to be looked over than overlooked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Adorable Fleece Baby Carrier Cover!  http://t.co/LpvXgAy9U8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do... or do not. There is no try. - Yoda - The Empire Strikes Back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion is not necessarily about labels. It's not about brands. It's about something else that comes from within you. - Ralph Lauren]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Daddy: Mommy just backed the car over my bicycle! "I told you not to leave it in the living room!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Steely Dan  http://t.co/7x376L9A0M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can Archery Be a Great Fitness Activity?  http://t.co/y4X7I66LJw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may have said the same thing before... But my explanation, I am sure, will always be different. - Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Wendy's  http://t.co/EKgZE88Df0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ELVIS - The King - One Person's Thoughts  http://t.co/4sRimrphv1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make the Most of Twitter for Your Business  http://t.co/nVxfUv3DBP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Jackson Browne  http://t.co/Pv1R538eac]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana’s Lyme Journey – Part 16 – Seven Months Later  http://t.co/0dJv9cMdDs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman's dress should be a like a barbed-wire fence: serving its purpose without obstructing the view. - Sophia Loren]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is Renter's Insurance?  http://t.co/7c2EG5JVVE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Kitty Kallen  http://t.co/dbJaPhhcck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is better than poverty, if only for financial reasons. - Woody Allen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Trini Lopez    http://t.co/3RnJsHlAMb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The Music of L.T.D.  http://t.co/deCJCApmuO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Green Acres is an American sitcom classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/r2CZw0PsgQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It isn't the mountains ahead to climb that wear you out; it's the pebble in your shoe. - Muhammad Ali]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About BMX Biking Born from Freestyle Motocross  http://t.co/RZ3TTFfcVJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Surviving a failure gives you more self-confidence. Failures are great learning tools.. but they must be kept to a minimum. - Jeffrey Immelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever hear of instant credit? You just add money]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Videos Games and Fitness with Wii and XBOX  http://t.co/kYUNwKlHnX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not anorexic. I'm from Texas. Are there people from Texas that are anorexic? I've never heard of one. And that includes me. Jessica S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Put on your red shoes, and dance the blues. - David Bowie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DC Comics Ultimate Character Guide http://t.co/9u4igGnVam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Ways Technology Helps Seniors  http://t.co/Bv3FTo2zjH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The Best of ABBA  http://t.co/5qIqyhML08]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Fort Worth, Texas  http://t.co/mRDBTcdM7E]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>