<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[White House Office Hours: A “To-Do List” That’ll Create Jobs and Help the Middle Class: 
	Over the past few week... http://t.co/t85Qdbxk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joplin: Remember, Rejoice, Rebuild: 

	Tomorrow marks the one ye... http://t.co/mkWsnQuD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#LatismAtTheWH – Latinos Active in Social Media Visit the White House: 
	To engage with Latinos active in social... http://t.co/DWpAzrn4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House Hangout: Small Business Week with SBA Administrator Karen Mills: 
	Throughout the next few days, we ... http://t.co/7IfiCGjr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Startup Stories: JOBS Act Expands Opportunities for True Investments: 
	Ed note: In honor of Small Business Week... http://t.co/RYTmRCqd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Attends NATO Summit in Chicago: 
	President Obama was in Chicago today for the first day of the ... http://t.co/wA73PZGD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch Live from the NATO Summit in Chicago: 
	This week, leaders from the 28 member countries of the North Atlan... http://t.co/dWrMCZy6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wrapping Up the G8 Summit at Camp David: 

	This weekend, the leaders of Britain, Canada, France, Germany, Ita... http://t.co/2yTvhulT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Putting Twitter’s “Do Not Track” Feature in Context: 
	This week, we got some terrific news about new ways indiv... http://t.co/d90utyaq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Address: Congress Must Move Forward, Not Back On Wall Street Reform: 
	President Obama discusses the refo... http://t.co/oXzyr545]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Wrap Up: Courage and Sacrifice: 

	A quick glimpse at this week on http://t.co/4TLTiIEJ:

	Fight for Your ... http://t.co/QQiKEOc9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By the Numbers: 1 Billion: 

	Approximately 1 billion people worldwide suffer from chronic hunger-- a prolonge... http://t.co/qtA3MXum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Announces New Partnership to Fight Global Hunger: 

    President Barack Obama delivers rem... http://t.co/LTY4XxQG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My First Job: Cris Comerford: 
	Summer Jobs+ is a call to action for businesses, non-profits, and government to ... http://t.co/bvNVpQxh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Alliance for Food Security and Nutrition: 
	This weekend, the leaders of the world’s largest economies and f... http://t.co/WiojW5Zc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch the G8 Summit Live This Weekend from Camp David: 
	This weekend, the leaders of Britain, Canada, France, G... http://t.co/GH5kPcHl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Administration Safety Data Initiative Challenges App Developers: 
	Safety is the number one priority at the US D... http://t.co/UxDhGj0v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Wing Week: "Reach High and Hope Deeply": 
	Welcome to the West Wing Week, your guide to everything that's h... http://t.co/nHnRrGnl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House Office Hours: Let's Move! with Sam Kass: 
	This has been an exciting week for Let’s Move! On Monday,... http://t.co/tsnC02RF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[National Plan to Address Alzheimer's Disease: 
	Today, as many as 5.1 million Americans suffer from Alzheimer’s.... http://t.co/AflAdyTP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By the Numbers: $1 Billion: 

	Thursday is the fourth day of National Women’s Health Week. Women often play a ... http://t.co/8x3B3rgh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Persistent Exporters Recognized for their Achievements during E-Awards White House Ceremony: 
	Ed note: This was... http://t.co/EpEpYNbZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch Live: Ambassador Rice and Nick Kristof Discuss Foreign Policy in a Google+ Hangout: 
	Today, join Ambassad... http://t.co/IVPVwEFe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Awards Posthumous Medal of Honor to Specialist Leslie H. Sabo, Jr: 

    President Barack O... http://t.co/rT7kPy2E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jon Bon Jovi Helps Young Americans Find Summer Jobs: 
	Jon Bon Jovi is a singer, a songwriter, an actor -- and a... http://t.co/Xz2BF5aQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By the Numbers: 2 Million: 

	Nearly 2 million companies that make new hires or increase wages would receive a... http://t.co/YGhrpMMe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Visits Taylor Gourmet: 

    President Barack Obama and Small Business Administrator Karen ... http://t.co/dM4Mxip8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Congratulates the LA Galaxy: 

    President Barack Obama welcomes Major League Soccer cham... http://t.co/IyOlGth7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My First Job: Gene Sperling: 
	Summer Jobs+ is a call to action for businesses, non-profits, and government to w... http://t.co/ZNTjseBu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rolling Out the Welcome Mat for our Military Families at National Parks and Public Lands: 
	As we celebrate Arme... http://t.co/8zJTPxkv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Pays Tribute to Fallen Police Officers: 

    President Barack Obama, with Chuck Canterbury... http://t.co/RTRE30gI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S.-Colombia Trade Promotion Agreement Now in Force: 
	Ed note: This was originally published on tradeology, th... http://t.co/8HMhsQT9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the Archives: President Abraham Lincoln Creates the Department of Agriculture: 
	True to his roots as a fro... http://t.co/zflPKw97]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[National Women's Health Week by the Numbers: 20.4 Million: 

	Tuesday is the second day of National Women’s He... http://t.co/TH4bj27w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ensuring that LGBT Victims of Domestic Violence Can Access Critically Needed Services and Protections: 
	Last we... http://t.co/XC6bB9ob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[VA and Department of Labor Program to Retrain 99,000 Unemployed Veterans Is Now Accepting Applications: 

 ... http://t.co/TsJjMl2y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama to Barnard College: "Fight for a seat at the head of the table": 
	This afternoon, President Oba... http://t.co/LLXcAppa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Share Your Ideas for Improving Transportation for Veterans: 
	Ed. note: This is cross-posted from fastlane.dot.g... http://t.co/FobQ4JL2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Addressing Violence Against Native Women in the Violence Against Women Act Reauthorization: 
	Last week, the Hou... http://t.co/kpTSuqjy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infographic: How Refinancing Can Help Families: 
	Ed. Note: This post was originally published on Treasury Notes... http://t.co/QJmS4T1G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By the Numbers: 237: 

	President Obama has been focused on maki... http://t.co/SfbQ6jNu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My First Job: Omar Epps: 
	Summer Jobs+ is a call to action for businesses, non-profits, and government to work ... http://t.co/ArZvj51C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't Forget!: 
	It's Mother's Day!

	As rewarding as being a mom can be, it sure isn't easy. That's part of why... http://t.co/rmZL7BLD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joining Forces to Say "Happy Mother's Day!": 
	It's a tradition in the White House to celebrate Mother's Day wit... http://t.co/dA8jfDz5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama &amp; Vice President Biden Honor the Nations TOP COPS: 

    President Barack Obama greets 20... http://t.co/dzqfxI1v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Address: Congress Must Act on "To-Do List": 
	President Obama is calling on Democrats and Republicans to ... http://t.co/sIduSyJf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Wrap Up: “Treat Others the Way You Would Want to Be Treated”: 

	A quick look at this week on WhiteHouse.... http://t.co/Mi43Ql8s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch Live: Dr. Jill Biden at Southwestern Community College: 
	Tonight, at 7:30 PM CT, Dr. Jill Biden will give... http://t.co/8QVTZGUl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Progress on a Key Goal to Train 500,000 Workers for Jobs in Manufacturing Sector: 
	On June 8, 2011, President O... http://t.co/R49prkXi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guaranteeing Value for Your Premium Dollars: 
	Ed note: this post was originally published on the blog at health... http://t.co/ppYFC5LW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rolling Back Protections for Domestic Violence Victims: 
	Ed. Note: This is the first in a series of posts on th... http://t.co/C2y5N3RY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Wing Week: 5/11/12 or "Teach Your Parents How to Tweet": 

	This week, the President traveled to Virginia a... http://t.co/0QQooZTc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#CongressToDoList Office Hours: Refinancing: 
	This week, President Obama announced a "to-do list" for Congress ... http://t.co/riN5L9e9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Supports Same Sex Marriage: 
	Yesterday, during an interview with ABC News, President Obama said... http://t.co/huY0IZfQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Educating and Empowering American Consumers: 
	Today, the White House hosted a Summit on Financial Capability an... http://t.co/mexa5Mjq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congress's To-Do List: 
	Earlier this week the President visited the College of Nanoscale Science and Engineerin... http://t.co/l99BQkJZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Joining Forces Honors Military Moms: 
	In honor of the upcoming Military Spouse Appreciation Day on May 11 and i... http://t.co/JcL1PpuY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making Regulation Smarter to Save Lives and Money: 
	Smart regulations save lives and dollars. For example, the ... http://t.co/uIzTdtH7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Supports Same Sex Marriage: 
	Today, in an interview with ABC News, President Obama said, "I thi... http://t.co/s3gPSRWl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celebrating a Landmark Anniversary for Women and Girls: 
	This week marks the 40th anniversary of Title IX, the ... http://t.co/0DXSKdV3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fighting to Protect American Families from Mercury Pollution: 
	In December 2011, President Obama was proud to a... http://t.co/rKtnikSe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Day One at the G-20 in Los Cabos: 

    President Barack Obama greets President Felipe Calderón of Mexico a... http://t.co/0BxY1T9E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Refi?  Your Questions Answered.: 
	Over the past few weeks we’ve been telling you about President Obama’s pl... http://t.co/nQ1d2Kab]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Bilateral Meeting with President Putin: 
	
	This afternoon, President Obama had his first face-to-face meeting... http://t.co/NpsRf9UA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch Live: Dr. Biden at the 2012 National Conference on Volunteering and Service: 
	Today, just after 4:15 PM E... http://t.co/3itxg8ny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Entrepreneurs and Innovators Rock 3rd Annual Health Datapalooza: 
	Imagine a scenario where a patient, from her ... http://t.co/5MRJi6QL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reforming Unemployment Insurance to Protect Jobs and Incomes for American Workers: 
	In his inaugural address, P... http://t.co/1msIzv9m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama is in Los Cabos for the G20 Summit: 
	
	This week, President Obama is in Mexico for a meeting of... http://t.co/Xrl44z7u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the Clock: Explaining Refinance in 60 Seconds (Or Less): 
	Over the past two weeks, we’ve asked you to raise ... http://t.co/cVBXyH4W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weekly Address: Ending the Stalemate in Washington: 
	President Obama tells the American people that the stalema... http://t.co/N7qIuqNE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Hosts LGBT Pride Reception at the White House: 

    President Barack Obama delivers remark... http://t.co/qlxB53iI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Promoting Responsible Fatherhood and Healthy Families: 
	As families across the country make plans to celebrate ... http://t.co/a5xcqHiz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Visa Legislation Enables Israeli Investors to Create American Jobs: 
	Last week, President Obama signed into... http://t.co/Xmt4eN3A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Delivers Remarks on Immigration: 

    President Barack Obama delivers remarks on the Depar... http://t.co/2E7cXNpb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Disclosure Reports Now Available: 
	Public Financial Disclosure Reports (OGE Form 278) for White House... http://t.co/fXkJNG5G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Office Hours on Deferred Action for Young Immigrants: Smart &amp; Sensible Immigration Policy: 
	Earlier today, Pres... http://t.co/HFlYBfN3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deferred Action Process for Certain Young People: Smart and Sensible Immigration Policy: 
	Secretary Janet Napol... http://t.co/e387bjwG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We Come Back Stronger: 

    Message signed by President Barack Obama on one of the final steel beams t... http://t.co/gwJFA5vZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the Archives: Presidents as Fathers: 
	
Click here to see the photo gallery. 

	As you celebrate Dad this... http://t.co/wiM7vNfC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tune In: President Obama Delivers Remarks on Immigration: 
	At 1:15 PM ET, President Obama will address the Amer... http://t.co/HokZdW3Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House Hosts  Meeting on Global Health Security: 
	Yesterday, U.S. Homeland Security Advisor John Brennan h... http://t.co/SQQTnER0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[West Wing Week: 6/15/2012 or "The Fatherhood Buzz": 
	This week, the President welcomed the Girl Scouts, the Pre... http://t.co/mxkPKvrr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today Is Flag Day: 

    President Barack Obama greets Hugh Hills, 85,  in front of his home in Joplin, Mo.... http://t.co/wSO8x90G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[From the Archives: President Obama's Trip to Ghana: 

	In the summer of 2009, President Obama traveled to Ghan... http://t.co/Mqaw52qF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By the Numbers: $3,000: 

	Right now, owning a home is a source of anxiety for many Americans. Millions of hom... http://t.co/RbeRitzs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Future of America’s Partnership with Sub-Saharan Africa: 

    President Barack Obama delivers remarks ... http://t.co/QN5Obpw2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Obama Honors Israeli President Shimon Peres: 
	In a ceremony at the White House on Wednesday, Presiden... http://t.co/tQrFD87h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honoring Fathers: 
	Yesterday, President Obama celebrated Father’s Day a little early with four dads at Kenny’s ... http://t.co/tSFnsu2I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making Broadband Construction Faster and Cheaper: 
	[Editor’s Note: Tune in to http://t.co/q0JzVCDt tomorrow ... http://t.co/RXqFSLAb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Five Is a Magic Number: 
	In one of the greatest humanitarian achievements of the past 50 years, child mortality... http://t.co/Rk0fcVlI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Americans Speaking Out in Favor of Mortgage Relief: 
	We've been talking about President Obama’s proposal to cut... http://t.co/J0mJhj8e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House Office Hours: Helping Homeowners Refinance: 
	President Obama believes that homeowners need help. He... http://t.co/RNdB5OMu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seventh Annual World Elder Abuse Awareness Day: 
	Elder abuse comes in many forms. It is recognized by experts a... http://t.co/iSonNfRA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keeping the Military’s Energy Options Open: 
	This morning, Secretary of Defense Leon Panetta testified before t... http://t.co/AczVYX4f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Photo Gallery: Behind the Scenes in May 2012: 
	The White House Photo Office just released their latest batch of... http://t.co/8Vhlgikx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My First Job: Betty White: 
	Summer Jobs+ is a call to action for businesses, non-profits, and government to wor... http://t.co/yDept6Lc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federal Reserve Data: More Work to be Done, But Household Wealth Up Every Year Under Obama: 
	This week, the Fed... http://t.co/y5qd44cv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My First Job: Richard Kind: 
	Summer Jobs+ is a call to action for businesses, non-profits, and government to wo... http://t.co/YG9uyLCp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unleashing Innovation &amp; Deepening Democracy Through Prizes: 
	Prizes have a long history of driving important br... http://t.co/uVUw3MLQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disability Employment App Challenge: Educating Employers and Job Seekers with Disabilities: 
	Nearly 22 years af... http://t.co/0pT1rrUx]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>