<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[88-86 Santa Cruz so far for me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is so fucking close]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a difference from the last fight, that's 3 zip Santa Cruz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is gony be a cracker this fight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really fancy Santa Cruz but I really can't decide what tae lump on ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thought he was a goner there ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a knockout, holy fuck ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it just me that fancies Santa Cruz tonight? ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1st time out in Bathgate in nearly 2 year, definitely a reason for that length a absence ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That Derby own goal ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gazwilliamson they had it in a tiny tent at Mint last year and it wasn't as good. If the line up is shite I'll be selling mines]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gazwilliamson they will aye, that'll sell out straight away as well. You'd think Elrow was the only decent night in Glasgow all year ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everycunt pure freaking out about Elrow, it's almost like there's nae other decent nights on every single weekend ðŸ™„ðŸ™„]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danielmurray67 if it is it'll be easy enough to flog them to some mug who's only interested in some confetti and blow up toys ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@danielmurray67 what a bastard that ðŸ™„ðŸ˜‚. Better no be a shite lineup now]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fucking Â£80 for 2 Elrow tickets and it's sold out already ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ed Sheeren's new song and the video for it would bring a tear to yer eye man. Getting old is pure shite]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vikkiferrier @ssgarrity the whole a Scotland has ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vikkiferrier @ssgarrity I mean either or, any advice helps cause we're a pair a indecisive bastards ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vikkiferrier @ssgarrity fuck, can ye no go earlier and tell us what it's like? ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vikkiferrier ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚, beats any yer sci-if shite any day ðŸ™ˆ. @ssgarrity should decide based on our opinions and our opinions alone tbh ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vikkiferrier depends what ye like, real life or kid on real life. It was never going to be as good as the first ðŸ™ˆ, no got the shock factor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vikkiferrier @chrislammie aye but the T2 reviews haven't been great either ðŸ™ˆ. In the end I'll be going where I'm telt anyway ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vikkiferrier @chrislammie you're no kidding ðŸ˜‚. It looks weird as fuck aye but it seems like a thriller which is right up our street]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@vikkiferrier @chrislammie Sam has convinced me to use our vouchers on that before T2, better no be shite ðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cannot believe we've made it ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ. This helps heal the wound of 2013 ðŸ˜‚ @SkySportsNFL #RiseUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gazmitchell92 be some laugh that ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gazmitchell92 fucking buzzing ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚. If the steelers win later you need to take a sicky for the SB, me and Pratt will be rolling about ðŸ™ˆðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YASSSSSSSSSSSSS!!!!!! Super Bowl bound now surely ðŸ™ŒðŸ™ŒðŸ™ŒðŸ™Œ @AtlantaFalcons @SkySportsNFL #GBvsATL #RiseUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@gazmitchell92 about 90% away ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚. Stop at the start of this half and I'm starting to celebrate ðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WHAT A FUCKING START ðŸ™ŒðŸ™ŒðŸ™ŒðŸ™Œ @AtlantaFalcons #GBvsATL #RiseUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WilliamHill Boswell #LastActionHero]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The nerves man ðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆðŸ™ˆ @AtlantaFalcons #GBvsATL #RiseUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing better than having a few beers watching the scores on a Saturday]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@chrislammie your life will be a fucking misery within 6 months. Nightmare journeys to spend the day listening to an even worse accent]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy fuck man, what an incredible game that was ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³ #DALvsGB #NFLPlayoffs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great fight and great judging]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarynPhillips superb mate and superb judging]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarynPhillips honestly mate, fuck knows! Good luck scoring that ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter what way it goes, there can be no argument. Draw for me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a fucking fight ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarynPhillips only thing you've no got is happening ðŸ˜‚. Some fight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarynPhillips rounds ye got? This is points bound. I'd have City before man utd the mora ðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarynPhillips biggest giveaway by the bookies this year that ðŸ˜³. I honestly wouldn't touch that game, City at evens is yer bet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarynPhillips fuck sake, some odds that! Wish to fuck I'd seen they odds ðŸ˜‚. No even worth the bet that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EastonDaz @GrantEaston1 keep ye posted ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarynPhillips aye fucking sure a have ðŸ˜‚. No even looked at the odds for the boxing the night at all. Lump the mora, money to be won]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EastonDaz @GrantEaston1 some talent! Bit like me telling ye about some Kazakh nobody a few years back  ðŸ™„ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarynPhillips I've turned over now, game over. No like ye to lump ðŸ™ˆðŸ˜‚. I don't fancy a knock out but I wouldn't be lumping against it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarynPhillips NFL is too good to miss ðŸ˜‚. I'd be shocked if he never won tbh but I reckon it's points bound]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarynPhillips fuck up ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚. Switching between that and the NFL, that last fight seemed a topper! I'll be watch the DeGale fight though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarynPhillips correct, she's more mental than me though ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Something weirdly hilarious about yer wee sister coming in blotto and causing it ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Couldn't be happier, roll on the NFC championship game! #RiseUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NFL: For the 4th time in franchise history, the @AtlantaFalcons will #RiseUp to the NFC Championship Game! https://t.co/hTC9eooyqD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yassssssssssssssss!!!!! #SEAvsATL #RiseUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aw man, this offence ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ðŸ˜ #SEAvsATL #RiseUp @SkySportsNFL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a half that was, more of the same please! #SEAvsATL #RiseUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't know whether this is excitement or nerves ðŸ™ˆ #SEAvsATL #RiseUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing would give me greater satisfaction than the Chinese fucking ravaging the premiership ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚. Reap what ye sow ya cunts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not an hour of the day goes by where I'm not wishing I was at @TheBPMFestival . Wit a comedown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some laugh it's gony be no making it to a 48 team World Cup and spending the summer getting blitzed, shouting on San Marino against England]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best league in the world eh? ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚. Can't wait to see Leicester get fucking pumped next round to complete the misery]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Something tells me everybody moaning about #indyref2 might not be as confident of winning this time ðŸ™„. Great news]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SeanTeven: Choose Celtic. https://t.co/sCtkX60zwA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally seen that penalty decision ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Update, still gutted about that defeat ðŸ˜”ðŸ˜”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cannot believe we got beat the day man, disaster ðŸ˜”ðŸ˜”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EastonDaz: Imagine celebrating a draw against a team you're 33 points behind in the league ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ðŸ˜­ no shame that lot!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's it folks, the Rangers are coming ðŸ™„ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adelante34 I'll be fucking shocked if we do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@euan_cairns1 aye man, staying in Glasgow after it but I'll be on the bus through]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adelante34 i usually am but no at all the night, hopefully that's a promising sign ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@daz___moore that's what I'm doing, can't sit doing nothing the night before these ðŸ™ˆ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a fucking buzz for tomorrow man, feels great no being nervous about playing these cunts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finished work and off till Tuesday, pint in hand, darts tonight and it's hunskelping weekend ðŸ™ŒðŸ™Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fucking incredible, I've never seen anything like that]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a tie this is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theboypez3 @ssgarrity got to save face in public but ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ssgarrity I see, will I just keep all the winnings to myself from now on? ðŸ™„ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cannot get enough of this tune the now ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜³ https://t.co/Q9CBMwgZsl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To see a cracking fighter like that crumble physically is no great. Some amount of respect for Haye though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was actually a shame to watch]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is fucking bonkers ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reckon he'll get schooled but the odds on Bellew are fucking no real ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarynPhillips ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚, correct! God bless @ssgarrity ðŸ™ŒðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarynPhillips thank fuck ðŸ™ˆ, he was in a sorry state! Thank fuck I've got a burd and no causing it in yours right now ðŸ˜³ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarynPhillips aye mate lying in bed, no sleeping anytime soon ðŸ˜‚ðŸ˜‚]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DarynPhillips some night/day kid ðŸ™Œ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some night! Glasgow Celtic champions ðŸ€ðŸ€ðŸ€ðŸ€ðŸ€ðŸ€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a night! One of the best aways days yet ðŸ˜. Love the Celtic ðŸ€ðŸ€ðŸ€ðŸ€]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RossNicholson12 @CelticSpares text me kid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RossNicholson12 @CelticSpares that's us here mate, ye about?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewisJack2 @CelticSpares  follow me back kid and I'll message ye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewisJack2 @Camymac_ @CelticSpares aye mate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shaynemair @Reeceybhoy88 @CelticSpares aye mate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Reeceybhoy88 @CelticSpares ye still looking? Got another spare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewisJack2 @Camymac_ @CelticSpares do not mate sorry, my other one is away]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LewisJack2 @CelticSpares  1 left mate]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>