<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysis: Why Donald Trump won't condemn Rob Porter https://t.co/7vzQmnoZKH https://t.co/CxhM9sM4A6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Blocks Release of Memo Rebutting Republican Claims - New York Times https://t.co/wEpqniBDPk https://t.co/ZNoLQN3SN4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finger-pointing in WH over abuse allegations https://t.co/MXepJXUwva https://t.co/y0DOuPqQjo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump will not immediately release Democrats' memo on FBI surveillance - Washington Post https://t.co/RlgWpV9KvA https://t.co/t2gCXOetPu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woodward and Bernstein: Trump's response to Russia investigation is eerily familiar https://t.co/N7Iy5Yts4A https://t.co/PiWkcc8Shu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump holds up Schiff memo that seeks to undercut GOP claims of FBI misconduct because it contains 'numerous' classified passages, White House says https://t.co/y6QgLk6FKt https://t.co/WejytgmsMh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winners and losers from the overnight shutdown - The Hill https://t.co/2mBpnE6xts https://t.co/XSvFVdQYCV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No. 3 official at Justice Dept. stepping down https://t.co/A8jbOBZ13B https://t.co/5bSrdN7W9O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House deputy chief of staff to become drug czar https://t.co/PyY8vRvrle https://t.co/pKkrZGjWgL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snow continues to fall in Midwest, while Southeast experiences heavy rain - ABC News https://t.co/1hugFvlgn6 https://t.co/kQV8N0jJkY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House denies Kelly offered to resign https://t.co/M3AAgONzAE https://t.co/pclJdQFqbk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Porter's ex-wives say Mormon church counseled them against divorce https://t.co/Qr4tyovTtO https://t.co/GGfP7ostFW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No. 3 Official at the Justice Department Is Stepping Down - New York Times https://t.co/YL1SFwlcb0 https://t.co/v6t5g7qzTj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Grassley Letter Everyone Is Ignoring Is Way More Important Than the Nunes Memo - Politico https://t.co/GLwWc54ccS https://t.co/VXrohGV7yy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: Budget deal a big victory for Trump https://t.co/SOSAijsR4Z https://t.co/pQgdhwymcA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kelly tells aides he secured Porter's resignation, source says https://t.co/L0Uept8Fkn https://t.co/xYRvwZjijS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mother gives birth, abandons baby in airport bathroom with handwritten note: Authorities - ABC News https://t.co/mBeuVlJWS2 https://t.co/0Cv3LaM5za]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysis: What Trump gets dead wrong in his Rob Porter defense https://t.co/mJHvPfJpeL https://t.co/SBP2bH3zQ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LIVE UPDATES: Officer dead, 2 deputies wounded in Henry County shooting, officials say - Atlanta Journal Constitution https://t.co/QX67lDoNNj https://t.co/aVV3yvNYQT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump on Rob Porter: 'We wish him well ... He did a good job' https://t.co/NqbsaJSomD https://t.co/WfJVS51x7x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former Trump administration officials, from Comey to McCabe - Fox News https://t.co/A2Tr4xRIuK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysis: John Kelly couldn't have handled this any worse https://t.co/PhqIstCkuM https://t.co/DkmT92xERS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber and Alphabet have settled their self-driving lawsuit with a $245 million equity payout - Recode https://t.co/P1B15WjcpP https://t.co/UtbZ5PHGmb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Porter isn't the only high-level Trump staffer ousted over past actions https://t.co/maaW4pZREJ https://t.co/e76gQp5nBL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump frustrated with Hope Hicks' role in Porter scandal https://t.co/mhVqt4CDpR https://t.co/4KqwBtJ2Mr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Logan Paul promised a 'new chapter' after vlogging a dead body. Then, the YouTuber Tasered a dead rat. - Washington Post https://t.co/bkWYoWHG6N https://t.co/90R5mag7jO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-SEAL who killed bin Laden calls Trump's parade idea 'third world bullsh--' https://t.co/8idDc8LZPG https://t.co/dGcQngGPko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President signs spending bill after brief uncertainty about timing https://t.co/aPKmajrvIm https://t.co/fSVuBlI7i3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon's answer to UPS is getting its first proper launch in LA - The Verge https://t.co/Eow4toEXJj https://t.co/AKnYp1GjNQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The moment a divided Korea comes together https://t.co/1nIsZcF7LP https://t.co/r0nWi8NT7A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shirtless Tongan comes out all oily again https://t.co/85i1G0AhGk https://t.co/H8en2HvSqp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China says new stealth fighter put into combat service - Reuters https://t.co/caJsYkoxvV https://t.co/bdXlbqMQPz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lindsey Vonn is moved to tears https://t.co/ioSUB0purA https://t.co/t7j2ZlI2w5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congress votes to end government shutdown - Politico https://t.co/kXkVAOLDlB https://t.co/dAjcvOKXMg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The opening ceremony for the 2018 Games is underway https://t.co/kjdnL64y0r https://t.co/JMkUe7XexU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Protests erupt over NK Olympics presence https://t.co/5bDP682afk https://t.co/yHXtrtMnTf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Banned From Election, Putin Foe Navalny Pursues Politics By Other Means - NPR https://t.co/96S8LvUAKx https://t.co/VeJAkCJKR2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These figure skaters will blow your mind https://t.co/CWfCVseD37 https://t.co/zF1iidEpnc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Records Show Public Paid for Hotel Tied to Prostitute Report - U.S. News &amp; World Report https://t.co/4wl0J3sYVd https://t.co/XCtUIJVm7r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Winter Games 2018: North Korea, Russia and condoms https://t.co/VriSCv6Tdh https://t.co/NHvj7uW2hN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senate passes bill to end shutdown, sending it to House - The Hill https://t.co/ytlT6Lo46Q https://t.co/LejL20ZPdK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 men accuse Assemblywoman Cristina Garcia — a vocal #MeToo ally — of sexual harassment - Press-Enterprise https://t.co/vUi3xvXi8R https://t.co/kCeJuFLmfM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sen. Paul: I never wanted government shutdown https://t.co/uNHcku9kat https://t.co/PGUp1jPdjD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OMB is preparing for lapse in government funding https://t.co/pYR4atcJ0o https://t.co/1a7oJrHhxD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Government shuts down as budget bill stalls in Congress - Washington Post https://t.co/zh9WMtNrc9 https://t.co/x196xBDWb6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David Axelrod says Sen. Paul wants to embarrass senators https://t.co/zGgFbeFCaH https://t.co/lYYf6NaBko]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Quiet Diplomacy to Save the Olympics in a Nuclear Standoff - New York Times https://t.co/0WK9g7mveg https://t.co/t5YRggKrMg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysis: Rand Paul is right https://t.co/eWi2j4abC9 https://t.co/fRAqPnrCeZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A small asteroid will pass very close to Earth https://t.co/LX9QJTdYm5 https://t.co/Wvok7FMILA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rubio on Warner contact with Russian lobbyist: It's 'had zero impact on our work' - The Hill https://t.co/YZpuDLrwCe https://t.co/AhXlrU05JJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aly Raisman: US Olympics is very much responsible https://t.co/PjPmGdRx3X https://t.co/Xxm5yFDRKf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Assemblywoman leading #MeToo movement at California Capitol accused of sexual misconduct - Sacramento Bee https://t.co/w2dayUXkvc https://t.co/kQsq8qsrTQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clash with witness shows drive to discredit dossier https://t.co/3wHJq1CC9v https://t.co/tOSKsvl7ck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rand Paul, House Democrats fuel shutdown threat - Politico https://t.co/GP81uHClOm https://t.co/oAAbU6UPBf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paul: GOP deficit spending hypocritical https://t.co/2xE5D63l9j https://t.co/uYERzN41EU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Major winter storm continues to pound Midwest - ABC News https://t.co/snMhYgy2fl https://t.co/lJYSMJbGEX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House hits back: 'Omarosa was fired three times on "The Apprentice"' - The Hill https://t.co/vbs8wSt6ck https://t.co/PkdKHuDQh2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aly Raisman skeptical US Olympics investigation will be comprehensive https://t.co/udgfNElWv0 https://t.co/oVg9GYRcV5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winter Olympics will be chock-full of firsts https://t.co/2F2ZQdmjgB https://t.co/iQRiAY2Amy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dow plunges more than 1000 points on specter of higher interest rates - Washington Post https://t.co/Kj0FULqjxO https://t.co/DuzrmR2kUs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Abuse accusations were widely known among Trump's top aides, including Kelly, deputy press secretary says https://t.co/70YwTWluNS https://t.co/0GmHfbcn7B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Porter's ex-wife details alleged abuse https://t.co/1X6VMLYSk2 https://t.co/Xebh9flgZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jimmy Garoppolo deal set to have impact on QB market - https://t.co/3HxkKlV5v1 https://t.co/yW2J0sYMOF https://t.co/GOovHuxwfH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WH chief of staff shows sides of his character that were hidden for years behind a cloak of military discipline https://t.co/ADJy98LXgs https://t.co/F0A6Pc3DQT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cavaliers trading Isaiah Thomas for Jordan Clarkson, Larry Nance - ESPN https://t.co/Id4rDHEbeA https://t.co/TLKs0wyOcq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysis: 6 questions the White House needs to answer https://t.co/odQTz4zkmR https://t.co/wKvA9KX3tt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ryan thinks House has the votes to pass budget deal https://t.co/gtPAJAsExP https://t.co/W3hQm7ell1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Florida boy gets trapped inside arcade claw machine - Fox News https://t.co/EoXkfZQx4Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump lauds faith in America as fallout over allegations swirl https://t.co/aDsrsao76V https://t.co/R412W8PxDq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazon launches free, 2-hour Whole Foods deliveries in four cities - USA TODAY https://t.co/rxIHfeFkH1 https://t.co/d6jLaHOXEM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Psaki: The defense of Porter is indefensible https://t.co/CEbVyYyVBt https://t.co/4MBAkInG7m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senator: Shame on WH if covering up abuse claims https://t.co/yz7bfoRaXC https://t.co/SN5tx2GhkZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is WH defending the character of Rob Porter? https://t.co/MuxqgGq1x3 https://t.co/DLA7ncFVXJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[George W. Bush: There's clear evidence Russia 'meddled' in 2016 election - Politico https://t.co/NpWwmr5Kqm https://t.co/hLoxKwyAI6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump sought prayers for Schwarzenegger at last year's event https://t.co/hduGiwJzCj https://t.co/vwPsnIEKSn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republicans learn spending money is much easier in Washington than saving https://t.co/ND45Qpj4WR https://t.co/gOO16r6uIl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Kim Yo Jong? Here's what we know about the North Korean princess. - Washington Post https://t.co/wSgYzztuMJ https://t.co/tUhLZZx1ZV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch Pelosi's marathon session https://t.co/kPFVbY5EWh https://t.co/7sGb2DlRGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Russian plane shot down in Syria https://t.co/xtDyAWZSJS https://t.co/WoUao61QCt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The coalition says it was responding to a tank and mortar attack by pro-Assad fighters https://t.co/ql8O5NBpnL https://t.co/XRA2Lg7BYD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The crowds are back. Now can the space industry build on the momentum? - Chicago Tribune https://t.co/NPzvrNnzUc https://t.co/GWgxU6bXMj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the full budget agreement https://t.co/jhSDJjTWki https://t.co/HwgRvR6hZ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Porter's ex-wife describes him as abusive and angry https://t.co/lDBNInPvr5 https://t.co/Ex14BKLnH1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Richardson officer hospitalized after shooting at apartment complex - Fort Worth Star Telegram https://t.co/8HcUxDU6kp https://t.co/nA2JPZlDuj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[White House scrambles to contain Porter fallout https://t.co/KDcAawdgQs https://t.co/9qXQxn3Fz6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Administration beset by domestic abuse allegations https://t.co/q21xJ9bhgO https://t.co/YUgoQfzAdx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[House Democrats face tough choice over budget deal and immigration https://t.co/BWnJnq2ew4 https://t.co/ywFqllvFuH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FBI Finds No Evidence Of Homicide In Death Of Border Patrol Agent - NPR https://t.co/bvAE2SUeUx https://t.co/b93s4pIvRZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: Democrats should take the deal https://t.co/BUg0etOKOO https://t.co/E45ykXmHzB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Black Lives Matter activist fatally shot in New Orleans - CBS News https://t.co/1gGV0Zh1Pt https://t.co/Mrh0nTRErJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sources say a scramble ensued to defend top aide Rob Porter, who denied the allegations but resigned today. https://t.co/tAcV8KD2Qn https://t.co/9qi6lHIqRT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nancy Pelosi's filibuster-style speech tops eight hours in bid to force immigration votes - Washington Post https://t.co/FTpvPmTCKw https://t.co/0bPUPtGplZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[National Prayer Breakfast features Trump and Rep. Scalise, who was shot at GOP baseball practice - Washington Post https://t.co/liTGgHs9Df https://t.co/Z0aKCsd2Rw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oklahoma man found guilty of hate crime in his neighbor's death - CNN https://t.co/vLzzZebxGT https://t.co/6NfZlgV4XW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rick Gates' lawyers say they have 'irreconcilable differences' with client https://t.co/6Q6uDFaSJq https://t.co/20YHwUx1ae]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The House Minority Leader has talked about DACA for 6 hours. It's the longest House floor speech on record. https://t.co/G366bnY7U8 https://t.co/o7dWaUO1ol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[2 dead; deputy-involved shooting shuts 95 in Lantana (watch live) - https://t.co/iQKzVewbky https://t.co/lTQzKJe7xR https://t.co/QkXTckB2Kr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What we know about what's in the deal https://t.co/LcpMjGkBEv https://t.co/VKG77wMvGR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poll: Trump's approval rating on the rise https://t.co/l0g45LFvD1 https://t.co/c6HfptLG0z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mattis says Trump's parade request reflects 'affection' for troops https://t.co/tSokXIjY4D https://t.co/X3yM4FwfrQ]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>