<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Education costs money, but then so does ignorance. - Sir Claus Moser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Saving Money With Solar Power  http://t.co/jTMnc4OMDh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spock, where the hell's the power you promised?" - Kirk  "One damn minute, admiral" - Spock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Second marriage --  triumph of hope over experience]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't win unless you learn how to lose. - Kareem Abdul-Jabbar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To the uneducated, an A is just three sticks. - A. A. Milne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Don Henley  http://t.co/zZfLVxmF57]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't do any vulgar movements.  -  Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read How to Use LinkedIn for Your Company   http://t.co/E3sdhARR0B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You maniacs! You blew it up! Oh, damn you! Damn you all to hell! - Taylor, Planet of the Apes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your Attorney Search: The Advantages of Flat Rates  http://t.co/bkFiQTXsnN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame Turf Wars: Such Rage; Much Death  http://t.co/s05fGi7D2a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool Hands Free Umbrella! http://t.co/nxJaAFMF6k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the history of the Modern Tennis Shoe  http://t.co/sI3dtlu4Ce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Totally Cool 80s Retro iPhone Case http://t.co/tsF3TQPZdO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take twice as long to eat half as much. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of England Dan and John Ford Coley  http://t.co/qe4s7OOL8l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Highland Village, Texas  http://t.co/DVDYZ8LZ9m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The needs of the many outweigh ... the needs of the few... Or the one. - Kirk and Spock - Star Trek II: The Wrath of Khan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overwhelming underdogs. - Yogi Berra While Referring to the 1969 New York Mets]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Horse! A Horse! my kingdom for a horse! - Shakespeare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome basketball t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the basketball lovers in your life!   http://t.co/vzkdiMlClw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future is always beginning now. - Mark Strand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to find somebody and you want to be married and you want to have children, don't make it a rock star. - Stevie Nicks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would love to change the world, but they won't give me the source code]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I believe you are your work. Don't trade the stuff of your life, time, for nothing more than dollars. That's a rotten bargain - Rita  Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Guide to Business to Business Internet Marketing on LinkedIn  http://t.co/b24RHnzvgn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any fact facing us is not as important as our attitude toward it, for that determines our success or failure. - Norman Vincent Peale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't save a pitcher for tomorrow. Tomorrow it may rain. - Leo Durocher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One day your life will flash before your eyes. Make sure it is worth watching - Mooie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Powerful Tools For Your Internet Marketing Program    http://t.co/xlHBaRt207]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Kool and the Gang  http://t.co/TW7sdFKSUl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's rough to go through life with your contents looking as if they settled during shipping. - Milton Berle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Simplicity is the ultimate sophistication. - Leonardo da Vinci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Sly and the Family Stone  http://t.co/moLxEn1QdZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before the marriage, he talks &amp; she listens.  During honeymoon, she talks &amp; he listens.  Later, they both talk &amp; the neighbors listen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alcohol and gas do mix but they taste terrible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I find your lack of faith disturbing. - Darth Vader, Star Wars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Joni Mitchell  http://t.co/KwsPhkPG4m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Top 10 fitness gyms  http://t.co/2CmEIYb9Xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Top Science and Tech Websites  http://t.co/1hbHnzKpUY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here I Am T-Shirt What Are Your Other Two Wishes http://t.co/FvCRvbtcKq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It just seems to happen that by the time most of us get a little money to burn,  "the fire goes out."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the largest life insurance companies in the US!  http://t.co/tGc7BFLXms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's better to have fewer things of quality than too much expendable junk. - Rachel Zoe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wait a minute, Doc. Ah --  Are you telling me you built a time machine --  out of a DeLorean? - Marty McFly, Back to the Future]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Tips on Using Other Websites for Link Building  http://t.co/X42nYzjmiO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome kayaking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the paddling lovers in your life!  http://t.co/ej2d23hFES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to know what a man is really like, take notice of how he acts when he loses money.  Simone Weil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you haven't got it, fake it! Too short? Wear big high heels, but do practice walking! - Victoria Beckham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you wish to grow thinner, diminish your dinner. - Henry Sambrooke Leigh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cricket is basically baseball on valium - Robin Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes a man to admit he's wrong but it takes a woman to prove it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can I build a high quality free website?  http://t.co/DHZeJRlRtK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the shoe fits, you're not allowing for growth. - Robert N Coons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To win without risk is to triumph without glory. - Pierre Corneille]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yum Yum Canned Unicorn Meat - great gag gift :&gt;)  http://t.co/N9nRmWCXhI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a moral imperative. - Chris Knight, Real Genius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good-bye, Broadcast.  Hello, Conversation.  Shel Israel - Co-Author Naked Conversations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Totally cool LEGO Star Wars R2D2 Awesome --&gt; http://t.co/fslRuCmJ50]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buzz: Be sure not to lock it on my way out. On surface, Neil: Isn't that something? Magnificent sight out here. Buzz: Magnificent desolation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Firefighters recently rescued two people from an industrial clothes dryer. They were listed in stable condition but missing one sock!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was twelve when I read my first scifi magazine - Philip K. Dick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The object of education is to prepare the young to educate themselves throughout their lives. - Robert M. Hutchins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman who doesn't wear perfume has no future. Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not whether you get knocked down; it's whether you get up. - Vince Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My dad is a marketing mastermind. - Serena Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Geek Decision Ball - Picks FAIL, WIN, meh, 404 error, LOL, PWND and More! http://t.co/xNAFnTDP1v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these top auto insurance companies!  http://t.co/S5UYlSFGNR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The easiest way to stay out of hot water is to keep a cool head]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you haven't got it, fake it! Too short? Wear big high heels, but do practice walking! - Victoria Beckham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Emerson, Lake and Palmer  http://t.co/r7WhVhsXXb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crack is cheap I make too much $ to ever smoke crack. Lets get that straight. OK? We dont do crack We dont do that Crack is whack - Whtney H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is A Derivative?  http://t.co/ycdenNeZSZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Grand Slam in Tennis – what's the big deal?  http://t.co/gA2kfbeyFY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Help with Planning Garage Flooring  http://t.co/nbwqc4dORE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good introduction to Minecraft Mods - http://t.co/pFXMRQ2WD0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God has no intention of setting a limit to the efforts of man to conquer space. - Pope Pius XII]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great History of Johnny Ace: A ‘One of his Kind’ Musical Legend  http://t.co/QErYFPPQmi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Eric Clapton  http://t.co/qjRBjCozt5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Damita Jo  http://t.co/3Ik3VMlyPv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Christians Making a Profession of their Religion  http://t.co/q1dsOVbZlm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How to Select Best Climbing Equipment  http://t.co/znOu9djPfA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now I have a machine gun. Ho ho ho. - John McClane - Die Hard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Experience is not what happens to a man. It is what a man does with what happens to him. - Aldous Huxley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be nice to geek's, you'll probably end up working for one - Bill Gates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need to tie some kerosene rags around his ankles so the ants don't eat his candy #$@ - Dale Earnhardt speaking of Mark Martin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Al Green  http://t.co/s04VWqikln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you find yourself in a hole, stop digging. - Will Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still love her. But she's retarded, too. Guy Ritchie on Madonna]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL - Cool - A Computer Mouse with a Spider in it!   http://t.co/Qv1hquQN48]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get a Minecraft Enderman! http://t.co/vTd72whXpF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Bee Gees  http://t.co/MS5eZl6Gx1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Humble Pie  http://t.co/akeCqGsjJq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Overview of Major Web Conferencing Services  http://t.co/9lMmIF0KT8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Successful Alternatives For Link Building  http://t.co/1mQjNi6hVl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you chase two rabbits, both will escape. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A shoe without sex appeal is as barren as a tree without leaves. - Rita De Acosta Lydig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Assisted Living in Your Own Home  http://t.co/SrH9H1Cacm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Johnny Ace: A Life of Unfulfilled Dreams  http://t.co/6uCzbXkiR5]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>