<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[What you don't know won't hurt you but it provides a lot amusement for other people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China has blocked Twitter!!  Now 2 billion people will have no idea what I'm having for lunch.  Bummer!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read a Great Profile of Bo Jackson – An Amazing Athlete  http://t.co/yt3W2sFC2Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It takes a man to admit he's wrong but it takes a woman to prove it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a stuffed toy! It's a sleeping bag. IT'S A SHARK! - Its COOL! http://t.co/1K23NTipa3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 1 - What the heck do I have????  http://t.co/HO7GXW0Wfi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Magic texting glove with conductive yarn finger tips for iPhone, iPad and all touch screen devices - 4 colors  --&gt; http://t.co/5uqySJkTL8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Grapevine, Texas  http://t.co/TzIfXWuDrc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overview of Social Bookmarking Sites  http://t.co/Wx5LooXRTQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Crosby, Stills and Nash   http://t.co/lzUuRTsxPv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Dallas, Texas  http://t.co/Gsl0o7NaIJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding the Right Fitness Gadgets  http://t.co/n3qujp5IWS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't see pitches down the middle anymore - not even in batting practice. -  Hank Aaron]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spring is when you feel like whistling even with a shoe full of slush. - Doug Larson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money cant buy happiness, but it sure makes misery easier 2 live with!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not wait to strike until the iron is hot; but make it hot by striking - William B. Sprague]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mick Jagger can't even make a successful solo album, and the Stones are the biggest rock group that ever was.  - Don Henley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The trouble these days is there's no arrest for the wicked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Guide – Business to Business Internet Marketing Tips  http://t.co/wbOsHQbzeS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Steve Miller Band  http://t.co/Gl3rLQ9v6j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Either write something worth reading or do something worth writing about.  Benjamin Franklin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Miss Toni Fisher  http://t.co/Tk22bcB7kJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Lettermen  http://t.co/DfxFwdreeQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Future generations will be born free, equal and in debt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I live by a simple philosophy: Wear fine shoes and enjoy the best luck. - Qiana Markham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education costs money, but then so does ignorance. - Sir Claus Moser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kate Austen: So what, I'm your prisoner? James 'Sawyer' Ford: If that sort of thing turns you on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good-bye, Broadcast.  Hello, Conversation.  Shel Israel - Co-Author Naked Conversations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Awesome BookBook for iPhone- Combine Wallet and Phone and Style  http://t.co/day9ElW6Bo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[High heels were invented by a woman who had been kissed on the forehead. --&gt; Christopher Morley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because the human history is the history of shoes. The history of places where we ever tread and stand.  - Stebby Julionatan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And God took a handful of southernly wind, blew His breath over it and created the horse. - Bedouin Legend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Use Twitter to Make the Most Of Your Business  http://t.co/NgMuQM2Y34]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Great Resort in Palm Coast Florida  http://t.co/xuDYlbc6Rp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Careers with a Creative Writing Degree  http://t.co/NpQCkWpcpM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some of the worst mistakes in my life were haircuts --&gt; Jim Morrison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our Review of Amazon’s Popular Kindle Reader  http://t.co/lvVThlnX6j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before you judge a man, walk a mile in his shoes. After that who cares? He's a mile away and you've got his shoes - Billy Connolly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Rose Royce  http://t.co/5pM4HpLwAu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Don Henley  http://t.co/X66hNZgcZd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mr. Bentley - He builds fast trucks. - Ettore Bugatti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To err is human, to purr, feline - Robert Byrne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Strategy Consulting Firms to Avoid  http://t.co/QHWEvQznxL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Tools for Finding Good Keywords  http://t.co/oiOXVSTsRI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Rufus  http://t.co/ZPHpwEGhBg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would not invest in any shoe that is too trendy. - Rachel Roy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fitness - If it came in a bottle, everybody would have a great body. - Cher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's behind you doesn't matter. - Enzo Ferrari]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't compare me to my father. Our similarities are different. -  Dale Berra about his father Yogi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Help with Planning Garage Flooring  http://t.co/5PMsQKSci1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, give us the man who sings at his work. - Thomas Carlyle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of Little House on The Prairie Episode - "In the Big Inning"  http://t.co/6vUzeeiF5N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For 45 cents, Americans deserve a postage stamp which tastes better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Youth is when we want to set the world on fire... Middle age is when we hope our children won't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Isaac Asimov  http://t.co/jfO3nUwiEi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cooking for Geeks: Real Science, Great Hacks, and Good Food  -&gt; http://t.co/T1bQmXr3gq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trying to sneak a pitch past Hank Aaron is like trying to sneak a sunrise past a rooster. - Curt Simmons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Elvis Presley    http://t.co/EUkjjciQVH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was born in 1950 and watched science fiction and horror movies on TV and was always really fascinated by them. - Rick Baker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep you can keep your devices charged via solar power - find out here - http://t.co/xrKGeyD8Q7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome marriage t-shirts &amp; gear - give the gift of marriage!  http://t.co/Z56urBaXqQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attorney Search: Hiring the Right Attorney  http://t.co/JZMOVWeSvK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His timing is perfect, so is his two-timing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to John D. Loudermilk  http://t.co/kXq8q0MqMK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Design is a constant challenge to balance comfort with luxe, the practical with the desirable. - Donna Karan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of James Gang  http://t.co/ZYcx2HXmSz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these alternatives to traditional beef hamburgers!  http://t.co/G8FMQxtteq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Though man through evolution, has learned to walk in an upright position, his eyes still swing from limb to limb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only thing worse than a Mets game is a Mets double header. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you love James Bond?  Check out these cool t-shirts, hats, stickers and more --&gt;  http://t.co/SjJiIZved6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the History of the Nautilus Fitness Equipment  http://t.co/ISJDJWsR9C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Orleans  http://t.co/FumaKXH7f9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Firefighters recently rescued two people from an industrial clothes dryer. They were listed in stable condition but missing one sock!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The dog was created especially for children. He is the God of frolic. - Henry Ward Beecher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One Family’s Adoption Stories  http://t.co/OYXVYidoh9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to 3D Printing  http://t.co/7pxzcTUwxp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ginger Rogers did everything Fred Astaire did, backwards and on high heels - Faith Whittlesey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who's gonna turn down a Junior Mint? It's chocolate, it's peppermint - it's delicious! - Kramer, Seinfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to J.R.R. Tolkien  http://t.co/ljpGPALevM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Grapevine, Texas  http://t.co/TzIfXWuDrc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Flower Mound, Texas  http://t.co/o48s4QK3Rf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Brady Bunch is an American sitcom classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/W9qjQ41lyy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very "COOL" Titanic Ice Cube mold - http://t.co/4pAauSBKbv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Sword Umbrella - Eye Catching http://t.co/EewQh2ScbH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Guide – Business to Business Internet Marketing Tips  http://t.co/wbOsHQbzeS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tennis is a pass time where love means nothing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotta Love It - 12 Nerd Rubber Duckies!  Makes Bath Time Fun!  http://t.co/ghkLXX4okR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes I can't figure designers out. It's as if they flunked human anatomy. --&gt; Erma Bombeck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Glowing "Moon In My Room" Wall Decal - Glows! http://t.co/cvE7sZd97l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A successful man is one who can lay a firm foundation with the bricks others have thrown at him... David Brinkley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More die in the United States of too much food than too little. - John Kenneth Galbraith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the largest life insurance companies in the US!  http://t.co/MoG422KPII]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Creative Writing Degree - Why You Should Consider One  http://t.co/0Drfb2yQez]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are three things you can do in a baseball game. You can win, or you can lose, or it can rain. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, I understand when they make a mistake and everyone at home is throwing their shoe at the television set. - Vanna White]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to ZZ Top  http://t.co/kZG6tPMHgM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automatic rotating laser light that provides hours of fun for your feline and canine friends - Keep the cat happy!  http://t.co/xMP2uBufuE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's behind you doesn't matter. - Enzo Ferrari]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You may have to fight a battle more than once to win it. - Margaret Thatcher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overheard:  "I don't mind going to work.  It's that long wait to go home that bothers me."]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>