<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn Great E-Commerce and E-Marketing Tips  http://t.co/WnP5td9vjE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Patsy Cline  http://t.co/NbcE952r9w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dogs come when they're called; cats take a message and get back to you later. - Mary Bly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Race cars are neither beautiful nor ugly. They become beautiful when they win. - Enzo Ferrari]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rock is so much fun. That's what it's all about - filling up the chest cavities and empty kneecaps and elbows.  - Jimi Hendrix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's easier to ask forgiveness than it is to get permission - Grace Hopper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The safest way to double your money is to fold it over and put it in your pocket. - Kin Hubbard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to WordTracker SEO Tools http://t.co/RkBe1nvNyj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The primary one being, like I said, I don't like rock 'n' roll piano.  - Warren Zevon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Lesley Gore  http://t.co/4mLWn63edb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Modern Homesteading  http://t.co/LS93mVDf95]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I could have played another year, but I would have been playing for the money, and baseball deserves better than that. - George Brett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like wrestling a gorilla- you don't quit when you're tired, you quit when the gorilla is tired - Robert Strauss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The box said 'Requires Windows 95 or better'. So I installed LINUX.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Increasingly, search is our mechanism for how we understand ourselves our world, and our place with in it.  John Battelle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is amazing how may drivers, even at the Formula One Level, think that the brakes are for slowing the car down. - Mario Andretti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Snooky Lanson  http://t.co/XKPoBo4JtV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do clever men make good husbands? "No, clever men don't become husbands!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Politicians should read science fiction, not westerns and detective stories. - Arthur C. Clarke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That which is bitter to endure may be sweet to remember. - Thomas Fuller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 1 - What the heck do I have????  http://t.co/c2SYBJjt10]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We never repent of having eaten too little. - Thomas Jefferson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Don McLean  http://t.co/NGkLZs6anI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids can learn over 20 optical illusions - lots of fun and great learning! http://t.co/DejBd1bKv3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of LA Gear  http://t.co/CgyR8SCrip]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am the best in baseball. - Reggie Jackson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very very cool SpyHawk RC Plane with 3.5 inch LCD Monitor/Controller &amp; video recording &amp; auto-pilot system - HOT - http://t.co/sJSS02qpCy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was a pretty good coach and working with marketing was like coaching. - Bernard Ebbers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have not failed. I've just found 10,000 ways that won't work - Thomas Alva Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to 3D Printing  http://t.co/UZcwgyAxdY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To win without risk is to triumph without glory. - Pierre Corneille]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Use SEO on Multiple Websites to Drive Traffic in Your Direction  http://t.co/a0Zv0XzcAl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious T-Shirt - “I Got Your Back” http://t.co/gUy7XXgYvJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laverne and Shirley is an American sitcom classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/djLg2msL5i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Doobie Brothers  http://t.co/eTk2igcSZh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only point in making money is, you can tell some big shot where to go. Humphrey Bogart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If having a soul means being able to feel love and loyalty and gratitude, then animals are better off than a lot of humans - James Herriot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people are born on third base and go through life thinking they hit a triple. - Barry Switzer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Alice Cooper  http://t.co/0iHZrFQymn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like to literally put women on a pedestal. - Vivienne Westwood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Al Green  http://t.co/NvaxZp4pIO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If opportunity doesn't knock, build a door. - Milton Berle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I believe you are your work. Don't trade the stuff of your life, time, for nothing more than dollars. That's a rotten bargain - Rita  Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All My Friends Are Dead - Kids Book - Darkly Hilarious!  http://t.co/WCR8bgpdF9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I got hit in the head pretty hard. My clock ran backwards for two years. - Buddy Baker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Average White Band  http://t.co/B3vwiuZy1z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[80% of the final exam will be based on the one lecture you missed and the one book you didn't read.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball has the great advantage over cricket of being sooner ended. - George Bernard Shaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about the Bay Area city of Danville, California http://t.co/1IXH3XXWvc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet - very cool mechanical pin clock - very unique - http://t.co/xzobtG4Frj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Auto racing, bull fighting, and mountain climbing are the only real sports --  all the others are games. - Ernest Hemingway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Formal education will make you a living; self-education will make you a fortune.  Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ways to Earn a Living with a Creative Writing Degree  http://t.co/AgX4MQy8Y5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Biking Guide BMX Review  http://t.co/xa3u4wKAuz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read an Introduction to Whataburger  http://t.co/kbqdL4kPjh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Blue Oyster Cult   http://t.co/UFziJ8jbLQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the fascinating history of the New York Yankees - http://t.co/gtR2phjVuf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good introduction to Minecraft Mods - http://t.co/spn7T5AVkH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To finish first, you must first finish. - Juan Manuel Fangio]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Music from this Bose Blue Tooth system - iPad, iPhone and more - easy great sound -&gt; http://t.co/2ALisBBYXr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read How to Use LinkedIn for Your Company   http://t.co/UjjquOFTE4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laser Tag anywhere - cool guns and app make it easy to play anytime!  http://t.co/s2G6Z8Rczu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Dallas, Texas  http://t.co/jMsXiF0YVj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome tennis t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the tennis lovers in your life!   http://t.co/z9aDyIuKKo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you cease to dream you cease to live - Malcolm Forbes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Courage is not the absence of fear, but rather the judgment that something else is more important than fear - Ambrose Redmoon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of Little House on The Prairie Episode - "In the Big Inning"  http://t.co/h7j7j8mipF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read The Story of the Dramatics Classic Rock Group http://t.co/2CPF3rNVMZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read a Short Introduction to ABBA  http://t.co/k590Xamy0g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is the way society functions. Aren't you a part of society? - Kramer, Seinfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool check out this Nerd Kit...  http://t.co/MmLxGk2xS7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Adoption Part II - the Bulgaria Phase  http://t.co/tWPuQiD814]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So cool - German Beer Steins - check out their history - http://t.co/RCYKH174fL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very "COOL" Titanic Ice Cube mold - http://t.co/V41V6YtuEw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Coors Beer  http://t.co/JQ4r6xVS0i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Very Unusual Hamburgers  http://t.co/i5xa1HZhuB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overheard in hollywood: "You said their marriage wouldn't last! They left the church together, didn't they?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Grand Slam in Tennis – what's the big deal?  http://t.co/ekoCz6kJCB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Top Tips for Using Facebook Pages for Your Business  http://t.co/iFpogDjbw4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow these Steps to Clean Your Credit  http://t.co/EA38qw0vBk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd make a wonderful Lady Macbeth. I'll wear a pair of platform shoes or something - Bette Midler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read How Customer Connects Mount-Up with Social Media Sites  http://t.co/JInEfzUvxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Budweiser  http://t.co/Dud1YGgWFU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helpful Tips for Web Marketing  http://t.co/DCB2DUwfie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am a fashion person, and fashion is not only about clothes -- it's about all kinds of change --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So my degree was in political science, which I think was - the closest I could come to marketing is politics. - Steve Case]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the History of the Nautilus Fitness Equipment  http://t.co/HrRcN0t0Km]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Condolence:  something that aches when everything else feels so good]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes I can't figure designers out. It's as if they flunked human anatomy. --&gt; Erma Bombeck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Great Resort in Palm Coast Florida  http://t.co/TgEVo2PcXv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Are the Major Kinds of Insurance?  http://t.co/H6pFxkZgsE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For 45 cents, Americans deserve a postage stamp which tastes better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It gets late early out there. - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Celiac Disease And Gluten Free Foods  http://t.co/WZSzPfZ0bO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Watches  http://t.co/q29tchmFNr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who Needs a Boyfriend to Snuggle With This Pillow! http://t.co/B4oYZ4okV8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Music from this Bose Blue Tooth system - iPad, iPhone and more - easy great sound -&gt; http://t.co/4WPitXPiMM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The History of The Six Million Dollar Man  http://t.co/XYT3aes5bI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are so many emotions involved that I would like to wait until I know I'm with the right person &amp; married. Britney on virginity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this gallery of the top 10 European beers!  http://t.co/p7txLftXD8]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>