<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't let a bad day make you feel like you have a bad life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look at everything as though you were seeing it either for the first or last time. -Betty Smith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FaithReeI: https://t.co/cZ1YrQZx7b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Talking about our problems is our greatest addiction. Break the habit. Talk about your joys.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't give up. https://t.co/dmI7xtZ4Pt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheDaiIyPuppy: I don't wanna wear the pink leash today :( https://t.co/0YBCyDou7i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When things aren't adding up in your life, start subtracting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To the man who only has a hammer, everything he encounters begins to look like a nail. -Abraham Maslow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FaithReeI: https://t.co/AEV9NxKeXd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you get to the end of your rope, tie a knot &amp; hang on. -Franklin D. Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You've got this!! https://t.co/UDbi6thiwq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God gives his hardest battles to his strongest soldiers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Decide that you want it more than you are afraid of it. -Bill Cosby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have faith, something great is waiting for you on the other side of FEAR. https://t.co/FLe9w6Uf1i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @coffee_lst: First things first. https://t.co/eDbt1u3qQn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Girls want a guy who say I love you every night and proves it every day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is beauty in simplicity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have faith that God is living out a divine plan through me. Have faith in God. - Mark 11:22]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live bold. https://t.co/abZGpcxU1K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When a goal matters enough to a person, that person will find a way to accomplish what at first seemed impossible. - Nido Qubein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @catscofffee: I don't care! https://t.co/dHixpAjGO9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't build a reputation on what you're going to do. -Henry Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never get so busy making a living that you forget to make a life..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you don't step forward you will always remain in the same place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is not what happens to you but how you respond to what happens to you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Challenges are what make life interesting. Overcoming them is what makes life meaningful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's difficult to follow your dream. It's a tragedy not to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mediocrity will always try to drag excellence down to its level. Don't trade your superiority for their inferiority.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Inspire_Us: Let your results speak for you!

Get this t-shirt here --&gt; https://t.co/fwvGJty79O https://t.co/xxx6Eq6Kie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whatever you want to do, do it now. There are only so many tomorrows.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LifeLimits: Happiness can be found in the darkest of times, if one only remembers to turn on the light.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The purpose of life is to live a life of purpose.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FaithReeI: https://t.co/n2SJtgJ5Z9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deal with the world the way it is, not the way you wish it was. - John Chambers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Faith in God includes faith in His timing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The tragedy in life doesn't lie in not reaching your goal. The tragedy lies in having no goal to reach. - Benjamin Mays]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TabithaKhaye: You never know how strong you are until being strong is the only choice you have.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Giving up doesn't always mean you're weak. Sometimes it means you are strong and smart enough to let go and move on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happiness is in the heart, not in the circumstances. - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FaithReeI: You will turn back to me &amp; ask for help, &amp; I will answer your prayers - Jer 29:12]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our experiences shape us.  Appreciate them, for you wouldn't be the person you are without them. https://t.co/gLzSzZ4D5p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your time is limited, so don't waste it living someone else's life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We all have difficult days, have faith. https://t.co/ezWl7dnZFM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is no love without forgiveness, and there is no forgiveness without love.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality means doing it right when no one is looking. - Henry Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A pessimist sees the difficulty in every opportunity; an optimist sees the opportunity in every difficulty.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If your ship doesn't come in, swim out to it. - Jonathan Winters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DogsCoffee: Relatable? :)

Get your tee here --&gt; https://t.co/9gO5X5Yfsa https://t.co/xdVvYrtWFs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the whole world was blind, how many people would you impress?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We all fall, pick yourself up and start a new. https://t.co/7ypManQdeu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For attractive lips, speak words of kindness. For lovely eyes, seek out the good in people. -Audrey Hepburn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The worst thing about being lied to is simply knowing you weren't worth the truth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FaithReeI: https://t.co/O3udcOJUYx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of my favorite quotes. https://t.co/LM7vRhcR59]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WomanDoItAll: A godmother is a gift sent from above. :)

Get this t-shirt here --&gt; https://t.co/5SChD0cS5R https://t.co/TlVxMiJ4na]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes the wrong choices bring us to the right places.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never bend your head. Always hold it high. Look the world straight in the eye. - Helen Keller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Men are disturbed not by the things that happen, but by their opinion of the things that happen. - Epictetus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @desire_lnspire: The happiest people don't necessarily have the best of everything but they make the most of everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you ever think about giving up, remember why you held on for so long. - Hayley Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing great in the world has ever been accomplished without passion. - Georg Wilhelm Friedrich Hegel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fall seven times, stand up eight. https://t.co/tc4C2ml2ZF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happiness cannot come from without. It must come from within. - Helen Keller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We lose ourselves in the things we love. We find ourselves there, too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The strongest people aren't always the people who win, but the people who don't give up when they lose.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be a blessing to someone today - Proverbs 11:25]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It always seems impossible until its done. -Nelson Mandela]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't go through life, grow through life. - Eric Butterworth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Train your mind to see the good in everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one has ever become poor by giving.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LifeLimits: You cannot protect yourself from sadness without protecting yourself from happiness. - Jonathan Safran Foer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Knowing is not enough; we must apply. Willing is not enough; we must do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We could never learn to be brave &amp; patient, if there were only joys in the world. -Helen Keller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great advice!! https://t.co/2eXeWDr9Pi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LV_Sports: Train for your life ;D

Get this tee here --&gt; https://t.co/vypJvNvmJp https://t.co/myOg4m6ZSd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Action expresses priorities.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FaithReeI: https://t.co/rgE9wUorcV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never let your fear decide your future.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The way we choose to see the world creates the world we see. - Barry Neil Kaufman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Quote_Soup: I am who I am today because of the choices I made yesterday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am who I am today because of the choices I made yesterday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Success is not final, failure is not fatal: it is the courage to continue that counts. - Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing you wear is more important than your smile. -Connie Stevens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be so busy loving your life that you have no time for hate, regret or fear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Quote_Soup: The past cannot be changed. The future is yet in your power. - Mary Pickford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The past cannot be changed. The future is yet in your power. - Mary Pickford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Faith is not the belief that God will do what you want. It is the belief that God will do what is right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look for the good in every moment. https://t.co/X35SjGhqCe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An honest answer is like a kiss on the lips. -Proverbs 24:26]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheDaiIyKitten: Purrrfect!

Get this tee here --&gt; https://t.co/MMgUqhPArS https://t.co/kkSUSFkTRg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You deserve a vacation :) https://t.co/7k3LfPogEv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weakness of attitude becomes weakness of character. - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @The_Gospels: Amen. To sign-up for our daily emails, Visit -&gt; https://t.co/1qRf0GTTd3 https://t.co/S1be2FiHrT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is change. Growth is optional. Choose wisely. -Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FaithReeI: https://t.co/alvqxE9u6w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You were born to win, although to be a winner, you must plan to win, prepare to win, &amp; expect to win.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be strong &amp; courageous. Do not be terrified or discouraged, for the LORD your God will be with you wherever you go. -Josh 1:9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FamousWomen: Never give up hope, because you never know, it could still happen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't measure a man's success by how high he climbs, but how high he bounces when he hits bottom. - George Patton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Losers quit when they're tired. Winners quit when they've won.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>