<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterhassett @tjyoshie77 New campaign: #RMNBXBringTheBeb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tjyoshie77 @russianmachine NO U? Y WOULD I GO?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@russianmachine I am ready! #RMNBX https://t.co/OkMR6DMYN2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JapersRink "He not fat."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OvercastFM Is there any plans that the web browser will be able to show folders?  Just hoping to organize all my desired podcasts.  Thanks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Something isn't right here @espn @Capitals #faceswap? https://t.co/UCNRy5ZF7A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Uber should have an option of which state your driver is from because I'd pick a #DC person over #MD or #VA any day of the week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ElyseBee Neither. Or both.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does anyone else think the mic looks like @DimFilipovic's foot in the @hockeypdocast image? Like he's climbing out of the hole? https://t.co/Tq8VsSgYfh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Puppies are great for Instagram, cuteness &amp; face licks. But they are terrible for sleeping, headaches, wires, cars or planes... so... https://t.co/C6HkEIXCRa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attached are 2016-01-12 numbers with rank results. West ended as expected. East - i guess a lot can happen...
@peterhassett @IneffectiveMath https://t.co/XdBhG32CbM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IneffectiveMath do you have last year's numbers at this point so we can compare results?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kjscarbro @gcscarbro https://t.co/7ZjGyZVTR9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@russianmachine If you had to face the #Pens, would you choose first or second round?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@russianmachine When 74 comes back separate from 27??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@russianmachine Seven Months Ago.  #NailedIt. https://t.co/2lWkiYruHf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I CAN GO!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!! https://t.co/bLXpQSxoVo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CAN WE ALL AGREE IT'S JUST 0-0 NOW??? #CapsPens]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeyJayJRogers "Kunitz isn't going to take anything from Wilson." wait... waht?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @NHL what are the chances the #playoff structure will screw one of these teams? #AskingForAFriend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@russianmachine I volunteer as tribute! https://t.co/Fa5LuakD6r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[i'm just so confused]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer crashed at 5:03pm on a #Monday... sounds about right. #BlueScreenOfDEATH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tjyoshie77 if ONLY!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@russianmachine All this Ovi &amp; Backy crap..Why havent we seen an article about #Oshie in top10 NHL +/-?  Such anti-USA bias. cc: @tjyoshie77]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turn on #caps game. 0-0. Commercial. Go to bathroom. Burky scores. Comes back from bathroom. Commercial. UGH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @calebgardner: Biden:&lt;whispers&gt; not Slytherin ... not Slytherin

Obama: Joe, this isn't--

Biden: ... not Slytherin ...

Obama: you know…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Besides @hockeypdocast and @JapersRinkRadio, anyone have suggestions for regular #Hockey #podcasts?  #NHL or #Caps preferably.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mickequ @JustinMcElroy going to the "Chug and Squeeze"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rockportlimited Ive spent too much time thinking about what impact of #Taako sacrificing himself for the good of the group would do to Magnus...#TheZoneCast]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ElyseBee @peterhassett @pfholden The good old days. Or bad? I'm still not sure what to believe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justinfung https://t.co/hFYm17jcmY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OfficialEmery So..I land at 8pm in Nashville on Feb 17 for my Bachelor party.Do you think I could make it to the venue in time for "Walls"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @russianmachine: Another outdoor game for the Caps? According to @FriedgeHNIC, the NHL's eyeing the Naval Academy as potential venue htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Stringhama I tuned out for a time but have recently been listening to @JapersRinkRadio and wanted to say you're doing great. Good hosting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listening to @JPress41 on @JapersRinkRadio makes me feel like I have a Brooks Orpik Hockey IQ... mainly just bc I agree w everything he says]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My phone made @russianmachine a restricted site... maybe it's telling me to spend less time there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DimFilipovic Post-CBJ-streak does @JonathanWillis change anything? #Caps #Caps #Caps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JapersRink @pfholden closes eyes "Take Grubi, take Grubi, take Grubi" https://t.co/mAuIZmVOUT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeyJayJRogers that gif is tied for first place on my desktop.  Tied with this beauty, https://t.co/4sgeHWcX6R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#2016 Wasn't so bad for me.  Big thanks to all involved.  My 2016 In Review: https://t.co/48EssJp3cB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aria_sharif @JustinMcElroy Nailed it. #Ango]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aria_sharif if that's true you're my favorite person.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aria_sharif do me a favor... if you remember.  What's the episode where @JustinMcElroy / #Taako yells "My Boy! My Beautiful Baby Boy!"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kjscarbro @downcastapp can i stream online (instead of downloading) and make folders for content? like work vs comedy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OvercastFM Hey.  Any way I can see my folders on the website instead of just the app? Heart you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheZoneCast #TAZCasting
Hear me out... 
Taako-Aaron Carter
Magnus-Shaq
Merle-Hilary Duff
$Profit$
@travismcelroy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JustinMcElroy @TheZoneCast 
#HaydenChristensen as every #RedRobe... #TAZCasting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#TAZCasting  Sean Bean as #BarryBlueJeans...
@travismcelroy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@travismcelroy I used to think Helen Mirren was the Director... but not so sure post her #SuffferingGame reveal #TAZCasting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for a #Podcast catcher that I can stream on my computer via interwebs and make folders/organize?
Have used Stitcher but cant add RSS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honest question: does @verizoncenterpr sell @ChickfilA on #sunday #caps games?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Why is PP2 out there right now.... oh." - me just now. #caps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonowles88 @jackerman86 I hate the playoff format. I already hate the pens. What benefit does it really bring the league?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jackerman86 @jonowles88 nope I lied. Won in 6 then lost in 6. Round one just felt like 7 games.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jackerman86 @jonowles88 game 7 with philly in round 1 and won, lost in 6 to Pitt in round 2.
I'll give up the future for a cup this year...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@lnovakk my phone remembers that night a bit different... https://t.co/5ugjAdIhux]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[you guys! I'm famous! https://t.co/C5axIPThAt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lnovakk holy poop you're like 9 blue lines away from me!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#SuspiciousPackage is apparently just someone's lost luggage. #FranklinSquare
(At least that's what it looks like from 6th floor) #fakenews? https://t.co/9IsMjd2341]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@lnovakk prove it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you think other #NHL teams see the #Shattenkirk trade and decide they should be sellers this year? #Caps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suspicious package. #franklinsquare https://t.co/SE3lD2nGjv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Something is going down in #FranklinSquare https://t.co/hlOtpaPFhE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kat326: https://t.co/nFRRbFKBsk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @peterhassett: NATE SCHMIDT DUDE https://t.co/4XuYYb9IEi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pfholden: https://t.co/quS3G6atGP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DimFilipovic shhh don't ruin this! https://t.co/ppepVqFuVN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DimFilipovic: IS IT THE CAPS YEAR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Im dying. #caps https://t.co/9Tqz65Lhb6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @carabahniuk: Anyone else catch @ianoland videoboming @MayHockeyCSN during the intermission report? https://t.co/z1wg1QzqrH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes I forget how much I like @Kuzya92... and then he plays a hockey game and I remember.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@MayHockeyCSN why are you wasting your time with #99 when you have the great @ianoland in the building??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@CSNCapitals can the #caps trade all of their President's trophies for one Cup? #capsoilers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AndrewWK: FORECAST FOR TONIGHT: https://t.co/ZBf7l18j88]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I guess I'm a #bro now. Sup? https://t.co/9HUv8j5cU3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the #Nashville Predators store. I found a shirt for @ianoland AND @peterhassett https://t.co/embX0Jfygx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An hour and half until I leave for my #bachelor party... https://t.co/9hiJxZjDsV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Ryan_Deem: If we're being honest, I've never been completely happy with the length of any pair of pants I've ever owned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kjscarbro @BrettTrapp #Linkedin just emailed my boss that I switched jobs. So thats exciting. Also I'm 90% sure I was involved in a lawsuit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LinkedInHelp it says "Feb 2017" not "Present"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LinkedInHelp Yes, but it's not a current position. But for some reason it thinks I have a new job...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LinkedInHelp I've already turned off the updates but for some reason people are STILL seeing this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LinkedInHelp Find a way, to you into your system, or my profile and stopping sharing infomation about my "new position" which isn't new.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LinkedInHelp So my boss just emailed me saying "Is there something you want to tell me?" in regards to you all emailing EVERYONE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CharlieMcManus9 Hey, quick question. Do YoShirt's shirt run larger or smaller?  Trying to decide what size shirts to get...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JapersRink @pfholden hey, me too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @AmericanAir my buddy just found out his grandpa died..so he wanted to switch his flight this weekend. But it's $500.Anything we can do?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YOU GUYS! Maybe.. just maybe... it's the Jeff Schultz karma coming BACK to us! cc: @JapersRink @russianmachine https://t.co/qGFLkKZd3K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@pfholden isn't that what we said with Weber and Gleason?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me during @Steve_Dangle Pod:
*I hope he talks about the #Caps
"How many President Trophy winners have won the cup? 2?"
*Lays down. Cries.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @comedysavage: My new Hobby is photoshopping the eyes from Pixar's Cars onto the rigs from Mad Max: Fury Road https://t.co/b2KG7NN3xA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT wouldn't let me have #spotify... but they would let me have #TeamViewer... so... now I have spotify. Suckers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JustinMcElroy: What I’m saying is that somewhere within its boundaries, Don’t Mess With the Zohan contains the SPARK OF THE DIVINE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterhassett #nice #schmidtuation https://t.co/XQlsI2n9pf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@LinkedInHelp have you thought about giving your user's control of their information becoming publicized? It's a pretty groundbreaking idea]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@LinkedIn for a company that got sued for spam shitting everyone, you'd think this wouldn't be a problem...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@LinkedIn next time ask me if I want you to cyber blast #alternativefacts to my entire network and screw me over.
FYI I would say "no"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@LinkedIn I don't have a new job. I have the same job. Now epeople are asking me what's going on... so I have to explain this bullshit 2/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@linkedin, all I put that I've been consulting another firm for a few months &amp; you decide to email every1 I know that I got a new job. 1/]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>