<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool check out this Nerd Kit...  http://t.co/glkB8VEKOA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The trouble these days is there's no arrest for the wicked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It wasnt a mission to be a rock star. It wasnt a mission of mine to even be a movie star. I just intended to be a good actor. - Don Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop praising a woman, she'll think you don't love her.  Keep it up and she'll think she is too good for you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So my degree was in political science, which I think was - the closest I could come to marketing is politics. - Steve Case]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Importance of Keywords for Search Engine Optimization (SEO)  http://t.co/bJNAycP0aF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Gardening Fall Flowers  http://t.co/qNF9Nly8Za]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great History of Johnny Adams  http://t.co/HqR4eTUE89]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've looked into the eye of this island, and what I saw was beautiful. - John Locke, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to ZZ Top  http://t.co/OhbVkHJskK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay, that thing in the woods, maybe it's a monster, maybe it's a pissed off giraffe, I don't know. Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once burned a lesson is learned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Real education must ultimately be limited to men who insist on knowing, the rest is mere sheep-herding. - Ezra Pound]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Tab Hunter - 1950s idol   http://t.co/MRSYPEj3Xg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You may have to fight a battle more than once to win it. - Margaret Thatcher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hello again, everybody. It's a bee-yooo-tiful day for baseball. -  Harry Caray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of Stargate Universe  http://t.co/g3RHZllKdf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Boz Scaggs  http://t.co/peUYNcKos8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Empty pockets never held anyone back. Only empty heads and empty hearts can do that.  Norman Vincent Peale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He who opens a school door, closes a prison. - Victor Hugo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do clever men make good husbands? "No, clever men don't become husbands!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is Renter's Insurance?  http://t.co/fgKDWQxC27]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tom Cruise is rumored to wear them - shoe lifts - read their fascinating history... http://t.co/hat8fsKj0x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does Food Dye Cause Hyperactive Behavior in Children?  http://t.co/GFVEg5B9WF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Joey Dee and the Starliters  http://t.co/akm4Ix0h9c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Andy Gibb  http://t.co/T6bCQXL4fj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people are born on third base and go through life thinking they hit a triple. - Barry Switzer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was a pretty good coach and working with marketing was like coaching. - Bernard Ebbers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Cool Types of Garage Flooring  http://t.co/syP42f29nB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The History of Rolex Watches – The Start of Something Great  http://t.co/A2D78LJtaK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are going to turn this team around 360 degrees. Jason Kidd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I was president of the good old U.S.A., I'd turn the churches into strip clubs and watch the whole world pray.  Kid Rock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must accept finite disappointment, but we must never lose infinite hope. - Martin Luther King, Jr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If my uniform doesn't get dirty, I haven't done anything in the baseball game - Rickey Henderson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Superhero caped glasses - totally cool!  http://t.co/fLrIBBekpk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dream house is one that cost twice as much as you ever dreamed it would…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A dog is the only thing on earth that will love you more than you love yourself. - Josh Billings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're a very expensive group; we break a lot of rules. It's unheard of to combine opera with a rock theme, my dear. - Freddie Mercury]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't win unless you learn how to lose. - Kareem Abdul-Jabbar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supporting Adopted Students: Parents and Teachers Working Together  http://t.co/u5CHlbFGHl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An expert is a man who has made all the mistakes which can be made, in a narrow field. - Niels Bohr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is what happens to you when you're busy making other plans - John Lennon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you ain't making waves, you ain't kickin' hard enough - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If high heels were so wonderful, men would be wearing them. - Sue Grafton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not the employer who pays the wages. Employers only handle the money. It's the customer who pays the wages.  Henry Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Millie Jackson  http://t.co/p2uMwTijlf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lot of rock bands are truly a legend in their own minds. - David Lee Roth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Spencer Davis Group  http://t.co/tfpV07Fpgj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Fun Science Ideas for Kids  http://t.co/7YBTipSWVa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never make fun of the geeks, one day they will be your boss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are so many emotions involved that I would like to wait until I know I'm with the right person &amp; married. Britney on virginity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Bob Dylan -- His Biography    http://t.co/Zdrq31SR6j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome darts t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the darts lovers in your life!   http://t.co/kIumbjf7F0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exciting History of Baseball  http://t.co/MUnrDLOAWF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Successful Alternatives For Link Building  http://t.co/E2IqPjbSx1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education costs money, but then so does ignorance. - Sir Claus Moser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rock n' roll is dream soup, what's your brand? - Patti Smith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LinkedIn for Your Company Proves to be Effective  http://t.co/8v0AMFKi6E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Dan Fogelberg  http://t.co/sy30DdUwru]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I won't be a rock star. I will be a legend. - Freddie Mercury]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know anything about music. In my line you don't have to.  - Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overheard:  "I don't mind going to work.  It's that long wait to go home that bothers me."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Windows has detected you do not have a keyboard. Press 'F9" to continue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tantrums, Sick Days, and Being a Patient Mommy  http://t.co/cf7z9YbjjE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one really knows who created Bitcoin - read about the fascinating history of Satoshi Nakamoto... http://t.co/7FyKat04Lm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome darts t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the darts lovers in your life!   http://t.co/kIumbjf7F0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating Introduction to Marmalade Insurance: How to Select an Insurance Agency  http://t.co/4Cmv8rjSrM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're told to pay as we go! But where are we going?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn the Best Spots for Mountain Climbing  http://t.co/sRgfXeZlZb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blogging Season 1 of Lilyhammer by Netflix   http://t.co/LuDOx4Fm0T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You maniacs! You blew it up! Oh, damn you! Damn you all to hell! - Taylor, Planet of the Apes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow these Steps to Clean Your Credit  http://t.co/cmn5NmN3Ob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Michael Jordan Shoes  http://t.co/5R5Vdpl1Rd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Average White Band  http://t.co/uOPZXdVQV5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Colonize Mars: Can This Dream Become a Reality?  http://t.co/kEQ96LMtAh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Underwater Scooter - How Cool! http://t.co/ReqT1wsnW4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Flying Alarm Clock - COOL!  http://t.co/9N2xfhjZXx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Small Dogs Can Make Great Pets - Picking the Right Breed  http://t.co/vrmJKe7z6o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who dares to teach must never cease to learn. - John Cotton Dana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Best Tips Given for Facebook Pages Geared for Business  http://t.co/Nu2ow03Pyk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman is as young as she feels like telling you she is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Molly Hatchet  http://t.co/85e4h9sP9X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't go into details, I've already told you  more than I overheard myself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can a leopard change his spots?  "By going from one spot to another"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Schnauzers  http://t.co/1KsbjbN2ae]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I realize that my place &amp; position in history is I will go down as voice of this generation of this decade. I will be loudest voice.  Kayne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Ral Donner  http://t.co/KUk8onvvjs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These Yoda Lights Must You Have!  Wonderful Geek Gear! http://t.co/UKVwNXWQAQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is a better safeguard of liberty than a standing army. - Edward Everett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overheard in hollywood: "You said their marriage wouldn't last! They left the church together, didn't they?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Rush  http://t.co/EYWM3uYE8O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes you can play 3 Man Chess - Check It Out! http://t.co/OXovfnQc1u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Success is where preparation and opportunity meet. - Bobby Unser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Linda Ronstadt  http://t.co/oqjlK3iYb6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Benefits of iPads for Seniors  http://t.co/l2UhCVaEvJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is what we are, and football is what we have become. - Mary McGrory]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about Oakland, California  http://t.co/VtIMQGcAw7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winners take time to relish their work, knowing that scaling the mountain is what makes the view from the top so exhilarating. Denis Waitley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I had never seen much of Star Trek, or any other science fiction, before I was cast. But Seven's wonderful. - Jeri Ryan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Doobie Brothers  http://t.co/Tjn82hvxOu]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>