<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@KevZCastle https://t.co/dBCThsNrgp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DonTonyD https://t.co/UF1ojV3iJ7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnLeinsterFan @Mikedragon32 @adamkeni @Vicki_McGrath @molloyjh @the_crouch @MaloneyCiara @LeinsterLeo Sooooooooooooo this is awkward.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorthomas89 As for I*na, a lobby group should never have charitable status. Are you sure this is the case?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorthomas89 Unfortunately I can't see this thread as revolution still has me blocked for daring to question him/her. Hope he/she is enjoying the bubble.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Renewed. Another season in the 'dork' side you goys. @Mikedragon32 @adamkeni @AnnLeinsterFan @Vicki_McGrath @molloyjh @the_crouch @MaloneyCiara]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GardaTraffic: Dundalk Road Policing Unit: First car stopped and seized for no insurance. Driver then 'phoned a friend' who arrived in a…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mikedragon32 Awesome.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CorkSeashell Wow Michelle! Enjoy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh no. Raided? https://t.co/W9PHpSveqZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where is your WCW Sting GIF? https://t.co/T4T1GpOcOp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Please. There is extremism on both sides. https://t.co/8VzcQEoHH8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@usmlr oooh thanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@usmlr How can we watch this in Ireland?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ImKateMc Very generous. Scarlets will have no fear of Aviva.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give @threeredkings your money. https://t.co/Qg5MdZbNTR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theblitzdefence American teams need a separate name in fairness. Chicago has a hockey team, a basketball team, a football team and two baseball teams.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rugbystig @LeinsterLeo How very dare you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keeeeeeeeeeeet https://t.co/KNxkc2AEAn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poor @LeinsterLeo. He's willing to get injured for his team! https://t.co/YOs13eExzH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RobbyRichmond Sarseholes 1.01]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Recognise someone? @WrestlingSoup :D https://t.co/S2XZoM2z3k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Extend their remit to the Premiership. :) https://t.co/gp4arIkTFQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorthomas89 Next? IRFU and Ulster Rugby are one in the same.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SandraMHayes @SkySports Hugh Bladen is a long time commentator. Wonderful accent!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Donal_OKeeffe @ELangfordMusic Then again, on reflection, I am giving the internet too much credit here. There are mad people out there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Donal_OKeeffe @ELangfordMusic There are "companies" that do this now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Donal_OKeeffe @ELangfordMusic Fake these days could mean paid for to tweet shite.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ELangfordMusic @Donal_OKeeffe Ah I didn't realise it worked like that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ELangfordMusic @Donal_OKeeffe Odd. I can see the tweet on her account but it's not appearing on your quote @ELangfordMusic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ELangfordMusic @Donal_OKeeffe *Too. Dear lawd.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ELangfordMusic @Donal_OKeeffe I'm not convinced that's a real account. Two hashtaggy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pity the tweet is gone. I'm sure it was gold. https://t.co/WZYUpKaJCR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WrestlingSoup @JoeNumbas I DUNNO WHA YE'RE TALKIN BOUT LADS!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeNumbas @WrestlingSoup Why no push for Becky?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoeNumbas @WrestlingSoup Any crazy ref bumps or botches in your referee days?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MaxBlomfelt: @FortniteGame Just can’t take this anymore.. https://t.co/9GiywmSXjK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorthomas89 @CoraSherlock She's not wrong. Identity politics won't convince anyone. Those people are the ones who vote in highest numbers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cianaf People's Republic?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cianaf Haha if it's in Dub I might join ya.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cianaf Any podcast plans?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cianaf :(]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cianaf Does Jacob Stockdale play WR? (Bears fan)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CorkSeashell How's it all going Michelle?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mikedragon32 @ClaireByrneLive PS4?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cianaf Where dis?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[W*rd has been writing moronic guff for years. https://t.co/OViVhJ2ODY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[W*rd is an absolute waste of time. https://t.co/H9HUdTkkRm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NotoriousJOS That...was interesting....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NotoriousJOS Turn it up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*giggles* https://t.co/KkvDoAwb7p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mikedragon32 @ImKateMc Thanks bro!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CorkSeashell Apparently Cronin injury is bad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Credit to all @Munsterrugby supporters out in SA.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ImKateMc I got a hug. :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Jnavidi: Let’s go to South Africa they said it would be fun, they said]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorthomas89 Facepuke has some content.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorthomas89 @ionainstitute Just going on social media campaigning. I could be wrong.

I have a feeling it won't be repealed. Just a gut feeling.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorthomas89 @ionainstitute Pro Life I mean is better funded.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorthomas89 I wouldn't use the US as a barometer for a lot of things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorthomas89 PLC is far more organised and funded by the looks of things.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorthomas89 In principle it's impossible to ban tourists from campaigning. Where do you draw a line?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorthomas89 Do you extend this to pro-choicers? Foreigners on both sides will come to campaign.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorthomas89 Detain people you don't like? Take it easy there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@robsmithrugby @SkySportsRugby You can't have a top 8 playoff from a 12 team comp. It would ruin interest in the regular season.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ormondlad @PRO14Official How should I know? :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ormondlad @PRO14Official Broadcaster's behest no doubt. Same reason why Six Nations doesn't kick off simultaneously.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MaloneyCiara Nope.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or Saturday rather!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LeinsterLeo Looking forward to another hug tomorrow. Everyone needs hugs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't peddle non-independent as independent. @angobansaor is watching.... https://t.co/1mgvThPGU8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lostboy: im crying im so happy for them https://t.co/WNxmnQxswY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@OpinionatedNbdz @Cianaf It's an Irish spoof website like the onion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Munster Vs Saints DG was absolutely incredible. https://t.co/VVhqtbBHWR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mourad's twitter is an interesting place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cryptic. https://t.co/JVMcGBTyth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorthomas89 What do you want them to do? They are conducting an internal review. They have to abide by employment law. Let's react when the decision is made.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorthomas89 @JOEdotie Like it or not, this visit will generate far more than 1.2m I wager. So it's smart.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CorkSeashell Doing both games?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ironically had ringrncing come in years ago Exeter wouldn't be there. https://t.co/hAm7uu0fRh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@adammoursy @buck_mitchell I hope Benetton don't get raided a la Leicester signing 4 of them a few years ago.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CorkSeashell Wow! Going global again! Enjoy Michelle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@threeredkings @SarahMc1986 I feel bad for them. To be that obsessed. Energy that could be spent more productively.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AdamCirc: I go upstairs for 2 mins https://t.co/W5sykF0APk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This. https://t.co/c7IVbzpkia]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ugh I don't envy the Gardai in that situation. https://t.co/Q623jxnvwJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SophieJarvis94: The BBC are introducing a 50:50 gender quota on the experts they have on their shows. How demeaning. I would never want…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@racheleustace When will you or your friend will be making a complaint to the IRFU? If this is true then action should be taken against the club. Right?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Second Captains are proof you don't need fat cats behind you to produce quality content. If it's good enough, listeners will fund it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@conorthomas89 Use some CS and ignore it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@briananglim2 No it's actually a smart reason. You will convince in the other direction if you lose your cool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LargeRugby I was there too. Happened to us.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LargeRugby This is inevitable at a Leinster match with 50k. Blow-ins turn up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnLeinsterFan Or maybe the curse is strictly an RDS curse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AnnLeinsterFan Backed Ringrose to score a try. Just saying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can the spare media tickets be given away? Seems a waste. @leinsterrugby https://t.co/BPGztsa86g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NiamhoNiamh I wouldn't bother. A small portion of Welsh will use any stick.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@threeredkings https://t.co/KHR7RxLlJ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The minority in rugby with an axe to grind against particular teams, referees or players who seek out numerous  tweets to retweet gets me every time.

Forget the validity or otherwise of your view. Surely your time/rage could be better spent elsewhere.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Argh I cannot unsee this. https://t.co/WF4scKwE4m]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>