<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Developer: Excellence Leaves a Lasting Impression: Bring Your Vision to shape a better world. At Arup, our innovative spirit compels us to express our ingenuity in unique ways — developing many of the world’s most innovative and sustainable… https://t.co/6Aos4UHDQv https://t.co/xLhgev65Vd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python/C++ Developer: Python/C++ Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position JOB DESCRIPTION: Responsibilities: Design and implement automation solution for BIOS validation test cases (in gherkin and python) Debug the test failures in automation and… https://t.co/AxKEY6auWw https://t.co/ScAUz3anWd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(Senior) Software Engineer: IoT Defense is looking for a strong, motivated developer looking to make an impact on our 2018 strategies. We are a start-up business looking to build out our development and engineering team to support our products. With the… https://t.co/reVodqLIVP https://t.co/eDTW3pwb3m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Engineer Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: Strong Python (&gt; 2.7 Version) Programming experience is a must. Should have Application Development experience using Python Strong… https://t.co/SYvI88Zpyk https://t.co/1Q3SzXFYnH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer/Lead – Container Networking Team: . Please contact ******************** if you need further instruction on how to do that. Developer/Lead – Container Networking Team Engineering | Santa Clara, CA | Full Time Job Description About Avi Networks… https://t.co/CmMw6Vm3yd https://t.co/7urPt99tQz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist: Data Scientist Ref No.: 18-11903 Location: Bentonville, Arkansas Hi, Hope you are doing great!! Enterprise Solution Inc. is currently looking to fill urgent full-time permanent job positions as Data Scientist with the client based in… https://t.co/CLzz8IBKmX https://t.co/h0kOr3BMzU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer 3 / MATLAB Developer (Cambridge, MA): At Northrop Grumman, our employees have incredible opportunities to work on revolutionary systems in air and space that impact people’s lives around the world today, and for generations to come. Our… https://t.co/z4My912jqw https://t.co/54SbG0CNpS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer (Python): Do you enjoy writing code that automates processes and focuses more on our infrastructure than the front-end? Our tech team operates in a fast-paced, collaborative, and iterative programming environment using c#, python… https://t.co/M2LHQSceD1 https://t.co/EyYIWlToKJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Lead: Sprinklr is 1,500 employees strong, valued at $1.8 billion, and positioned at the forefront of the customer experience management industry. At a time when consumers are connected and empowered like never before, Sprinklr is helping the… https://t.co/saNX9q4Coc https://t.co/iZdOFKX3iP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Operations Engineer: We’re looking for a system operations engineer to join our Woburn office, playing a pivotal role in our growing global Operations team here at SilverRail. This team provides site reliability services across all technical… https://t.co/rm3wJZw9fz https://t.co/tDeHc1gOPf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: What We Do: The CERT Program is part of the Software Engineering Institute (SEI), a federally funded research and development center at Carnegie Mellon University (CMU) in Pittsburgh, Pennsylvania. CERT engages in state of the art R&amp;D… https://t.co/j6vx2SFj43 https://t.co/46zKxlATIg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK investigators search London office of firm at center of Facebook data storm: LONDON (Reuters) - Investigators from Britain's data watchdog searched the London offices of Cambridge Analytica, the data analytics firm at the center of a storm over… https://t.co/UOaSAOcgqB https://t.co/oLF4MD2CyZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python Familiar… https://t.co/2tt80qItqh https://t.co/FXKWJVARvm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SR. Business Intelligence Analyst/Programmer: SR. Business Intelligence Analyst/Programmer JOB #17/90 (Classified as ANALYST/PROGRAMMER-CAREER) Full time temporary position available on or after April 2, 2018 and ending on or before April 1, 2019 in the… https://t.co/7XguIFBweN https://t.co/xMnWCyw4rw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Research Engineer – High Assurance Software Protection: Why join Irdeto? We are on a mission! A mission to secure the world’s digital platforms. Why? Because a secure platform allows our clients to produce and deliver great content. In return, you can… https://t.co/6IhQlSpaYY https://t.co/XjEdiXcZJW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Infrastructure Engineer – SLC: Anonyome Labs was created to give people control and freedom over their personal and private information. We believe that people should be able to determine how, what, and with whom they share their personal details. We… https://t.co/Dgzt9fAsmL https://t.co/A1mYFnEiyp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Infrastructure Engineer – SLC: Anonyome Labs was created to give people control and freedom over their personal and private information. We believe that people should be able to determine how, what, and with whom they share their personal details. We… https://t.co/gFgnr6g2jC https://t.co/3u0HVNZlsk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer, AI: At Informatica, We DATA. We Do Good, Act As One Team, Think Customer First, and Aspire For The Future. Informatica enables companies to unleash the power of data to become more agile, realize new growth opportunities, lead… https://t.co/eMbjrCi4AC https://t.co/9zprDkdy26]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Web Engineer: Home About Employment Lead Web Engineer Lead Web Engineer Lead Web Engineer InsureMyTrip is looking for software engineers to join our team to help build our next gen web technology. We’re looking for natural leaders who can understand… https://t.co/oPoZDTGzvG https://t.co/Y3qasSqvGn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Programming Skills – Python (mandatory), Shell Scripting ,OOPS Concepts (Mandatory). Development of Test Script and Execution Hands-on… https://t.co/t2qjLKXrVi https://t.co/ji6nQEDXZ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python developer: Python Developer Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: Strong Python (&gt; 2.7 Version) Programming experience is a must. Should have Application Development experience using Python Good experience in HTML, XML, JSON. Strong… https://t.co/pqTgmdMxVJ https://t.co/WMqsgCivVw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[python Automation developer: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python Familiar with any one… https://t.co/rpBKp4M7lq https://t.co/ZLnlImJ8Fj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Cloud Systems Engineer: Our Team: The CloudTrust team powers Informaticas transformation and ensures that all our cloud platform and products are available, performant and safe. We implement industry-leading technologies and practices to bake in… https://t.co/hsJJeTvmiX https://t.co/16lXA0w59W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CX – Software Engineer – Full Stack: Company Description Dropbox is a leading global collaboration platform that’s transforming the way people work together, from the smallest business to the largest enterprise. With more than 500 million registered… https://t.co/TU84acUvIC https://t.co/DoqQLOAD7C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Cloud Security Engineer: Our Team The CloudTrust team powers Informaticas transformation and ensures that all our cloud platform and products are available, performant and safe. We implement industry-leading technologies and practices to bake in… https://t.co/Pnrvf2mONd https://t.co/ciwa1HYl8R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python – C++ Developer – Hillsboro OR: Python/ C++ Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using Python/C ++ Familiar with any one Scripting language Python/Perl Strong debugging… https://t.co/tJBg9twEIN https://t.co/vi0tAzcrB4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Management Specialist 15385: Camber Corporation is seeking a Database Programming and Data AnalysisSpecialistto join our diverse, team-oriented company that is customer focused – employee driven. The successful candidate will join our team of… https://t.co/uvNzXfTDi2 https://t.co/3EGUe93G5n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Full Stack Application Engineer: Primary Responsibilities: Advance the state of the art in building services products with React.js, Node.js, Ruby on Rails and AngularJS, Java, PHP and mobile (Android/iOS) frameworks. Full stack development for… https://t.co/VfY2vhn5cR https://t.co/7lFz7cwXjT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[San Jose – Data Engineer: San Jose – Data Engineer 020000 NPI Center Apply for this Job! Positions 1 Location San Jose LILEE HQ LILEE Systems has an immediate opening for a Data Engineer. This position involves in designing, implementation, enhancement,… https://t.co/mZ7zYWkwLM https://t.co/q814A7W6Ph]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Developer Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: Python programming experience is a must. Should have atleast 2+ Years of experience in Python Application Development Able to understand OOPS concepts… https://t.co/WQnU7Np9Zh https://t.co/WA8ueOcAhI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Developer: Why join Irdeto? Every industry has to come to grips with the ramifications of being in an increasingly connected world. From cars, to heavy vehicles, to fleets, to industrial equipment, today’s vehicles increasingly run on… https://t.co/jL1MBXbOEw https://t.co/TrQBLPxvDU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Programming Skills – Python (mandatory), Shell Scripting ,OOPS Concepts (Mandatory). Development of Test Script and Execution Hands-on… https://t.co/O0rLW7MNy2 https://t.co/prGPDgyLCq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python/C++ Developer: Python/C++ Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position JOB DESCRIPTION: Responsibilities: Design and implement automation solution for BIOS validation test cases (in gherkin and python) Debug the test failures in automation and… https://t.co/OvJX5auaJ3 https://t.co/z12tSvNMLu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Qualcomm re-elects board of directors with tepid support: SAN DIEGO (Reuters) - Qualcomm Inc re-elected its board of directors on Friday with weak support from shareholders, who grilled the U.S. chipmaker over its strategy following its successful… https://t.co/hmA2gpwbme https://t.co/pxfyGehkw2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Electronic Trading Director: Belvedere Trading is looking for a team-player to help advance our electronic trading systems and usage. This individual will work intimately with each trading desk to better understand electronic trading issues, and will be… https://t.co/yD6JhtW7hs https://t.co/TOAk6nRxUa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior Data Engineer: Junior Data Engineer Stonecrop Technologies, a telecom innovator focusing on improving the speed and motions of developing and improving communication networks seeks a savvy Data Engineering Manager to lead our Supply Chain Data &amp;… https://t.co/m0fBhcy8W4 https://t.co/mtaqhdYdBI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Python Application Developer 4 – Top Secret Clearance Required:   Job Description – Sr. Python Application Developer 4 – Top Secret Clearance Required (18002106) Sr. Python Application Developer 4 – Top Secret Clearance Required Requisition ID :… https://t.co/Na2cUvArU2 https://t.co/Me2w8Unj0W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Developer: We have an exciting opportunity for a mid-level full stack developer who is motivated to work in a highly agile environment and including DevOps. The full stack developer will be part of a talented software team that is building out… https://t.co/P1vEpzuopk https://t.co/EkITBsudvN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remote Full-Stack Developer (Python): Company Introduction OneinaMil is a talent matchmaking firm, we specialize in culture driven recruiting. Our mission is to change the way traditional recruiting is done. We put human connection and culture back into… https://t.co/BSXcNh0xAB https://t.co/JJmQdlKJpm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist: Would you like to perform rewarding, mission-focused work while contributing to the success of an established, growing company? Pragmatics, Inc. is seeking a Data Scientist to join our growing intelligence community team and provide… https://t.co/vl4PfXPaWt https://t.co/I8baCQgVov]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer in Test: Software Engineer in Test The Software Engineer in Test is responsible for designing, developing, and analyzing automated test suites and tools for Accruents asset management software. Responsibilities include mentoring entry… https://t.co/HzPxnGKtTm https://t.co/D9kjgS36zn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Solutions Engineer: IMPORTANT: If this describes you, please apply by pasting this URL into your browser and following the directions to complete a short survey and upload your resume https://t.co/D6ugj6Ff39 The Solution Engineer is located within… https://t.co/ULIafvQzOT https://t.co/VATxsFghPu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Data Scientist (Python, R, SaaS): Redwood City, CA Full-time $140k – $160k Posted Today If you are a Senior Data Scientist with experience, please read on! What You Will Be Doing Due to massive growth and demand for our services, we are currently… https://t.co/YaXT4GlYdc https://t.co/Fd44yaACjA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Django / Python DevOps: If working with a sophisticated cloud environment spanning multiple service providers and using a range of technologies such as Python, Django, Docker and many others is what youre aiming for, then wed be happy to welcome you to… https://t.co/YUhqJFjPCC https://t.co/pFdGCzoYGa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer: Automation Engineer (C++/Python) Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Responsibilities: Implement automation solution for BIOS validation test cases through Python programming Debug the test failures in automation… https://t.co/qmHu8k2pzG https://t.co/mnqmlNo9TK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Linux Engineer: Job Description North American Bancard is looking for a Senior Linux / DevOps engineer to join the team in Troy, Michigan. If you’re looking for an environment that won’t silo you or get you ‘stuck’ in a certain area, come join the… https://t.co/7e4ilpIaIB https://t.co/gM7w4GZpqW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blipp Developer: Blippar is hiring a front-end software engineer for its Blipp development team, to help us build a wide range of engaging augmented reality experiences for leading brands, agencies and publishers. We are looking for enthusiastic, engaged… https://t.co/ye7jlEx10u https://t.co/b4YlWoPN8m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Full Stack Developer: About (MHA) of New York City. The organization is at the cutting edge of harnessing new technologies to expand methods in which consumers can receive clinically sound behavioral health services. MHA operates 14… https://t.co/1GtyQ31wiQ https://t.co/H8mozF39Or]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Backend Web (Python): Trimble is an exciting, entrepreneurial company, with a history of exceptional growth coupled with a disciplined and strategic focus on being the best. While GPS is at our core, we have grown beyond this… https://t.co/lrbo2y86d8 https://t.co/78nMJdH3gg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GIS Developer: Job Description Radiance Technologies is an employee-owned company with benefits that are unmatched by most companies in the Dayton OH area. Employee ownership, generous 401K, full health/dental/life/vision insurance benefits, paid time… https://t.co/LyaCPRvxe4 https://t.co/jVJmB5eRIP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python – C++ Developer – Hillsboro OR: Python/ C++ Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using Python/C ++ Familiar with any one Scripting language Python/Perl Strong debugging… https://t.co/WlZd1snJu2 https://t.co/93eKW887Cn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Intelligence Engineer: A2Z Development Center, Inc. and https://t.co/LMWNyczHXz Services, Inc. seeks candidates for the following position (multiple positions available for each title): Business Intelligence Engineer, Job Code AZ0136: support… https://t.co/GWjJNUC4fi https://t.co/DBca9dbshk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer: Automation Engineer (C++/Python) Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Responsibilities: Implement automation solution for BIOS validation test cases through Python programming Debug the test failures in automation… https://t.co/HcZtULvXWu https://t.co/3SVbFvucVe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Architect- Containers and Private Cloud: Description: THE COMPANY Are you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by… https://t.co/axAb7k6XXh https://t.co/6UVzgeze1n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Programming Skills – Python (mandatory), Shell Scripting ,OOPS Concepts (Mandatory). Development of Test Script and Execution Hands-on experience… https://t.co/1CahetnAmQ https://t.co/A9uCTehj9P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Test Automation Engineer: Covestic is looking for a Sr. Test Automation Engineer who has experience building automated test suites in Python. This position is within a product organization focused on releasing new versions of an enterprise scale… https://t.co/LpK1seURYH https://t.co/jnmG0RvGdP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Lead Software Developer: CenturyLink (NYSE: CTL) is a global communications and IT services company focused on connecting its customers to the power of the digital world. CenturyLink offers network and data systems management, big data analytics,… https://t.co/SroEwRjyRS https://t.co/dXuCaHHY8k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rolls-Royce says Trent 7000 engines not affected by turbine blade issues: LONDON (Reuters) - Britain's Rolls-Royce said its Trent 7000 engines which power the Airbus A330neo jet are not affected by the issues with the Trent 1000 engine, some of which… https://t.co/vcK9VqhF46 https://t.co/2i4NsykhFu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (C++/Python) Job: Software Engineer (C++/Python) (Job Number:434869) Description: SAIC has an exciting opportunity in the growing field of robotics. In this position you will be using and modifying a web based multi robot control unit… https://t.co/V4QvBetUjW https://t.co/syh2W0KSmJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Application Developer (Mid-Level to Senior): FullStack Labs is a fast growing software consultancy with offices in Sacramento, CA, Washington, D.C., and Barranquilla CO. We build web, desktop, and mobile applications for businesses, from small… https://t.co/5yzs0cAAHl https://t.co/mKEZiXFkgp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python Familiar… https://t.co/Nvg0cxWy05 https://t.co/RN7yi2HKlh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer Docker, Python (Cleared Position!): You should have experience with Java 8, python, and Docker to develop, maintain, and enhance complex and diverse software systems (e.g., processing-intensive analytics, novel algorithm development,… https://t.co/URwA7HCoYz https://t.co/BGkhVPYJ2d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Software Engineer Python: Web Software Engineer $75-140K +bonus Lenexa, KS Prestigious Financial Firm is seeking a Web Software Engineer with strong Python skills or a desire to learn Python. We build websites that handle millions of requests per… https://t.co/55CjTzGF4R https://t.co/3hhyPV4yev]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Backend Developer: The Senior Backend Developer’s primary responsibilities are to code robust solutions and assist in managing a flexible pool of vendor and freelance developer talent to expand BlueprintNYC’s core products.He or she will uphold… https://t.co/kZD2RMxBx9 https://t.co/OztehT8OUA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer, Platform API: Welcome to Planet. We believe in using space to help life on Earth. Planets mission is to image the whole world every day and make global change visible, accessible and actionable. We build compact satellites and… https://t.co/Q4DRosWBgc https://t.co/cRCFSoIeV5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Python Developer: Financial Python Developer McLean, VA $100-120K Prestigious Organization is looking for a developer who has quantitative finance experience and is strong in Python development. Design, develop and support systems within the… https://t.co/cz7f7lethy https://t.co/l6YrLriX1t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer/Support: Description: THE COMPANY Are you interested in helping solve today’s most critical housing challenges? In simplest terms, Fannie Mae serves the people who house America. We work at the heart of housing by providing… https://t.co/1ipLCm1EJk https://t.co/ZYBS6KuDE0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Job Title: Python developer Duration: Minimum 3 Months Contract with POSSIBILITY of extension) Job Description We are seeking a Python developer responsible for building and maintaining Django and AWS lambda based systems. Your primary… https://t.co/3Rm5QMenl5 https://t.co/6lBmTyNNUs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Linux Dev Ops Engineer: CenturyLink (NYSE: CTL) is a global communications and IT services company focused on connecting its customers to the power of the digital world. CenturyLink offers network and data systems management, big data analytics, managed… https://t.co/O951etsJ6p https://t.co/EAwD7pCMQ8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Engineer Client: CMMi Level 5 Company Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Programming Skills – Python (mandatory), Shell Scripting ,OOPS Concepts (Mandatory). Development of Test… https://t.co/AVCt0w38bQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python/C Developer: Req ID 91829BR Business Title Python/C Developer Group MCIS Location USA VIRGINIA Herndon Clearance Level Needed Secret Category Cyber Job Duties and Responsibilities The Python/C Developer will be a key member of our mission… https://t.co/afTRd88qeB https://t.co/HL2GOPZqTV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Data Scientist: Do you want to make a difference? Illuminas mission is to improve human health by unlocking the power of the genome. If that inspires you, lets talk. Weve built a culture fueled by innovation, collaboration and openness, and… https://t.co/yfCSwekVJU https://t.co/sfarhhM0sX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embedded Developer Level 1: Careers Center | Embedded Developer Level 1 (IWK) Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job.… https://t.co/0gpfQLhLJe https://t.co/cjo110nc0C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Developer: Senior Developer Job Close By continuing to use and navigate this website, you are agreeing to the use of cookies. Accept – SAP employees – Join our talent community Search by Keyword Search by Location – SAP employees – Join our talent… https://t.co/LU5aIJShOo https://t.co/b1ItUJrWJM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Software Engineer – C/Python, Herndon VA: Req ID : 423985BR Job Code/Title : E2553:Cyber Intel Analyst Sr Job Description : Do you have a passion for low-level code development? Do you pride yourself on solving problems that others think are… https://t.co/IpwnTqI9Pp https://t.co/jxyz8b4uEZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GIS Software Engineer: ## This Position is available either in our San Francisco, CA Office or Bellevue, WA Office. Welcome to Planet. We believe in using space to help life on Earth. Planet’s mission is to image the whole world every day and make global… https://t.co/xjeeEYzw8L https://t.co/e5xUSHreI1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (C++/ Python): Software Engineer Hillsboro OR Job Responsibilities: Closely work with client POC to understand the requirements and priorities Contribute to the development of test automation framework Work with customers to determine… https://t.co/MbwHbzGRkq https://t.co/WjDhnMnw5b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Python Software Engineer: Title: Senior Python Software Engineer   Location: Milpitas, CA   The Company:   FireEye is the intelligence-led security company. Working as a seamless, scalable extension of customer security operations, FireEye offers… https://t.co/1Rq91N5fHE https://t.co/3UlYQ5HslL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Engineer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C# (or) Python Familiar with any one Scripting language Python/Perl Strong… https://t.co/wfyfLoNgY3 https://t.co/2B2Mf2FHnj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Engineer in Test (Python): We are looking for a motivated Software Development Engineer in Test (SDET) with extensive experience in hands-on development. As an engineer at Logikos, you will will have key role in building and… https://t.co/XqpSqwfZfT https://t.co/f64jRPc3pF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Django / Python DevOps: If working with a sophisticated cloud environment spanning multiple service providers and using a range of technologies such as Python, Django, Docker and many others is what youre aiming for, then wed be happy to welcome you to… https://t.co/KfOGnzs5O6 https://t.co/u12vzQY3LC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stock market principles needed in crypto world: SEC official: NEW YORK (Reuters) - The cryptocurrency trading marketplace could be improved by applying some of the principles from the stock market such as best execution and surveillance, a senior U.S.… https://t.co/3eu0k3nkeB https://t.co/dSVnG6hB6G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer-Python: Phantom is the only purpose-built Security Automation &amp; Orchestration platform, and the first to provide an open community for sharing Playbooks and Apps. It makes security smarter, faster, and stronger. We are an early-stage… https://t.co/dc09NaZQX7 https://t.co/aptuBQBZqN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Tools: Seeking a Senior Software Engineer to work for a groundbreaking open source technology helping companies with their Cloud-Native Environments.We are looking for innovators that want to join a startup team on a journey to… https://t.co/izHDYVU7Qo https://t.co/pw60jSWlH8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer: Python Automation Engineer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Experience in developing using Python / C# / C++. Candidate should have good experience or knowledge in scripting languages such as Python, Linux… https://t.co/TWIJKep441 https://t.co/2MWI6TPxQE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer: Python Developer Ref No.: 18-10920 Location: Des Moine, Iowa Position: Python Developer Location: Des Moine IA Duration: Long Term Contract Job Description: Expert in Python2.x and Python 3.x… https://t.co/JaqQesGQqR #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/MEtuZ6fICt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Application Developer – Newport News, VA: Web Application Developer Newport News, Virginia Full Time Position The developer will work on several different Automotive diagnostic and configuration tools, as well as a… https://t.co/y3dL815YC3 #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/eoLS7u4E0F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: You should possess at least a Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science, Computer Engineering or related field. A Master’s degree is preferred.… https://t.co/E0fCP3xGrt https://t.co/j3sEEZmUH9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer: Python /Linux Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++. Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python. Familiar with any… https://t.co/DXvUHmwqfZ https://t.co/CkQK4rvEor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Financial Python Backend Developer/Engineer Professional: Looking for a Financial Developer/Engineer Professional that has Python Backend Developement Salary: $100-120k Location: McLean, VA 1-2 years plus hard core Back… https://t.co/8qSKU6uoCE #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/nNKaakBQUo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python/C Developer: Req ID 91829BR Business Title Python/C Developer Group MCIS Location USA VIRGINIA Herndon Clearance Level Needed Secret Category Cyber Job Duties and Responsibilities The Python/C Developer will be a… https://t.co/0RlaBXcnpG #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/QQ9a5B5pPt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Engineer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Engineer Client: CMMi Level 5 Company Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Programming Skills – Python (mandatory), Shell Scripting ,OOPS… https://t.co/gwrO0RGVl1 #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/2bgUcqL0xT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Developer Full Time Position Hillsboro, OR Job Description: Strong Python programming experience is a must. Should have Application Development experience using Python Able to develop Test Automation Frameworks… https://t.co/hoGhP8U4NB https://t.co/XVeSF91ZNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer – Node API Development: Since 1938, new parents in Finland have been sent home from the hospital with one unique, yet simple gift: A cardboard box. Filled with newborn essentials, the boxes are… https://t.co/x1X1qpBtFu #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/Xxo8BdikwH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – PHP/Javascript: Whats Curvo? Glad you asked! Curvo is clinical spend management for the modern hospital supply chain. We engineer cost out of provider organizations. So, what? Theres no better time… https://t.co/HQbbc9UbPy #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob https://t.co/tpFiLofWsK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Programming Skills – Python (mandatory), Shell Scripting ,OOPS Concepts (Mandatory). Development of Test… https://t.co/7fuTWimVyg #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation… https://t.co/4FNB7OlmHl #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Golang microservices developer – REMOTE ROLE: Must have 5+ years of software development experience. 2+ years of programming experience with Golang. Prior experience with other languages like Python, Java. Design,… https://t.co/s5BNBvyY0o #python #jobs #IT #techjob #ITJob]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer – Hillsboro, OR: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: You should possess at least a Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science, Computer Engineering or related field. A Master’s degree is… https://t.co/iOCkvIS49K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer: Automation Test Developer : Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: must have at least 2 years of experience developing C++ test framework and test cases OR C++ application development experience Good to have 3… https://t.co/Hgfb8s2UKS]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>