<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst: BUSINESS KLA-Tencor Corporation currently has openings in our Milpitas, CA location for: Business Analyst (Job ID# 117976): Support the Global Spares Planning team with data analysis and modeling activities for KLA-Tencor’s service… https://t.co/sW5vJAckN7 https://t.co/QMj4SrFR4k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test Technician: Test Technician F/T: Test mobile device and Analyze results. Resume: JND INC @ 5901 College Blvd. STE 300 Overland Park KS 66211 recblid 4iauff3tkhcwemkvybghedx16bxxcn https://t.co/GNOFEqrBjr https://t.co/e4t1NNw5Xt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finance and IT Manager: Finance and IT Manager The Brattleboro Food Co-op has an immediate need for a Finance and Information Technology Manager. Reporting to our General Manager, this position oversees all of our financial and IT management operations.… https://t.co/Q3wXVVy1hF https://t.co/wFBcx595OB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Processor: Description: MSW-ARS performs global market research, primarily through online surveys. By collecting information on consumers’ needs and preferences, market research enables informed decision making. Data Processors transform raw data… https://t.co/Aai5jQIn1C https://t.co/ykxkl1wc6U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Engineers #IRVEYO: Software Developers Western Digital Technologies, Inc. has opportunity in Irvine, CA for Principal Engineers. Experience in C, C++, Java &amp; programming languages required. Equal opportunity employer. recblid… https://t.co/CVaSqcAZY8 https://t.co/w29FhGPrt8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineering Manager, Analytical Product Engineerin #FSAP01: Software Engineering Manager, Analytical Product Engineering FactSet Research Systems, Inc., Norwalk, CT: Manage team of software engineers and/or projects w/in Analytical Product… https://t.co/t1CtpOqfeN https://t.co/uiISbHHPAl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bigger, Brighter, Simpler: A Tablet for the Mature User: We asked researchers to help us build a device that's optimized for folks whose sight and motor skills are beginning to fade. https://t.co/jvw8WA3AWx https://t.co/0Z8Vh3DQwG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Applications Development Technical Specialist: Applications Development Technical Specialist for Citigroup Technology, Inc. (Tampa, Florida). Lead the configurable architecture for company’s regulatory platform from conceptualization to implementation,… https://t.co/fIXsDjnfNo https://t.co/YPgdhyazXp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Research and Development Engineer: CCC Information Services Inc. seeks  Research and Development Engineers for Chicago, Illinois location to gather, interpret information, translate requirements into software applications. Master’s in Computer… https://t.co/VOQBnuAEOL https://t.co/zhDFemv0pg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Scm/Devops #MP6334: Senior Scm/DevOps Engineers (Calabasas, CA) Be part of team responsible for development &amp; support our continuous integration/ deployment infrastructure which consists of automated software version management, software build,… https://t.co/vnLOCKTBy2 https://t.co/k1LF1pgchh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Info Security Engineer 4: Job Description Let’s talk about building a rewarding career You’ve got the passion. You’ve got the skills. Now you just need the right opportunity. At Wells Fargo, you’ll have the chance to join a team of smart and talented… https://t.co/QvZX7k3Dnb https://t.co/EBWD1ElNmf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UI/UX Designer: We are looking for a hands-on visual designer with experience in UI/UX design to work closely with our creative team. Candidate must be able to follow directions, interpret objectives, and work as a team player while also being autonomous… https://t.co/pcwKEGa2Km https://t.co/dNxnZInSUE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer (C#): Software Engineer (C#) Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: Applicant should have a Bachelors degree in Computer Science, Computer Engineering and/or Electrical Engineering with at least six years of related… https://t.co/rUV6nsZEP5 https://t.co/zpxcWkNOIW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Client Technical Lead: At Panaseer, we exist to empower enterprises to conduct business in the digital world with confidence and control. We believe that automation and visibility are the first steps on the road to successful risk management and good… https://t.co/YOYnbckdm7 https://t.co/6qETp79dfs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dotnet Developer: Dotnet Developer Ref No.: 18-10074 Location: Florence, Kentucky Hi, Hope you are doing great!! Enterprise Solution Inc. is currently looking to fill urgent full-time permanent job positions as Dotnet Developer with the client based in… https://t.co/KPFgQChjgk https://t.co/qUumSXlxsW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Tech Lead – Partner Facing Applications: IT Tech Lead – Partner Facing Applications at Hewlett Packard Enterprise CompanyTo top Skip Navigation Hewlett Packard Enterprise Careers – Overview – Search and apply – Sales Graduate Program – Students &amp;… https://t.co/rfeBs0ZjIr https://t.co/JzOckvV1Qq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Windows Developer: .NET WINDOWS UI DEVELOPER LOCATION: DULUTH, GA 30096 C/CTH: $55/HR Our client is looking to add a .NET Windows UI Developer to their team in Duluth, GA. In this role you will be adding functionality to an existing… https://t.co/flXlhBr2Y5 https://t.co/an2k4vE4Da]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineering Manager, Analytical Product Engineerin #FSAP01: Software Engineering Manager, Analytical Product Engineering FactSet Research Systems, Inc., Norwalk, CT: Manage team of software engineers and/or projects w/in Analytical Product… https://t.co/ES801x3NPh https://t.co/YomDGrKAry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Delivery Senior Analyst: Deloitte Consulting LLP seeks Project Delivery Senior Analyst, Technology, Application Management Services in Richmond, VA and various unanticipated Deloitte office locations and client sites nationally to assist in… https://t.co/7KZQQHXDVi https://t.co/IAQxayLFIB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[App Roundup: Services for Savvy Seniors: We all get old, and at some point, everyone's going to need an app that embiggens that doggone tiny mouse type. https://t.co/rRlzzV21dN https://t.co/k3On6GuO7C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SYSTEMS ANALYST: IT Positions available at Irving, TX &amp; various unanticipated locations throughout the U.S.: SYSTEMS ANALYSTS: Analyze, design, develop &amp; test applications. Prepare test plans. Create &amp; automate test scripts. Perform risk analysis.… https://t.co/CXNsbzmFz3 https://t.co/dGA773zb7r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Project Manager: Technical Project Manager With Masters Degree or foreign equivalent in IT, Computer Science, or Computer Engineering, and 1 year experience in job offered. (or) Bachelor’s Degree or foreign equivalent in IT, Computer Science,… https://t.co/tFM6MZu2Ji https://t.co/sDGlUSLalz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Developer: The Herrick Corporation, a leading Structural Steel Fabricator, is seeking an Application Developer. Must be experienced with: .NET application development in C# in Visual Studio, TSQL backend coding, knowledge of UWP, WinForms,… https://t.co/2cb7tD54Bq https://t.co/2Fq6Cyh25F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finance and IT Manager: Finance and IT Manager The Brattleboro Food Co-op has an immediate need for a Finance and Information Technology Manager. Reporting to our General Manager, this position oversees all of our financial and IT management operations.… https://t.co/1vqpOf9Ke2 https://t.co/YXFj1sREa1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Materials Program Manager: A2Z Development Center, Inc. and https://t.co/3oDnQZgHNq Services, Inc. candidates for the following positions (multiple positions available for each title): Senior Materials Program Manager, Job Code AZ0140 to design,… https://t.co/UHExCIywT5 https://t.co/I3i9NMiibj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Energy Solutions Development Engineer II #ESDE-RVA: Engineering: Johnson Controls, Inc. is seeking Energy Solutions Development Engineer II for its Rockville, VA location to provide technical, process &amp;/or financial support during the design process;… https://t.co/3XuTFAgXon https://t.co/mQK0eRi2mc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Technology Project Supervisor: Gratiot County is seeking an Information Technology Project Supervisor for oversight and operation of our IT systems. This position will oversee, coordinate and assist the county’s full service IT contractor… https://t.co/EAVczP3gjJ https://t.co/zPiGYSg3jA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Intuit Inc. has openings for the following positions in Mountain View, California: Software Engineers (Job code: SW318): Apply software development practices to design, implement, and support individual software projects. Senior… https://t.co/e7sd1NryGM https://t.co/5z1HQd64rK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer:   TECHNOLOGY Help build the next generation of systems behind Facebook’s products. Facebook, Inc. currently has multiple openings in Fort Worth, TX (various levels/types): Data Center Technician (133532N) Assist with all Data Center… https://t.co/1D0c7Opq5U https://t.co/RT2xycHZTm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Patent Engineer: Patent Engineer, IBM Corporation, Research Triangle Park, NC: Analyze security software and other software commercial products to identify patents needed for each feature of the product. Develop evidence to prove identified patent being… https://t.co/WUtaqe9D3p https://t.co/zMWXqEjN2Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Application Developer: Sr Application Developer for US Bank National Association in Denver, CO to perform &amp;/or lead tech design &amp; develop of complex app system. At U.S. Bank, we’re passionate about helping customers and the communities where we live… https://t.co/5TAserN9pU https://t.co/u4CQUgSH18]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Engineer, System Software: TECHNOLOGY Mountain View, CA Sr. Engineer, System Software Responsible for designing infrastructure and interfaces, developing integration software, coding quick scripts and utilities as required, researching tools and… https://t.co/IZbli39aSz https://t.co/usFarrKPa1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best Smart Earbuds for Travel: AirPods, Pixel Buds, Erato Verse: Super portability and easy access to AI assistants make these wireless headphones must-haves on your next trip. https://t.co/a2kscEtXN4 https://t.co/hPsy0J5c00]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[S/W Dvlprs: S/W Dvlprs HGST, Inc. has opptys in Irvine, CA for Sr Engrs. Mail resume to Attn: HR, 951 SanDisk Dr, MS:HRGM, Milpitas, CA 95035, Ref #IRVSKO. Must be legally auth to work in the U.S. w/o spnsrshp. EOErecblid 0jsmfadii2bse5ztuo6ysb359tzndu https://t.co/iWNRdpNE8B https://t.co/L9dUPr4YU7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineers, Game Development #55: Software Engineers, Game Development (Ref job # 55) Research, design, engineer &amp; develop specialized software system &amp; apps for 3-D interactive graphic elements for use in tech media formats. Position at Valve… https://t.co/hG4o9xElyA https://t.co/Vk3PAE5Hhb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RN- Tucker: PURPOSE AND SCOPE: Functions as part of the hemodialysis health care team as a Staff Registered Nurse to ensure provision of quality patient care on a daily basis in accordance with FMS policies, procedures, and training.  Supports the FMCNA… https://t.co/6uAjx4H0Oy https://t.co/Euslg800Rv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior System Administrator: Description Are you looking for the next step in your career ? Check out TETRA CONCEPTS! TETRA CONCEPTS, a PSS Company, is actively seeking 2 Senior System Administrators t o join our growing team located in Annapolis… https://t.co/HjJBlD3fca https://t.co/npUVLTfnWU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Automation Developer: Python Automation Developer Hillsboro, OR Full Time Position Job Description: 2+ years of programming experience in Python or C++ Experience in developing Test Automation frameworks using C++/Python Familiar with any one… https://t.co/dWZlpECZOG https://t.co/v9snnIQzcZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: Senior Java Developer Ref No.: 18-08631 Location: Sunnyvale, California Title: Senior Java Developer Location: LIC, NY; Irving, TX; NJ; Sunnyvale, CA; Charlotte, NC: Mclean, VA; GA Duration: Full Time Job Description: 1. 6+ years… https://t.co/wk0w4qhw5B https://t.co/b1bnwMejAy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chief Engineer / JASSM / Orlando, FL: Req ID : 422453BR Job Code/Title : L1475:Research Engineering Mgr Job Description : At Lockheed Martin, you’ll have an opportunity to create a better world every day. For most individuals, our work challenges belong… https://t.co/W7ONUOpm4R https://t.co/PNxni1Vyan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jr. IT Change Manager: Fivesky is looking for a highly motivated and talented Jr. IT Change Manager to join a fast-paced, dynamic, and challenging environment. The ideal candidate must possess strong project management skills, have the capability to… https://t.co/etVcLovkcq https://t.co/SwyK5O57Me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analyst, Sr. Business Intelligence (Microstrategy): Job Description Position Summary The Senior Business Intelligence Analyst is responsible for providing high quality data driven solutions that address key business questions. The Senior BI Analyst works… https://t.co/34vEnqJq3r https://t.co/vSvu1vAgy0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology: TECHNOLOGY Data Domain LLC (a Dell Technologies company) is seeking a Software Sr. Engineer at our Santa Clara, CA facility to develop software solutions for external clients based on detailed specifications from technology/ systems… https://t.co/ofeaK3kfyV https://t.co/wP0WboBiwH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mechanical Design Draftsman: General: Mechanical Design Draftsman Eckel Manufacturing Company is looking for a Mechanical Design Draftsman. Desired skills include Inventor 3D Modeling, AutoCAD experience and knowledge of CNC and manual machining, welding… https://t.co/jIxJbSLDXk https://t.co/cFMY0IrscR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smart Suitcases: Raden A28, Rimowa Limbo Multiwheel Electronic Tag: Increase your total baggage awareness with some technologically enhanced luggage. https://t.co/VDKRRrL8jR https://t.co/QnOUyUPMyu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Analyst &amp; Substation Supervisor: Network Analyst $87,131 – $111,529 Annually + benefits Performs professional level work to ensure the stability and integrity of in-house voice, data, video, and wireless network services; plans, designs, and… https://t.co/A0IDfQ075b https://t.co/uFwNeuZsqJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Qa Engineer: ENGINEERING: Software QA Engineer, AT SLEEP NUMBER CORPORATION, 111 W Saint John St Suite 1200 San Jose, California 95113, 8+ yrs exp software tester;Tech fld BS rqd;Exp design verification, reviewing specs/ test planning;Exp… https://t.co/pZJIBiA5Mh https://t.co/snyVzxhYkO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate, Software Engineering: Associate, Software Engineering Columbus, OH. Provide high quality tech. solutions that address bus. needs by developing apps. within mature tech. environments. For reqs. &amp; to apply, visit https://t.co/hm4gfGs1ju &amp; apply… https://t.co/PR7zie5pZH https://t.co/QxPtpOy9Fz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TG DEVELOPER: TG Developer – Enovia / PowerSource for Kiewit Engineering Group (Lenexa, KS). Provide technical applications design, development &amp; support engineering in the implementation of the Enovia Enterprise PLM (Product Lifecycle Management) system… https://t.co/HhISqY3HtI https://t.co/hzSPGudnPk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator: Systems Administrator Below you will find the details for the position including any supplementary documentation and questions you should review before applying for the opening.  Posting Details: Position Information: Position… https://t.co/WPYDIKwuDU https://t.co/tsvRGM7lnV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Digital Marketing Sales Consultant: Digital Marketing Sales Consultant Are you looking for an exciting career that lets you work independently, yet have the benefit of an outstanding support team behind you? Have you had sales experience and found that… https://t.co/8VQUwqEeZZ https://t.co/zH4RDLynC0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Technology Specialist 5 (Application Developer) #02487: Description The Department of Social and Health Services (DSHS) Children’s Administration Technology Services (CATS) Division is currently accepting applications for Information… https://t.co/nAmU4gwtmh https://t.co/oFX8RnFRtP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Class B CDL Driver: Class B CDL Driver  Oconee Waste is a locally owned and operated company that has provided unmatched commercial waste and sanitation service to NE GA for over 15 years. A reputation for great service, not promises. We are in search of… https://t.co/pdamq6wtoS https://t.co/JeeQukfmJa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Analyst: Systems Analyst BriXcel Inc Richardson, TX BriXcel Inc, a Texas based Software &amp; Technology Consulting Company, has multiple openings for Systems Analyst. Oversee engagements with focus on ERP applications, Cloud solutions, System… https://t.co/DY05QzLe8I https://t.co/91av1GclLh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Manager of Development #JSWM: Senior Manager of Development (https://t.co/v3lJTGCUBk, Inc., Midvale, UT) Multiple openings available. Lead multiple teams working on significant &amp; critical projects, provide tech &amp; team leadership &amp; mentorship. Work… https://t.co/BtjAmjGCHg https://t.co/8J9I70U8s9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Operations Analyst – Eng Systems Modeling Simulation 3: Job Description The individual in this role will support the Global Strategy and Mission Solutions (GSMS) group in the development of advanced concepts and technologies, carrying out analysis tasks… https://t.co/bDZHniZwTS https://t.co/N9dZQUyKPV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Data Services Manager: ABOUT US:As a mutual company, we are independent by nature, so we think about insurance solutions a little differently. Through listening, problem solving, examining your challenges and collaborating on the right… https://t.co/yTt0c5x5a3 https://t.co/ytPudOX9Xm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best Unlimited Data Plans: T-Mobile, AT&amp;T, Sprint, Verizon: Which wireless carrier has the best unlimited data service (and price)? https://t.co/KnXNoCzoHq https://t.co/CFTyRFsfF0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Help Desk Support Analyst – Entry Level: Provide IT Help Desk support services to all Penn Virginia users including hardware, software, and certain application systems support. Install, configure, and deploy desktop/laptop hardware, software, printers,… https://t.co/87Uhxq4TSI https://t.co/vNeyqKaDUi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales Director – New York: This role will be based in our NYC office with travel required to our customers and our headquarters in Austin, TX. Responsibilities: Passion selling our social media platform into high quality accounts in the Enterprise space… https://t.co/rXKmQYgGL8 https://t.co/31vLarKrg3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Sr. Fullstack Software Engineer (JS) Our video intelligence platform gives visibility into every store, every location, every day, from anywhere. We provide the insight into the most important events so real-time changes can be… https://t.co/fiEJ5ot6cP https://t.co/ZicEFyn3En]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Information Assurance / Security Specialist (Level 3): Overview:The following is an immediate fillable role!!!! Apply now and join the best of the best!!! ASRC Federal has been awarded an opportunity identified as DHS Secure Enterprise Network Systems,… https://t.co/TBkWU8P5BB https://t.co/CBqYZCequv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Analyst: Position Summary Analyzes data and conducts research to assist with ERIE projects or initiatives. Develops and communicates change management plans in support of project management staff. Assists project managers with related project… https://t.co/egLHNKfi1k https://t.co/9J6qGPwbdG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – St. Louise, MO: Software Engineer St. Louise, MO Full Time Position Job Description: Looking for Strong technical expertise in designing and developing C# (must have) and C++ (desirable) Looking for strong experience on Database:… https://t.co/mSJOw8JjLR https://t.co/XXNuCznVJU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Project Manager: Are you a self motivated senior IT Project Manager or Scrum Master looking for a new and exciting opportunity? Our industry leading company is seeking a dynamic IT Project Manager to work closely with the CTO to manage the… https://t.co/sBj3DNU0nL https://t.co/hxbW4R8wnU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manager, IT Sourcing: Are you looking for an opportunity where you can showcase your excellence in procurement, strategic sourcing and category management? We are looking for an experienced IT Sourcing individual to manage the acquisition of IT products… https://t.co/ayKoDMxqF1 https://t.co/YK0EFPfQWm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer This is a Federal Opportunity !!!!The candidate should have lived in the country for over a period of 5 Years &amp; should not have left the country for over 90 days consecutively !!Back-End:Java/J2EEEJBJPAStruts… https://t.co/q0DqpCmorm https://t.co/twqsWoJ3dn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Lead: Sprinklr is 1,500 employees strong, valued at $1.8 billion, and positioned at the forefront of the customer experience management industry. At a time when consumers are connected and empowered like never before, Sprinklr is helping the… https://t.co/LEkAJ1BIrv https://t.co/OZLRBO77fi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce Solution Architect: Company Overview: Do you want to be part of a fast-paced environment, supporting the growth of cutting edge technology in cloud computing? Silverline employees are passionate about what they do. Were a diverse group of… https://t.co/rPVNCgwe1R https://t.co/ywnkQtzxLI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Symfony (PHP) Developer: We are seeking a highly‐talented Programmer / Developer who will be responsible for creating beautiful, engaging web experiences for high-end clients. We are looking for an innovative thinker who is fully committed to web… https://t.co/RSUW2NzAlI https://t.co/nFqKOENDBf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gadget Lab Podcast: More Questions Than Answers in Uber's Fatal Arizona Crash: This week, Alex Davies and Aarian Marshall join us to discuss the latest news in self-driving car safety. https://t.co/iZMDnUVowb https://t.co/tM7oK1DyRZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Engineer (3) – Ground Systems: Overview: The Systems Engineer will support a Boeing Ground Systems development program. Responsibilities: Defining and documenting specific interfaces, establishing clear requirements, determining appropriate… https://t.co/GFNQVz9whY https://t.co/l95oHKX00h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full-Stack Developer – Philadelphia Innovation Center: Are you interested in creating world class client experiences while working in a contemporary, truly-agile manner? As a Full Stack Developer on Vanguards Client Experience program, youll work on a… https://t.co/PksBERzwBs https://t.co/gYFQgJxSr6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Counter-Air Threat Modeling Lead – Eng Systems Modeling Simulation 5: Job Description The individual in this role will lead the Counter-Air Threat focus area for the Systems Analysis &amp; Simulation team within the Global Strategy and Mission Solutions… https://t.co/tVIfxe7VWf https://t.co/ZeUg24Wlod]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer, Marketing Technology: Job Posting Title:Sr. Software Engineer, Marketing TechnologyJob Description: Ever wonder what happens to the data collected on you that serves up sometimes relevant ads as you browse the web? Ever felt… https://t.co/NmNkalJTMn https://t.co/mVhRK1Z2Gr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Architect Level 2: REX is an internationally-acclaimed architecture and design firm based in New York City, whose name signifies a re-appraisal (RE) of architecture (X). Operating across many scales, REX consistently challenges and advances building… https://t.co/PLSfNCDPol https://t.co/vtLASlEx7S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Team Lead – Desktop Support: PEAK6 was brought to life by the idea that the development of integrative technology can improve how business is done. The passion for that idea powers our firm still. As a Team Lead for Desktop Support at PEAK6, you are free… https://t.co/j9MtjEixVa https://t.co/oeVDJk2ahU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer: DevOps Engineer DevOps Engineer Sandata Technologies, Inc. was founded in 1978 and is undergoing rapid recent growth as the leader in web-based information technologies serving home health care providers, social service agencies and… https://t.co/WOcHEUUdmi https://t.co/zRMJcEOmy0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Software Engineer: Our mission is to help people everywhere find a job and company they love. We are disrupting an industry by changing how people search for jobs and how companies recruit top talent. Responsibilities As a Senior Java… https://t.co/fYQNVyI8oZ https://t.co/DpnSizRLWt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer/Data Processor: Summary Complete all processes to ensure all scheduled drop dates are met and that established quality standards are adhered to for all jobs produced to ensure maximum client satisfaction by performing the following duties.… https://t.co/SrLd7kceQt https://t.co/V1bFjFI7j6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Tools DevOps Engineer: Who is SugarCRM SugarCRM enables businesses to create extraordinary customer relationships with the most empowering, adaptable and affordable customer relationship management (CRM) solution on the market. We are the… https://t.co/dWUEDSsTTd https://t.co/4XALp46qcp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior IT Cyber Vulnerability Analyst: Zurich Services LLC (a division of Zurich North America) is currently hiring an Senior IT Cyber Vulnerability Analyst. This person will report to the Vulnerability Management Lead, Americas and will sit in the… https://t.co/wGqTru76gs https://t.co/6zadNnWrPn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to Translation Tech, Talking to Strangers Will Be Even Easier: Instant translation will help us all enjoy a more intimate experience, no matter where we explore. https://t.co/0uBSGX2jYS https://t.co/kxP4gU95Hp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce Solution Architect: Company Overview: Do you want to be part of a fast-paced environment, supporting the growth of cutting edge technology in cloud computing? Silverline employees are passionate about what they do. Were a diverse group of… https://t.co/dQ9RiXpRAF https://t.co/Hzy3twQx3R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Cloud Systems Engineer: Our Team: The CloudTrust team powers Informaticas transformation and ensures that all our cloud platform and products are available, performant and safe. We implement industry-leading technologies and practices to bake in… https://t.co/KCK2RTyARG https://t.co/dL1aAbyh74]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C# .NET Developer (Entry Level): Looking to start your Tech career? Let us train you! Junior .NET Developer Program GEICO – proven online, mobile, and industry leader – seeks college graduates to join our growing team of over 2,000 IT experts in our… https://t.co/CXREsMfmTf https://t.co/rJrxKGULa3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Requisition Number 18-0421 Post Date 3/1/2018 Title Software Engineer City Lombard State IL Description Designs, modifies, develops, writes and implements software programming applications. Supports and/or installs software… https://t.co/niTI9Svt70 https://t.co/xg6RCqnWzZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Master Software Engineer: Capital One Services, LLC in Richmond, Virginia is looking for Master Software Engineer. Responsible for overall technical design, development, modification, &amp; implementation of computer applications using existing &amp; emerging… https://t.co/B9kPfF02s6 https://t.co/agZ6nSXWzv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer – Front End: About Us: Ripcord is the world’s first robotic paper digitization company. We’re going after the outmoded, but very large paper records market (think, medical records, company HR records, company financial records,… https://t.co/yYAkFvUjGG https://t.co/ScVa7zhwkQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer, Web: Government has become one of the final frontiers for technological disruption. The more people use technology as consumers, the more they expect technology to shape their experience as citizens. Brigade believes building a… https://t.co/A11dxqoIxG https://t.co/nxZVyXG8OS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Backend Developer: The Senior Backend Developer’s primary responsibilities are to code robust solutions and assist in managing a flexible pool of vendor and freelance developer talent to expand BlueprintNYC’s core products.He or she will uphold… https://t.co/ZBE4uiKsWX https://t.co/ih0QbPvoOs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Automation QA Tester https://t.co/HAF96PcqGU https://t.co/2xqmdz4mer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Engineer (3) – Ground Systems: Overview: The Systems Engineer will support a Boeing Ground Systems development program. Responsibilities: Defining and documenting specific interfaces, establishing clear requirements, determining appropriate… https://t.co/7G1Eh59V6v https://t.co/2mU1ineGW2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Red Tactics Development MS&amp;A Lead – Eng Sys Modeling Simulation 5: Job Description The individual in this role will lead the Adversary Tactics Development Modeling, Simulation, and &amp; Analysis focus area for the Systems Analysis &amp; Simulation team within… https://t.co/8VSJo4O16z https://t.co/3NYSURdJsF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hotels Data Specialist: The Company Hopper believes that planning travel should be easy and fun. We empower and inspire travelers by analyzing trillions of past and current trips and notifying travelers when to buy a flight ticket or rent a hotel room in… https://t.co/oAXpT3GGOR https://t.co/xTynNnHf6K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best Travel Gear: Mophie, Amazon Kindle, Allbirds, Lululemon, Hex: Fit everything for your trip into a bag that slides under the seat in front of you. https://t.co/Cf9uNxfzdx https://t.co/nRGaeuOHcz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Development Specialist: HCR ManorCare provides a range of services, including skilled nursing care, assisted living, post-acute medical and rehabilitation care, hospice care, home health care and rehabilitation therapy. The Business Development… https://t.co/Ch233C76wC https://t.co/YKsEMdYDdV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Cloud Systems Engineer: Our Team: The CloudTrust team powers Informaticas transformation and ensures that all our cloud platform and products are available, performant and safe. We implement industry-leading technologies and practices to bake in… https://t.co/dJlEfrHB3e https://t.co/CAwRnkfu8g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Development Analyst II: *Overview** If you want an exciting job with one of the largest off-price retailers in the nation, join the Burlington Stores, Inc. team as an Application Development Analyst! Are you a detail-oriented technology… https://t.co/GYKUb4FYvZ https://t.co/1PPsqEMj27]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Customer Care Help Desk Analyst: Primary Objective/Scope: Responsible for providing level two service, support and training via phone or web to customers experiencing equipment or network issues related to their office technology. SPECIFIC… https://t.co/cFeKzeEjYA https://t.co/YrjN8BBVr5]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>