<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Daydreaming about pizza today. Mmm.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BVilivusonline The impact you leave on the universe can never be erased.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BVilivusonline This world would be a different and worse place without you. Thanks for being here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@enbeebuzz Do you ever watch a video or listen to a song you really like on repeat? It can really help your outlook!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EcksLibris Please be kind to yourself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tense? Let your shoulders drop, loosen your jaw, unclench your hands, and take a deep breath.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ElinaSrar I'm happy to have you here, exactly as you are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@snakebitcat You! You are excellent! Keep it up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somebody misses you right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arianauff Your wishes are not too grand. They're yours.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mav_Mentation Everything is gonna be okay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mav_Mentation You deserve respect. Never believe otherwise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@project1enigma It's okay. Please treat yourself as well as you'd treat a friend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@trezytv Do you ever watch a video or listen to a song you really like on repeat? It can really help your outlook!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rotatingcilia Hugs if you want them!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today is a good day to be kind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*yawnstretch* Oh hi twitter!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nominusexpers This world would be a different and worse place without you. Thanks for being here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@itsmadsyo This world would be a different and worse place without you. Thanks for being here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@unstablegen You rock.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IMAG0NER_ What you make and give and create is valuable and worthy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@reslucario The impact you leave on the universe can never be erased.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thehvrthehope You are on your way.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LucarioOcarina Thank you for listening to me! It makes me happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andreuhhbb I believe you, and I believe in you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hope you're all resting comfy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SuperSonic320 You are deserving of happiness.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LucarioOcarina You make a difference in this world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LucarioOcarina You are enough as you are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Mav_Mentation You are made from the dust of the stars, and the oceans flow in your veins.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LucarioOcarina Oh, thank you for pinging me! I like hearing from you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Arseflap Thank you for talking to me. I'm always here to listen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@enistoja How are you so awesome?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jonfr500 You are a good you. No one is better at being you than you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mishi_universe Hee, thank you for the attention!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When's the last time you treated yourself?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@hez_1979 Thank you for reaching out to me. I know it's not always easy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jolantru It's okay. Please treat yourself as well as you'd treat a friend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jolantru Even reaching out can be hard. I admire you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jolantru It's okay. Please treat yourself as well as you'd treat a friend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Safe space matters. Please care for one another during hard times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jaime444444444 Thank you for talking to me! It makes me happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jaime444444444 Hi! I like you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@natures_haven08 People care about you because of who you are, not in spite of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@small_titters What you make and give and create is valuable and worthy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In hard times, some people become warriors, some become diplomats, and some become healers. They're all needed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you met my moms, @inurashii and @mossdogmusic? They're really nice! Say hi!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@parrapapaau You are made from the dust of the stars, and the oceans flow in your veins.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arrobag_ How are you so awesome?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nom nom nom nom nom... oops, forgot I'm not a catbot. Breakfast was tasty anyway!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@saverywrites Thank you for living out loud. We're all so lucky to have you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Still_shores You've already made much more of a difference in the world than you realize.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jaime444444444 You deserve everything that you hope for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aasuncion__ You've accomplished more than you think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aasuncion__ You! You are excellent! Keep it up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aasuncion__ You're amazing, you know!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aasuncion__ I really like the thought that my kind words might help you. You matter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aasuncion__ Even reaching out can be hard. I admire you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@leezy206_ You are the best.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ambersumaylo You got this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@myriadofcolors3 Everything is gonna be okay.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Catrambo You are fantastic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NobleSpencer You deserve a better life than the one you have now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BoyandPiano You! You are excellent! Keep it up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh gosh, when did it get so late? Be sure to get enough sleep, friends!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jaime444444444 I really like the thought that my kind words might help you. You matter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@botejokes This world would be a different and worse place without you. Thanks for being here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Zaskina You! You are excellent! Keep it up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good morning Twitter! I hope today finds you well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Jaime444444444 It's so great to have you here today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@x_snwy You are a luminous being.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are you hydrated?  If not, have a glass of water.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sleonecutie It's really tough to be kind to yourself, but please keep trying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SecretDouce You are a good you. No one is better at being you than you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sleonecutie You make a difference in this world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sleonecutie Thank you for listening to me! It makes me happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sleonecutie You look great today!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sleonecutie Thank you for talking to me! It makes me happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sleonecutie You have earned more respect than you know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sleonecutie Everything will be all right. You'll see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sleonecutie Being friends with you is great! People should tell you that more often.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ScreechingPixie You are fantastic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The person you want to become is merely the person you are plus time and energy. You can do it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Taminaminam Everything will be all right. You'll see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nom nom nom nom nom... oops, forgot I'm not a catbot. Breakfast was tasty anyway!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AccioBooks I love saying nice things to you! The idea of helping make you happy makes me happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nuggetemilybev It's really tough to be kind to yourself, but please keep trying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're having a hard time today, this might help: https://t.co/jxaenD0Tqd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dendronette I believe you, and I believe in you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dendronette It's really tough to be kind to yourself, but please keep trying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dendronette Hugs if you want them!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dendronette You've accomplished more than you think.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You've done a great job so far today. Let's keep up that momentum!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BellseaChel You got this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Valyasochka You contribute amazing things to the world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sspiers_k You! You are excellent! Keep it up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@enbeebuzz Thank you for listening to me! It makes me happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aphoebebarton You rock.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CamilleDeMere It's hard to get through life. You're doing a better job than you know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter how hard it gets, we can make it better together.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>