<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MrMarkBeaumont: Goats guarding my bike at the brilliantly named Modern Hotel at lunch today #AfricaSolo http://t.co/Kb7DTc0K7J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just earned the 'God Save the Queen (Level 5)' badge on @untappd! http://t.co/hKcUeJMtSN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where did it all go wrong for Parma? http://t.co/olH67UzSKQ - What a team #parma had in '95 - Crespo. Buffon, Chisea, Thuram, Cannavaro...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PhilippeAuclair: Bravo aux fans des Spurs pour leur chant: "Walking on the beaches, Super Vlad Chiriches Duh, Duh, Duh..." Nice. via @I…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Scotlandteam: BREAKING: Disappointed to confirm @Scotlandteam and Bristol back-row Ross Rennie is to retire http://t.co/s3XS0DJ4TW http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just earned the 'Playing the Field' badge on @untappd! http://t.co/yzXVJDwTPI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JLLScotland: Meet Susie Pierce, currently working on @TheAberdeenMal, the group’s most successful branch #JLLpeople http://t.co/nLcWChA…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @investinfife: WWF Scotland reports that in November Wind turbines generated an estimated 812,890MWh of electricity enough for 107% of a…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BQLive: Glasgow office of @JLLUK continues to grow underlining its faith in Scottish property market.
http://t.co/OqLcQcc7Ea http://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JLLUK: Top tips on how to make your property more environmentally friendly from @JLLupstream in @estatesgazette http://t.co/0mXuH2EvSQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chrishoy: What an atmosphere!! Just amazing! http://t.co/Fmr1IyJNMm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WelshIrvine: Colombia easily the most exciting team and James Rodriquez easily the most exciting player in tournament so far. #vamoscol…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rory_g_macrae yup! He was a complete bomb scare at centre back. Much better the further away from the box. Hibs signed him from Dunfermline]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rory_g_macrae It certainly is! Made the ex hibs World Cup cut along with Jorge Claros of Honduras. Bamba was brilliant when he played DM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Alanrobertson6: Watch me live @skynewsarabia talking about real estate transparency. At 6pm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I scored 17/30 in the Mirror MirrorFootball End-of-season Quiz quiz, can you beat me? http://t.co/BsKIrlVAT2 via @mirrorfootball]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Grado #itsyersel !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My god Suarez... #Suarez #LFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Kenny_Millar: What a story to wake up to. Still Game back! http://t.co/7MMT1XYg3P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cant wait to see him in the Prem - Stevan Jovetic: a winning combination of focused professional and big kid  http://t.co/Mt15LxjRyr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @StillGameQuote: "Oh look it's Lambert &amp; Butler" "Shut it Boaby, you're the only fag in here!" #StillGameQuote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mrdanwalker: Lots of you claiming a bare foot on Lego is worse than a plug-based injury. I would put Lego at level 8 and a plug at 9.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@u01naf6 Who???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lovsushi: One more for 300 follower RT to
Give us a hand, thanks #sushiboys]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aspy87 @rustyboy2310 keen for 1 or 2. Give me a ring xx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PepFujas: Loving it http://instagr.am/p/GFKNs/]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheChainSpokers: Great news - we have smashed our £5k target for @mariecurieuk! Thanks 2 everyone who has donated. We will be on our ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @simonpegg: Oh and because I'd like to make this tweet an annual tradition ... Happy Father's Day motherfuckers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Home! The english are too many! #braveheart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holiday booked! fuck yeah!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matthannah1987 Pretty much the same thing anyway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Beathhigh: Not in the #EdinBookFest programme, but Iain Banks' event will be chaired by Alex Salmond!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What I've forgotten about bullshit, you ain't even learnt yet" Classic Sugar #bbcapprentice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[really enjoying Jim fighting his corner. Go'an my son! #bbcapprentice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PKHunder: Google is one smart dude.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matthannah1987 I reckon so. Might as well!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matthannah1987 yeah bit of a gutter really. How can you get on reserve list?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rossmcnairn Now following @mcnairn . Huge.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[lipvine is launching soon and I'm one of the first in line! Join me. #launch http://t.co/sL7Qres via @lipvine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good evening ride tonight for #LEJOG training. Great numbers on the speedo! New @GoreBikeWear kit was ace.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rossmcnairn Really interesting article. thought you would enjoy http://bit.ly/iQzF8x #genius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow @TheChainSpokers folks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @joelycett: Just made this joke in Starbucks: 'Tall? Yes, I'm 6 foot 3!' Literally everyone there wished they were friends with me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SethMacFarlane: Yon lasse did slobbere on my nobbe. -- Dirty Chaucer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MrMarkBeaumont thanks for that. #LEJOG training!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hi @MrMarkBeaumont anywhere I can find a map of that training ride on @countrytracks right now? Cheers!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rossmcnairn what happens If you lose your phone?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rossmcnairn: top idea, http://tcrn.ch/jLNdkz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matthannah1987 ich don't think so. Moving in with lize tomo so will prob give it a miss #happytheseasonisover]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rustyboy2310 @rory_g_macrae @rossmcnairn just on way back from Forrest game, won't be back til 7ish. #beeroclock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rory_g_macrae @rustyboy2310 @rossmcnairn long time boys! Been on @FootballAid adventures. Beers tonight?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rossmcnairn I met that guy yesterday, he was in the office 'bout a new project]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matthannah1987 ooh check you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rustyboy2310 #jealous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Invisible: The "Fast & Furious" sequel just made $80M in 3 days. Fine Hollywood, you win. For our next film, we'll take out the plot ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@philmcnulty I don't think rangers have any illusions phil...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@rory_g_macrae: @rustyboy2310 tickets booked* ----) I'm not invited yeah? Dick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rustyboy2310 no chant for junior as yet. I think that something along the lines of wake me up before you gogo would be appropriate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rustyboy2310 holiday was brilliant yeah. Loadsay food and booze!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rory_g_macrae time and place me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rustyboy2310 Thursday is lizas birthday so could be a tricky one. Work going great enjoying it. How's glesgae?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right, who wants a #beer with me tonight?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matthannah1987 used to be shite now he's betta? I'd take him at hibs! #stillgotit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just back from awesome holiday in #italy. Internship at Miller Developments starts tomorrow morning!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Contador, you are a beast. How is he still attacking? #tdf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[last day at work. not really doing anything except watching the #tdf !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FIS are changing GS ski regulations for next season. min length of 195 and 40m radius. good one dickheads #FIS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GrahamSpiers: I’m concerned about Hibs, this daft new strip of theirs, and the strange, distant, enigmatic creature called Colin Cal ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great article for any fellow interns out there! http://t.co/aITCbdD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Property Week supplement finds hope for grads.: http://t.co/loy5IPL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rustyboy2310 @rory_g_macrae Include Meeeee!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@matthannah1987 Tom a bit of a Ben Reed lookalike?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[stick them together Sugar! curveball coming! #bbcapprentice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know he's getting annihalated in the interview, but i rate Jimbo #bbcapprentice]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FRabbits @thetwilightsad More of a lamb & black pudding pie man myself #Tebay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lancearmstrong: Alright Scotland - it's on. Twitter ride! Meet 5pm tomorrow (Sunday) in Dornoch (Sutherland County) at The Eagle Pub ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @matthannah1987: Signed #Hibs football on ebay http://t.co/lVgVfYT All profit going to @mariecurieuk as part of @TheChainSpokers fund ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[actually its only a single. weak!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never get tired of this @sethmorrison1 double backie from #focused it's outrageous http://t.co/FIUf5R9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rory_g_macrae @rustyboy2310 Aye whatevs. I'll prob be out for a couple anyway around stocky with lize and a mate so let me know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rory_g_macrae still up for a beer after footy tonight?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rory_g_macrae could be tough tonight mate. off to my mums for tea! How would you feel about tomorrow night? #beer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rossmcnairn Bonne Chance!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GARYTANK: @GeorgeMichael George, it's Gary- hiya! Listen, oot ay interest, dae you make money fae Wham bars? Uv goat a pal called "W ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CJ! Sort your hair ya mink! #eggheads]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Lorwills: #TEDGlobal is in Edinburgh next week. Maybe all that brain power can be used to stop the rain. Forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @andrewviner: ANDY COULSON. Cheer up. I read in #notw that prisons are like 5-star hotels, and you can live a life of luxury on benef ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MarkCavendish: 1 point today I got bad stomach cramp & farted unintentionally. Really thought I'd..ahem..followed through. So sorry  ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SquareFoot launch page up and running. Bookmark it bitches! www.squarefoot.me]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GeorgiaLawePR: "The active encouragement of reading for pleasure should be a core part of every child's curriculum" MP's report http ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Freeskier: [Breaking] The IOC announced that the 2018 Winter Olympic Games will be held in Pyeongchang, South Korea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alan sugar's got shit on Signor Corleone #thegodfather]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sicillian weddings look like outrageous banter #thegodfather]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BoingBoing: Han Solo in Carbonite ice-molds http://t.co/STxjvvz I want one!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/WY2p9Tf @rossmcnairn thought this might interest you if you haven't seen it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rustyboy2310 4 okay? Or too late? Got some stuff to do.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rustyboy2310 Got some work experience this week which is cool. Bank holiday today. Fancy meeting for coffee later?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rustyboy2310 miller was great yeah cheers. Was hung on Saturday and no use to anyone. Went to nandos. Heard you drew the rugby? U in glasgw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rustyboy2310 How are you getting on mate? did you hear back from that B&M interview]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is getting embarrassing for arsenal]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>