<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MBMBaM: HELP GET THE WORD OUT! The NYC/DC/Boston (early) Shows start at 7 PM! RT/Share the hell out of this! Some tix misprinted w/ 8!…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MBMBaM: Apparently some tickets have different info but: our shows this weekend in NY, DC and Boston start at 7 pm, with doors 30-60 mi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JapersRink: Well, when it's laid out like that... https://t.co/eeYoQdoPRw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DCPoliceDept definitely a shoots fired around 1600 K st NE last night after midnight before 5am. #CarverLangston]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our #roomba loves hiding under the chairs instead of getting dirt in the giant open space... https://t.co/j5KXj1XJNn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey. This is our wedding video. K, Bye. 
#ThisWeddingIsBenAnnas
https://t.co/e4c4FZ4GNO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justinfung hi.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At @BookofMormon. For some reason I keep singing “Hello, my name is Elder Merle”... 
#TheZoneCast 
cc: @DocCurm @TheZoneCast https://t.co/sw6G4krldX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“You think we’ll see @Lin_Manuel ?” - me
“Uh, we are seeing #BookOfMormon.”
“So? Isn’t he in all #Broadway shows?”
“We’re in #DC...”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @Marriott I’m on a telemarketing call that’s (super suspicious) offering me a free stay promotion
Want me to tell them anything for you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PuckSoupPodcast In the venn diagram of maple pecan lattes and @davelozo’s hot takes, the middle is “a bad taste in my mouth.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@patlikestotweet @CarlosCrits @TheDungeonRats Hmm. I’ll need to see some fan art before finalizing my opinion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarlosCrits @patlikestotweet @TheDungeonRats First image on google image search “metal hat”. #NailedIt. https://t.co/YJkqygBBt0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@KeBr0n11 The life of @BryndenBFish]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@russianmachine "And He Not Fat" -
 Pierre https://t.co/FnxjrEBjxs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeyJayJRogers “Dear poor people that can’t afford to spend money on sports websites: eff you. Love, cofounder of athletic.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ryan_Deem That’s not a deer! That’s four ducks!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ryan_Deem Also. Pics or GTFO.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ryan_Deem Morning? Like early in the morning? Perhaps it was so early it was “Fawn”.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish the puck was glowing because this was just too much. https://t.co/aPXHrf6pXM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MFW I find a piece of wood: https://t.co/3EqrLIIlSG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tjyoshie77 @peterhassett @russianmachine 2121 but Pre-Sale is going on now. #ICanDoIt #YouCanDoIt #YouCantSpellWeWithoutIAndU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterhassett @russianmachine #Visualize Peter. 
#Dream bigger. 
Now #Go! 
You can #Create!
You are the #Maker of your destiny.
Build and Empire!!!
#Believe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @edwinsongs: Uncontrollable Pride, how much love does it take to make thi(ng)s right. @songtradr has the first song up today. https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @edwinsongs: You Have No Idea, Man is on it’s way. https://t.co/sa3S0Veo4f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RadioWesteros: RIP Roy Dotrice https://t.co/WwbqQYLMUx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@notbuckingham @ElyseBee @pfholden @tjyoshie77 @peterhassett @ianoland Ooo! https://t.co/m8Uoi0nba6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterhassett What even IS “net front presence”?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My wife asked if I wanted to watch the #Caps game... (checks score) "Nope! I'm good.  Let's have a quiet night just us."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm just going to start calling Bowey "Goatman".
(it's a Bowie/Bowey joke) 
cc: @peterhassett https://t.co/F2zkpmYzAl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HeyJayJRogers The answer is “Harvey Dent” https://t.co/Eebqt4F9q3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This could be good in the sense chorney, orpik, ness only take up half the slots. So Barry HAS to play at least one rookie... right? https://t.co/wwey5Q0VnB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DimFilipovic: my eyes just rolled so far back into my head that I am now dead and tweeting from the afterlife https://t.co/hsjJuvjKs7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ElyseBee Not close enough. Get in Barry’s ear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new employee is a lot of fun! #Fridays https://t.co/Yqss8Ynd5e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still do dance. BUT I also make money move.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@millerra8 All great question.
One company on the floor. Only 75 employees.. BUT there’s like 30 big wigs here today. CEO and such.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Legit Question: if you found this in your work bathroom would you take? 
#AskingForAFriend #NeedToKnowASAP https://t.co/CzAiOz0Ao8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@notbuckingham @HeyJayJRogers Minnesota?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What am I doing here? @JordanPeele https://t.co/UgZDAgAUwS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd move to Utah and take them all as sister-wives.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[F, Marry, Kill
In honor of the last #MvsW: 

@JeffMarek @wyshynski @davelozo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Kid scores a goal and assist... maybe he needs to be benched for more grit and leadership.” - Barry Trotz, Probably. https://t.co/4kSO3zB2l2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DimFilipovic His brothers make some great music.
https://t.co/9q7pxWWiT3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[wait... i forgot who we were playing against.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TAKE THAT BARRY TROTZ!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't worry everyone! Ever Mighty Ducks movie taught me you have to lose to the EVIL team first.  And then beat them in the final...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I haven't watched baseball in a while but that's a lot right? https://t.co/2q1MrQWEFW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Djoos looks like a sweet sweet summer child.  
Like in the face. Not on the ice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tjyoshie77 oh bae! that totally blows, sorry man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have no idea have I've made it this far in life without microwaving metal... it's only a matter of time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BookishSpider @TheDungeonRats Is the answer "Cassandra Shahinfar" because if not, this gif has set me up for disappoint.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CarlosCrits HIDDEN BLADES!?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@justinfung you might want to check out @sleepingatlast’s podcast. He’s diving into the Enneagram.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“If you ice a bad player in 3 on 3 overtime you’re a bad coach... (I’m talking to you Barry Trotz).”
@Steve_Dangle #Caps
(Emphasis my own)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NonHepCat: 30 Anyone who finds sports apolitical has their politics represented in sports. And that says a lot about your politics.

Fin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @notbuckingham: Visibly uncomfortable Phil Kessel is my aesthetic https://t.co/NG8OWQnA6v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sleepingatlast Just now finding out about your pod. Really enjoying it. My Wife &amp; I walked down the aisle to "Sun" so Eclipse is a new fav.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Barry: “if I play only defensemen then we can play defense!”

Everyone Else: “or you’ll only be playing defense...”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@DimFilipovic I listened to you talk about Vancouver for an HOUR today. And this is how you repay me?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tjyoshie77: Yikes, djoosee that defending?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m gonna be really sad to see Grubi go in the @GoldenKnights expansion draf... wait, what? THAT WAS LAST YEAR???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Y’all. I’m not gonna lie. I don’t get this joke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nick Backstrom has Szechuan sauce.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ElyseBee *account*
*account notifications*
*all tweets* https://t.co/9JQOY5xsEO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterhassett “I voted for Hilary.” - God, probably.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ShmannersCast @travismcelroy My first wedding anniversary is coming up... how do I do it? I’ve heard there are metals involved?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theRocketboys I don’t mean to be needy but can you play in DC for not $150+?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@amandaclockwood WE GET IT, AMANDA, YOUR CLOSET IS BALLER! JEEEEZ.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tjyoshie77 @bobinarlington In French I believe it Le Showoff.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HeyJayJRogers: IT'S NATHAN WALKER'S GOAL!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh crap!!! Do you think the #Leafs kept Eric Fehr just because of the outdoor game against the #Caps???? 

Cc @russianmachine @Steve_Dangle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vrana saw an apartment for cheap rent and missed his shot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#caps went from 14-7 in shots to 17-24... #ClassicTrotzTurtle https://t.co/HzH6odsKCu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ngreenberg: Ovechkin: hold my beer https://t.co/rP9FOFL4ps]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I had a great tweet about Vrana but never mind]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ikhurshudyan Selfish Russian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I did everything @HeyJayJRogers told me not to do to Alzner. But no one could understand me through my sobbing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ovechkin has 5 goals in two periods...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone that is worried about the Vrana line not being defensive]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still don't get this.. is this how hockey works now? https://t.co/rzi0BzwsRv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't understand]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We tried. #NextTime]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't see an Australian flag... but there's still hope. #caps https://t.co/o34WyT4c2v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I LIED ALL SUMMER I AM EXCITED https://t.co/eaxIjQ4hYz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Caps #Spandex #Australia https://t.co/IKqH6XN7OS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tjyoshie77 Heart you https://t.co/sWR2mSkdZ8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@peterhassett I'm genuinely and deeply hurt by you. https://t.co/fWwGeIESVG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MullyDiesel23 @saskystewart @RoseColoredFact Can you Australians get your ish together? I need to know how serious to take my ridiculous petition!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@saskystewart @RoseColoredFact My bad... #TheMoreYouKnow!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @saskystewart: @RoseColoredFact Outside the grand final, we don't play anthems at domestic sporting events in Australia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has anyone checked to see if @noazark151 or @bobinarlington know the #Australian anthem?

https://t.co/JgXUFUfTqg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tjyoshie77 Also, I'll be at the game tomorrow.  If you want a hug.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tjyoshie77 How do I make this sound smart AND legal? https://t.co/JgXUFUfTqg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ikhurshudyan Sign the petition? https://t.co/N4BaaozTH8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Capitals @NathanWalks10 @NHL Hi. https://t.co/N4BaaozTH8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey, @TedLeonsis think of the market of an entire continent buying jerseys...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JustCallMe_AA Nah. there's a pro market in every other country represented... but not in Australia... and he's the first... ever!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tjyoshie77 can you be my editor? I need help sounding more smart english-y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I did a bad thing... https://t.co/JgXUFUfTqg cc: @russianmachine https://t.co/OvPyst3VO8]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>