<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Style is a simple way of saying complicated things." - Jean Cocteau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He ran out of talent about halfway through the corner. - Buddy Baker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about the Bay Area city of Danville, California http://t.co/JXGSYxEpfj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't do fashion. I am fashion. - Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Billy J. Kramer and the Dakotas  http://t.co/I22TGO74r1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A shoe has so much more to offer than just to walk. - Christian Louboutin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Triple Crown Sports Organization  http://t.co/Fksst0As7g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The average dog is a nicer person than the average person. - Andrew A. Rooney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Big-Dog Pet Fountain - Keeps Fresh and Tasty Water for Your Big Dog! http://t.co/q6DJR6wyy0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every boy should have two things: a dog, and a mother willing to let him have one - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Rufus  http://t.co/MTY4D7FTxX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Great Music of Bill Justis  http://t.co/dVComR5c0Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About BMX Biking Born from Freestyle Motocross  http://t.co/RaxIhjbPxO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My advice if you insist on slimming: Eat as much as you like - just don't swallow it. - Harry Secombe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't concentrate in flats! - Victoria Beckham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Advanced Weight Scales and Body Monitoring – Keeping Track of your Body Weight  http://t.co/WLLtvLAocW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Setup an iPad Speaker System  http://t.co/dl5PmLkViI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Jack in the Box  http://t.co/OJDlPJEBxi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apollo: I will not serve under a man who questions my integrity. Adama: And I won't have an officer under my command who doesn't have any.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Skeeter Davis  http://t.co/d1DeRLgUi3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Buffalo Springfield  http://t.co/heRSaCtLmk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Millie Jackson  http://t.co/I61fA2dxFJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Champions keep playing until they get it right. - Billie Jean King]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious T-Shirt - “I Got Your Back” http://t.co/M2vZYMfrpM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool 14' Iceberg For Your Pool or the Lake! http://t.co/SLff7RU9GK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The truest test of moral courage is the ability to ignore an insult]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Beautiful Canadian Rockies Tour  http://t.co/yHsaRdPVP8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're really getting old when your work is less fun and your fun is more work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've never wanted to go to Japan. Simply because I don't like eating fish. And I know that's very popular in Africa.  Britney Spears]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Gary Lewis and the Playboys  http://t.co/JcsQZgNUer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 11 - Waiting  http://t.co/zkbbasjPN3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Millie Jackson  http://t.co/I61fA2dxFJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine his nerve -- .. I was all ready to refuse him, and he didn't even ask!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marriage lets you annoy and aggravate one special person for the rest of your life.  What a joy LOL!!  :&gt;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep you can keep your devices charged via solar power - find out here - http://t.co/7EsKpQGm8s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fool and his money are never without friends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ah Robe You Must Have - Star Wars Master Yoda Bathrobe! http://t.co/YFp7Fy9uyI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Once burned a lesson is learned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Evolution of the Wooden Clog  http://t.co/TzsfyLsG6e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana’s Lyme Journey – Part 16 – Seven Months Later  http://t.co/47BzxOjAy5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Eric Clapton  http://t.co/AMTV89M79q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Few people SUFFER from egotism. With most of them it's a PLEASURE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriousness is stupidity sent to college. P. J. O'Rourke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the History of the Nautilus Fitness Equipment  http://t.co/WttudUwvld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laverne and Shirley is an American sitcom classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/gsGR9gmuFc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gary US Bonds was an amazing musician and rocker - read his history - http://t.co/AmyQsZgEFA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is simply the soul of a society as it passes from one generation to another. - Gilbert K. Chesterton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Flower Mound, Texas  http://t.co/54kgeQefk8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bright light! Bright light! - Gremlins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome biking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the biking lovers in your life!   http://t.co/o9gLFLbj1j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stumbling is not falling. - Portuguese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the God Particle – Higgs Boson – On the Run  http://t.co/3YeDkw4Pdh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome fine wine t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the fine wine lovers in your life!   http://t.co/PCSTD3aoiF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Allstate Insurance  http://t.co/7mE09egTP4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Willie Mays' glove is where triples go to die. - Jim Murray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must accept finite disappointment, but we must never lose infinite hope. - Martin Luther King, Jr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Uriah Heep  http://t.co/pEu8Pa5RM0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Arthur Alexander - The Unknown Legend  http://t.co/eXsPOP5mFl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Who Invented the Modern Watch?  http://t.co/txNtzqdJIw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Each man has his own vocation; his talent is his call. There is one direction in which all space is open to him. - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just want one day off when I can go swimming and eat ice cream and look at rainbows.  Mariah Carey (pre-rehab)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't see pitches down the middle anymore - not even in batting practice. -  Hank Aaron]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As far as I'm concerned, there won't be a Beatles reunion as long as John Lennon remains dead. - George Harrison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Awesome Nintendo Wall Graphics! http://t.co/rSWMaBgAD8]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahh Read About Loving Fine Wine  http://t.co/8kPF9PpkN8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No heaven will not ever Heaven be; “Unless my cats are there to welcome me.” - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's later than we think and most of us aren't even thinking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are what you do. If you do boring, stupid, monotonous work, chances are you'll end up boring, stupid, and monotonous. - Bob Black]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I raced a car last it was at a time when sex was safe and racing was dangerous. Now, it's the other way round. - Hans Stuck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting Your Creative Writing Degree Online  http://t.co/mSY0HawSyO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes are the quickest way for women to achieve instant metamorphosis - Manolo Blahnik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Advanced Weight Scales and Body Monitoring – Keeping Track of your Body Weight  http://t.co/WLLtvLAocW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Three Dog Night  http://t.co/yzVJCMazmI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best way to show appreciation for a favor is to enjoy it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lend your friend $20, if he doesn't pay you back then he's not your friend. Money well spent - Ted Nicolas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can a leopard change his spots?  "By going from one spot to another"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The absolute fundamental aim is to make money out of satisfying customers. - John Egan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool just found these 25 Original Unopened Packs of Vintage Baseball Cards (80s-90s) - can find some value in there!  http://t.co/xAXouXtJ0g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women should look like women. A piece of cardboard has no sexuality. - Alexander McQueen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the top 25 health insurance companies in the US!  http://t.co/Qzjdyal5J7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't know who invented high heels, but all women owe him a lot! - Marilyn Monroe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If high heels were so wonderful, men would be wearing them. - Sue Grafton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Manolo Blahnik  http://t.co/p74BmxLOpJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Religion Both Protestant and Catholics  http://t.co/nAUuvmOLjI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People share read &amp; generally engage more with any type of content when its surfaced through friends &amp; people they know and trust - Facebook]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Overview of Domestic Adoption  http://t.co/O1CbgGyWQB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Moon is the first milestone on the road to the stars. - Arthur C. Clarke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahh Read About Loving Fine Wine  http://t.co/8kPF9PpkN8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have enemies? Good. That means you've stood up for something, sometime in your life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of the hilarious "I Love Lucy" episode - The Kleptomaniac  http://t.co/3TLyRCOA88]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I'm not back in five minutes, just wait longer. - Ace Ventura, Ace ventura, Pet Detective]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always laugh heartily at your boss' jokes - he may be giving you a loyalty check.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Holy Cow!  Harry Caray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Aerosmith  http://t.co/HnzD8IheQZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the business world, everyone is paid in two coins: cash &amp; experience. Take the experience first; the cash will come later - Harold Geneen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 13 - Covering the costs of treatment – is it worth it all?  http://t.co/7TT29rQW2P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you wish to grow thinner, diminish your dinner. - Henry Sambrooke Leigh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[High heels are pride and privilege, the passkey to decadence. - Karen Heller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About these Burial at Sea Options  http://t.co/2KS1K9ogcD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The reality of science is that it takes 40 years to get to Jupiter, and that's a dull show. - Glen Morgan, "Space: Above and Beyond"]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>