<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ThePlumLineGS: This tweet is highly misleading. Trump did not criticize the gutting. Any casual reader would assume he did. https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jonfavs: Trump didn't do this. You did this. Remember that. https://t.co/OlfRKNyHkw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @safeclimatecamp: "The energy transition is real, and Mr. Trump is not going to stop it." Fight #Globalwarming. @realDonaldTrump. https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[(and a happy 125th birthday to J.R.R. Tolkien, by the way) https://t.co/h6Wa6AAht3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the scene, considering likely threats to the environment in the new congress:

https://t.co/FkHVae6FCV

#ActOnClimate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, PEOTUS, don't worry. We know what to do. https://t.co/dKlHvcaVlj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This was pretty great to watch in KC with the fam. Merry Christmas indeed. https://t.co/rJGwQth281]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@rebleber @MotherJones congratulations!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't blame #cleanercars standards for rising sticker prices--just for cleaner air and savings at the pump: https://t.co/uZg7yIzGPt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kenkimmell: Take note, Mr. Trump--new poll shows Trump voters want clean air,water&amp;climate regulations to stay in place.https://t.co/cW…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Earthjustice: Roses are red
Violets are blue
We're lawyers
Not poets
Help us save the wolves  https://t.co/zGp3jq6ZDv #ValentinesDay ht…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JoshatNRDC: States, red and blue, are going to continue to deal with climate and clean energy no matter what's up in DC https://t.co/ke…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let's clean up lead
And keep the sky blue.
If you undermine EPA,
We'll be the ones who sue.

#PruittValentines
#pollutingPruitt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["He had the opportunity to prove his point. He was on TV to prove his point. He didn’t." @KrisKobach1787  https://t.co/OIXdgCOg6m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Earthjustice: #PollutingPruitt refuses to release his emails with polluters. So much for draining the swamp. https://t.co/mLC7sGi35h ht…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JoshatNRDC: “we can save [this critically endangered bee] – but not if the White House stands in the way.” - @RRileyNRDC https://t.co/c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @thehill: #BREAKING: Trump not planning to appeal travel ban ruling to Supreme Court https://t.co/dgyiba5JrP https://t.co/VkbNIRe0Xo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AriBerman: Trump lies about voter fraud again in Senate meeting, says "thousands" were bused from MA to "illegally" vote in NH https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ashleyfeinberg https://t.co/2jDk8NkG5p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KyungLahCNN: Cong Chaffetz Town Hall crowd chanting "Do your job!" He's having a hard time answering over crowd noise @UtahIndivisible…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is he referring to today's article that literally starts with "President Trump told President Xi Jinping of China on Thursday evening..."? https://t.co/8AkXLYTL0g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ashleyfeinberg: no the constitution decided that https://t.co/EWt9VcU0Mh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @calvinstowell: Captain America is fighting with the Red Skull on Twitter right now. This is too real. https://t.co/B3mK0d1HDx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JohnDingell: Trump loses. Constitution wins.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @collinrees: Beautiful show of resistance at #WhiteHouse tonight.

We are here to protect, &amp; we will say #NoDAPL over &amp; over again until…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ACLU: Trump's EPA Pick: Something Doesn't Add Up https://t.co/VQIB3eV2rH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ACLU: BREAKING: Jeff Sessions confirmed as attorney general. 

If he violates the Constitution, we'll sue. https://t.co/le02tuG2Pg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NoDAPL rally amassing at the White House. #WaterIsLife https://t.co/Gcmd2oazAV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heading to the protest at the White House in 30 min. Who's joining? #NoDAPL https://t.co/eBgZMPjZtN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RheaSuh: Trump’s help-one-harm-two deal puts our health and safety at risk. We’re confident the court will agree. https://t.co/8aZ65uob…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If discussion of Sessions' offensive record is inappropriate for the U.S. Senate, approving of that record must also be. #letlizspeak https://t.co/Rebr5HY119]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senators can't vet cabinet nominees whose work and career they are not allowed to discuss.  

#neverthelessshepersisted
#letlizspeak https://t.co/OCU45vYV3q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mic: Elizabeth Warren was silenced at the US Senate. Here's the Coretta Scott King letter Republicans don't want you to hear. https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump forcing through Dakota Access Pipeline before public comment period even closes. Time to rally. #NoDAPL https://t.co/NCISHK0ieS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JesseLehrich: "END THE TYRANNY OF POLITICAL CORRECTNESS!"

[censures female Sen. over criticism]

[complains SNL is 'mean']

[decries p…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jwalkenrdc: Answer: No. https://t.co/VloLYh1wo2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WomensMarchKS: @JerryMoran @PatRoberts - We will remember your vote for #Devos. We will remember your choice to not listen to the Kansa…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nprpolitics: Pence Becomes First VP To Break Senate Tie Over Cabinet Nomination https://t.co/LENVnFVgrT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ChrisMurphyCT: Ok, I'm wide awake and about to start holding the floor in opposition to #BetsyDeVos. Tune in, insomniac CSPAN nerds!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @clairecmc: DeVos is so out of touch.Parents in rural Mo don't have choices b/w public &amp; private schools.They rely on strong public scho…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SenateDems: Watch now for more on #DeVos &amp; her conflicts of interests from @SenWhitehouse: https://t.co/FSNimOttlT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SenJeffMerkley: Hey night owls in Oregon, I've got the 2-3 am PST shift holding the floor tonight to stand against #DeVos. Tune in! htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NickMerrill: 2 questions for @PressSec tomorrow:
1) Which of these weren't covered?
2) Which of these was the result of foreigners ente…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC: Three weeks into Trump's presidency and climate science is already under attack. Time to #StandUpForScience: https://t.co/b4b2C7c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We know they can succeed because they are already succeeding. #ResistTrump  https://t.co/serGKiuKMe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Trump follows an aggressive anti-environment agenda, she said, “there will be a big backlash in the heartland.” https://t.co/XDYXl6WO59]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @deliberateloris: Today and all the days to come
#LoveTrumpsHate #notaswamp #DCprotest https://t.co/cOaxf1OjX1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1) Shut down White House comment line

2) Discount all polling, and millions in the streets

3) Enjoy your own authoritarian fantasy world https://t.co/9N7S4rzaTi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC: Disqualifying: EPA Nominee Scott Pruitt Misled Senators https://t.co/J8kNI3wdtb  by @jwalkenrdc https://t.co/vgG6wPBZW2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NateSilver538: At least the Falcons won the popular vote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BraddJaffy: President Trump “has some meetings and may play a few holes of golf” today, White House aide says

(Quick reminder of previ…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jonfavs: The President tells Americans to blame our own judges for any future terrorist attack, and then lies about our vetting process…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oof. Poor Ralph. https://t.co/QvUfynQcCQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What are you up to this weekend?" 
"Oh, you know, the usual."
#NoBanNoWall https://t.co/EZpWcFWPnM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PeterGleick: Here's the "problem": he's using a long debunked, misleading graph. This is fake science. #SEJTrump https://t.co/R8GqzNtcZN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CaseyLefkowitz: Ebell questions "authority" of scientists. I think he really means that he questions the authority of facts. #alternati…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jwalkenrdc: I remember when most heavily funded corporate attorneys on planet challenged IPCC climate science in U.S. courts &amp; lost MIS…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC: The Case for Tackling Climate Change: Why America, and the World, Need the #ParisAgreement https://t.co/RWj2nkuGq2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @scott_tobias: Find someone to look at you the way these guys look at a bill freeing mining companies to dump coal debris in streams. ht…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Ianpgary: Without SHAME @SenateGOP rolls back global oil anti-corruption law in pre-dawn hours today. Gift to #Exxon #Russia  https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chrislhayes: Not *one word* about the Muslims slaughtered in their house of worship by a white supremacist Trump fan. Not one. https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ChrisMurphyCT: WH aide just refused to confirm on NPR whether Trump considers Islam to be a real religion. Not joking. 

But no, it's n…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is incredible. Let's make more history as  engaged citizens than Trump makes with his #cabinetofpolluters. https://t.co/I16ogeZjyi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ParkerMolloy https://t.co/qiJgWTAQ0B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SenatorCantwell: Republicans want to destroy the #StreamProtectionRule. How about we do what’s in the public interest, not special inte…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @timkaine: If Scott Pruitt rejects science on climate change, I suspect he will ignore other science as well. I will oppose him, full st…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[House Republicans target 1st of many possible casualties of CRA: protections keeping mining debris out of streams. https://t.co/g92KMlCOYn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EPWDems: It is irresponsible to force through an extreme nominee without essential information: https://t.co/vQgS8oQKin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jwalkenrdc: Outrageous abuse by GOP Senators with @EPWMajority, ramming thru EPA nominee Scott Pruitt &amp; abetting his cover-up of confli…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Elections have consequences," certainly, @SenJohnBarrasso, but so do #pollutingPruitt's evasions on ties to polluters and intent for EPA.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They just suspended the rules to override the @EPWdems boycott - now clear we will not get straight answers they demanded. #pollutingPruitt https://t.co/S9hDAV40gD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republicans of @EPWMaj starting new effort to force thru #pollutingPruitt nomination without the minority.  https://t.co/0KSSv2Xxun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @whitjones: 100 ppl protesting #PolluterPruit + getting ready to go inside @SenatorCollins office to demand she #StopPruitt #mepolitics…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDCFedGov: “NRDC: the Congressional Review Act is a Public Health Menace.” Read: https://t.co/IUEWOQ53jL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump admin says Iran is "on notice." But... I think they also effectively told Australia today they're on notice. https://t.co/ul0doYWd96]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jonathanchait: If Clinton had suggested last fall Trump was so unfit for office he might do this, nobody would've believed her https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @petealtman13: New @USAToday editorial: #PollutingPruitt is “hostile” to the EPA’s mission of protecting our health. https://t.co/yfnZ4s…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For an overview of #pollutingPruitt's ties with polluters and his awful resume, check out Bill Moyers' new video: https://t.co/AA8iKEQ063]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @david_turnbull: Just a few minutes into voting and #RexTillerson has received more NO votes than any Sec of State nominee in last 40 ye…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RheaSuh: Pruitt is stonewalling, telling senators 19x to file records requests for answers—knowing there’s a 2+ yr. Oklahoma backlog to…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jonfavs: One more Republican defection and Devos is done. Anyone know where Heller (R-NV) and Flake (R-AZ) are? Both have tough races i…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nicole_soojung: Murkowski is also a no on DeVos!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jwalkenrdc: I've read all of those answers. No reasonable person would call his non-answers "answers." He also refused to provide 1,000…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SenatorCarper: When @EPWDems asked Scott Pruitt for information, he told us to go to the back of a 2-year line for information requests…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jwalkenrdc: Huh, Republican Senators didn't describe their own boycott of Obama nominee Gina McCarthy that way, when they stalled confi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @alexcguillen: Wicker, of course, was among Rs who boycotted Gina McCarthy's committee vote in 2013. https://t.co/9GuzwvuiRW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JerryMoran or 213 KS lives saved annually by smog standards #pollutingPruitt has attacked. https://t.co/bjI09TkGVn
https://t.co/wr3mWQkIPq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JerryMoran it's not about politics, but abt 160 KANSAN lives saved annually by mercury and toxics standards #pollutingPruitt has attacked.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JerryMoran, you say your view as a Kansan may be different. Here's my view as a Kansan: #pollutingPruitt's evasions are not answers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SenatorCarper: The @EPWDems asked Scott Pruitt important questions about his record as AG and his vision for the EPA. Those questions r…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you @EPWDems for standing against the efforts to push #pollutingPruitt's nomination without straight answers. https://t.co/B6GyLUAYdh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sen. @jiminhofe suggests Dems submitted too many questions for #PollutingPruitt. Well, he has a lot to answer for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jwalkenrdc: Senator @JimInhofe lists past EPA nominees who got fewer Senator Qs than Scott Pruitt--w/out noting Republicans submitted m…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC: These cabinet nominees refused to answer Q’s about record &amp; conflicts of interests. Now Republicans are changing rules to help th…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WaterkeepersCP: Tonight on #EPA building! Stop #PollutingPruitt! It's not too late to send email: https://t.co/ttKVZ8c9oY Or call https…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CleanAirMoms: Moms, Dads and Kids on Capitol Hill making it clear that #MomsDisapprove of Scott Pruitt to head EPA! #PollutingPruitt @E…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the lives saved annually by state with just one of many enviro protections #pollutingPruitt has attacked: https://t.co/wr3mWQkIPq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you @SenJeffMerkley for setting the record straight on #pollutingPruitt https://t.co/s5dC9vyVdS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NRDC_AF: Thank you @CoryBooker for protecting kids from Trump's dangerous nom for @EPA. Click link in video to call your senator and ur…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#PollutingPruitt has not provided substantive answers to critical questions. Reasonable to demand them before any vote! https://t.co/TbWz0nf2JT]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>