<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[At a funeral, Lamar Alexander mistakenly tells Omarosa Manigault that Kremlin officials are hiring lobbyists. Ann Coulter donates blood.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a coffee shop, Sam Brownback rudely informs Rick Perry that retirees are refusing to cooperate. Adam Sandler talks awkwardly about sex.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While flirting, Ryan Zinke reluctantly explains to Omarosa Manigault that Nazis are not real. Peggy Noonan slides down the bannister.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With gritted teeth, Ted Cruz tells President Trump that Tea Party Patriots are comfortable with nudity. Don King harasses celebrities.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a prank call, Carly Fiorina reveals to President Trump that transgender people are not really important. A corporate lobbyist pretends to be deaf.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In front of the press, Ted Cruz reluctantly admits to Ben Carson that Ponzi scheme conmen are big league. Scott Baio admits to pranking Trump.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A blank-faced Reince Preibus convinces Katrina Pierson that Fox reporters are hoarding Trump steaks. Trump's body double quits smoking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On a hot mic, Nikki Haley reveals to President Trump that Tumblr users are big fans. The gardener has an intervention.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While soaking wet, Justin Amash fails to persuade Kellyanne Conway that Somalian immigrants are on point. The maid harasses celebrities.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a parking garage, Jared Kushner calmly tells Kellyanne Conway that North Koreans are excessively fastidious. Michael Savage joins a cult.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A leering Rick Snyder reluctantly explains to President Trump that neoliberals are still waiting on hold. The maid finds a cursed sword.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An intense Rick Snyder tries to persuade Katrina Pierson that ACLU members are enlightened leaders. Adam Sandler fails the Turing test.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Dallas, Jared Kushner mistakenly tells Katrina Pierson that Hollywood liberals are capable bureaucrats. Jon Voight vacuums all the rugs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the hot tub, Hope Hicks announces to President Trump that the voters are becoming too powerful. A lovable old man listens to jazz for the first time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Without meaning to, Steve Bannon fails to convince Jeff Sessions that Scientologists are still waiting on hold. Tucker Carlson negotiates a peace deal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bedridden Scott Pruitt divulges to Jeff Sessions that the caterers are always strapped. Dana Perino flirts with White House interns.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While drunk, John Kasich admits to Jeff Sessions that the New Black Panthers are conservative Christians. Carl Higbie quotes Zinn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Jerusalem, Lindsey Graham explains to President Trump that the caterers are waiting in the Lincoln bedroom. Dana Perino laughs, then cries.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An indifferent Butch Otter persuades Ben Carson that Kremlin officials are in covert ops. Jon Voight tries on new outfits.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While sharing a cab, Mike Huckabee persuades Betsy DeVos that white women are withdrawing support. Alex Jones has an intervention.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An indifferent Lindsey Graham informs Ben Carson that Kremlin officials are not to be trusted. Peggy Noonan gets tangled in cords.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over drinks, Jason Chaffetz reluctantly explains to President Trump that Chicago teens are headed to prison. Dennis Miller solves a Rubik's Cube.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the basement, David Shulkin carefully explains to President Trump that millennials are drug addicts. Ivanka's bodyguard removes the mask.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On live TV, Paul LePage fails to persuade President Trump that international bankers are drilling for oil. Willie Robertson makes a regrettable bet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A tense Carly Fiorina fails to convince President Trump that NAACP members are filing another lawsuit. Sean Hannity edits Wikipedia pages.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Chicago, Justin Amash announces to President Trump that their Twitter followers are big fans. The White House chef tries to use street slang.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A delirious Lindsey Graham overhears someone tell President Trump that Lutherans are infiltrators. An obnoxious neighbor listens to reason.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On a hot mic, Rick Snyder calmly tells President Trump that drug dealers are on Air Force One. Carl Higbie quotes Dostoyevsky.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A visibly sick Steven Mnuchin boldly informs Omarosa Manigault that the New York Mets are not very affluent. Scott Baio hallucinates.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During Christmas, Jared Kushner fails to persuade Melania that Kentuckians are utterly useless. Sarah Palin pretends to be an alien.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A stone-faced Paul LePage explains to Katrina Pierson that retirees are big supporters. Bill O'Reilly picks flowers and sighs deeply.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Thursday, Roger Stone calmly tells President Trump that Asian immigrants are hoarding Trump steaks. The gardener plays Candy Crush.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On a long hike, Roger Stone tries to convince Omarosa Manigault that school teachers are Schwarzenegger fans. A local TV anchor cancels an appointment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the basement, Steve Scalise proclaims to Omarosa Manigault that LA Times reporters are crushed by excessive regulations. Don King tries to use street slang.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While sunbathing, Carly Fiorina fails to convince Ben Carson that FBI agents are capable bureaucrats. Ivanka's bodyguard makes a regrettable bet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Via email, Jason Chaffetz announces to President Trump that leftist college students are useful idiots. Scott Walker serenades White House guests.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A grinning Jared Kushner boldly informs President Trump that ACLU lawyers are advocates for secession. Scott Baio pulls a muscle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Easter, Lindsey Graham admits to Rick Perry that Iranian immigrants are reading Breitbart. The sommelier drinks too much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After the two argue, Justin Amash fails to convince Rick Perry that the interns are selling land in National Parks. Scottie Nell Hughes discovers Pornhub.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A delirious Mitch McConnell admits to President Trump that Texans are buying up Trump properties. Jon Voight wears a tutu.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the locker room, Steve Bannon reveals to Rick Perry that several Senators are lurking everywhere. Don King collects a welfare check.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In New York, VP Pence announces to Omarosa Manigault that Japanese reporters are spies. Michelle Malkin quotes Naomi Wolf.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After a rally, Rick Snyder tries to convince Kellyanne Conway that Nazis are hunting dolphins. Peggy Noonan naps in the Oval Office.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Via email, Rick Santorum overhears someone tell President Trump that AARP members are part of the shadow government. Glenn Beck jumps in the pool.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An angry Sean Spicer reveals to President Trump that the hired help are part of the prank. Mike Tyson adopts a black child.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After too many drinks, Ivanka explains to President Trump that Teen Vogue reporters are heavily armed. Melania's bodyguard solicits donations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Late at night, Rand Paul calmly tells President Trump that red state governors are airing their grievances. President Bush finds change in the couch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the locker room, Pete Sessions calmly tells Ben Carson that Hollywood liberals are pro-Trump. Rush Limbaugh listens to reason.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An angry John Kasich insists to Jeff Sessions that phone companies are in the Oval Office. Scott Baio quotes Goebbels.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Without meaning to, Rick Scott decides not to tell President Trump that the Koch brothers are waiting at Trump Tower. Chris Christie collects dust.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before a rally, Stephen Miller patiently explains to Melania that several dictators are not coming over for Christmas. An obnoxious neighbor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a confusing mixup, Elaine Chao informs President Trump that agnostics are waiting in the green room. Richard Spencer sniffs glue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A paranoid Hope Hicks carefully explains to President Trump that the stars of Friends are hiding in Trump Tower. Benjamin Netanyahu pays for an abortion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In front of guests, Roger Stone announces to President Trump that CNN reporters are withdrawing support. Arnold Schwarzenegger calls the police.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before a rally, Marco Rubio confesses to President Trump that the Koch brothers are international bankers. Trump's bodyguard gets an extreme makeover.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Over hors d'oeuvres, Rex Tillerson tries to persuade President Trump that Mar-a-Lago members are total winners. Sarah Palin runs for office.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rick Scott mistakenly tells Jeff Sessions that CNN reporters are hiding in Trump Tower. Bobby Jindal returns no phone calls.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the phone, Rick Scott reluctantly explains to Omarosa Manigault that Black Lives Matter activists are double agents. Trump's bodyguard is "disappeared."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a bar mitzvah, Jared Kushner reluctantly admits to Betsy DeVos that Chinese officials are phishing .gov email accounts. The sommelier wears a hijab.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a flashback, Nikki Haley reluctantly explains to Melania that Teen Vogue reporters are hiding in Trump Tower. Carl Higbie has plastic surgery.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shivering uncontrollably, Rex Tillerson reluctantly admits to Rick Perry that oil executives are free at last. A "fixer" forgets to flush.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Jerusalem, Jason Chaffetz politely tells President Trump that conspiracy theorists are human, all too human. Bill O'Reilly gets a second job.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Trump Tower, Stephen Miller admits to Rick Perry that phone companies are not very smart. Chris Christie fails the Voight-Kampff test.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A blank-faced Stephen Miller reluctantly explains to Betsy DeVos that KGB spies are digging holes in the yard. Ivanka's bodyguard is hired, then fired.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Without meaning to, Mark Sanford tries to persuade Omarosa Manigault that Mormons are enemies of the people. Melania's bodyguard dresses in drag.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a prank call, Lamar Alexander accidentally convinces Jeff Sessions that Jews are jealous of Trump. Mike Tyson shakes the wrong hand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Mar-a-Lago, Paul LePage reluctantly admits to Katrina Pierson that red state governors are Schwarzenegger fans. Karl Rove opens all the windows.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A sneering Hope Hicks boldly informs President Trump that Hollywood liberals are Schwarzenegger fans. God Almighty quotes Plato.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a limousine, Roger Stone fails to convince President Trump that White House employees are reading Breitbart. An obnoxious neighbor quotes Nietzsche.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before a speech, Steve Bannon patiently explains to President Trump that Texans are planning something ominous. An ex-girlfriend drinks all the booze.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a wedding, Darrell Issa proclaims to President Trump that Lyft and Uber are harmless. Sean Hannity learns to cook.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On July 4th, Paul Ryan explains to Rick Perry that Protestants are real. Dana Perino wins an arm-wrestling contest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As part of a hazing ritual, Rick Santorum explains to President Trump that CNN reporters are moving in next door. Carl Higbie vacuums all the rugs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After dinner, Marco Rubio accidentally convinces President Trump that Russian officials are requesting donations. The valet downloads an app.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A leering Reince Preibus persuades Jeff Sessions that the IT guys are enlightened leaders. Peter Thiel lies under oath.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Trump Tower, David Shulkin proclaims to Kellyanne Conway that Japanese reporters are not what they seem. Sarah Palin rides in Air Force One.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sighing deeply, Lindsey Graham patiently explains to Jeff Sessions that teenagers are moving in next door. Dana Perino checks out a CIA black site.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Trump Tower, Steve Bannon announces to Rick Perry that Protestants are withdrawing support. The sommelier is thrown in Guantanamo.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On the phone, H.R. McMaster explains to Rick Perry that Satanists are lurking everywhere. The White House chef plays Candy Crush.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An angry H.R. McMaster reluctantly explains to Betsy DeVos that white working-class men are utterly useless. Ted Nugent quotes Mussolini.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a panic, Rick Scott reluctantly admits to Ben Carson that Baptists are begging for donations. Clint Eastwood seeks justice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the season finale, Wilbur Ross proclaims to President Trump that Russian businessmen are victims of a misunderstanding. Michael Savage attends a funeral.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a limousine, Ryan Zinke divulges to Kellyanne Conway that Republicans are not coming over for Christmas. A "fixer" cooks breakfast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In front of the press, Rex Tillerson confesses to President Trump that corporate lobbyists are Schwarzenegger fans. Kayleigh McEnany quotes John Wayne.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a coffee shop, Elaine Chao admits to President Trump that rappers are actually gay. Sarah Palin tries too hard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a wedding, H.R. McMaster explains to President Trump that Fox reporters are calling for impeachment. Trump's bodyguard begs for a job.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While sunbathing, Rex Tillerson mistakenly tells Omarosa Manigault that the Koch brothers are enlightened leaders. Glenn Beck has to pay the bill.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A weary Roger Stone decides not to tell President Trump that Satanists are not coming over for Christmas. Jesus Christ does an AMA on reddit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While playing poker, Rick Snyder carefully explains to Betsy DeVos that Canadians are tying up the phone lines. Ted Nugent unloads a pistol.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On live TV, Rick Snyder fails to persuade Betsy DeVos that corporate lobbyists are up to no good. An obsequious reporter kneels before a new master.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a press conference, Steve Bannon reluctantly admits to Jeff Sessions that international bankers are useful idiots. Trump's body double]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a sleepover, Lamar Smith reveals to President Trump that FBI agents are sitting on vast reserves of oil. Corey Lewandowski is hired, then fired.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a panic, Peter King overhears someone tell President Trump that the hired help are Schwarzenegger fans. Bill Kristol loses an eye.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An exhausted David Shulkin boldly informs Melania that White House employees are terrorists. An adorable orphan kisses a woman.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the War Room, Butch Otter reluctantly admits to Ben Carson that unicorns are standing in the kitchen. Pat Buchanan gets an extreme makeover.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After too many drinks, Rex Tillerson reluctantly explains to President Trump that coal miners are buying up Trump properties. Adriana Cohen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A paranoid Rick Snyder insists to President Trump that Amazon and Walmart are hiring lobbyists. Karl Rove gets way too drunk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before a speech, Marco Rubio reluctantly admits to President Trump that the minions of Soros are extremely wealthy. Dana Perino discovers Pornhub.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[During a sleepover, Jared Kushner admits to Jeff Sessions that corporate executives are requesting donations. Alex Jones guest stars.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a limousine, Jared Kushner convinces Betsy DeVos that Syrian refugees are about as dangerous as kittens. Mike Tyson gives up on a project.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>