<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing worse than when someone buys you a shot of Jameson. #ThanksButNoThanks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CTVNews: Refugee family running N.S. chocolate business mentioned in Trudeau's UN speech https://t.co/kt4KXcyG1w https://t.co/rErVCACsxJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Scorpio_A7: #Scorpio hide their emotions with humor.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Sports_Greats: Life isn't about waiting for the storm to pass, it's about learning to dance in the rain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Fact: The Philippine island of Luzon contains a lake that contains an island that contains a lake that contains another island.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Forbes: Countries with the most business aircraft:

1. U.S.
2. Brazil
3. Mexico

https://t.co/S7DceGon4H https://t.co/SF7HXvuGi8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cbcnewsbc: Class-action lawsuit filed against B.C.'s foreign buyer property tax: https://t.co/TNqwVRW2sg https://t.co/GvfOIHwibb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WhatTheFFacts: When female servers draw a happy face on the bill, tips increase 20%.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Quote_Soup: There is beauty in simplicity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @globeandmail: UN suspends all Syria aid after air strike https://t.co/ZXgSo6gD7d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep. https://t.co/6u5RNWPCQQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hands up. Don't shoot. #TerenceCrutcher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WhatTheFFacts: Leonardo Da Vinci signed his initials on the right pupil of the Mona Lisa.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WhatTheFFacts: Mike Tyson was arrested 38 times by the time he turned 13.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@TheFactsBook: Male koalas have two penises." And the females...???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WhatTheFFacts: Bill Clinton only sent two emails while in office.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Fact: China has 350 million smokers — meaning the Chinese smoking population is higher than the entire population of the United States.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Btw our beer league hockey result...up 5-2 halfway through the second.   Lost 6-5 with 6 seconds to go in the game. 1-1 now.   #bush]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm thinking more solid dress shirts with vivid colour is the way to go. #FallFashions]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beer league hockey game tonight at 5:30pm.   Due to blackout restrictions in your area the game will NOT be televised.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@EliasTheodorou. I see your name everywhere now.   Even on the locks in my building. https://t.co/L72edIVreg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Quote_Soup: No one has ever become poor by giving.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@MlNDBLOWINGS: There is no single food that provides all the nutrients that humans need, except for breast milk." Little late for that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Fact: Jellyfish and lobsters are considered biologically immortal - They don’t age and will never die unless they are killed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WhatTheFFacts: Shaq is a pro investor. He owns 17 Auntie Anne's Pretzel restaurants, 150 car washes, 155 Five Guys restaurants and 40 2…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GlobalBC: Chinese buyers are leaving Vancouver real estate and turning their attention to #Toronto and #Seattle. #VanRe https://t.co/8o…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Houston. We've got a problem. From the surgery a couple of weeks ago. Something just burst. I'm ok. Just feeling temporarily awkward.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mondinion: Good job @BenKielb, you are 90 on #MondREACA the Canada leaderboard of real estate agents. https://t.co/9m2vUdUP0x #MondREA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My nephews first day of school.   Think he looks ready? https://t.co/kSmntSsgbQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CBCVancouver: New tax of up to 2% aimed at secondary properties left empty year round is expected to generate $2M/year in revenue https…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@Fact: Kakakku kata kuku kaki kiriku kaku - ku kikis kuku kaki kiriku. is the toughest tongue twister in Malay." Go figure.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does the moon move?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My diet isn't the best however there's way worse. #diesel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@BrentToderian: What's with the fireworks that were just happening in downtown #Vancouver? What's the occasion?" Ya. What's up with that?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ScanBC: #Burnaby #RCMP are responding to Hastings &amp; Gilmore for reports of a male fighting a Hydro Pole.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Quote_Soup: Deal with the world the way it is, not the way you wish it was. - John Chambers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @VancouverSun: Vancouver housing market set to enter a correction with prices falling at least 10%: National Bank #realestate  https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@Fact: 1% of people are addicted to exercise." I am NOT one of them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Fact: Never argue with an idiot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Paul_Vigano UBC.   The Bulldogs. The Cup or bust.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making pulled pork from scratch. Cooking it overnight.  Things happen when you're sleepin'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WTFFacts: Dreamt is the only English word that ends in the letters "mt."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had my first beer league game of the season. We won 5-1.  No points for the kid.  That's ok. And don't worry - I'll keep you all informed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kingsthings: Why can't I remember my dreams?…
#itsmy2cents]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FactsEmpire: You must have all ten toes to enlist in the army.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't believe 9/11 was 15 years ago.   Time flies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9:11 on 9/11. https://t.co/pFIStFyaT8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Fact: Sweet potato ranks Number One in nutrition of all vegetables.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@HuffPostCanada: One-third of Kyrgyzstan’s marriages are non-consensual https://t.co/JR50C1TtuL https://t.co/pX3qUaOoiY"  Rough start.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CTVNews: Reagan shooter John Hinckley Jr. released from DC mental hospital https://t.co/jM4uRIXjEO https://t.co/kAjxQMCVlJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@FascinatingVids: Male seahorses are the ones that give birth to their young https://t.co/fZC85LBx2G"  Interesting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@Fact: Breathing the air in Beijing has the same health risks as smoking 21 cigarettes a day." Lovely.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Amazing_Maps: Nordic Cross Flags of Northern Europe https://t.co/r6dww6Sg1s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BiIIMurray: Who decided that we should sit together in groups while we chew food?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[USA, USA, USA... https://t.co/AfI9P0gODG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beer league game update.  Up 3-1, then down 4-3, then came back and won 5-4. We are 4-1 after 5 games. #TheShow #BecauseItsTheCup]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@NEWS1130: BREAKING: Wind warning is ended for Metro Vancouver #BCStorm : https://t.co/WrmDPBmQip"  That was the tail end of a typhoon?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heading out in the #BCStorm to go play beer league hockey. #TeamPlaya #brave #fearless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fur protesters are back at it.  And now they have duck calling whistles.  All during the #BCstorm.  Clowns. https://t.co/4CU1emY1x4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @_matt_hammer: That awkward battle for arm rests when you have the middle seat on the plane. 

#travelproblems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why did Hillary delete 33,000 emails after being subpoena'd?   I would kinda like an answer to that one.   What was she hiding?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@GlobalBC: Drinking and starving is the new trend among Canadian undergrads. https://t.co/LzwCCu6GVe" So glad that I'm an overgrad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@NEWS1130: Samsung Note 7 recall to cost at least $5.3 billion
https://t.co/Wau9vRzq1V" Still lovin' my BlackBerry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I put together a land assembly tonight.  4 houses in a row.   Already have the Buyer.   This is the next level of real estate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The calm before the storm. Literally.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Fact: If you replace the "W" in "where" "what" and "when" with "T" you get answers to the questions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@Fact: People tend to confuse being mean with being honest."  Agreed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DavidValente: CMHC data shows foreign buyers have almost disappeared from Vancouver market. #RealEstate #Vancouver #Homes #Realtor http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was just 10:10 on 10/10.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turkey coma.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dailyzen: Karma is simply the fact that your actions ripple out and have endless repercussions. https://t.co/LRIs8NnzL8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@WhatTheFFacts: In French, a walkie-talkie is called a talkie-walkie." Everything is backwards there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@WhatTheFFacts: Alaska was sold to the United States for about 2 cents an acre." Too expensive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[12:12]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @garybizzo: #BizQuote - Early to bed and early to rise probably indicates unskilled labor. – John Ciardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GlobalBC: A wind warning has been issued for Metro Vancouver as over 40,000 are without power. #BCStorm https://t.co/wRSbFznDmB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mondinion: Well done @BenKielb, you are 81 on #MondREACA the Canada toplist of real estate agents. https://t.co/9m2vUdUP0x #MondREA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@Fact: Is Your Cat Depressed? 9 Signs... https://t.co/E7kPjTAStA"  I'll be honest with you...I'm not a big fan of cats....at all.   Period.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you @BlueJays for relieving stress tonight.   By doing that you will be creating a whole lot more stress in the coming days. Good luck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who wants to be a hero?  #Jays]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[11:11]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WhatTheFFacts: Mexico's official name is the United Mexican States.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CKNW: Data to be released today expected to show plunging #VanRE sales due to foreign buyers' tax https://t.co/GYxEaXBoTv https://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @VancouverRentIt: Judge orders Vancouver strata to impose $16 million levy to repair leaky condo problems https://t.co/UrzH9CNraG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Fact: Karma has no menu. You get served what you deserve.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On this day in 1994  I moved here from Toronto.   Happy Moving Anniversary to me.   #Oct2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beer League game result. We won our 4th game. 3 and 1 now. First place.   #ItsEarly]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@ScanBC: #Delta crews are on scene with a Cessna that crashed at the end of the runway at Bounday Bay Airport. #CZBB" Rough start. #PullUp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Fact: Albert Einstein didn’t speak in full sentences until the age of 9.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Fact: When Ashton Kutcher was 13 he almost committed suicide by jumping off a hospital balcony so he could donate his heart to his dyin…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Fact: In Chinese writing, there is no capital letter, there are no spaces between characters, and characters have 10 strokes, on averag…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Signed up a new listing tonight. 1600 sq ft 1/2 duplex in Kits north of 4th.  In the quiet part. 3100 block. Shows well.  2.298M. Call me!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Horses in the bike lane.   Is that a violation?   #YaletownProblems https://t.co/djWKrl3LSM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Quote_Soup: You don't have to have it all figured out to move forward.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@Horocasts: #Scorpio can't deal with someone that never show up on time or make promises they can't keep." I have to agree on this one.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@Lifeldeas: I can officially say that  are definitely an Extremist. https://t.co/nmyHMw7I1N" That doesn't look too hard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big shout out to @klondike_silver on being the newly elected Premier of the Yukon.   Great guy. He will not disappoint.  Congratulations!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JustinTrudeau: Congrats @klondike_silver - next Premier of Yukon! My thanks to @PremierPasloski for his many years of service: https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The supposed super moon. #DoesntSeemThatSuperToMe https://t.co/ARgB8Yyhov]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cbcnewsbc: Canadian golfer Dawn Coe-Jones has died. 
The 3-time LPGA winner was battling cancer.
https://t.co/YCffEJAbtd https://t.co/w…]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>