<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The 7 ages of a woman are the right one and 6 wild guesses!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only undertake what you can do in an excellent fashion. There are no prizes for average performance.- Brian Tracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Tips from Web Building Experts  http://t.co/7EwcBoLcvV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Different Types of Beer  http://t.co/mC0W9DgDW4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your body is the baggage you must carry through life. The more excess the baggage, the shorter the trip. - Arnold H. Glasgow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're really getting old when your work is less fun and your fun is more work]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snow and adolescence are about the only things that disappear if you ignore them long enough]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's hard to win a pennant, but it's harder losing one. - Chuck Tanner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just in time for winter - Touch Screen Texting Gloves  - http://t.co/kZoBPJKWJf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool man a Switch Blade Pocket Comb - look tough!  http://t.co/RjiPB8ISdZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Find Gluten Free Recipes  http://t.co/PVt0xtT2mo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like my money right where I can see it -- hanging in my closet. - Carrie Bradshaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft MiniGame QuakeCraft: Victory was in Sight!!!!! http://t.co/VJLN9JaQlU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your culture is your brand.  Tony Hseih CEO, Zappos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Running SUCKS! How to Run for Fast Weight Loss - For Busy Women Who HATE Running --&gt; http://t.co/VCoJFrBgc0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Mott the Hoople  http://t.co/84m2CFwuMr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You gotta love that - an aquarium coffee table!  Drink with the fishes! http://t.co/ziFLpRwc9R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Who  http://t.co/A8GivQQDlQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Heineken International  http://t.co/3hh1ffEhEU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True friends are like diamonds - bright, beautiful, valuable, and always in style. --&gt; Nicole Richie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The main part of intellectual education is not the acquisition of facts but learning how to make facts live." - Oliver Wendell Holmes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ginger Rogers did everything Fred Astaire did, backwards and on high heels - Faith Whittlesey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I may be dumb, but I'm not stupid.  Terry Bradshaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of James Brown  http://t.co/KkwOT6ze69]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know kung fu. - Neo, The Matrix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fantasy is the impossible made probable. Science fiction is the improbable made possible.  - Rod Serling, creator of The Twilight Zone]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NASA Unveils a Very Cool New Space Suit  http://t.co/V3AAJ6DnBw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WOW - Very Cool A Sticky Note Wrist Watch! http://t.co/iDdmUfnTeb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The task of the modern educator is not to cut down jungles, but to irrigate deserts. - C. S. Lewis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Simple Way to Bond with Kids? Use Cooking!  http://t.co/RcLqjnhZE6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of LA Gear  http://t.co/dc7HCOwICY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Clarence Carter  http://t.co/7lM8zWR9dH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awww How Adorable! A Smile Star Design - Color Changing - LED Light Toss Pillow! http://t.co/OYlJKyCekL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If a lot of people said what they think, they would be speechless]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read about the Emerging Threats From An Electromagnetic Pulse Attack  http://t.co/OLfNYiAKlr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing worthwhile comes easily. Work, continuous work and hard work, is the only way to accomplish results that last. - Hamilton Holt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Design is a constant challenge to balance comfort with luxe, the practical with the desirable. - Donna Karan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Temptations  http://t.co/gCpt5FI9QK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All men are born free and equal, but most of them get married.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boys are Whatever, Shoes are Forever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Leon, Mexico - Shoe Capital of the World!  http://t.co/J2xvT9NsaW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your chances of winning, I've got to believe are really, really small when you score one run in 18 innings. - Clint Hurdle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Monopoly Money Extra Long Tie - Fun! http://t.co/8TPgVVEQru]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It wasnt a mission to be a rock star. It wasnt a mission of mine to even be a movie star. I just intended to be a good actor. - Don Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He who laughs last, didn't get it!!  :P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I was president of the good old U.S.A., I'd turn the churches into strip clubs and watch the whole world pray.  Kid Rock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get a Minecraft Enderman! http://t.co/NxF34C7oec]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotta love the Beverly Hillbillies - Get the collection!  http://t.co/Y8duUAJjWc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is the best deodorant. - Elizabeth Taylor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To confine our attention to terrestrial matters would be to limit the human spirit. - Stephen Hawking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read How to Use LinkedIn for Your Company   http://t.co/WZRsboQqGK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making the Most of Twitter for Your Business  http://t.co/so6c33d4ZM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lend your friend $20, if he doesn't pay you back then he's not your friend. Money well spent - Ted Nicolas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't call me a mindless philosopher, you overweight blob of grease! - C3PO, Star Wars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of Armies of Magic – Facebook Game  http://t.co/Z9vDH8A9GU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really wish I had invented the flipflop. I love flipflops. Its the one style of shoe I would be so proud of inventing. Christian Louboutin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One thing you get for more of your money these days is bills.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How To Grow Your Business With Twitter  http://t.co/dOV7Cj8bt3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If traffic gets any worse you'll need an appointment to make a left-hand turn.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Carlos Santana  http://t.co/1lAKEhu9P6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As far as cheating goes, they'll never stop it. The only way it can be done successfully, only one person can know about it. - Smokey Yunick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women need food, water, and compliments.  That's right.  And an occasional pair of shoes. Chris Rock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wouldn't feel right wearing clothes covering my body.  Christina Aguilera]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Ral Donner  http://t.co/ZE2RCrnrgM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's hard to shake hands  with a clenched fist!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft House Showcase: Touring the Winning House  http://t.co/GZKu7D5r4K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The one thing my mom will let me get is a nice shoe sometimes. - Chloe Moretz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good teachers are those who know how little they know. Bad teachers are those who think they know more than they don't know. - R. Verdi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never wear the same shoe twice. - Dion Sanders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only thing that ever sat its way to success was a hen. - Sarah Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Do Parents Pick Favorite Things for their Kids?  http://t.co/TnAJJ9bxEQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is tool cool a LED Kitchen Sink Faucet Sprayer Nozzle - make the water turn blue!  http://t.co/oYFCVBLW9e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is what happens to you when you're busy making other plans - John Lennon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One person with courage makes a majority. - Andrew Jackson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Heineken International  http://t.co/3hh1ffEhEU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You could get rich manufacturing crutches for lame excuses.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool just found these 25 Original Unopened Packs of Vintage Baseball Cards (80s-90s) - can find some value in there!  http://t.co/huU0UwsP0o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Hire a Strategy Consulting Firm?  http://t.co/ww1h1YILjt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Dallas, Texas  http://t.co/WxGaWwhqt2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You miss 100% of the shots you never take. - Wayne Gretzky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Introduction to Steak 'n Shake  http://t.co/LSbsqwsD2G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Strategy Consulting Firms to Avoid  http://t.co/85nlwAE19G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clarity trumps persuasion.  Dr. Flint McGlaughlin - Director MECLABS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it's too close to bother to buckle your seat belt it's close enough to walk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious Cat Scratch Rapper Music Mixer - Awesome!  http://t.co/b6jreJtdlC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ginger Rogers did everything Fred Astaire did, backwards and on high heels - Faith Whittlesey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lassie is an American TV classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/2opL4uwF5A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Use Twitter in Business  http://t.co/3rudC9DKsC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Youth is when we want to set the world on fire... Middle age is when we hope our children won't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bird does not sing because it has an answer...  It sings because it has a song. - Chinese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fall seven times, stand up eight. - Japanese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a rock 'n' roll thing to have one-night stands. - Rick Springfield]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the Major Work Shoe Brands  http://t.co/B0clQz78YQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Hilarious 60s Comedy – Get Smart  http://t.co/82TW4PLqfU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think about it... Mistakes are just small steps to perfection...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To succeed --  You need to find something to hold on to, something to motivate you, something to inspire you. - Tony Dorsett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Attitude: It is our best friend or our worst enemy. - John C. Maxwell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Useful Products to Help Housebreak Your Pet  http://t.co/jCs1jqer2y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Plano Texas is an up and coming area of Dallas - read more here!  http://t.co/8EIf8aGkVN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's later than we think and most of us aren't even thinking]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>