<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Read an Introduction to Whataburger  http://t.co/Ba5AkQaUVG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On of life's little ironies is the fact that when you finally master a tough job, you make it look easy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is a thousand times better to have common sense without education than to have education without common sense. - Robert Green Ingersoll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet!  A 3D Printer - Very Awesome!  You have to check this out! http://t.co/d61ywVWD9f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Motown, Motown, that's my era. Those are my people.  Hillary Clinton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Air Supply  http://t.co/zJMi68Jso0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is what we are, and football is what we have become. - Mary McGrory]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About GPS Technology and Fitness Watches  http://t.co/TqeP9PjyS1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Overview of Major Web Conferencing Services  http://t.co/mqIzmGWWxP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Allman Brothers Band  http://t.co/CIdvw5HAz0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Scientific Explorer's Mind Blowing Science Kit! http://t.co/0c2ZSw6gfi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Pat Benatar  http://t.co/B43fx9KxZ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Mountain Climbing from Novice to Experts  http://t.co/aNNJVHVXPe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Twilight Zone is a scifi TV classic - read its fascinating history here - http://t.co/AH2NTTP42s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Hire a Strategy Consulting Firm?  http://t.co/ehbEFO4dzS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Barbara Acklin - The Popular Singer  http://t.co/lKwYERHOS1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the star wars lover in your family - Jedi Dressing Gowns - May the force be with you!  http://t.co/csmppLfgMB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you find yourself in a hole, stop digging. - Will Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If science fiction is the mythology of modern technology, then its myth is tragic. - Ursula K. Le Guin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Little Feat  http://t.co/YJbDrRj42f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Mott the Hoople  http://t.co/mYLVetD6zX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The sky is no longer the limit. - Richard M. Nixon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Everly Brothers  http://t.co/z1NMx3ZaJi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Lesley Gore  http://t.co/rdzWHpB7ae]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd make a wonderful Lady Macbeth. I'll wear a pair of platform shoes or something - Bette Midler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always wear expensive shoes. People notice. - Brian Koslow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be not afraid of growing slowly, be afraid only of standing still. - Chinese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame: Capture the Flag  http://t.co/SAJBnNzR8H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you chase two rabbits, both will escape. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Steve Miller Band  http://t.co/kI3KNXHlEL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am the legal guardian over a massive shoe collection. - Linda Dominique Grosvenor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the hot new Minecraft Youtube channel Crimson Mine - https://t.co/t5ZM2oMaYB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Who is The Grass Roots Classic Rock Group?  http://t.co/YqwT8nm7HY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To know when you have enough is to be rich]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Mets have found ways of losing that I never knew existed. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And in the end, the love we take will be equal to the love we make. - The Beatles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Importance of Competitive Analysis of Strategy Consulting Firms  http://t.co/KdzRiqfYqj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Jackson Five  http://t.co/GC1tcqTbDT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Spinners  http://t.co/R3aZVoHpDi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Damita Jo  http://t.co/zJ2tyNA9P6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I'm not back in five minutes, just wait longer. - Ace Ventura, Ace ventura, Pet Detective]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Fitness Apps – Is There One That Is the Best?  http://t.co/2KFn2TOeTc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The person who doesn't know where his next dollar is coming from usually doesn't know where his last dollar went.  Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Very Fun and Geeky 8-Bit Tie!  http://t.co/v3VDbTf8Uv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best way to show appreciation for a favor is to enjoy it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know money is the root of all evil if you would like to find out more - just send me $10 - DM me ASAP !!  :&gt;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Five card stud, nothing wild. And the sky's the limit - Captain Jean Luc Picard - Last Line of Star Trek the Next Generation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Jay Ferguson  http://t.co/1huoyF61WQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was a pretty good coach and working with marketing was like coaching. - Bernard Ebbers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money was never a big motivation for me, except as a way to keep score. The real excitement is playing the game. - Donald Trump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes I can't figure designers out. It's as if they flunked human anatomy. --&gt; Erma Bombeck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's better to have fewer things of quality than too much expendable junk. - Rachel Zoe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Natalie Cole  http://t.co/6iPIcIPEef]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome basketball t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the basketball lovers in your life!   http://t.co/4G2EwcZxx7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahh Read About Loving Fine Wine  http://t.co/6g3WD0fBho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He was born with a silver spoon --  but  never made a stir with it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Little Feat  http://t.co/gOUZ5C8zjd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space Invaders Taito Astronaut Video Game T-Shirt Tee  http://t.co/TEtz9vQo7U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About the Hallmarks of a Quality Insurance Company  http://t.co/AxZ2LdimI6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Yanjing Beer  http://t.co/DGiyeA2aTa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So say we all. - Battlestar Galactica]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips for Effective Use of LinkedIn for Your Company  http://t.co/WxJXiL3eQ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One person with courage makes a majority. - Andrew Jackson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Daddy: Mommy just backed the car over my bicycle! "I told you not to leave it in the living room!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Corona Beer  http://t.co/9HaMefzPyU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool All Wood Watch! http://t.co/7n03vjT6Tn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very very cool SpyHawk RC Plane with 3.5 inch LCD Monitor/Controller &amp; video recording &amp; auto-pilot system - HOT - http://t.co/kuaSqnEEui]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Eating Gluten Free  http://t.co/saf9i9ETFd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's only during an eclipse that the Man in the Moon has a place in the sun. Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If at first you don't succeed; call it version 1.0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Europe – Best Places to Tour  http://t.co/9eVTqqkqvd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Driving a car is like playing baseball. The object in both is to get home safely. - Joe Moore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Marvin Gaye  http://t.co/AteNzLFEpu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He was born with a silver spoon --  but  never made a stir with it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where everything is possible miracles become common place, but the familiar ceases to be self-evident. - Eric Hoffer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of that Odd Olympic Sport – Curling  http://t.co/ykFjnpNeUE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Elvis Presley    http://t.co/htA8D9tzsm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's the most fun I have ever had and. also the biggest pain in the ass I have ever experienced. Brad Pitt, on fatherhood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guys - combine your wallet and smart phone in one compact case - and its cool and stylish - Book Book http://t.co/c0qsQ61Nqw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blow off some steam, or rather, shoot some smoke rings. The Zero Fog Blaster is a ray gun - totally cool!  http://t.co/oF3wPMGzH6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bright light! Bright light! - Gremlins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And now, I'm just trying to change the world, one sequin at a time. Lady Gaga]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To the uneducated, an A is just three sticks. - A. A. Milne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He who begins many things finishes but few - German Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Air Supply  http://t.co/665wp1CzV5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Michael Jordan Shoes  http://t.co/1er5yY9Hdm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You only have to do a very few things right in your life so long as you don't do too many things wrong. - Warren Buffett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Bread  http://t.co/OgunCU9BSs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making money is not gonna change anything about what I am, except I won't answer the door. Abel Ferrara]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pair off in threes. - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Mountain Biking – A Real Adventure  http://t.co/9lsDxRvYG0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not wait to strike until the iron is hot; but make it hot by striking - William B. Sprague]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I looked and looked but I didn't see God. - Yuri Gagarin, 14 April 1961]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 10 - Support Group Meeting  http://t.co/GcRLCyGf53]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sex and the City changed New York - New York's become a big shoe store now, unfortunately. -  Chris Noth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One deer to another:  "I wish I had his doe"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome burgers &amp; beer t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the burgers &amp; beer lovers in your life!  http://t.co/cxaPQix7Uw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I mean, we're lost on an island, running from boars and monsters -- freakin' polar bears.  Hurley, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 15 - The Cowden Protocol  http://t.co/ttsb5jIs2W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A professor is one who talks in someone else's sleep. - Anonymous]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>