<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @distractedfilm: Martin Scorsese and Joe Strummer on the set of The King of Comedy. https://t.co/4oVjbgFg8L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @brainpicker: Advice from @neilhimself on finding your voice as a writer: "You write—you write lots and lots of stuff, and eventually yo…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: The fall of the Berlin Wall, 26 years ago. November 9, 1989. https://t.co/9MWxaLpSTn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: @HistoryInPics Early 1930s Hollywood is commonly referred to as "Pre-Code," before studios self-policed themselves. http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: Marlon Brando in 'A Streetcar Named Desire,' 1951. https://t.co/e960Yhi6Qn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MYSADCAT: My cat is sad because my other cat thinks he is an amazing artist and won't stop gloating about it. https://t.co/fPvHjCwC0s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CDHill9: When the funniest thing on your comedy  program is the musical acts headgear you know you have a problem. #SNL #TrumpTrainSNL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MYSADCAT: My cat is sad because he is pondering the transient nature of time, forever accelerating until we reach the abyss. https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ubermichael Okay, you qualify.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ubermichael Let's hear your "Get off my lawn!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HeerJeet: Best thing ever written on SNL? Frank Rich's essay on the snobbery of the show's humor: https://t.co/0z7dKEyw5K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Ghostbusters" is the most USAnian movie ever made: https://t.co/Yjgj95dHja.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Movie-makers do not need (and are actively harmed by) people like Rachael Prior, who create "The Gap": https://t.co/bUOj6KdQ0L.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nooMcinaP @TrixieCanuck @ItsAdamCanuck It's the kids! Filthy little germ vectors!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MYSADCAT: My cat is sad because my other cats are having a party &amp; he is standing nervously at the margins, unsure what to do. https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MYSADCAT: My cat is sad because he switched the stickers when nobody was looking and now he must live with a lie. https://t.co/n3MYhEGF…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cinemaquanon: Blowup
(1966, Michelangelo Antonioni) https://t.co/pCnuLz4XPw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ORachaelO Have you seen this article? Might be relevant. https://t.co/3JcIWXeuUq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Kurt_Vonnegut: Comedians and jazz musicians are more comforting to me than preachers or politicians or philosophers or poets or painter…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Julian Fellowes is a big weenie. https://t.co/XbqFCzsG27]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LifeCheating: https://t.co/GoJODmAkcT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@michaeljnelson At least they kept his trademark move of waving guns around at every opportunity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: James Dean examines some vinyls. https://t.co/GYL2juiFYx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsAdamCanuck Where? Oh ... you mean the movie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JeremyDyson: I’m delighted that @Scammerhead is starting to get some recognition: https://t.co/qiC9y2zSpT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: Michelle Pfeiffer, 1980. https://t.co/oWCOVtouEl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@wilw It's all about Starbase, no Tribbles!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @alex_macdonald: I will fight to support the Oxford comma until I draw my last breath. http://t.co/Y0T6c3F4iI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kjstrasser: "Plans are only good intentions unless they immediately degenerate into hard work."
#PeterDrucker

#quote #success https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @bobyperu: Fellini directs "Giulietta degli spiriti" in 14m video, via Cinephilia &amp; Beyond https://t.co/1VWHSoChtG https://t.co/l9f8YTGq…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ubermichael No, "striker" is a term from soccer. I'm down with the different sportsball games! How about that local team or individual?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey movie-makers! How often, alas, have you had this conversation? https://t.co/WCaP1gHhPI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ubermichael Bats! No, not you; that's what the cricket instruments are called.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WorstMuse: It's finally an election year! Don't you think it's about time you started that heavy-handed political allegory?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cox_tom: Been to pub. Saw cat at pub, flirting with people. Thought "That looks like my cat." Went over. Checked. Was my cat. http://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: Marlon Brando, 1948. Photograph by Serge Balkin. https://t.co/LoVviwlwNK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JMDeMatteis: An amazing website for Beatles obsessives (not casual fans):  https://t.co/CGksCCsNdE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MysteryIndie @briankoppelman John Badham directed "Saturday Night Fever". Sylvester Stallone directed "Staying Alive". Signed, A/R Guy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool! Convert your floor dolly into a track dolly: https://t.co/O79m3VB3Fs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: Party girls, Paris 1966. https://t.co/FrLhvtNj0n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First one to say 'I'll be in my bunk," gets a pie in the face. https://t.co/DcSszVX4J6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: Marilyn Monroe singing 'Happy Birthday, Mr. President', 1962. Photograph by Bill Ray. https://t.co/vxC260sqoo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @playwrightnow: There's a thrill to seeing a protagonist put in an impossible position that's almost as great as seeing her get out of i…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Tis the season to watch "Star Wars". No, no the new movie; the 1978 Christmas special. Enjoy! https://t.co/ZddSxbrh0P. (Eh, @ItsAdamCanuck)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CampbellGord I like to end controversial statements with, "Of course, that's just your opinion."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey indie movie-makers! "Are DVDs Worth It For DIY Film Distribution?" https://t.co/1Rquo1RUw4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsAdamCanuck In a bank? "Star Wars", eh? I think I've read about that. If only they'd advertised it more, they might have made real money.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Criterion: Happy weekend, everybody!  @WhitStillman's METROPOLITAN (1990): https://t.co/SFQBwctYN1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AmericanFilm: Before #TheForceAwakens, look back at our 1977 interview with George Lucas on STAR WARS: https://t.co/Jlsfx6fhPq https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsAdamCanuck Were they telling people to "Live long and prosper"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: Carrie Fisher, age 19, 1975. https://t.co/y2l98vW8KC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LaFamiliaFilm: A rare photo of Stanley #Kubrick on the set of BARRY LYNDON (still photographer: Keith Hamshere). https://t.co/pj0ZWjSjnF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BanjoHfuhruhur: Alan Bennett, Peter Cook, Dudley Moore Jonathan Miller 'Beyond the Fringe' at the BBC. https://t.co/NRqodopFMt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @colebrax: Director Bob Fosse dancing with Jessica Lange at Studio 54. https://t.co/NiEgG7lGND]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TATJANASL: Sam Peckinpah and crew in Mexico filming 'Bring Me The Head of Alfredo Garcia' (1974) https://t.co/FgazpTjSLB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ghweldon: Barbie got a TARDIS.

BARBIE GOT A TARDIS YO https://t.co/SZPQNaUgRw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ColleenDoran: Chicks Making Comics: it's not about getting a piece of the pie, it's about making your own pie. I made my own pie. I did…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: Reservoir Dogs, 1992. https://t.co/SjNYlHzRx1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BrentSpiner: Seems like yesterday. https://t.co/fMnSU7x8Um]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ReneeStephen @ubermichael I've often said it: Your brain is out to get you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cox_tom: The best part of a visit to my local otter sanctuary is when the otters stand solemnly for their national anthems. http://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It'll be okay, man." https://t.co/SwQSV9o5xg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @saladinahmed: "Happy Hanukkah from the Kirby family." (1976) https://t.co/2lVUyreoGm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @realtorsuzanneo: Holly Woodlawn, One Of Warhol's Greatest Superstars, Has Died https://t.co/uK4pNJqQQJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Context is important. It makes the difference between sweetly romantic and downright creepy. https://t.co/czx3ibDDem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: Marilyn Monroe photographed by Sam Shaw, 1957. https://t.co/mwaKfDWUAb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson And Patsy Walker lasted over 20 years in her own comic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MeanwhileinCana: My letter to Santa.
#MeanwhileinCanada https://t.co/ngbT2OFN1g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SallyPoulsen: Seriously, Netflix, please never fix this. https://t.co/B3Hx8XNhO1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FilmHistoryPics: Stanley #Kubrick directs Sterling Hayden in Dr. Strangelove, 1964. (Kubrick estate). Watch: https://t.co/YfIFtm06Bf ht…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LaFamiliaFilm: Just WOW. Original vintage six-sheet film poster of Alfred Hitchcock's TO CATCH A THIEF. https://t.co/fVLpcJDsU6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StacieBee Wow! Now you're done for the month.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mistressmatisse: You can talk about how sexist and bad the porn industry is, but they moved faster on the James Deen issue than Hollywo…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StacieBee I think your stomach has hacked your account, and it posting as you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Criterion: "It actually changes the movie." What we found when restoring DONT LOOK BACK's audio: https://t.co/ylcCef6D04 https://t.co/I…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dammit! '6 Depressing Realities Of Writing Young Adult Fiction": https://t.co/hIooyShGNY.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wanna watch a 13-year-old Russian girl sing the Diva's song from "The Fifth Element"? Sure you do! https://t.co/CngujKOIKD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any writer -- or literate English speaker -- should not get these wrong: https://t.co/jerQR6ekos.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Problem with low-res Web images: it's hard to find the "Nina"s. https://t.co/X83VOcsYMC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @asherxai: 1. "Diane Keaton &amp; Woody Allen in Annie Hall" by Al Hirschfeld.

2. "Annie Hall" (1977) by Woody Allen.

@colebrax https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TATJANASL: Michelangelo #Antonioni directs #JackNicholson and Maria Schneider on the set of 'The Passenger' (1975) https://t.co/bueJYgz…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Too bad that, legally, he has no say in the matter. https://t.co/dWd7gydYcS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @davidehrlich: if JJ Abrams just said “no Star Wars until we have competent gun control”, america’s nerds would un-fuck this country by …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MYSADCAT: My cat is sad because he arranged to play Twister with several other cats today but every one of them cancelled. https://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LaFamiliaFilm: ICYMI: Our massive post on Mike Nichols’ WHO’S AFRAID OF VIRGINIA WOOLF https://t.co/TJqEOHwkA7 https://t.co/qsCks8J0vh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @playwrightnow: Weaponize your exposition. You need to find a way to turn information about one character into an assault on them by ano…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: Marilyn Monroe, 1953. Photograph by Alfred Eisenstaedt. https://t.co/UfrGvP9UhC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FilmHistoryPics: Brian De Palma &amp; DP Stephen H. Burum while shooting BODY DOUBLE (photo by Ralph Nelson). https://t.co/nZRF1LEV50]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @IanBoothby: "Genius is one percent inspiration, ninety nine percent perspiration." - Edison
"Take a bath stinko!" - Edison's coworkers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: Cigarettes being promoted as being good for health in the early 1950s. https://t.co/Zatt9m5YnM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: Bob Dylan, New York, 1965. Photograph by Richard Avedon. https://t.co/MNRFjR9au4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsAdamCanuck It'll be okay. "And then along came Jones!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FilmHistoryPics: “You exist only in what you do.” Federico Fellini. https://t.co/2tFlZJJaGG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've decided to capitalize on my terrible sense of humour: I'm writing a theatrical script about puns. It's a play on words.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey movie-makers! Don'tcha hate it when people ask, "But how do you make a living?" Now you can answer! https://t.co/YGeMkJ5l2A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson That was just a cheap joke, but serially folks -- is it online? Some of what I do is educational, so I'm interested.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson The first two are cool, but is that last one a job or "No, really, Mom, we're just friends -- we were just watching TV."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @takecareofUUU: Now's the time to get started. No more procrastination. This is your time to shine. U Can &amp; Will Succeed.#TA https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ProfBrianCox Alas, I know that what you mean by that is that they looked at you and said, "Yep, that's Brian."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsAdamCanuck "Take me take me take me now!"]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>