<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA["Accidents happen. People you love will die. Nothing you treasure will last forever. And I need to accept and embrace that fact."
- Rant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["This is your life and it's ending one moment at a time."
- Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You cannot be the person they know and the great, glorious person you want to become. Not at the same time."
- Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I'm in love. So kill me."
- Lullaby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I may be me--but at least I have the good sense not to be YOU."
- Damned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Invisible Monsters Quote.
#ChuckPalahniuk http://t.co/wGdOHFZXvb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["On a night without moon or stars you can't see a thing, but you can imagine anything." 
- Survivor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I am an invisible monster, and I am incapable of loving anybody. You don't know which is worse."
- Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @xDisappearHerex: The best way to remember how Chuck's name is pronounced is what kids in high school used to chant to taunt him:
"Paula…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To everybody, everybody else is a liar."
- Rant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What kind of dining set defines me as a person?"
- Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The only reason why we ask other people how their weekend was is so we can tell them about our own weekend."
- Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Just keep asking yourself: What would Jesus NOT do?"
- Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I am free to revise my story, to reinvent myself, my world, at any given moment."
- Damned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Everyone smiles with that invisible gun to their head."
- Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I might be a touch of a sadist and a little bit jejune... but at least I'm not a victim, not any longer."
- Damned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If we can leave all of our stories behind. Our being villains or victims. Only then can we maybe rescue the world.” http://t.co/wxXPobznib]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["No matter how much you love someone, you still want to have your own way."
- Lullaby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Amphetamines are the most American drug. You get so much done. You look terrific, and your middle name is Accomplishment."
- Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Everything you do is a self-portrait."
- Diary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Those worst parts of your life, those moments you can't talk about, they rot you from the inside out."
- Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Every person is obsessed with himself. You are your own favorite hobby."
- Rant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who's excited about the Fight Club sequel? http://t.co/g5lmkdKgPQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“You are not special. You're not a beautiful and unique snowflake. You're the same decaying organic matter as everything else."
- Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chuckpalahniuk: There will be a sequel to FIGHT CLUB (the novel) in graphic novel form. Details here - http://t.co/WPPZkCtHEs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chuckpalahniuk: Ready for some big news with this next Tweet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @_GeeFam: "You're about as free to act as a programmed computer, as one-of-a-kind as a dollar bill." (cc: @PalahniukQuote )  #invisiblem…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Future scientists will call it the Pollyanna Syndrome. I'd say mine has been a way-long case history of chasing rainbows."
- Damned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To some of us, the nights are too long. To some, the days."
- Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @xDisappearHerex: "Next year's book is going to be 'Fifty Shades Of Grey' squared, but with more anal. A lot more anal."
- Chuck Palahni…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Quit your job. Start a fight. Prove you're alive. If you don't claim your humanity you will become a statistic. You have been warned.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Get out of your apartment. Meet a member of the opposite sex. Stop the excessive shopping and masturbation."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["No matter how much you think you love somebody, you'll pull back when the pool of their blood edges up too close."
- Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["No one really gives a damn about books. No one has bothered to ban a book in decades.”
- Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Happiness is like a ticking bomb."
- Romance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You have a choice. Live or die. Every breath is a choice. Every time you don't throw yourself down the stairs, that's a choice."
-Survivor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Everything is important. Every detail. We just don't know why yet."
- Diary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My first time I jacked off, I thought I'd invented it. I looked down at my sloppy handful of junk and thought, This is going to make me rich]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For everyone confused, that was a fan-made Invisible Monsters movie poster. It was supposed to be made starring Jessica Biel but never was.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Birds ate my face.
#InvisibleMonsters http://t.co/ueczeLtpus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Advertising has us chasing cars and clothes. Working jobs we hate, so we can buy shit we dont need.”
- Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I would say any behavior that is not the status quo is interpreted as insanity... Insanity is sorta in the eye of the beholder."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I hate to advocate drugs, alcohol, violence, or insanity to anyone, but they've always worked for me.”
- Hunter S. Thompson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If there's any trick to doing a job you hate it's to find a job you hate even more."
- Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“The girl is infectious human waste, and she's confused and afraid to commit to the wrong thing and so she won't commit to anything.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LexWebsta: @PalahniukQuote I love reading your quotes, it keeps me up at night #thinking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The damaged love the damaged. Cyanide and sugar. Poison and antidote. Like maybe we balance each other out."
- Snuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Two lips and a tongue can promise you anything."
- Damned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In America, if your addiction isn't always new and improved, you're a failure."
- Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[" There are worse things you can do to the people you love than kill them. The regular way is just to watch the world do it."
- Lullaby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's easy to attack and destroy an act of creation. It's a lot more difficult to perform one."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["98.3 percent of lawyers end up in Hell."
- Damned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["This isn't about love as in caring. This is about property as in ownership."
- Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @xDisappearHerex: These are the Invisible Monsters shoes... http://t.co/9TllAdaBnr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["She's not wearing makeup so her face just looks like skin."
- Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Love_Darrien: "But me being dead, that opens up a whole world of possibility." @PalahniukQuote #InvisibleMonsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When did the future switch from being a promise to being a threat?"
- Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @xDisappearHerex: Cool points to anyone who can tell me which 3 @chuckpalahniuk books are missing from this collection... http://t.co/4e…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you keep waiting for someone perfect, then you'll never find love, because it's how much you love them that makes them perfect."
Romance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Something or someone lived or died so you could have this life. The mountain of the dead. They left you into the daylight."
- Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[" She'd wear shades of lipstick you'd expect to see around the base of a penis."
- Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[" He was the kind of boy any young girl should date while she's still able to recover."
- Rant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Reality means you live until you die... the real truth is nobody wants reality.”
- Survivor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Without just one nest
A bird can call the world home
Life is your career"
- Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["No matter how much you love someone, you still want to have your own way."
- Lullaby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Every woman is just a different kind of problem." 
- Choke http://t.co/pEaq7yuwmP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Your heart is my piñata."
- Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Hope is something really tough and tenacious you have to give up. It's an addiction to break."
- Damned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We can spend our lives letting the world tell us who we are. Sane or insane. Saints or sex addicts. Or we can decide for ourselves."
-Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Whatever the blessing, the talent, or technology, we can still find some way to fuck it up."
- Rant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I'm so tired of being me. Me beautiful. Me ugly. Me blonde. A million fucking fashion makeovers that only leave me trapped being me."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I'm now simplifying myself. Somewhere balanced in the perfect middle between happiness and sadness."
- Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Until you find something to fight for, you settle for something to fight against."
- Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Our purest form of joy comes when people we envy get hurt. That most genuine form of joy."
- Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The purpose of Hell is not so much to forget the details of our lives as it is to forgive them."
- Damned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We all have some proper noun to blame."
- Tell-All]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You're a different human being to everybody you meet."
- Rant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Since change is constant, you wonder if people crave death because it’s the only way they can get anything really finished."
- Survivor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What I want is to be needed. Who I need is somebody that will eat up all my free time, my ego, my attention. Somebody addicted to me."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["People fall so in love with their pain, they can’t leave it behind. The same as the stories they tell. We trap ourselves."
- Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What's sex and what's death--I can't tell the difference."
- Snuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You realize that there’s no point in doing anything if nobody’s watching."
- Survivor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We all die. The goal isn't to live forever, the goal is to create something that will."
- Diary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I wanted to breathe smoke."
#FightClub http://t.co/hcWyuracWG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I just don't want to die without any scars."
- Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["All God does is watch us and kill us when we get boring. We must never, ever be boring."
- Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I would say any behavior that is not the status quo is interpreted as insanity, when, in fact, it might actually be enlightenment."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The weather today is partly angry, leading to resignation and ultimatums."
- Diary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The only way to find true happiness is to risk being completely cut open."
- Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We've taken the world apart but we have no idea what to do with the pieces."
- Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Reject the basic assumptions of civilization, especially the importance of material possessions."
- Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We’d turn our lives into a terrible adventure. A true-life horror story with a happy ending. A trial we’d survive to talk about."
- Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Fathers. Mothers. With all their caring and attention. They will fuck you up, every time."
- Snuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["At this rate, we'll never get to the future."
- Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What we call chaos is just patterns we haven't recognized. What we call random is just patterns we can't decipher."
- Survivor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There are bodies buried everywhere, you just have to know where to look."
- Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["No one wants to admit we're addicted to music. No one's addicted to music and television and radio. We just need more of it."
- Lullaby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The universe is stuck and I'm the monkey wrench in God's gears."
- Craig Clevenger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“You know how both life and porno movies end. The only difference is life starts with the orgasm.”
- Survivor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["My life might be little and boring, but at least it’s mine--not some assembly-line, secondhand, hand-me-down life.”
- Rant]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>