<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @playwrightnow: Your play's not done until you can look at every role and think "there's something in there that an actor could have fun…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KenJennings: RIP theater designer who died in the middle of dictating this sign https://t.co/XzNGLtSsyD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blu-ray players are much more annoying and less consistent than DVD players.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: Andy Warhol, 1983. Photograph by Albert Watson. https://t.co/C41nfjWVBC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MYSADCAT: My cat is sad because my other cat's weed addiction causes him to waste whole days sleeping &amp; playing computer games https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Criterion: This week, watch films from David Lynch, René Clair, Mikhail Romm &amp; more for free on @hulu! https://t.co/55ropo5JZR https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevecavers Yeah, one mistake in a chain ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @Dell, your website is simply awful! Hard to navigate, hard to use, keeps timing out, logs me out when I'm actively using the site.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson "Okay then, what's your opinion on Sim?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KinoLorber: .@leonardmaltin on the 5-disc Buster Keaton shorts collection new from Kino Classics: https://t.co/219ijagiy7 https://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awards we don't need: https://t.co/auCF3na9rz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The special features on this disc of "The Dark Knight" are better than the movie. Cool how they blew up the hospital and flipped the truck.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NathanFillion: Wolverine is Canadian. You’re welcome. Happy Canada Day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @playwrightnow: Learning to plot is crazy difficult but not optional. Start by turning your events into dominoes. How could the first ca…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ubermichael No ... no ... But Ducky is a great performance by John Cryer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Canada Day! https://t.co/QAEDWPhiSN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MYSMUGCAT: My cat is smug because he gives passionate talks on poverty &amp; suffering, for which he is paid over a million pounds. https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @prof_elemental: Silly old football. It really is rubbish. I've never seen headlines that say: 
'DRUNKEN FANS CLASH WITH POLICE AT COMIC…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dcorsetto Never heard of you or "Girls With Slingshots". Thanks to @HopeLNicholson for the reTweet. Will check out the strip.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Filmkritter I researched this years ago, and actually got as far as drawing up plans. Cold in the winter, though, where you live!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Season 3 of "Agents of SHIELD" was so awful that it made me physically angry.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My ambition in two panels: https://t.co/bZUG5Ljc6H.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cox_tom: "I thought it was inspiration but it was just caffeine." - my epitaph]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Kurt_Vonnegut: Plato says that the unexamined life is not worth living. But what if the examined life turns out to be a clunker as well?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Filmkritter Seen him singing in Woody Allen's "Everyone Says I Love You"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anxiety reward stickers: https://t.co/YVlGKB3DK1.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @IntrovertDoodle: Seems legit, right? (See more at https://t.co/uQBLRxe2IS.) https://t.co/aUhajkiWP8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: The Hollywood sign was changed by a prankster in 1976, following the passage of the state's relaxed marijuana law. https…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CMF_FMC @Telefilm_Canada Telefilm is interested in the future of Canadian content?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How would Dave know? By his own admission he doesn't visit comics shops or read comics (except those sent to him). https://t.co/PkZy9W2yzV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MYSADCAT: My cat is sad because he arranged to go camping at the weekend, but his friends left without him. https://t.co/jJqNjX4tJT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @evanier: Congrats to HAMILTON, the musical for people of all races, all genders, all walks of life...as long as they can afford $850 fo…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone: Never, ever buy a "President's Chocice" brand coffee-maker! Its design is fundamentally flawed. Total crap! Damn you, @PresChoice!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @historylvrsclub: "Her nipples were about to come onto my plate. In my face you can see the fear" - Sophia Loren on Jayne Mansfield '… h…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: Trinity Site explosion, 0.016s after detonation. The very first detonation of an atomic bomb, July, 1945. https://t.co/f…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gad! "Agents of SHIELD" is dumb up one side, dumb across the top, and dumb down to the ground on the other side. It's D - U - M dumb.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disappointing to see John Cleese off on a right-wing Twitter rant. But the funniest man on the planet has always been a terrible person.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MattOswaltVA: today's been so lazy and uninspired Adam Sandler just bought the rights to it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@_Matty_H_ @evanjstern If your coffee tastes like mud, that's because it's fresh ground.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @_Matty_H_: I love coffee because it's so medieval. It's like, "to feel more alert, drink this muddy potion."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or get out of Hollywood. You wanna be a movie-maker? Forget pitching and learn project management. Fuck Hollywood! https://t.co/V1rUhzg3Di]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mightyjoanna That is all kinds of disturbing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mccrabb_will: Scuba DePalma confers with DP Vilmos Zsigmond while shooting BLOW OUT. https://t.co/jH4g2PCNBc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NathanFillion Hey, the whole world is your living room!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @FidoSolutions: An hour on the phone has yielded temporary satisfaction. I am not pleased with your company.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @Fidomobile, why are you stealing my $26.96 credit balance from me?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @alyankovic: Try not to be jealous of my Darth Vader playing an accordion balloon hat. https://t.co/EjaxfalPCv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cox_tom: The cat that my house deserves but not the one it needs right now. https://t.co/Fnv7H5sSdF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StacieBee How much older than Luke was Han supposed to be, anyhow?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson I can tell you're really Canadian, 'cause you got the lyrics to our national anthem wrong. That's Canadian patriotism!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson Try nodding yer head and grunting, maybe with a raised eyebrow and sudden eye contact, then looking away and frowning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey movie-makers! Want money to make your short movie? https://t.co/vglEWX76kO (See this, @ItsAdamCanuck?)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ubermichael I have faith in you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson What were they expecting from a title like that? Surely not a book about geeky girls and their loves which they keep secret.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LaFamiliaFilm: New Post: ‘The Parallax View’; Pakula's Unsettling Examination of the Post-Compliant America https://t.co/wn5UHy11HQ htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StacieBee As the man said, "Great, kid! Don't get cocky."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FidoSolutions Also, I couldn't find the Group ID login on your site; I had to find it with a very specific Google search. That's bad.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FidoSolutions I sign in with my Group ID and password. A window pops up, telling me to log in with my username and password. No dice!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["All 47 Woody Allen movies -- ranked from worst to best": https://t.co/dsmBSn2Ey0.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson Alas, I fear most creators don't really know who their audience is.)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson (I've heard, "Crowd-funding is two parts, but if you don't have the crowd you won't get the funding." How to get the crowd?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson Biggest knowledge-gap is usually not how to make campaign, but how to attract backers -- put campaign before interested eyes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @StatsBritain: Top 4 things 100% of Britons wish J K Rowling would do:
1 Leave Harry Potter alone
2 Stop changing the past
3 Let it go
4…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just heard that North Korea has banned sarcasm. Yeah, that'll work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: Kelley, Shatner and Nimoy pretending to shave with their phasers on the set of Star Trek, 1968. #StarTrek50 https://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MysteryIndie Just because you've lost doesn't mean you have to stop fighting!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsAdamCanuck Also, by "River's last episode", do you mean "Silence in the Library"?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsAdamCanuck Donna's last episode was the saddest of all. She grew as a person, enlarged her world, and then was forced to give that up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson So your cups runneth over?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KurtBusiek: But alas, NETWORK and BROADCAST NEWS weren’t just critiques. They were prophecies of doom.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @stevecavers: Dear sci-fi FX artists: if the scene calls for an alien moon over an alien planet, don't use OUR moon. It's kind of recogn…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Lincoln Park Zoo names baby camel 'Alexander Camelton'": https://t.co/7CxOPSHiRW.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @simonhoupt: Would you pay $58 to see a movie? Fans are blasting #TIFF16's new "demand-based pricing." https://t.co/9zIlSFM3N7 https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GonzoVice: How long, O Lord, how long? Where will it end?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Criterion: #readabookday, you say? — Claude Jade &amp; Jean-Pierre Léaud in Truffaut’s bittersweet 1970 film BED AND BOARD https://t.co/4wP…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson I think that meal is more Chinese than pierogi.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @playwrightnow: Line of dialogue. Cut it or don't cut it? The simple test. Can an actor use it to get something? if not, cut it. It's cl…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right to stand still! Left to walk! What's the problem, people? https://t.co/6RLatlAzlg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @thenfb: Watch 5 films that deal with subjects relevant to Canadians today: https://t.co/AoyiPsryCp https://t.co/nkNWyNt0Cv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @StatsBritain: 16% of John's dreams are about being wrapped up in Sherlock's long coat.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattdagley Well, maybe in Toronto.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson Reminds me of Margaret Cho's line: "My problem is that I look this way, but I talk this way."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Gingerhazing: Fuck that. Destroying artist's bodies and mental wellbeing for pennies should NOT be an expected part of making art. http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NachosaurusRex I find it hard to believe there is such a thing as a good episode of "Voyager". "DS9" was good some of the time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NachosaurusRex Yeah, Myer's involvement is a good sign. He's (partly) responsible for two of my favourite "Star Trek" movies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NachosaurusRex The last coupl'a TNG movies, "Enterprise", "Voyager", and the last 2 reboot movies have kinda squashed the ol' enthusiasm.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nostalgia ain't what it used to be. https://t.co/QOPR5fPrOX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @thenfb: Enjoy a spectacular, animated view of our solar system: https://t.co/YngSHVtaAw https://t.co/CyHyJouBnC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: Harrison Ford taking a break on the set of Return of the Jedi, 1982. https://t.co/HmNBWIfgq7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @movingsideways: "Samuel L Jackson speaking."
"Oh, hi. I..."
"I'll do it."
"Sorry, I dialed the wro-"
"I said I'LL DO IT."
"uh..."

[MOV…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @playwrightnow: The three scene/play keys. 1 Conflict always. 2 Stakes high as possible. 3 Protagonist driving the action. (Voila! You'r…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tarakjpratt @akonkin That's not camping! I don't see a single pillow fort.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What kind of low-budget films break out?" https://t.co/rPPW1SXE2O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: "Weird Al" Yankovic in school, circa 1970s. https://t.co/1ByNvn7V5O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Kurt_Vonnegut: We are healthy only to the extent that our ideas are humane.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guy on CBC Radio says that Canadians' least-favourite word is "moist". Grrnnrghghgh ..! "Moist". It just feels unpleasant in the mouth.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Panic Mooniverse expands by another small chapter, thanks to @ItsAdamCanuck, @lessicajee, and more!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ThatEricAlper: I don't know where this is, but I love it. https://t.co/Le52l99ikr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @spockosbrain: She doesn't pay her family either. https://t.co/S9H5wtT80p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @playwrightnow: Very astute. (And very common.) https://t.co/crEslMDYvJ]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>