<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[c++ developer: c++ developer Ref No.: 18-29409 Location: Philadelphia, Pennsylvania Role:-c++ developer Location:-Philadelphia,PA JD:- loud operations experience 2. Strong embedded software engineer background in C/C++ 3. Strong knowledge of Software… https://t.co/RzQGpkCYbS https://t.co/CCdsskoXGT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tiger Global takes $1 billion stake in SoftBank, calling it undervalued: source: U.S. hedge fund Tiger Global has built a stake worth over $1 billion in SoftBank Group Corp as it considers the Japanese firm to be undervalued, a source with direct… https://t.co/QR8jgJDMWL https://t.co/WWp247sgPn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Data Analyst – II: Job TitleBusiness Data Analyst – II – ID:31609 Duration12 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsAIX, Machine learning LocationIrving, TX Date Posted04/30/2018 Our client, a Fortune 50, global telecommunications company is looking… https://t.co/TU1U9Hs5ml https://t.co/gL0TLKhJsa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Communications Support Analyst (Part Time): Communications Support Analyst (Part Time) ========================================== Req #: ******Location: Tinker Air Force Base, OK USJob Category: ConsultingSecurity Clearance: TS/SCIClearance Status: Must… https://t.co/UDwvdAlZVj https://t.co/wetg23jRKL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Operations Analyst: Cisco Systems, Inc. is accepting resumes for the following position in San Jose/Milpitas/Santa Clara, CA: Business Analyst/Business Operations Analyst (Ref.# SJ011B): Use Case/Business case development skills by interfacing… https://t.co/KiBkajh0XT https://t.co/DCpHsl4kQD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chipmaker Broadcom nears $19 billion deal to buy software company CA: sources: Broadcom Ltd is nearing a roughly $19 billion deal to acquire business software company CA Inc, as it seeks to diversify its technology offerings beyond semiconductors, people… https://t.co/xj2ZfB3l52 https://t.co/BwqLoAUYiB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering Quality Specialist: Quality Specialist for Ariba, Inc (Palo Alto, CA) to to work in a cross functional development or testing team with special focus on quality assurance and test related tasks within the product creation process. Bachelor’s… https://t.co/MgBssU5qyw https://t.co/9SrqszTvcg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook faces small but symbolic UK fine over data protection breaches: Britain's information regulator slapped Facebook with a small but symbolic fine for breaches of data protection law after millions of users' data was improperly accessed by… https://t.co/H13hMcYz6J https://t.co/Fvl3yBwaEf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist: For Johnson &amp; Johnson Data Scientist job – R &amp; D – New Brunswick, New Jersey Skip to Main Content Our Stories – Latest News – Innovation – Caring &amp; Giving – Personal Stories – Health &amp; Wellness – Our Heritage Our Company – About J &amp; J –… https://t.co/xjJsOZXKCa https://t.co/OksjU4OI2l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Network Engineer: Senior Network Engineer Enter job title or location Search menu open clear text Search jobs Recent Searches – Deloitte home – About Deloitte – Job cart – Location: United States – Global (English) English Available in 145… https://t.co/D0EMZJ8riE https://t.co/J1HEKpG7l1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Entry Level Software Developer: Company Description . Job Description No Computer Science degree? No problem. We love self-taught developers! LaunchCode offers paid, software developer apprenticeships at one of our employer partners that include VML,… https://t.co/3gUNFfcVlD https://t.co/7LsdvqhP41]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Operations Data Analytics Engineer: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Washington, DC Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/4/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest… https://t.co/gAqbc0EUWw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Application Developer: Microsemi Corporation (MSCC) puts technology to work for people. We offer a comprehensive portfolio of semiconductor and system solutions for communications, defense &amp; security, aerospace and industrial markets. Microsemi’s… https://t.co/x0qm2zI1p9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Software Engineer: 17825BR Job Description and Requirements Responsible for designing, developing, troubleshooting, or debugging software programs. Develops software tools including operating systems, compilers, routers, networks, utilities,… https://t.co/imo0GquXHh https://t.co/wXx5OGQ0UG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Australia prepares to ban Huawei from 5G project over security fears: Australia is preparing to ban Huawei Technologies Co Ltd from supplying equipment for its planned 5G broadband network after its intelligence agencies raised concerns that Beijing… https://t.co/5kPk8KZI96 https://t.co/6CyUs7m2W0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Developer, Senior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Chantilly, VA Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/22/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management and… https://t.co/8LyXBYs6TH https://t.co/6wo6zAFvJ1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Communications 2 (AS2C ME/9850):   Job Description – Network Communications 2 (AS2C ME/9850) (18009597) Network Communications 2 (AS2C ME/9850) Requisition ID : 18009597 Location : United States-California-Edwards AFB US Citizenship Required for… https://t.co/Xyh5Xz1yVh https://t.co/k6yYSTd2It]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer – .NET: – Sr. Software Engineer – .NET Company Nexsys Technologies LLC Location US-MI-Detroit Who We Are Nexsys Technologies is a financial technology company founded by mortgage IT experts to create and deliver innovative solutions… https://t.co/NdNrJn17e5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Performance Engineer: System Performance Engineer – Job ID #: 13202 – Job Category: Information Technology – Employment Type: Experienced Professionals – Division: Technology Services Group – Department: Technology Services – Engineering Flows –… https://t.co/Auvf89jcSX https://t.co/j9FU5Ng4Kq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Manager Solutions Architect Pre Sales Engineering: Job Description What you’ll be doing. You will lead a team of Architects with subject matter expertise in intelligent networking and application enablement, to drive excellence in solutions… https://t.co/0E4I2WCdEX https://t.co/aWCahW2CiI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SoftBank's Son says to carry on with deals despite trade jitters: SoftBank Group Corp CEO Masayoshi Son said on Tuesday he was optimistic that U.S. President Donald Trump's escalation of trade disputes and heightened scrutiny of foreign investments would… https://t.co/MA7WRUo1SU https://t.co/6616pADuMS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Administrator Entry Level: Company The Boeing Company Job ID ********** Date posted 07/06/2018 Location Bellevue Washington United States Other Locations Saint Louis;Missouri;United States~Seal Beach;California;United States~North… https://t.co/6NzqiowBWn https://t.co/FX9pvPnlKu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Accountant: Accountant JYK Accountancy Corporation (DBA SangHoYoo CPA &amp; Co/CK Fidelity) in L.A. Requires Bachelor in Accounting, Economy, Finance or related. recblid q6x923mji8ufgk0gkeyy06nd9qsgsa https://t.co/NHRixtTnxt https://t.co/Of3fWD0vvh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Lead Engineer: QA Lead Engineer (Private National Mortgage Acceptance Company, LLC- Ft. Worth, Texas) Utilize minimum requirements to perform automated software testing of web based and database applications. Will guide and mentor offshore QA analyst… https://t.co/JrPczVEWXs https://t.co/0MeTupfWBW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inference Developer Model Abstraction: Job Description What you do at AMD changes everything At AMD, we push the boundaries of what is possible. We believe in changing the world for the better by driving innovation in high-performance computing,… https://t.co/iNkRBl0DmQ https://t.co/Xi60qIeXdJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tech Lead BioPharma Analytics Reporting: The BioPharma Reporting &amp; Analytics – Tech Lead is a software engineering craftsman that is a full-stack engineering lead and coach that is an expert at working in all layers of an application and guiding and… https://t.co/ULEewyPPXq https://t.co/oHquffbr6d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China's Didi signs up Continental for purpose-built electric cars: China's Didi Chuxing signed an agreement with German automotive supplier Continental AG on Tuesday to cooperate in developing internet-connected, electric cars tailor-made for Didi's ride… https://t.co/HfAq7j3vXn https://t.co/V0nmyqLjJA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TeamCenter Developer: TeamCenter Developer in Sunnyvale, California, United States | Technology &amp; Engineering at CognizantJob Details | Cognizant – ************* – Industries – – – Services – – – Latest Thinking – – – About Cognizant – Careers Home – Get… https://t.co/rruQYTje1z https://t.co/56SCmp5tmL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staff Software Developer / Software Engineer: 17608BR Staff Software Developer / Software Engineer General Atomics Aeronautical Systems San Diego California General Atomics Aeronautical Systems, Inc. (GA-ASI), an affiliate of General Atomics, is a world… https://t.co/pwbR9Jq9ej https://t.co/WPAkwJCPeg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Performance Test Lead: Job Title: Performance Test Lead Location: Scottsdale, AZ Job Number: JO-1805-27262 Description ProKarma currently has an exciting opportunity for a Performance Test Lead that would like to join our team as a full-time employee.… https://t.co/VYuTtMKzqm https://t.co/9xHepgPK8q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Process Developer: Process Developer ================= Location: Clinton, NJ, US Company: ExxonMobil [IMAGE] Job Role Summary ExxonMobil Process Technology Department located in Annandale, New Jersey, has an immediate opening for a Process Developer for… https://t.co/N0KRVc5FB0 https://t.co/oG8wcMHNkB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Developer: POSITION OVERVIEW: Our client, one of Chicago’s Best and Brightest Companies to work for, is currently seeking a talented Applications Developer. This person will work with the technology team on new systems and maintenance of… https://t.co/uvPpQpGZ0t https://t.co/QVmiOwfhBA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warehouse Management Business Systems Analyst: Albertsons-Safeway Company is one of the largest food and drug retailers with 2,300+ stores. The Albertsons-Safeway family of brands includes some of the most prominent brands in food retailing, with a… https://t.co/KChgZf7qOL https://t.co/IypMFNlgWR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Administrator: Develop your career. Enhance your life. Strengthen your future. NOW HIRING! SYSTEM ADMINISTRATOR Seeking an individual with excellent problem solving skills, a strong desire to learn and exceptional communication skills. Knowledge… https://t.co/hTZMVy6Gpm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Warehouse, ETL Engineer: Arrow Electronics, Inc. seeks Data Warehouse, ETL Engineer in (Centennial, CO) to perform advanced ETL development activities using Informatica, PL/SQL, Oracle Database tuning, SQL tuning, Informatica Server admin &amp; related.… https://t.co/MNKPUYAFQv https://t.co/AdQ3GvX3NA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: COMPUTER/IT Softw Dvlpr, IBM Corporation, San Jose, CA: Write productn quality code, unit tests, test plans, QA, &amp; documentatn. Prep technl proposals &amp; proof of concepts for various networking use cases. Dvlp web UI for cloud based… https://t.co/BmQStvAVgs https://t.co/lZESpBO0v4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter shares fall after report says account suspensions to cause user decline: Shares of Twitter Inc fell 9 percent on Monday after a report said the social media company had suspended more than 70 million fake accounts in May and June, which could… https://t.co/ZlmpA1Vs3g https://t.co/9r1MsMRcjG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate: COMPUTER: DB GLOBAL TECHNOLOGY INC. seeks an Associate in Cary, NC to provide strategic, quality assurance and business analysis services. Requires a Bachelor’s degree in Electronic Engineering, Computer Science or related field or equivalent… https://t.co/m4xPeNU9yc https://t.co/pxrsntOjSb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Programmer: GDIT is seeking a Principal Programmer who builds and codes applications and/or models using various computer programming languages. Responsible for coordinating the design, development and testing of complex and efficient… https://t.co/6272ijjBbW https://t.co/zD2Bl4CMU2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Service Desk Specialist: Job Description Job Description Specialist, Service Desk Service Desk Specialists are the single point of contact for T-Mobile employees in need of support for IT incidents and service requests. This includes 247 triage,… https://t.co/E1KUrz9OlN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Xiaomi's weak debut signals trouble for upcoming Hong Kong tech listings: Xiaomi Corp made a weak debut in Hong Kong on Monday, with the Chinese smartphone maker's shares sliding as much as 6 percent on valuation concerns, in an ominous sign for its… https://t.co/1VtBLSNIS2 https://t.co/KuAa0hVM3o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer – Virtualization: Location PL-Remote Posting date 7 hours ago(6/19/2018 7:01 AM) Job ID 62404 Category Software Engineering Company Description At Red Hat, we connect an innovative community of customers, partners, and… https://t.co/zeMISejQze https://t.co/5VL2ngy3gj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finance Systems Project Manager: What you’ll be doing. As an effective leader within the Finance Systems Group, you will work closely with revenue business partners to provide vision and strategy to various project initiatives, and partner with key… https://t.co/yeAdTYEYGb https://t.co/5Lv3d8x7Oy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Customer Support Analyst Summer Intern: Our vision is to be the best provider of building products in the eyes of our customers, employees, shareholders, suppliers and communities. At Masonite, we understand that people are key. We are a composite of… https://t.co/kr2k1snwyO https://t.co/hahHIe3V83]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Registered Nurse-PHP Part Time: PRIMARY RESPONSIBILITIES – Demonstrates knowledge of and follows Timberline Knolls’ operating procedures and policies. – Establishes collaborative working relationships with the multidisciplinary team, including… https://t.co/AL0zoTMQlk https://t.co/IhJMePDuNt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helpdesk-Service Desk Associate – Austin, Texas: Job Snapshot Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Austin, TX, US Job Type: Information Technology Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 7/4/2018 Job Description TTEC is seeking a Service Desk Associate to… https://t.co/SyGkEChA3W https://t.co/Rsk1RVCdPH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smartphone maker Xiaomi's shares set to open down 2.4 percent in HK debut: Chinese smartphone maker Xiaomi Corp's shares are set to open down 2.4 percent on debut in Hong Kong on Monday, in a blow to investor sentiment for the tech sector as a raft of… https://t.co/c651XRakVt https://t.co/QJUH56NnZ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Administrator Sr.: Job Description To be considered for the position, applicants must have an active security clearance. A BS degree with at least 4 years of related experience is preferred or candidates must have at least a HS diploma and 8 years… https://t.co/W44UHbZgK6 https://t.co/gIIIGyh9Dq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Paypal to spend $3 billion a year on M&amp;A: CEO to German paper: PayPal Holdings Inc is on the lookout for further acquisitions following its recent takeover of iZettle, the Swedish fintech startup, for $2.2 billion, in the U.S. payments company's biggest… https://t.co/hNcKim4IuC https://t.co/wpEGtFFRen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr SharePoint Engineer/Developer: Sr Point Engineer/Developer – Spalding Consulting, Inc. ************** *************** – Home – About – Solutions – Careers – Contracts – Contact – My Account Job Openings &gt;&gt; Sr Point Engineer/Developer Sr Point… https://t.co/zDLbxoGsLn https://t.co/MWGEg4BtPR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP CRM: SAP CRM Ref No.: 18-01555 Location: Houston, Texas Position Type: Contract Start Date: 06/14/2018 Description: Summary: Designs, develops, maintains and enhances application programs supporting SAP – ISU/CRM applications. (i.e. customer… https://t.co/jKlESsLrz0 https://t.co/5whVFiq5PL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Singapore's Temasek set to report record portfolio; tech deals in focus: Singapore state investor Temasek Holdings Pte Ltd [TEM.UL] is likely to book a record S$300 billion ($221 billion) for the value of its portfolio, powered by gains in DBS Group Ltd… https://t.co/zwHzvpUThU https://t.co/LNJwVd0uui]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Analyst: Network Analyst =============== Req #: ******Location: Chantilly, VA USJob Category: Information TechnologySecurity Clearance: SecretClearance Status: Must be Obtainable Job Description CACI is currently looking for outstanding IT… https://t.co/ujilKtLAPG https://t.co/hvkxRVqJhs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst: Our client is looking for a Data Analyst for a contract to hire position here in Austin, TX. You will be joining a team that provides critical information to internal and external stakeholders. What you will be doing: Extract, manipulate,… https://t.co/cWm9zM0ENT https://t.co/heGTNqjlAx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Principal Data Analyst: Requisition ID 2018-40320 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Secret Full/Part Time Part Time Job Description General Dynamics Information Technology is in search of a Senior Data… https://t.co/3OeHXMuPfQ https://t.co/UH5vwNo4oh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huawei says does not expect U.S. sanctions: press: China's Huawei, the world's largest maker of telecommunication network equipment, does not see itself becoming the target of U.S. sanctions and will keep buying U.S. chips this year, one of its three… https://t.co/4xcnfcZcmr https://t.co/5lVBzFgo3T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[TITLE SOFTWARE ENGINEER LEVEL 3 (SS): Careers Center | Software Engineer Level 3 (SS) Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a… https://t.co/Hmen8Q9tgz https://t.co/e6nDy8u2UG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big Data Software Engineer: Big Data Software Engineer in Princeton, New Jersey, United States | Information Technology at Deloitte Toggle menu – Deloitte home – About Deloitte – – Location: United States Available in locations and languages – Students –… https://t.co/Eh3Vl7biNf https://t.co/DddQtDoAV5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mechanical Engineer Stf: Req ID : 429716BR Job Code/Title : E1412:Mechanical Engineer Job Description : Here within Lockheed Martin we are looking for a Mechanical Engineer to join our team. Lockheed Martin Laser and Sensor Systems delivers innovative… https://t.co/B7UbFGOPeS https://t.co/zPhu0hzDHm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Configuration Analyst 3 or 4:   Job Description – Software Configuration Analyst 3 or 4 (18011122) Software Configuration Analyst 3 or 4 Requisition ID : 18011122 Location : United States-District of Columbia-Washington US Citizenship Required… https://t.co/ft710gXqXA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETL Developer: ETL Developer Charlotte, North Carolina – United States Job Start Date – 07/02/18, Posted Date – 06/11/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview Top 3 requirements: 1. ETL Development (informatica) 2. SSIS and tearadata (moving from SSIS to… https://t.co/EzX1EmRNfJ https://t.co/OHB0BnSkzu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Senior Developer: Senior Developer for SAP Labs, LLC (Palo Alto, CA) resp for dev focusing on dsgn, cdng, qlty assrnc of cmplx prdct features in a dev team. Bach dgr in Comp Sci, Engg, Math, or rltd &amp; 6 yrs exp req’d. Will also acpt Master’s dgr &amp; 4… https://t.co/eZHu616RLf https://t.co/SM94vmcLID]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UX Designer: UX Designer : 18-02810 Ref No.: 18-02810 Location: Foster City, California Akraya is looking for an UX Designer for one of our clients. If the job description below is a fit, please apply directly or call Swapnil at ************. If this… https://t.co/zXvApN6dcw https://t.co/UxaCkQjmy8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales Force Developer: Sales Force Developer Ref No.: 18-32498 Location: new york, New York Hello, Greetings for the day ! We have an urgent requirement for Sales Force Developer in New York , NY. Please let me know if you are looking for a new project.… https://t.co/Vdb5hwJwF2 https://t.co/UrP1PsOOqK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer III: Overview Are you proficient in Java, C#, PHP or Python? Are you experienced in AWS services? Were looking for a skilled influencer and self-starter whos familiar with Agile methodologies to join our team as a DevOps Engineer, where… https://t.co/rdkvrUgmm5 https://t.co/9LMZiqJsLY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Security Specialist, Sr Principal: Req ID 99340BR Business Title IT Security Specialist, Sr Principal Group MCIS Location USA MARYLAND Hanover Clearance Level Needed TS/SCI Category Cyber Job Duties and Responsibilities "Required: IAT level II… https://t.co/AEbNWZlALz https://t.co/8BiAPoic9s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Selenium Developer: Selenium Developer in Fairfax, VA | CACI International – Small Business | – Suppliers – About Us – | – What We Do – | – Media &amp; Events – | – Investors – | – Careers – | – Contracts – | – Contact Us Join Our Talent Network – About Us –… https://t.co/XXEdv4JZFP https://t.co/IWgtEGh7xT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project-Manager: Join Schneider Electric and power your career Discover the opportunity to join an international, dynamic, and responsible company that fosters the development of all its people around the world. Every day, we empower employees to achieve… https://t.co/1nAQDXBx7e https://t.co/YFhWULUsi4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer Java: Senior Software Engineer – Java at EXPERIANSkip Navigation Consumer Small Business Business More.X Experian Site Sections About Experian Consumer Support Credit Advice Global Sites Company Profile Corporate Fact Sheet… https://t.co/zCIEr9o7La https://t.co/rvVt8zQgFm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marketing: MARKETING Intuit Inc. has openings for Marketing Managers (Job code: I-3584) in Mountain View, California: Responsible for quantitative pricing research survey design and result analysis to drive decisions and influence pricing strategy across… https://t.co/fid56HaocZ https://t.co/wYIsPTetx8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Operations Engineer: Intuit Inc. has openings for the following positions in Mountain View, California: Software Engineers (Job code: SW718): Apply software development practices to design, implement, and support individual software projects.… https://t.co/jUxqwNHgcQ https://t.co/rEMSTodZ65]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAS programmer: Sagarsoft Inc has multiple job openings for the following positions to work in Glastonbury, CT and / or various client sites throughout the U.S: Must be willing to travel and/or relocate. * Senior ETL Software Engineer to design, develop… https://t.co/d1UFjdK0DT https://t.co/yRtFpBEwfX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager / Lead Systems Specialist: Job Description Project Manager / Lead Systems Specialist (HVAC Controls) (WD***********) What will you do Under general direction, acts as the on-site project leader to plan, execute, and complete control… https://t.co/RpFfVOlS7M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Administrator: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: North Charleston, SC Job Type: Engineering, Information Technology Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 7/15/2018 Job Description Job Number: R******* Database Administrator Key Role: Support… https://t.co/nfpwQYPQRO https://t.co/rjAqV1bnem]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JATS Senior Program Manager: JATS Senior Program Manager =========================== Req #: ******Location: Chantilly, VA USJob Category: Project and Program ManagementSecurity Clearance: SecretClearance Status: Must be Obtainable Job Description CACI is… https://t.co/PDBYXncTB8 https://t.co/TKNZGT9m1j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adobe Experience Manager/Systems Administrator: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Lexington Park, MD Job Type: Management Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 7/24/2018 Job Description Job Number: R******* Adobe Experience Manager/Systems… https://t.co/ikw6Z6x85I https://t.co/04yPxxgvqv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer: Job Description What you’ll be doing… You will be part of the Intelligent Edge Network (iEN) Support Team, focused on developing solutions that drive the success of our bleeding-edge networks and platforms. Utilizing your… https://t.co/EzUYZo4MGf https://t.co/zaBbMruBfd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Training Developer: POSITION SUMMARY: Performs as a Change Management Practitioner for the Integrated Personnel and Pay System Army (IPPS-A) Increment II Program to deliver organizational alignment products including jobs and teams, reporting… https://t.co/KVAoZAyOkH https://t.co/7o2zBccu2y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer – Referral Partnership: Are you an independent web developer with a large network of clients who process e-commerce transactions? Do you design web pages that require an e-commerce solution? Are you looking for proven opportunities to… https://t.co/8K6nF6WLLM https://t.co/85ixE5b1jp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World Bank taps Australia's CBA for blockchain bond: Commonwealth Bank of Australia has won a mandate from the World Bank to arrange a pioneering bond issue to be created and run using only blockchain, aiming to simplify capital raising and trading. https://t.co/eYRHxlpOY3 https://t.co/DpXtUGdOSa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: Software Engineer Columbus – Ohio Design and develop highly efficient Ab Initio solutions that meet approved business requirements under delivery timelines. Performance tuning of Ab Initio graphs to meet processing SLAs and maximize on… https://t.co/rHNGwdvM3n https://t.co/v4zQcYlyDe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is SpaceX the model for a private Tesla?: Tesla Inc Chief Executive Officer Elon Musk has held up his closely held space transportation company SpaceX as a model for taking his loss-making electric car company private, saying he wants existing Tesla… https://t.co/ySMbcCBV2C https://t.co/zqyy66luvx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Architect: SOFTWARE ARCHITECT, IBM Corporation, Durham, NC: Define product and solution architecture. Demonstrate analytical and creative ability to anticipate trends and knowledge of leading-edge products, technology, and industry. Update… https://t.co/nSolVy7wQn https://t.co/tcWRKnNWO5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Requisition ID 2018-42495 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level None Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description For more than 50 years, General Dynamics Information Technology has served as a… https://t.co/yYKjyHf479 https://t.co/zKgX6giS0s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CND Network Analyst: Requisition ID 2017-32818 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Top Secret/SCI Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description Contract: I2TS 3 Position Title: Sr Analyst, Information Security –… https://t.co/J4yonDXAEZ https://t.co/3n8NqGTmfz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Data Analyst: Job Description Senior Data Analyst Location: US-WA-Seattle Job ID: ****** Company: : ********** Services, Inc. Position Category: Operations, IT, &amp; Support Engineering Job Description We’re a company of pioneers. It’s our job to… https://t.co/mcsMBRtGj7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Process Analyst: Business Process Analyst in Frederick, MD | CACI International – Small Business | – Suppliers – About Us – | – What We Do – | – Media &amp; Events – | – Investors – | – Careers – | – Contracts – | – Contact Us Join Our Talent… https://t.co/pTxs8KWjLm https://t.co/JstccaKals]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After Mercari: Japanese asset managers see new era in venture capital investing: The hugely successful IPO by online marketplace Mercari in June was a bonanza for its shareholders – and may transform lukewarm attitudes among mainstream asset managers… https://t.co/B8gVMi6uRk https://t.co/cTwnALTC6D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist Job: Company Information PACCAR is a Fortune 500 company established in 1905. PACCAR Inc is recognized as a global leader in the commercial vehicle, financial, and customer service fields with internationally recognized brands such as… https://t.co/VZHf1gaR7q https://t.co/IGfHd1Tdi3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager I – Design Build (Civil/Highway): Job Description – Project Manager I – Design Build (Civil/Highway) Job LocationUS-MO-Kansas CityJob ID0318-18202 HNTB Job TitleProject Manager I – Engineering Position TypeRegular Full-Time… https://t.co/9Atwi3lPWn https://t.co/75FiCPW3RW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Systems Analyst (Contract Management Team): DCCA is a veteran-owned high-technology company specializing in providing information technology services to a variety of government agencies and commercial enterprises since 1982. DCCA is proud to… https://t.co/Nn0Ak6zEmI https://t.co/b14jC7SqbZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SEC examining Musk's tweets on taking Tesla private: WSJ: U.S. regulators are asking Tesla Inc why Chief Executive Elon Musk announced his plan to take the electric carmaker private on Twitter and whether his statement was truthful, the Wall Street… https://t.co/TGPBLeXJlU https://t.co/PzXJ4DAv5W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infrastructure Automation Developer: Infrastructure Automation Developer – Language – English – French – Worldwide Careers Site – Sign in – Accessibility – Working at Merck – Why Merck? – Diversity at Merck – From Service to Science – Prepare to Launch –… https://t.co/spNYMdRLDe https://t.co/7VTDY7RAQG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Business Systems Analyst GRS Strong SQL: Technical Business Systems Analyst’ ‘ GRS ‘ Strong SQL Formulates and defines system’s scope and objectives based on both user needs and a good understanding of the application, business, operational… https://t.co/jlqIOJCtoZ https://t.co/hB1KDM3ANT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer: Calance Job Opening – .NET DeveloperJob Openings | Calance IT StaffingJob Openings – Calance Calance Creating Customer Alliances – Job Openings – By Job Title – By Date Created – By State – For Employeers – Contact Us – Corporate – All… https://t.co/DW4vIZprKO https://t.co/BKSlowDtpa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[React-Native Developer: – Services – Training – Careers – About – Thoughts – Contact Menu – Services – Training – Careers – About – Thoughts – Contact – Follow us – Twitter – Facebook – React-Native Developer Dallas/Fort Worth, TX &lt; Back to Careers… https://t.co/jkBATHJwY1 https://t.co/xfvSyYMGH9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Account Executive, Senior (Mandarin speaking): Account Executive, Senior (Mandarin speaking) Job Location US-CA-Newark Req No. 2017-2256 Category Sales/Presales Overview We have an immediate opportunity for a Senior Account Executive on our Sales team in… https://t.co/ChPq2izW3T https://t.co/eUR3mMhQxy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Tester w/Polygraph: Requisition ID 2018-43350 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Top Secret/SCI with Polygraph Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description Reviews and evaluates software products and systems… https://t.co/gJGteCQtfF https://t.co/2bO2DwBFNy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer Planning Analyst 4:   Job Description – Engineer Planning Analyst 4 (18015035) Engineer Planning Analyst 4 Requisition ID : 18015035 Location : United States-Colorado-Aurora US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation Assistance:… https://t.co/YckZg9Aazo https://t.co/SnltyLZDKH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Toshiba posts record quarterly profit on chip sale, outlook unclear: Japan's Toshiba Corp reported a record quarterly net profit on Wednesday, thanks to the $18 billion sale of its flash memory chip business earlier this year to a consortium led by U.S.… https://t.co/nWvPVIXhCq https://t.co/QFBc9nvQMz]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>