<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA["The only thing I know is everything you love will die." 
- Survivor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Hope is just another phase you'll grow out of." 
- Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Our world of only humans, a world without humanity." 
- Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @codename_rondo: @PalahniukQuote http://t.co/sJwidQLDTe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Think of spoiled cat food and ulcerated cankers and expired donor organs. That's how beautiful she looks." 
- Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Maybe it's just a daughter's job to piss off her mother."
- Diary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you died right now, how would you feel about your life?"
- Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Invisible Monsters #ChuckPalahniuk ... http://t.co/4sdZfLmeX1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The easiest way to avoid living is to just watch. Let Big Brother do the singing and dancing for you."
- Lullaby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 more months... "@doubledaypub: For #samplesunday, an excerpt of DOOMED by @chuckpalahniuk: http://t.co/AAU2sFLccE"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Your whole life is about discovering who you already were."
- Diary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AllenHenson: It's remarkable how replaceable the Bible seems next to a copy of Chuck Palahniuk's fight club.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["One man's god is another man's devil."
- Damned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Maybe you don't go to hell for the things you do. Maybe you go to hell for the things you don't do. The things you don't finish."
- Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Maybe the point is not to forget the rest of yourself if one little part might go bad."
- Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When we don't know who to hate, we hate ourselves."
- Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The difference between how you look and how you see yourself is enough to kill most people."
- Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Survivor fan art. #ChuckPalahniuk http://t.co/MDzNR21Gad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love is a skill you learn."
- Rant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Don't do what you want. Do what you don't want. Do what you're trained not to want. Do the things that scare you the most."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @InnocuousMariam: Retweeting pretty much everything on @PalahniukQuote cause Chuck Palahniuk is a genius!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I feel my heart ache, but I've forgotten what that feeling means."
- Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Honest is how I want to look. The truth doesn't glitter and shine."
- Survivor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We've spent so much time judging what other people created that we've created very, very little of our own."
- Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @perezelizabeth: "@MarinasDiamonds: Just for the record, the weather today is bitter with occasional fits of jealous rage" @PalahniukQuo…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Life's greatest comfort is being able to look over your shoulder and see people worse off, standing in line behind you."
- Rant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You ever wonder if Adam and Eve were just the puppies God dumped because they wouldn't house-train?"
- Lullaby.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["What I want is to be needed. What I need is to be indispensable to somebody. Somebody addicted to me. A mutual addiction."
- Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Long-term, we're all going to die. Then our bodies will rot. No surprise there. Short-term, we're going to live happily ever after."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Every generation wants to be the last."
- Lullaby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The moment the world declares a person to be immortal, at that moment the person will strive to prove the world wrong."
- Tell-All]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Burn the Louvre, and wipe your ass with the Mona Lisa. This way at least, God would know our names."
- Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Doesn't reincarnation strike you as just another form of procrastination?"
- Lullaby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Watching television and surfing the internet are really excellent practice for being dead."
- Damned]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @neon_toad: “Because beauty is power the way money is power the way a loaded gun is power.”  -@PalahniukQuote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You have endless ways you can commit suicide without 'dying' dying."
- Diary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You can only hold a smile for so long, after that it's just teeth."
- Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Your past goes with you into every day of your future."
- Lullaby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @xDisappearHerex: "The lower you fall, the higher you'll fly." #FightClub #ChuckPalahniuk...
 http://t.co/oiwln319yy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @_VintageBones: Used one of my favorite Palahniuk quotes for my ceramics project. @PalahniukQuote http://t.co/JV5OXBz9d2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I'm breaking my attachment to possessions, because only through destroying myself can I discover the greater power of my spirit."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Find joy in everything you choose to do. Every job, relationship, home... it's your responsibility to love it, or change it."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @xDisappearHerex: Whenever I take the bus, I think of this great short story by a very young Chuck Palahniuk... 
http://t.co/zQJOuBZR0I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["That's why I write. You can't control life, at least you can control your version."
- Stranger Than Fiction]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["She's the blasé eye of the hurricane that's the world around her." 
- Survivor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["She's so thin she's either dying or rich."
- Lullaby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The joke is, we all have the same punchline."
- Survivor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It happens fast for some people and slow for some, accidents or gravity, but we all end up mutilated."
- Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Is evil something you are? Or is it something you do?"
- Bret Easton Ellis, American Psycho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Our culture has made us all the same. No one is truly white or black or rich anymore. Individually, we are nothing."
- Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's only in drugs or death we'll see anything new, and death is just too controlling."
- Survivor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A baby is such a blank slate, like training an understudy for a role you're planning to leave."
- Tell-All]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ZOMbreezy: @PalahniukQuote http://t.co/1BFu5xkwIn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["More and more, it feels like I'm doing a really bad impersonation of myself."
- Choke, #ChuckPalahniuk http://t.co/f9ItfCAJi6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If a tree falls in the forest and nobody is there to hear it, doesn't it just lie there and rot?"
- Survivor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["My life might be little and boring, but at least it's mine--not some assembly-line, secondhand, hand-me-down life."
- Rant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Just for the record, the weather today is partly suspicious with chances of betrayal."
- Diary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["All you need to get by is to know how to float on your back in a violent sea full of sharks."
- Charles Bukowski]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["By the time you're thirty, your worst enemy is yourself."
- Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The only way to find true happiness is to risk being completely cut open."
- Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @xDisappearHerex: Anyone who wants to read an awesome short story, this is one of my favs from 'Knockemstiff' By: Donald Ray Pollock... …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And if you have the stomach for it, read and retweet: the infamous 'Guts' ...
You'll never eat calamari again...
http://t.co/RhsARe4IE6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the short story that became 'Invisible Monsters'...
#BirdsAteMyFace
http://t.co/5yvf6qbebd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The lower you fall, the higher you'll fly."
- Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We have pain and hate and love and joy and war in the world because we want them."
- Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["After you find out all the things that can go wrong, your life becomes less about living and more about waiting."
- Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Are these things really better than the things I already have? Or am I just trained to be dissatisfied with what I have now?"
- Lullaby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Any smart woman knows a beautiful man is her best fashion accessory."
- Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We'll never be as young as we are tonight."
- Rant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["That's the American Dream: to make your life into something you can sell."
- Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Survivor' quote...
#ChuckPalahniuk http://t.co/yrHTpISuok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["For this moment, nothing matters. Look up into the stars and you're gone."
- Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[History is nothing except monsters or victims. Or witnesses."
- Rant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We all die. The goal isn't to live forever, the goal is to create something that will."
- Diary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most guys will fight to know you. Some will deny you're a real person, and some will just ignore you. The zealot. the atheist. the agnostic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The laws that keep us safe, these same laws condemn us to boredom."
- Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You are permanent, but this life is not."
- Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I don't want to die without any scars."
- Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Some people never go crazy. What truly horrible lives they must lead." 
- Charles Bukowski]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I want my whole life lined with a topical anesthetic."
- Survivor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It boils down to the fact that we're all jackals feeding off each other."
- Tell-All]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There's worse ways to be dead than dying."
- Rant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If death meant just leaving the stage long enough to change costume and come back as a new character... Would you slow down? Or speed up?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Have your adventures, make your mistakes, and choose your friends poorly--all these make for great stories."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing Madison Spencer Art via @melizimo &amp; @ModernEden...
#Damned #ChuckPalahniuk http://t.co/VLHaoxceLu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The only way to find true happiness is to risk being completely cut open."
- Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#FF 
@chuckpalahniuk 
@BretEastonEllis 
@CraigClevenger 
@DougCoupland 
@WelshIrvine 
@stephengjones72 
@brandontietz 
@xDisappearHerex]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you love something set it free, but don't be surprised if it comes back with herpes."
- Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @xDisappearHerex: For those who want to know the difference between Invisible Monsters &amp; Invisible Monsters Remix, let Chuck explain... …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The ballad for our revolution, turned into background music for a television commercial."
- Lullaby]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Every family is a regular little cult."
- Rant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Worker bees can leave
Even drones can fly away
The queen is their slave"
- Fight Club]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You will always have some excuse not to live your life."
- Haunted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Isn't a kid alive who doesn't dream about rewarding her folks, or punishing them."
- Snuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Our real discoveries come from chaos, from going to the place that looks wrong and stupid and foolish."
- Invisible Monsters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We've taken the world apart but we have no idea what to do with the pieces."
- Choke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In Hell, whenever the demons announce they're going to treat everyone to a big-name Hollywood movie, it's always The English Patient."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Inspiration needs disease, injury, madness."
- Diary]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You know how both life and porno movies end. The only difference is life starts with the orgasm."
- Survivor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Sex pretty much cures everything."
- Choke]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>