<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Parkland students return to a school they say 'feels like jail': Students of Marjory Stoneman Douglas High School return to class Monday, their first day back since organizing one of the largest youth-led protests in US history. https://t.co/0IcB9oRZOg https://t.co/gYqkvLH54U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fox host takes a week off as advertisers flee https://t.co/btkY8fZRip https://t.co/WdDNeA43Rs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An inside look at driverless cars: CNN's Christi Paul gets an inside look at the way semi-autonomous cars operate and how they're different from fully autonomous cars. https://t.co/dKKHwm2xxj https://t.co/jHeuPVF8c2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How these parents raised three pro athlete sons https://t.co/kTSfKnAyrj https://t.co/ggwQnsKpDg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Worst royal wedding dress code mistakes: With a career spanning three decades, British fashion critic Colin McDowell knows a thing or two about aristocratic dress codes -- so much, in fact, that he wrote a book, "A Hundred Years of Royal Style," on the… https://t.co/YYPMN6usw8 https://t.co/IMXYslOzuZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world's most extreme airports https://t.co/06LP3vrRiJ https://t.co/QgtNyC8zyy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Memo says Pruitt flew first class to avoid 'lashing out from passengers': Documents provided to Congress fail to show Scott Pruitt got federally required waivers to fly first class -- and if he did, then his office has twice declined to hand them over to… https://t.co/cWLuKEhDtr https://t.co/RjhB0mqa7v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Comedian stops show to rescue fan during medical emergency: He really is "Dr. Ken." https://t.co/UwXvh6oYzL https://t.co/1EpoTxRMeK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fans rehash pot-filled Uruguay episode https://t.co/48Ath6nk6v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stars arrive at the Met Gala https://t.co/5UDETZtdJd https://t.co/5ouCiYOWTu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 things you need to know today: Check out the world's longest sea-crossing bridge (it's 34 miles!), which opens this summer in China. Here's what else you need to know to Get Up to Speed and Out the Door. (You can also get "5 Things You Need to Know… https://t.co/8BpgQ2wzwJ https://t.co/lT7dWKOMW6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nunes threatens Sessions with contempt: House Intelligence Committee Chairman Devin Nunes warned Sunday that he plans to urge lawmakers "this week" to hold Attorney General Jeff Sessions in contempt of Congress for failing to hand over classified… https://t.co/qcixzuJqid https://t.co/5icFPZuRsC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big Island resident: Life completely upside down: Leilani Estates, Hawaii, resident Steve Gebbie says, "life is completely turned upside down," after a seventh volcanic vent opened in a Hawaiian neighborhood. CNN's Stephanie Elam reports. https://t.co/mPYwAfMLI3 https://t.co/nrjlGyNlyu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WaPo: Gina Haspel sought to withdraw nomination to be CIA director: Gina Haspel on Friday sought to withdraw her nomination as President Donald Trump's pick to head the CIA after some White House officials raised concerns that her role in the agency's… https://t.co/0jJ59pz3Bq https://t.co/0QTHmWPUYx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In high school, I no longer felt safe in unsupervised places: Two decades ago, when I was in the second grade, a substitute teacher asked me to stand up in front of my class and talk about my religion: Sikhism. At 7 years old, I tried to explain it as… https://t.co/qkjtP7r92e https://t.co/rpn4CFI7qt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[132-pound ovarian tumor removed: A 132-pound ovarian tumor was removed from a 38-year-old Connecticut woman this year, according to two doctors involved in the case. https://t.co/9l4PyVwNwv https://t.co/poZI6TbgeH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['GoT' star crowned World's Strongest Man https://t.co/gbtLbU6O5w https://t.co/dcj77aqNzK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['RBG' earns favorable verdict: Stirring in all the right ways, "RBG" is much more than just a profile of Ruth Bader Ginsburg, the unexpectedly iconic Supreme Court Justice. The documentary, rather, turns out to be a wonderful love story, with a buddy… https://t.co/6q2CpFTXZE https://t.co/dYvyyCuMmD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buffett defends Wells Fargo's 'cardinal sin' https://t.co/Yqs2zxh1L2 https://t.co/M7uN3BzzBE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Waffle House shooting hero hasn't heard from President: President Trump has yet to contact or publicly praise Waffle House hero James Shaw Jr. https://t.co/8hGj50MmP6 https://t.co/D9rR5D0G4W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7 miners killed in cave-in in South Africa: Seven miners were killed in a cave-in this week at a South African gold mine, the nation's President and the mining company said Saturday. https://t.co/Btj3VOvHTU https://t.co/ks3btR8qGr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump ending protection for Hondurans was unnecessary https://t.co/qhHT4HXu5E https://t.co/MEqOdGjB82]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pence's doctor resigns: The White House physician assigned to Vice President Mike Pence, Jennifer Pena, has resigned, his office told CNN in a statement Friday. Pena worked in the White House medical unit. https://t.co/LLBxP715wx https://t.co/sW15qTGp4u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['We are over it': Detroit radio hosts pull Kanye West's songs: Kanye West's recent comments outraged a lot of people this week. And there's one group who no longer wants to hear any of it: the morning show hosts at Detroit radio station 105.1 The Bounce. https://t.co/7fE5SqYlE6 https://t.co/2M95B9nogS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Acosta to Sanders: Were you lying?: CNN's Jim Acosta presses White House press secretary Sarah Sanders on contradictory statements she has given about President Trump's attorney Michael Cohen's payment to porn star Stormy Daniels. https://t.co/y8mmMU1TJY https://t.co/ZPmoh1y0yj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teen's prom dress was trashed on Twitter. Why?: Prom dresses are designed to get reactions, and the history of social media is littered with viral prom outfits -- dresses made out of unusual materials, dresses that send statements and dresses that are,… https://t.co/cJwI7yCPPF https://t.co/tcdDgYtUms]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pruitt reimbursed himself $65,000 from campaigns: A CNN analysis has found that embattled Environmental Protection Agency Administrator Scott Pruitt paid himself nearly $65,000 in reimbursements from his two campaigns for Oklahoma attorney general, a… https://t.co/utxLmuCWZk https://t.co/S9Whe8POHx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: We must stop giving Kanye a platform to lie: There are opinions, and then there are facts. As the saying goes, people are entitled to their own version of the former, but not the latter. https://t.co/9TnCEpLpCx https://t.co/qmYnJK5mrn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These are the 9 National Guard airmen killed in the plane crash: Puerto Rico's National Guard on Thursday identified the nine airmen killed a day earlier when an aging cargo plane nosedived into a Georgia highway. https://t.co/fHMbRS6z2j https://t.co/1Saz9MW0vN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A scientific measure of an extraordinary life: The closest I've come to a profound religious experience happened at a Zen Buddhist monastery in the mountains. I was a sophomore in college, and my mom invited me to join her for a long weekend group… https://t.co/B6fCvrETzI https://t.co/3fdm4J943H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Giuliani: 3 Americans to be released by North Korea today: Three Americans held in a North Korean prison are set to be released, former New York City Mayor Rudy Giuliani said Thursday. https://t.co/TmOXBw1SiI https://t.co/tWZQ62b8SE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meghan Markle faces UK citizenship test: Despite marrying into the Royal Family, Meghan Markle will have to take the standard UK British citizenship test. CNN's Michael Holmes reports. https://t.co/2y58eLC7xz https://t.co/zlSzp0EFuT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Texas wants ex-Rep. Farenthold to pay for election to replace him: Former GOP Rep. Blake Farenthold of Texas said in an open letter dated Wednesday that he would not pay for the special election to replace him. https://t.co/nAH7SAH7Nd https://t.co/gWRCD6XQtg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Video shows how close Air Canada jet came to landing on taxiing planes: Newly released video shows just how close an Air Canada Airbus A320 came to mistakenly landing on a crowded taxiway at San Francisco International Airport last year. https://t.co/TIqeihtfVv https://t.co/bHMgJ0zVeZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This nation is losing best and brightest: How do you extinguish hope in Afghanistan, a country that despite four decades of war has somehow managed to keep dreaming of something better? https://t.co/ZpOIrFd0rn https://t.co/XaW4Ac6RYK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scott Pruitt's decisions have triggered nearly a dozen reviews: Ethics watchdogs, federal auditors and congressional committees are conducting nearly a dozen inquiries into Administrator Scott Pruitt's actions at the Environmental Protection Agency. https://t.co/1xTR4npSfF https://t.co/8Ro2Jbbeya]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump threatens to take on DOJ: President Donald Trump threatened Wednesday to "get involved" with the Justice Department's efforts to provide documents to lawmakers after accusations the agency has refused lawmakers' requests on a variety of topics. https://t.co/ADgqoYtJEm https://t.co/r1fnKMlUPw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Immigration Sponsorship for F1 or OPT Visaed Registered Nurse only: Seeking qualified foreign students on a student visa or on OPT to join our green card sponsorship program. U.S. Nursing License and F-1 Visa or OPT REQUIRED. You will receive a permanent… https://t.co/OGQ0ld0XVC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[California leads states in suing the EPA https://t.co/3SdKopjNUq https://t.co/fuJzFO1iig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Marco Polo' producer accuses Weinstein of multiple sexual assaults: Alexandra Canosa, an associate producer on the Netflix series "Marco Polo," has filed a lawsuit in Manhattan Supreme Court alleging Harvey Weinstein raped, physically assaulted and… https://t.co/PGkNh7cMZX https://t.co/nvxxxS9lvV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hillary Clinton changed her Twitter bio and it doesn't start with wife: Hillary Clinton has changed her Twitter bio following her conversation with Nigerian writer Chimamanda Ngozi Adiche at a literary event in New York. https://t.co/uLUlocJkp5 https://t.co/N2y8BuIi0G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iconic guitar maker files for bankruptcy https://t.co/wC8PD9P8mW https://t.co/DQ92WzZydo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Breast cancer: Innovative pill may aid diagnosis: Many cases of breast cancer are either misdiagnosed or remain undetected, due to the unclear nature of some tumors. Could a pill solve this problem? https://t.co/QE2zzYa6nb https://t.co/1UkKafnTik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump slams leak of Mueller questions: President Donald Trump on Tuesday slammed the disclosure of special counsel Robert Mueller's questions for him, calling the leak "disgraceful." https://t.co/rkBOEhZTRT https://t.co/Letb65vjNB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysis: GOP majority is in deep trouble: On Monday, CNN's key House race tracker ranked a dozen seats currently held by Republicans as being in more electoral danger, the latest in a series of developments that suggest the majority party is… https://t.co/IuHdw642tg https://t.co/VNgY2b3crB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump vents at Merkel, seeks advice on Putin: President Donald Trump questioned German Chancellor Angela Merkel about how to deal with Russian President Vladimir Putin during their at times heated discussions at the White House last week, according to… https://t.co/uAmcEwXbtk https://t.co/MjBI7UHmvD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: The smearing of Ronny Jackson is a disgrace: The shameful smearing of Dr. Ronny Jackson, the White House physician who was nominated by President Donald Trump to be Secretary of the Veterans Affairs Administration and has now withdrawn, is… https://t.co/Hk2Nqp4AMQ https://t.co/CiuWEZYyNE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$99 &amp; up: DC-area Hilton summer sale deals https://t.co/S7xorXb4yG https://t.co/wGwaJmzBLI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jazz could hold the key to creativity in your brain: Fingers graze a keyboard, poised to play. A trumpet rises to the lips. Drumsticks perch in the air, ready to fall. The improv begins, and this combo of jazz musicians instantly creates a piece of music… https://t.co/fyVoZOnsKH https://t.co/zfKZbyeCDh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As Pompeo's star rises in Trumpland, Haley and Kushner risk getting eclipsed https://t.co/os1cE6h5GI https://t.co/iGdFs0yoqD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[North Korea will invite US experts in after shutting nuclear site in May, South says: North Korean leader Kim Jong Un told South Korean President Moon Jae-in that he will close his main nuclear test site in May and invite experts and journalists from the… https://t.co/DfCmitpgLI https://t.co/zIRcruRSGe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time's up, Bill Cosby: Bill Cosby's legal team attempted to use "Rape Culture 101" tactics to discredit his accuser in court, but the guilty verdict handed down Thursday demonstrates that the days of blaming women for the sexual violence and crimes of… https://t.co/LQ0VXPTu8f https://t.co/xE0W1nnKE4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US doubles down on tracking North Korea: The intelligence community is doubling down on tracking North Korea as a potential one-on-one meeting between President Donald Trump and Kim Jong Un draws closer, following a historic summit between the North… https://t.co/428OMw9DUS https://t.co/3hZshwsAP6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eagles draft rugby player who hasn't played football https://t.co/xFC6RvgNQ0 https://t.co/J359D8ubin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Immigration Sponsorship for F1 or OPT Visaed Registered Nurse only: Seeking qualified foreign students on a student visa or on OPT to join our green card sponsorship program. U.S. Nursing License and F-1 Visa or OPT REQUIRED. You will receive a permanent… https://t.co/WqlbDYXZk4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CNN reporter follows a caravan of migrants: CNN's Leyla Santiago is in Puebla, Mexico, tracking the caravan of Central American migrants that drew the attention of the President. https://t.co/RFgvkLE4q7 https://t.co/TY2Kzs4Lgl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teams make day 2 draft picks https://t.co/FshDYorZzv https://t.co/EMNxCXOhDF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Amazon made Prime into an indispensable product you'd pay anything for https://t.co/5oarVcvYkU https://t.co/8f3wUqpCWq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's the ex-con coal exec the GOP fears could be their nominee: Watching Republican Senate candidate Don Blankenship on the campaign trail, he does not immediately come across as someone his party leaders would be concerned about. https://t.co/5VIAgve2Y0 https://t.co/bEo6jdX4PW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Airbus can't get enough engines for its planes https://t.co/2sdh1JcXLs https://t.co/MleMTN4fPG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inside the dramatic collapse of Ronny Jackson's bid to lead the VA: Dr. Ronny Jackson exuded confidence when he emerged from a Capitol Hill office Tuesday evening, telling reporters that he looked forward to answering tough questions from lawmakers about… https://t.co/2ZALy23Bpq https://t.co/mgcIj0FFSz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suspected Golden State Killer is set to appear in court: A man who police believe is the Golden State Killer will be arraigned Friday as police continue looking for more clues that connect him to the decades-old crimes. https://t.co/hOU5IDUf3O https://t.co/zJgucZHdYi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hollywood sounds off: As Bill Cosby faced a retrial for allegedly drugging and sexually assaulting a woman in 2004, there was a question as to whether the #MeToo and Time's Up movements against sexual abuse would factor into his case. https://t.co/FRZNYJ4kZK https://t.co/vDIY43v7ez]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Millennials explain why they have nothing saved for retirement https://t.co/4Z4INDoNmb https://t.co/GveCWZpiuk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goodell to use NFL legends as draft 'boo insurance' https://t.co/QWyizFVdVa https://t.co/3AZ4RVPxHz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A one-handed fighter gets a chance at a UFC contract https://t.co/CiDCjIgFaX https://t.co/uuvsc9RvKv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sexual harassment blind spot you don't know about: In the wake of #MeToo, we know that we are all protected by law from workplace discrimination, right? https://t.co/BTFEpuHEL1 https://t.co/5zijGfIZcb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See who didn't make royal wedding invite list: Prince Harry and Meghan Markle have released their wedding invitation list. CNN's Max Foster reports on who made it, and who didn't. https://t.co/Vd2E2jMTSR https://t.co/8xMYGAd0iR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Concealing the Clinton email probe status would have been 'catastrophic,' Comey says: Describing his decision as the best of two bad choices, former FBI Director James Comey said Wednesday that informing the public about the status of the Hillary Clinton… https://t.co/tfiInKkVKf https://t.co/FiQR1OwAnv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Golden State Killer is accused of 12 killings and 45 rapes over 40 years: A person believed to be the so-called Golden State Killer -- accused of 12 killings and 45 rapes across California from 1976 to 1986 -- is under arrest and in custody, FBI… https://t.co/lcb2ImSbbt https://t.co/CXVzhd9e3f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China fears Kim is moving out of its orbit as South Korea, US talks loom: China and North Korea boast an alliance forged in blood -- more than 130,000 Chinese troops, including the son of Mao Zedong, died defending the North during the Korean War -- but… https://t.co/kjYXepyQkM https://t.co/zHnjciJelV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meek Mill is released from prison: Meek Mill is a free man. https://t.co/0nyWboeqND https://t.co/zhXGAlDnVe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge orders reopening of DACA, after 90-day delay: Another federal judge has overruled the Trump administration's efforts to end a popular immigration program -- this time saying the government has to accept new applications. https://t.co/jt87VCy7yp https://t.co/vjd99Yxfpv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The other man responsible in Waffle House shooting: Travis Reinking, the man alleged to have shot up a Waffle House and snuffed out the lives of four innocent souls, thankfully is in custody. But he's not the only one who should pay for this terrible… https://t.co/13ufyDmYAb https://t.co/sFYz653k7r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why NFL teams are worried that he plays 10 instruments https://t.co/eELz7X19EF https://t.co/ccDHW3FrRe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The young President is cozying up to Trump, realizing he needs the US to help restore France's prestige: Donald Trump is not the only President who wants to make his country great again -- his first state dinner guest, Emmanuel Macron, wants to do the… https://t.co/4WwsEMILq5 https://t.co/WmsGjQvL2D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Study: Drinkers have more bad mouth bacteria: Your mouth naturally contains about 700 types of bacteria, some good but others not so much. The mouths of people who routinely drank one or more alcoholic beverages each day contained an overabundance of bad… https://t.co/anmxCcBvZN https://t.co/hiU5MS6bXA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See the royal baby: The Duchess of Cambridge, wife of Britain's Prince William, has given birth to a son, the royal family announced Monday. https://t.co/3IJ3vLlDR3 https://t.co/8Tcyqv1Ybh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Romney to face US Senate primary: Mitt Romney did not win the Utah Republican Party's nomination on Saturday, meaning he must compete in a June primary election as he seeks to replace retiring US Sen. Orrin Hatch. https://t.co/SaDtEnuNjN https://t.co/REQcSLTvgx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's huge law and order blind spot https://t.co/v86uIrSeGW https://t.co/2VJgkzKrhK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man hailed as hero: It could've been me: James Shaw Jr. talks with CNN's Fredricka Whitfield about his encounter with a gunman in a Waffle House near Nashville, Tennessee. https://t.co/esZDg67Pvb https://t.co/u85zLmbkKg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10 of our favorite historic lodges at national parks: Waking up near the rim of the Grand Canyon, at the edge of a Yellowstone geyser or within view of a Hawaiian volcano are some of the highlights of these hotels in the USA. https://t.co/l8oSsCneKr https://t.co/DU05rE4yJj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He dated a white woman, and the Justice Department called it a 'crime against nature': On Saturday, President Donald Trump said he was weighing whether or not to grant a posthumous pardon to boxer Jack Johnson, after it was suggested to him by actor… https://t.co/UFf5O5Dx8I https://t.co/frmZ74qQ7w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Verne Troyer's family mentions suicide in announcing his death: Verne Troyer, who played Mini-Me in two of the Austin Powers comedy films, has died at the age of 49, according to statements posted to his social media accounts Saturday. https://t.co/Q54WdPEZZe https://t.co/PnN3uL7HvW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will Gronkowski play this year? 'Maybe.' But if he does, he promises a 'freak-a-leak' https://t.co/pVkzMmXSxp https://t.co/9kHVhmVXKI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why LA's Mexican-American-Jewish-Italian mayor is in Iowa and South Carolina: Eric Garcetti isn't exactly a natural fit in Iowa. https://t.co/JuOsGLATUP https://t.co/tkP4IUJNXx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysis: A high for marijuana legalization: Marijuana in the past was considered taboo in American culture and politics. Just check out the "Saved by the Bell" episode, "No Hope With Dope." https://t.co/nALXBalR5M https://t.co/j8PeyUyXGO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Death of McMaster's father 'suspicious': Philadelphia police are investigating last week's death of H.R. McMaster's father as "suspicious," the department told CNN on Thursday. https://t.co/Vhbq5EaPZV https://t.co/VqbLWZUWMs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will Power wins Indy 500 https://t.co/jnHe2BuVuz https://t.co/E9UUbuRYvQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Deadpool' franchise is a box office rarity: An R-rated hit https://t.co/xMtY3W03Zf https://t.co/RIWmrBgMPM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Survivor of near-fatal tick bite has a lesson for everyone: On the eve of Memorial Day weekend, Jennifer Slone wants you to know that bug bites are more than just itchy. They can be deadly. https://t.co/2V66ohmMkq https://t.co/xChLB0Udbn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On this Memorial Day, remember the trauma of 1968: America was a mess on Memorial Day 1968. https://t.co/kbpPA7WunY https://t.co/hEzwTnWe30]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Best places to go this summer https://t.co/mfKn7vKORN https://t.co/XcXEWNVIg3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UFC star arrested for domestic violence https://t.co/wLB0AToEsm https://t.co/hfBybx7THu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Border Patrol union chief calls National Guard deployment 'a colossal waste': The leader of the union that represents Border Patrol agents slammed the deployment of National Guard troops to the border by the Trump administration, calling it "a colossal… https://t.co/PXS6oyfxkO https://t.co/PYII3Ch8VM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Assange's refuge in Ecuadorian embassy 'in jeopardy': Julian Assange's nearly six-year refuge at the Ecuadorian embassy in London is in danger, opening the WikiLeaks founder to arrest by British authorities and potential extradition to the US, multiple… https://t.co/eX7qrht0Y6 https://t.co/FxWBIIKhaF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two people wounded at Louie's Grill &amp; Bar, police in Oklahoma City say: Police in Oklahoma City are investigating a shooting at a restaurant near Lake Hefner Parkway. https://t.co/TPDSxqKFwF https://t.co/L9i8gI6zlx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Using a CPAP machine can improve sex lives for some: Regular use of a continuous positive airway pressure or CPAP machine could improve the sex lives of people with obstructive sleep apnea -- especially women, a new study says. https://t.co/LEx0seAcsp https://t.co/zDwctWrehR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cameraman to Cohen: You gonna flip on Trump?: Michael Cohen is seen being chased almost every day by the press on the sidewalks of New York. So what's it like to be in Michael Cohen's shoes ... literally? CNN's Jeanne Moos reports. https://t.co/XnwOD8EX5s https://t.co/5K1e02Zdhn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See Weinstein leave in handcuffs: Harvey Weinstein leaves the NYPD precinct in handcuffs after he was arrested, processed and charged with rape, criminal sex act, sex abuse and sexual misconduct for incidents involving two separate women. https://t.co/iraOgH4P5B https://t.co/Wl4q7wqu4N]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>