<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[This is so exciting! I can’t wait. https://t.co/3GdJO2FQRE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yay! https://t.co/hLWdYZhZxa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @benjaminwolk: Kim Jung Un has turned down the Tennessee job https://t.co/3o4a0XtSRC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @richarddeitsch: NBC will announce today that it will air more than 2,400 hours of coverage of the 2018 Olympic Winter Games from Pyeong…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The @KathyWilsonFndn is an awesome #nonprofit in #alexandriava to support for #GivingTuesday https://t.co/WaES4ZIlnk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Brett_McMurphy: After Kevin Sumlin’s firing &amp; Dan Mullen to UF Sunday, there have been 28 head coaching changes in the SEC since Nick S…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[😳 https://t.co/4ca8UxizmR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BillKristol: The highest ranking Republican in the nation, Donald Trump, is pro-Roy Moore.
The highest ranking Democrat in the nation,…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That Lisa McKinnon dress is gorgeous on Ashley. #fierce #SkateAmerica]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m so happy for Serefima! I loved her skating when she was a junior. Glad to see her have some success with Plushenko. #SkateAmerica]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That’s the best I’ve seen Sakhanovich skate in a long time. #SkateAmerica]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s so weird to see Plushenko at the boards. #SkateAmerica]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@olyphil I was trying to watch #OSUvsMICH and #SkateAmerica at the same time this afternoon. I get it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bradie is a very pleasant and consistent skater. But she lacks that special spark. She doesn’t have the x-factor. #SkateAmerica]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NickMcCarvel: Nathan Chen becomes the first US man to win both his Grand Prix assignments since Johnny Weir did so in 2007 #SkateAmerica]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @olyphil: Props to Adam Rippon for making Grand Prix Final less than a year after foot surgery.   He saw an opening and grabbed it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow. Adam won the free skate #SkateAmerica]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SkatingLesson: Adam trains his spins. Respect.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The bird program is probably my favorite Adam program. #SkateAmerica]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get well soon Danny! #SkateAmerica]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @icenetwork: Daniel Samohin fell on his second quad attempt and immediately grabbed his left shoulder. He has left the ice. #SkateAmerica]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh no! Daniel’s hurt! #SkateAmerica]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FOX19Jeremy: I spoke with someone who saw what happened with JT Barrett. They viewed what happened with JT as malicious, not accidental…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AriWasserman: Urban Meyer said the JT Barrett injury was a non football injury and a camera man hit him in the knee. Meyer said he’s so…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ESPNStatsInfo: Jim Harbaugh joins Rich Rodriguez as the only Michigan coaches to lose their first three games aganst Ohio State. https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SportsCenter: Another year, another @OhioStateFB win over Michigan.

That's six straight. https://t.co/0OhXWiyDlh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FakeUrban: #sorrynotsorry https://t.co/kcYYOsMTRm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @darrenrovell: Vs. Ohio State:

Jim Harbaugh, 0-3
Brady Hoke, 1-3
Rich Rodriguez, 0-3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BillLandis25: Ohio State's quarterback depth saved the Buckeyes. Michigan's lack of quarterback depth killed the Wolverines]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @icenetwork: The ISU announces that Maxim Kovtun has withdrawn from #SkateAmerica because of a right foot injury.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @YahooDrSaturday: This player could be seriously injured AND NOW A QUICK MESSAGE FROM DURACELL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who decided to have #SkateAmerica at the same time as #OSUvsMICH?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always give the ball to Dobbins. #OSUvsMICH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a nightmare. #OSUvsMICH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This first quarter #OSUvsMICH https://t.co/GuBz08V2OS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sparker388 This is a disaster]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @huskerextra: It's official: Mike Riley has been fired as #Huskers football coach.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PeteThamel: SOURCES: UCLA is finalizing a deal to make Chip Kelly the next coach there. An agreement is expected by the end of the week…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @USFigureSkating: Ok. You do you, @nathanwchen. The U.S. champ scores 104.12, a new personal best, and takes the lead with one skater le…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SkatingLesson: Everything about Nathan says Olympic Champion. He has every ingredient.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just love Nathan’s short this year. #SkateAmerica #slaythan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SkatingLesson: The stars are aligning for Nathan Chen to become Olympic Champion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank goodness https://t.co/h9wG8E9RNr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ifsmagazine: Ilia Tkachenko unable to obtain Israeli citizenship so no Olympics for he and Isabella Tobias. https://t.co/ATOubWCU9t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ifsmagazine: Evgenia Medvedeva revealed doctors diagnosed a crack in the metatarsal bone of the right foot, which may stop her from com…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I joined the lottery for $30 tix to #MeanGirlsBway at @NatTheatreDC on @TodayTix! https://t.co/EHr12DfIs8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just entered to win! https://t.co/4oku0LqKty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[thebandsvisit is the best show on #broadway. It’s grown so much since @atlantictheater.… https://t.co/siQdW15D7h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A magical evening for #brigadoonnycc @nycitycenter with @kelliohara, @robbiefairchild,… https://t.co/jU9JUO0TPc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A fantastic afternoon onceislandbway philliptheboycan @HaileyKilgore @msleasalonga #broadway… https://t.co/9WjNwIzWq7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Periryan @robbiefairchild @NYCityCenter I was there last night too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JonathanBeyer81 @SkatingLesson Don’t let them get to you! I always appreciate your commentary especially with your background and knowledge in music. *hugs*]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @icenetwork: Gabby and Guillaume do it again, breaking their own world records for free dance score and total score! #IFP2017 https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NBCOlympics: Gracie Gold to miss U.S. Championships, #WinterOlympics: https://t.co/9mGJM3qDQo https://t.co/pulXt5MDiO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This delay is really long..... #IFP2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ifsmagazine: The International Olympic Committee will decide on Dec. 5 if Russia can compete at the PyeongChang Winter Games. https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Periryan: Love that the mascot @ #IFP2017 is the Bumble from Rudolph The Red-Nosed Reindeer... https://t.co/39zHzMtmrl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Yeti in Grenoble? #IFP2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JonathanBeyer81: Well...Who knew a Barbie could have such a nice triple triple combo ;) @SkatingLesson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sotskova, that dress is kinda a mess. #IFP17]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Zagitova opened the door. Who will walk through it? #IFP2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can’t wait to see Brigadoon this weekend! #BrigadoonNYCC https://t.co/c216301SIb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeepersdebbie My brother was with me and he’s like is he one of your theater friends? 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeepersdebbie He actually said Hi Natalie to me when I ran into him before Torch Song 😂]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ForecasterEnten: Sexual assault/harassment is not one party's problem. It's the country's problem.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes we get a special visitor at the office. #Nosey #Cats #alexandriava #catsofinstagram @… https://t.co/M9eWV6BzSq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Brett_McMurphy: UM beats Notre Dame 41-8. Last time Irish played unbeaten team on road in November was 2004 at USC &amp; Irish lost 41-10.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SkatingLesson: Madison Hubbell has just come alive in 2017.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Brett_McMurphy: This loss will severely damage Notre Dame’s chances to win a conference championship]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m that person going between #collegefootball &amp; #FigureSkating. #NHK17 #NDvsMIA #BAMAvsMSST]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chrisfallica: Notre Dame has been outscored 55-0 in the 1st half in its last two games in this building. 28-0 vs Alabama in 2012 Champi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mark Richt is having fun #NDvsMIA #CatholicsVsConvicts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[😳 https://t.co/tOOL426zbj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Turnover chain! #NDvsMiami #CatholicsVsConvicts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @espn: No. 13 Ohio State 48, No. 12 Michigan State 3

The Buckeyes hand the Spartans the most-lopsided loss of the Mark Dantonio era. ht…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Adaripp: 10 months ago, I was off the ice with a broken foot. Today, I turned 28 and feel stronger than before my injury. Age is only a…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KirkHerbstreit: I’m sorry, but seriously boys, has the @bigten lost a bowl game?!?? Keep piling it on boys!!! What happen to “strong, p…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SportsCenter: The Big Ten has been perfect in bowl season.

The Pac-12 has been, well ... https://t.co/TdI9KP7TtG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @espn: That 7-game losing streak to USC is no more. https://t.co/6W8KsaGA4V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ESPNStatsInfo: Urban Meyer's 11th bowl win ties Nick Saban and Kyle Whittingham for most by active FBS coaches. Whittingham picked up h…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#USC’s just keeping it classy #CottonBowl #GoBucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Loving this game right now #CottonBowl #GoBucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Sari_W Wisconsin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jeepersdebbie Semi-annual sale success!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SI_PeterKing: Merry Christmas everyone.
On Christmas, @LarryFitzgerald writes a tribute to his friend, @SenJohnMcCain for @theMMQB. Wha…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@LisaKot Just say they’re for Orthodox Christmas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NBCNightlyNews: JUST IN: Olympic gymnastics star McKayla Maroney files suit; alleges that USA Gymnastics tried to silence her from shar…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[🙄 https://t.co/WVizDv0Qd6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ifsmagazine: Evgenia Medvedeva is out of Russian nationals this week according to Russian news reports. Her cast was removed a week ago…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SInow: Breaking: John Skipper resigns as ESPN president, the company announces. https://t.co/LcQoBzBpkh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I’m not crying. 😭 😭 😭 https://t.co/sKQskLV2iS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RichLowry: Lesson for the GOP: if there is a bridge too far in Alabama, there is a bridge too far in every other state where Steve Bann…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LizMair: One of a handful of times in my life when I can say I'm really, genuinely not sorry the Republican lost.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nytimes: As far back as 1993, dancers have accused Peter Martins, the powerful ballet master in chief, of verbal and physical abuse htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PeterSaccoDC @DCCirculator It runs on snowflakes and hot chocolate!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WesTayTay &amp; @ethansaslater after @spongebobbway #plankton #spongebobsquarepants… https://t.co/FiaP70GbCW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celebrating the 80th Anniversary of @disney’s Snow White &amp; the Seven Dwarfs @saks #saksholiday… https://t.co/3EKn24XCLO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celebrating the 80th Anniversary of @disney’s Snow White &amp; the Seven Dwarfs @saks #snowwhite… https://t.co/xaG1xiHJVL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Experiencing the light show for the 80th Anniversary of @disney’s Snow White &amp; the Seven Dwarfs… https://t.co/go0soQV4KO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#RockinAroundTheChristmasTree rockcenternyc #themostwonderfultimeoftheyear #winterwonderland… https://t.co/RidFny2f2Y]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>