<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[What if we feared nothing? What if we didn't allow fear to torment us at all? What if we just did what we needed to do with no hesitation?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seek clarity - ask questions - never assume.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I found this on Pinterest!
https://t.co/gb8QyUB7nv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Current Read: "Boundaries" by Dr. Henry Cloud and Dr. John Townsend]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More education = More power]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be simple + Be grateful = Happiness]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WomenOfHistory: Great reminder. https://t.co/QkChlO9gwY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Quote_Soup: If you desire to make a difference in the world, you must be different from the world.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FamousWomen: Peace is not the absense of trouble, but the presence of Christ.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @evangelistmatt: Worship your worries away. Our God is bigger than anything you face.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love to learn and my learning will never end #allforthekids....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is freedom in getting out debt - there is a goal behind getting out of debt - a home with no mortgage.....#DaveRamsey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let patience have its perfect work...James 1:4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Words to live by: Love, Forgive and Serve.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Say YES to GOD and see all that GOD will do in you and in your life!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am a great SAVAGE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm not obsessed with money, I'm obsessed with freedom.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter what - remain positive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is one of my thought journals......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't have regrets - just great lessons.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm building an empire and it won't be easy.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FamousWomen: Give love away like your life depends on it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SBSDHealthy: Located this lovely quotation on @jenjgb73's inspirational Twitter page &amp; am grateful to share. Thank you, @edutopia. http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheQuoteToday: Far too many..

#quote #life https://t.co/c7x1PTvUyD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Quote_Soup: By being yourself, you put something wonderful in the world that was not there before. - Edwin Elliot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LV_Sports: Great attitude. https://t.co/O2Gh4YFPRS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enjoy every moment of your life - it is so short.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Speak excellent and extraordinary things over you and those you love DAILY.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GOD love + self-love - are the best kinds of love....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I blame it on me - its my fault. I did it so I can correct it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She's: a black queen, brilliant, wise, forgiving, learning to let of offenses quickly, self-educated, self-motivated, driven, ambitious and loves the children.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is nothing without love + forgiveness + fun......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My LIFE: God, Me, Family, Friends, Legacy, Bless!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are worthy of all that is awaiting you...walk through the doors proudly.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We all have multiple talents....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LV_Sports: Accept responsibility for the good and the bad. https://t.co/8CbDCV0S9l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All I see are my dreams as true....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Imagine only good things happening to you, over and over again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fear is torment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I fear - fear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When they go low - always go high......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am grateful for: love, the light, truth, freedom, salvation, my dreams, my hopes, the children, the ability to see, hear, smell and touch.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never stop imagining myself winning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just love them more. When they hate you, love them more.
When they say mean things, love them more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OCBFChurch: Faith that forgives is the faith that moves mountains. https://t.co/PS442ziWGN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @educationweek: Teachers recognize those who "dive into the fray" with us. https://t.co/LS4q7rgGGt #ewopinion https://t.co/TmBU8dXdP0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DavidRoads: Live bold. https://t.co/NL171gdnDT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LifeLimits: Respect yourself enough to walk away from anything that no longer grows you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @God_Loved: When you pray, don't give God instructions... Just report for duty!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am SOOOOOOOO grateful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't believe what "they' say, believe what GOD says.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always follow your passions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Epic_Women: Life is all about taking risks. If you never take risks, then you'll never know what you're capable of.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LifeLimits: GREAT ADVICE https://t.co/Urqqa3N60y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WomenOfHistory: Sometimes you have to forget what's gone, appreciate what remains, and look forward to what's coming next.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How do you want to be remembered?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its not that we cannot fly - we just put on our wings - thank you LaShone Bulter]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must teach our children to create by using social media - not merely be entertained by social media.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intense hard work + Diligence + Patience = Results]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It must be about reaching all of your possibilities.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have an unstoppable spirit.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cthagod I say the ones that have nothing....because if you took more time to focus on your own stuff you wouldn't have to worry about what others are doing...just my opinion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Quote_Soup: Looking back, makes you smart. 
Looking forward, makes you mature. 
Looking down, makes you wise. 
Looking UP, makes you st…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WomenOfHistory: You are GOOD enough, SMART enough, BEAUTIFUL enough, and STRONG enough. Believe it and never let insecurity run your li…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @lnspire_me: Be strong https://t.co/a926KY6vVs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Quote_Soup: Do what you feel in your heart to be right - for you'll be criticized anyway. -Eleanor Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm into this minimalist lifestyle.....
Wanting less and less.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your flaws don't define you as a person - they show your humanity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are brilliant - and don't ever forget it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is something liberating in not being offended by the things said and done to you. Feel it but don't let the offense mess up your moment and life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't aspire to be wealthy - I aspire to make my children wealthy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What I see, others don't see and there is something magical in that......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am grateful for a love that is so unconditional and so forgiving of me and my flaws.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GOD is LOVE - and we show the world GOD by loving others well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I believe in speaking things into existence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Action kills all fear!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The heavens never want you to FEAR - fear is tormenting. Just think about it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[May the student in us - never die.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must teach our children to have their own business alongside their job - they quit their job when their business can sustain their lifestyle.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must teach children at age 5 to start their own business.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wealth is mine - but it will be given to the children.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't worry about things you cannot control.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happiness is your responsibility. I mean known else knows you that well.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Take the limits off so faith cam make you fly.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A changed perspective can lead to a changed life....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must decide to take the limits off -]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hate being afraid to do something -- thank you Will Smith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think Tiffany Haddish is so dope - she's so down to earth, honest and funny on so many levels....Hollywood not ready for you, but you are surely ready for Hollywood!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRealDaytime You deserve it - great show....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ChrisBrownOnAir: THIS WEEK on the show! 

We have a choice each day. https://t.co/30wI4JrSma]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was yesterday - today is a new day....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live the dream - don't merely think about it.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DavidRoads: The happiness of your life depends upon the quality of your thoughts.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With freedom follow every great idea.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being the best ME I could ever BE is all that matters to ME.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Fit_Motivator: #Motivation #Inspiration https://t.co/Gcn8XpeJ9M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LV_Sports: So true! Work = Results no exceptions. https://t.co/ZhI2JebgGZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful girls are happy girls.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must teach our children, empower, build up our children.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is only way to become all that we are capable of - by becoming all that we are capable of.........]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>