<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Think about what a user is going to type. - Matt Cutts - Google]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The roots of education are bitter, but the fruit is sweet. - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Star Trek Enterprise Pizza Cutter! http://t.co/vXpBT7nqG2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Top Secrets for Using Facebook Pages for Your Business  http://t.co/QkC1M7IBJI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Orleans  http://t.co/gBOUu4QTcv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Uriah Heep  http://t.co/zscaPWFtLU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It ain't over 'til it's over - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[College isn't the place to go for ideas. - Helen Keller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two big firms are fighting for his services, the loser gets him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read about the Emerging Threats From An Electromagnetic Pulse Attack  http://t.co/34e1SZKwXS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's so timid he wouldn't open an oyster without first knocking on the shell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool 14' Iceberg For Your Pool or the Lake! http://t.co/BYKYNnYwrz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Lewisville, Texas  http://t.co/us7mf6TYXM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Peter Townshend shows us it's all right to grow up. There is dignity after rock'n'roll. - Sting]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out Crimson Mine’s awesome Tumblr page... http://t.co/Mxo1TVgs3w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cowboys, Mavs, Rangers and more read about the Sports teams of the Dallas Fort-Worth Metroplex - http://t.co/7Xs69YwCFo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space Invaders Taito Astronaut Video Game T-Shirt Tee  http://t.co/pvbvP1ihgS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advertising is the life of trade. - Calvin Coolidge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is A Derivative?  http://t.co/9o1FtIdrSt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The universe, as far as we can observe it, is a wonderful and immense engine. - George Santayana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Joe Simon  http://t.co/RxJzsh1U80]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gary US Bonds was an amazing musician and rocker - read his history - http://t.co/zEas0Ws08g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Home is where -- . You hang your head]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are 10 types of people in the world: those who understand binary, and those who don't.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome kayaking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the paddling lovers in your life!  http://t.co/EsNQlN6GvC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion changes, but style endures. --&gt; Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion is what you adopt when you don't know who you are. --&gt; Quentin Crisp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Book The Queen's Empire  http://t.co/QtZ1IFpUSQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Using Instagram for Web Marketing  http://t.co/uhIn4Ol2CB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this Scientific Explorer's Mind Blowing Science Kit! http://t.co/B7BoBnFGcM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About GPS Technology and Fitness Watches  http://t.co/e1a2a6dlbj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to J.R.R. Tolkien  http://t.co/wvU0T7jDFf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A girl should be two things: classy and fabulous. - Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trust people and they will be true to you; Treat them greatly, and they will show themselves great. - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just got my Google Chromecast HDMI Streaming Media Player - SO COOL - http://t.co/5kIoUlDrpZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I look at modeling as something I'm doing for black people in general. Naomi Campbell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A mosquito is just like a child, when it stops making noise, you know it's getting into something.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding the Right Fitness Gadgets  http://t.co/3npPvLAlcJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the fascinating history of that classic baseball park - Wrigley Field - http://t.co/IRWVzXg1lz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have a very striking face. How many times were you struck there?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awe cool - A Lock N' load target alarm clock/Gun alarm clock - shoot the dang thing! http://t.co/GPSsZi3wKi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winning is everything. The only ones who remember you when you come second are your wife and your dog. - Damon Hill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give a girl the right shoes, and she can conquer the world. - Marilyn Monroe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Importance of Keywords for Search Engine Optimization (SEO)  http://t.co/Voaoy8RTFy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An extravagance is anything you buy that is of no earthly use to your wife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Michael Jordan Shoes  http://t.co/SC1iI9350G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Natalie Cole  http://t.co/NN3roD0g13]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome soccer t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the soccer lovers in your life!   http://t.co/mAWDHSZJRJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Simple Way to Bond with Kids? Use Cooking!  http://t.co/a1Ug3vYfwu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to the Chitika Ad Network - An Alternate to Google AdSense  http://t.co/fUFfcuDyCO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Faster, faster, faster, until the thrill of speed overcomes the fear of death --  - Hunter Thompson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the Little House on the Prairie Episode The Nephews  http://t.co/1sZjCzWf75]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have no use for bodyguards, but I have very specific use for two highly trained certified public accountants. - Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Steve Miller Band  http://t.co/Ho2O4GznO1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Seniors and Social Networking  http://t.co/U0EFSNBrqY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious T-Shirt - “I Got Your Back” http://t.co/pGm1qWDMeS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of Young Samurai: The Way of the Warrior  http://t.co/LqF3aCbsnN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Pat Benatar  http://t.co/ZiqLLOGQKG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Players have been bought, sold and exchanged as though they were sheep instead of American citizens. - John Montgomery Ward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The worst examples of snap judgment are usually found in the old family album]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In youth we learn in age, we understand.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, I understand when they make a mistake and everyone at home is throwing their shoe at the television set. - Vanna White]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you chase two rabbits, both will escape. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where to find Great Gluten Free Recipes  http://t.co/7mO2PvWqaZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it time to go home yet? I keep clicking these damn shoes, but nothing happens. - Robin Hecht]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't read other science fiction. I don't read any at all. - Jack Vance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is Horology?  http://t.co/IxP0Rh9zqQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You are flirting with danger when you buy high-heeled sandals - Eileen Allen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Linda Ronstadt  http://t.co/CQqnpdgdwN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gotta love this Minecraft wall torch - http://t.co/JtVxNPo1qg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I live in heels. Give me a pair of flip-flops and I'll trip all over myself. - Brenda Song]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Kalin Twins  http://t.co/60H3xLA0ub]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snow and adolescence are about the only things that disappear if you ignore them long enough]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Google Webmaster Tools  http://t.co/mu2rwcU9g2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Paul McCartney and Wings  http://t.co/b5hOMnbhqC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one is too big to be kind and courteous, but many are too little]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada has Great Tourism Just Across the Border  http://t.co/6CrtYEPejX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The studios have been taken over by marketing people and accountants. - Joe Eszterhas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A shoe has so much more to offer than just to walk. - Christian Louboutin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can never be overdressed or overeducated. --&gt; Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who think they know everything are especially annoying to those of us who do]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your Business Guide for Small Business Internet Marketing  http://t.co/NJLCIgQvCD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the Lorax Movie     http://t.co/4hAPufhaIX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Superhero caped glasses - totally cool!  http://t.co/AjsrTSHnu4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome tennis t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the tennis lovers in your life!   http://t.co/Qipxlc8axR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Their marriage is a partnership, he's the silent partner.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Grapevine, Texas  http://t.co/WzK2uvmACA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Rolling Stones  http://t.co/pJtyLCvwFT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making money is a hobby that will complement any other hobbies you have, beautifully. Scott Alexander]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Let's Play: LOTR Ep 1: Meeting the Hobbits  http://t.co/8Y0caEiy6A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The good Lord gave you a body that can stand most anything. It's your mind you have to convince. - Vincent Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1f u c4n r34d th1s u r34lly n33d t0 g37 l41d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In order to break the ice --  crack a smile]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Flying Alarm Clock - COOL!  http://t.co/VCvvBfaZoT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All our dreams can come true -- if we have the courage to pursue them. - Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Overview of the X-Files  http://t.co/OPtngOfN4o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going Camping? – Select the Right Equipment!  http://t.co/K8DnQRfjAE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yesterday our troubles seemed so far away, I believe in yesterday. - The Beatles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mr. Bentley - He builds fast trucks. - Ettore Bugatti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is not preparation for life; education is life itself. - John Dewey]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>