<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: @marcthiessen: Kavanaugh's fate — Prosecutor Rachel Mitchell may be the ... https://t.co/k8fvsfK6Vw https://t.co/Y4Pm8v8hYA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: For his latest exhibition, artist Nick Gentry uses old technology to craft portraits and sculptures https://t.co/xys8KWhkZL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BuzzFeedNews: A US Navy veteran was arrested in connection to ricin-laced letters ... https://t.co/TV03OJblGa https://t.co/zU4KOUBYGW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: .@LindseyGrahamSC on Kavanaugh’s confirmation chance: “I’ve never felt more ... https://t.co/pU2Nr8bKtw https://t.co/CrL7RQGXLl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: Stroke patient's smile restored after pioneering surgery https://t.co/E1kT7MniGs https://t.co/aio3shKOnx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AP: Senate Majority Leader Mitch McConnell has set a crucial threshold vote on Brett ... https://t.co/IU6CQhIUL7 https://t.co/gF4sBR5WzC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cnnbrk: A California federal judge temporarily blocked Trump's administration from ... https://t.co/2rGEkPW8Tr https://t.co/fb3dCdRj00]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @realDonaldTrump: My thoughts and prayers are with the Florence County Sheriff’s ... https://t.co/aYIo3NigbU https://t.co/X2caOuK1NY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: Louis Vuitton debuts futuristic, crystal-strewn looks at Paris Fashion Week https://t.co/kIAtARzzBS https://t.co/8Hx1G1o3aE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: Connie Chung claims she was sexually assaulted during college. https://t.co/CAwDJNkcRD https://t.co/1HGiZLxUcj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WSJ: Barnes &amp; Noble to evaluate strategic alternatives, including possible sale, ... https://t.co/bWG8AgnTdt https://t.co/nNvji15mjW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: With an American flag in hand, Wayne Parfitt takes to the streets once or ... https://t.co/aFeqibiCfD https://t.co/4nPpJRJ5ZA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AP: 'When all you have are rich, white men discussing policies, things will never ... https://t.co/7wzN3HCVfH https://t.co/7bm0rafqCV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WSJ: In Alaska, the battle for Lisa Murkowski's vote on the Kavanaugh nomination is ... https://t.co/bb5fKGTiz5 https://t.co/O0uNmOQPSm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: Bezos' space company designing large lunar lander https://t.co/kNB0kzKETb https://t.co/w0l8I1IycA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BuzzFeedNews: Jonathan Bennett spent #MeanGirlsDay Eve handing out copies of his new ... https://t.co/jRAPWeH9ef https://t.co/eOKochLOyu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: .@SenJohnKennedy: "Both the accuser and the accused are entitled to respect ... https://t.co/bPsq0cOoHs https://t.co/EfYxwxxZsA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WSJ: What happens when an extreme weather event hits a home where the risk was ... https://t.co/8vHb2CU6tB https://t.co/HMef2JUXBN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: NASCAR announces big rule changes for 2019 https://t.co/RDVSvnFQZ9 https://t.co/IKjtuUrPPF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: Seema Kashyap, Timsy Dhawan, Nida Mahmood and fashion label Madame close out Delhi Times Fashion Week https://t.co/2VKoC5ZYfU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: UK Prime Minister Theresa May dances onto the stage at ... https://t.co/sZrU1SBDBS https://t.co/z4uh2V49OW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: Vandalism suspect says he's 'happy' about damage outside local Republican ... https://t.co/zOVfwZHK0z https://t.co/Eu39cORaJZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: .@madisongesiotto on Judge Kavanaugh’s temperament: “Anybody who’s been, as ... https://t.co/g60xHCABxj https://t.co/9PTiQBZKDy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: .@JohnJamesMI: "I promise that I will lead in Washington the way I led in ... https://t.co/ogJiP5rWtf https://t.co/UN89uUcfqM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BBCBreaking: Zoe Ball is to take over as presenter of BBC Radio 2 Breakfast Show ... https://t.co/iMS6YfORx4 https://t.co/4hWfciXMuj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: President @realDonaldTrump: "This is really an incredible time for our nation. We are respected again." https://t.co/cYe2hXbIRt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: Jonathan Turley: “Any answer that is not openly and frankly embarrassing and ... https://t.co/JgANp7HKBM https://t.co/j4Fht1vJvO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: .@JesseBWatters on @HillaryClinton bashing @POTUS supporters: "Every time ... https://t.co/enQZThXiyF https://t.co/898rERxVI9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: Requested of Dr. Ford’s legal team: https://t.co/oEqs4QJ2gx https://t.co/oAsnJI0Dx1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AP: The Senate majority leader says the chamber will vote this week on Supreme Court ... https://t.co/jITKkCVs8d https://t.co/8xjqo8vlGc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @realDonaldTrump: Thank you Mississippi - I love you! https://t.co/zlpAqQ6F7H https://t.co/nZvGnX42Tk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: Brett Kavanaugh's Clinton comment 'deserves a lot of laughter,' ... https://t.co/pFgCDabbZ6 https://t.co/3QPwqK7vT4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: North Carolina man dies of Florence-related bacterial infection https://t.co/cFrph7o9M9 https://t.co/kfSfsDxk02]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BuzzFeedNews: Christine Blasey Ford's attorneys say she still hasn't been interviewed ... https://t.co/qHJZmeHZOn https://t.co/jJwnQ33b8I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: Senator @LindseyGrahamSC sounded off on the Kavanaugh confirmation battle ... https://t.co/N7GhGO2wNf https://t.co/2gQ9P00TM3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WSJ: Listen to this WSJ podcast with reporter Joe Palazzolo on his exclusive about ... https://t.co/btgK6Nh6gD https://t.co/Pc12IHWcAa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AP: BREAKING: Iraq's parliament elects a veteran Kurdish politician as the country's ... https://t.co/hbTta1aguB https://t.co/sA8jFcqybn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: Two envelopes testing positive for ricin sent to the Pentagon https://t.co/VZHFbBfQvg https://t.co/yMawjkQ9cw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: RT @ReutersPolitics: JUST IN: Trump says he thinks Kavanaugh confirmation will get a positive vote ... https://t.co/6DycNPITl4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BuzzFeedNews: This teen has millions of online followers. She also faces harsh abuse ... https://t.co/xjwYIDJCvf https://t.co/PP38y0vv4X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: Amazon lifts minimum wage to $15 for all U.S. employees starting November 1 ... https://t.co/wXnzd2JNSp https://t.co/ay55pB7ag3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: .@senatemajldr vows Kavanaugh vote this week https://t.co/p8oRbHy8SS https://t.co/rQsMqDsqC3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WSJ: The world’s cybersleuths are investigating a new mystery: Who is behind an ... https://t.co/1T4Sp4AnEU https://t.co/PUgupEzUrU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WSJ: Japanese Prime Minister Shinzo Abe has said he wants to create a nation where ... https://t.co/yNhVx4PFKF https://t.co/bG7d2i6sMZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AP: BREAKING: Amazon says it is increasing its minimum wage for all US workers to $15 per hour starting next ... https://t.co/cflvNehcNY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AP: Suicide bomber kills 13 in election rally in Afghanistan. https://t.co/n2DjYCLWQb https://t.co/5DDzHYwtYL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: ⚡️ Daily Briefing: Global news headlines https://t.co/O7ytquFoRR https://t.co/uSFa3EHPNW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: NASA needs to return to ‘pushing our boundaries,’ says Neil Armstrong’s son. https://t.co/Zd0GwFYxtO https://t.co/AQw8RQGMIz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WSJ: There won’t be a Nobel Prize for literature in 2018. So a nonprofit called the ... https://t.co/ZPk4Br7ToL https://t.co/ycamqRgB60]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AP: The Latest: Las Vegas marquees go dark for 2017 shooting tribute. https://t.co/C5HNtajhtz https://t.co/fnZydbxhR4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AP: RT @APCentralRegion: Authorities say a Minnesota man fatally shot as he opened his door was targeted by ... https://t.co/1OsAcCpPHb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WSJ: More people are getting hand tattoos, but in some workplaces the stigma around ... https://t.co/HojGvpf6Hy https://t.co/buQxSkkxHn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BuzzFeedNews: Ethics complaints have been filed against Brett Kavanaugh.

For now, ... https://t.co/ORZ15fuNTo https://t.co/x2cE8MTZGC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: Students stand in the formation of India's map to celebrate Gandhi's 150th birthday https://t.co/1VLraDETsg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: Clare Waight Keller's sophisticated tailoring and gleaming evening wear on ... https://t.co/ADfdQRtwWW https://t.co/Yvo9KNK6zo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: Vigils and memorial services were held throughout Las Vegas on Monday, ... https://t.co/SCs8h20TUO https://t.co/A51LhdKRt1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: What's next in Kavanaugh confirmation process? https://t.co/1955E4YCvZ https://t.co/2VsQf5I7L7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoxNews: Las Vegas remembers the mass shooting, one year later. #SpecialReport https://t.co/sKgzoX0wPR https://t.co/fkkx7vvr90]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nytimesworld: But are archaeological finds enough to bring tourists back to Egypt? https://t.co/zOtZnd0SNK https://t.co/HC3siQApox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @realDonaldTrump: ....a persecution of the President.” Daniel Henninger, The Wall ... https://t.co/Ku55R0E3gG https://t.co/98HtDk6EGZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: British government is not planning for second Brexit vote - minister https://t.co/KKZmKt5CrN https://t.co/eBqyKmk66m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: Is Yemen finally on the road to peace? https://t.co/4MWsyJXquM https://t.co/QRMRV7Te8I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: Qatar Petroleum to invest $20 billion in U.S. in major expansion https://t.co/zqjlV2WjYT https://t.co/olQWPLGKSx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WSJ: This time of year has too many "best of" lists, writes @jasongay. Big chunks of ... https://t.co/tNb475gKlO https://t.co/gjjkPmjDQS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AP: RT @AP_Top25: The scar on Anthony Jones’ neck is a constant reminder of something the FIU running back ... https://t.co/9toHEYyTWf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: Brexit pressure rises, but UK government says no to second vote https://t.co/Fc3kadmPam https://t.co/dHIctkjt6q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WSJ: Opinion: Conservative women have been left out and stigmatized too long, writes ... https://t.co/0GMwR5sOKV https://t.co/iGvNME1Mgx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AP: Syrian activists: Bomb blast in a northern town held by Turkish-backed opposition ... https://t.co/uIXYVzpLDd https://t.co/DlKvTmONGL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: Fearless 102-year-old grandmother goes skydiving https://t.co/9nCKbmbS1S via ... https://t.co/9nCKbmbS1S https://t.co/L6EerLhCXc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: Labour will try to force parliament Brexit vote next week https://t.co/BiCiXsYSAL https://t.co/XNbvPV9tAF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: Confidence motion against UK government could pass: Scotland's Sturgeon https://t.co/iFMuuxnRdA https://t.co/Z8cz6EyJMD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: .@Reuters reporters Wa Lone and Kyaw Soe Oo have been imprisoned in Myanmar ... https://t.co/FacYRNTrOi https://t.co/CSyp8AB4f0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: 2018 in review: Eleven-year-old Sofia gets new heart and famous friend via @ReutersTV https://t.co/0LGLnRqvdP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nytimesworld: Hundreds of supporters of the move cheered and some wept as President ... https://t.co/MN9YF1lPu2 https://t.co/3zGSfnxM88]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WSJ: If you really want to know how to be an effective hockey parent, why not ask a ... https://t.co/v4YgrgMIqX https://t.co/o5uyqL9eBC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BuzzFeedNews: If you have an idea of what the Clintons should look like speaking, ... https://t.co/FoQalRf48e https://t.co/p9xOoWov0a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BuzzFeedNews: In 2018, slavery is very much alive, with a cruel twist — people from ... https://t.co/JqL4pmOkej https://t.co/20AcluCZbe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nytimesworld: It is the closest approach to Earth in centuries, and it won't be this ... https://t.co/Cv54bCVAAY https://t.co/iwqlnj0HxJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cnnbrk: For the first time since the Camp Fire devastated parts of Northern ... https://t.co/f8OIwo9Jls https://t.co/Dtjo978jHw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BuzzFeedNews: Prosecutors said they would reopen the case of a man who said he was ... https://t.co/BS5RvJk2P4 https://t.co/SuDNYNK2AV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WSJ: Opinion: It’s too early to write Modi off, but the Indian prime minister’s ... https://t.co/jqRXYAiqUh https://t.co/ViWWr5NuUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: Egypt unveils 'one of a kind' ancient tomb, expects more finds https://t.co/pV8uiabLje https://t.co/gMKtZCYiYW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BuzzFeedNews: Adenovirus — a highly contagious virus that can cause everything from ... https://t.co/rBVGKxpSXc https://t.co/gg2wWbvDY3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: Wary whistleblower casts light on dark Danish drama https://t.co/mahMHVrx3e https://t.co/Z15YAI5CJm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: A delegation from Easter Island lobbies the British Museum to return one of its ancient 'Moai' statues https://t.co/7Sy2KiKFGG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BuzzFeedNews: Sarah Sanders on teargassing at border: "The White House would never ... https://t.co/IGmp3lPEQH https://t.co/1hgtGzj8NF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BuzzFeedNews: Three US service members were killed today by a roadside bomb ... https://t.co/TM7iahxpdA https://t.co/5bn8l2pUxP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BuzzFeedNews: RT @mattmittenthal: in response to a lawsuit by @aclu_mo on behalf of @BuzzFeedNews ... https://t.co/vo2GagE58N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: What is the ‘post milk generation’? Follow the round of the alternative milkman. Via @ReutersTV https://t.co/I6X9BzXPpJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: 'I wasn't expecting it. We never thought they were going to fire these bombs ... https://t.co/kEH0keOO3J https://t.co/ansndyarPV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: Mitsubishi Motors says Nissan-Renault alliance can survive turmoil https://t.co/Q5DpFRNhyn https://t.co/EJm05CYhE9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BuzzFeedNews: New York City Council questioned the investigations commissioner ... https://t.co/A1YbU10vki https://t.co/JysHsdRA94]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @realDonaldTrump: ....The Fake News Media builds Bob Mueller up as a Saint, when in ... https://t.co/jVGUQ9rYft https://t.co/f6LkkXQ6JM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: EU's top court urged to rule Brexit can be reversed https://t.co/s6Q1YL03TT https://t.co/Z1QbDJWta6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: Breakingviews - Jack Ma and Xi Jinping: dubious comrades in arms https://t.co/2N0f80g1sK https://t.co/edI06TcXSN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Reuters: As Singapore enters twilight of Lee era, ruling party ... https://t.co/cyuo1yoMmg https://t.co/jySqb6ppFy https://t.co/cwd4SnVP9M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BuzzFeedNews: Maria Mendoza-Sanchez lived in Northern California for two decades ... https://t.co/NbJu7yWrnZ https://t.co/8MSOsgw3iO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WSJ: It was the eighth time that NASA managed to land a craft safely on Mars https://t.co/xRiOolBSB3 https://t.co/tSxjeRZ6O2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WSJ: Opinion: The tragic death of missionary John Allen Chau should serve as a ... https://t.co/NJA9lyGOgQ https://t.co/1WaTQQdgd2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nytimesworld: By making referendums part of Taiwan’s political culture, the ... https://t.co/XxX61m0ent https://t.co/XFvfjxhKuJ]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>