<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[You maniacs! You blew it up! Oh, damn you! Damn you all to hell! - Taylor, Planet of the Apes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making money is art and working is art and good business is the best art.   Andy Warhol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Their marriage is a partnership, he's the silent partner.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Success is where preparation and opportunity meet. - Bobby Unser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Molly Hatchet  http://t.co/IDE7X7n216]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laser Tag anywhere - cool guns and app make it easy to play anytime!  http://t.co/ffIofVTjVZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apollo: I will not serve under a man who questions my integrity. Adama: And I won't have an officer under my command who doesn't have any.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to write a book about shoes that's full of footnotes. --&gt; Jarod Kintz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eat, drink and be merry, for tomorrow ye diet. - William Gilmore Beymer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Ben E. King - his story and music  http://t.co/29tvfdKOHh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They call him "magician".  He walks down the street and turns into a saloon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A theory is a hunch with a college education]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yum! Even MORE Brownie's Edge In This Baker's Edge Nonstick Pan  http://t.co/5ISp3qkMO3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Bread  http://t.co/P8aJFj6KZC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life begins when we first realize how soon it ends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fish Hotel Aquarium - Jazz Up Your Office! http://t.co/l8ocPPvhI8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oooh right, it's actually quite a funny story once you get past all the tragic elements and the over-riding sense of doom. - Duckman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriousness is stupidity sent to college. P. J. O'Rourke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I make Jessica Simpson look like a rock scientist.  Tara Reid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So what is Bitcoin and the Bitcoin block chain exactly? http://t.co/ovbSgrkjWc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Love Unlimited  http://t.co/1y5Ur7ZT2n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of James Brown  http://t.co/7anLEqLJNp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Strategy Consulting Firms: Gaining a Competitive Advantage  http://t.co/K9zAGAP5yc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cinderella is living proof that a pair of shoes can change your life…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Chemistry  http://t.co/3aAyZxdhVf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very cool 23 mile range walkie talkies!  Stay connected!  http://t.co/ZKEdjlr0UI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I did not have three thousand pairs of shoes, I had one thousand and sixty. - Imelda Marcos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Al Green  http://t.co/s04VWqikln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can a guy win a game if you don't give him any runs? - Robert Bo Belinsky after Losing 15 - 0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only person who is educated is the one who has learned how to learn and change. - Carl Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Return the shoes?! I can't talk to you when you're being hysterical! - Gabrielle, Desperate Housewives]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the fascinating history of the Boston Red Sox - http://t.co/Kix5d7RCIV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do clever men make good husbands? "No, clever men don't become husbands!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Boston  http://t.co/qc5dxkxCVc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gary US Bonds was an amazing musician and rocker - read his history - http://t.co/f7X9EArQPs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The glass is neither half-full nor half-empty: it's twice as big as it needs to be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Flip flops  http://t.co/xuX1y8rPji]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The studios have been taken over by marketing people and accountants. - Joe Eszterhas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The process of growing old is a question of mind over matter. If you don't mind, it doesn't matter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If science fiction is the mythology of modern technology, then its myth is tragic. - Ursula K. Le Guin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Modern Glo Night Light - Night Light Fashion!  http://t.co/5NWdEy9JNK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Blue Oyster Cult   http://t.co/7AYj3abdzc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Daddy: Mommy just backed the car over my bicycle! "I told you not to leave it in the living room!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[1f u c4n r34d th1s u r34lly n33d t0 g37 l41d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the Romans had been obliged to learn Latin, they would never have found time to conquer the world. - Heinrich Heine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a stuffed toy! It's a sleeping bag. IT'S A SHARK! - Its COOL! http://t.co/OQ9gpZhj6I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool iPhone 4 Review  http://t.co/IaqP6mgYos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd like to compliment you on your work -- When will you start?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Calorie and Activity Tracking Technology  http://t.co/72w0ZEkpwZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doctor, giving prescription to a patient "Let me know if this stuff works. I'm having the same trouble myself."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Every day, in every way, I am getting better and better. - Emilie Coue]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Mindy Carson  http://t.co/Dx7laQKNo6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm on a 90-day wonder diet. Thus far, I've lost 45 days. - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Very Fun and Geeky 8-Bit Tie!  http://t.co/6r0NIquqUv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Commodores  http://t.co/Tt5GYxhldM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have never let my schooling interfere with my education. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the great department store of life, baseball is the toy department. - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Planning Beach Camping Tips  http://t.co/wAZIPuFAW3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Fashionable Jackets for Fall &amp; Winter  http://t.co/xhKwWlfk56]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Auto racing began 5 minutes after the second car was built. - Henry Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing worthwhile comes easily. Work, continuous work and hard work, is the only way to accomplish results that last. - Hamilton Holt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the beginning, God created man, but seeing him so feeble, He gave him the cat - Warren Eckstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Review of The Little House on the Prairie Episode Called "Four Eyes"  http://t.co/Mz2AJW0y2y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is not the strongest of the species that survive, nor the most intelligent, but the one most responsive to change. - Charles Darwin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You teach best what you most need to learn. - Richard David Bach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science fiction, outside of poetry, is the only literary field which has no limits, no parameters whatsoever. - Theodore Sturgeon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Rolling Stones  http://t.co/cRaHOINdyh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Whispers  http://t.co/UtALohqArz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gary US Bonds was an amazing musician and rocker - read his history - http://t.co/f7X9EArQPs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've got rock 'n' roll in my blood. - William Shatner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It isn't necessary to blow out the other person's light in order for yours to shine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[E.T. phone home - E.T.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do you love James Bond?  Check out these cool t-shirts, hats, stickers and more --&gt;  http://t.co/A8hQcyzsiE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Janis Joplin  http://t.co/MmMbPlIKvv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celiac Disease Requires Gluten Free Foods - Learn More  http://t.co/kiJohgLB8l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LinkedIn for Your Company Proves to be Effective  http://t.co/c23A6pfokh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Billy Joel  http://t.co/LwaUMxxjpR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I started out writing much more science fictiony stuff and writing about science fiction. - Neil Gaiman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Tsingtao Beer  http://t.co/Afl7Lf0oZ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I won't be a rock star. I will be a legend. - Freddie Mercury]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eat, drink and be merry, for tomorrow ye diet. - William Gilmore Beymer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Ensure You Have Safe Drinking Water in a Disaster  http://t.co/w04HawEKHo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Try not. Do, or do not. There is no try. - Yoda, The Empire Strikes Back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think that gay marriage is something that should be between a man and a woman. - Arnold Schwarzenegger, on gay marriage]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Mac and Katie Kissoon  http://t.co/FeIsMcXfUl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cooking for Geeks: Real Science, Great Hacks, and Good Food  -&gt; http://t.co/tEHXFG2wVq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Hire a Strategy Consulting Firm?  http://t.co/V2gIAw9tYu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow the whiskey.  - Kid Rock, who arrived with "Redneck Woman" singer Gretchen Wilson, on his plans after the Country Music Awards]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet!  A 3D Printer - Very Awesome!  You have to check this out! http://t.co/JvrAsdD3nX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Link Building With Social Media Sites  http://t.co/E0GPUvGKFQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Fitness Apps – Is There One That Is the Best?  http://t.co/e7f5WRpHRk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahh Fond Memories of San Antonio  http://t.co/erE68zwumV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Five card stud, nothing wild. And the sky's the limit - Captain Jean Luc Picard - Last Line of Star Trek the Next Generation]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pop culture is not about depth. It's about marketing, supply and demand, consumerism. - Trevor Dunn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to Robert A. Heinlein  http://t.co/YFlxxOLdLy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Ten Years After classic Rock Group?  http://t.co/JMhSusFQqm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you don't do what's best for your body, you're the one who comes up on the short end. - Julius Erving]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[High heels were invented by a woman who had been kissed on the forehead. --&gt; Christopher Morley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is nothing permanent except change. - Heraclitus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is what you get from reading the small print in a contract. "experience " is what you get from not reading it]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>