<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Application Developer:   Job Description – .NET Application Developer (00001PRO) Job Description .NET Application Developer – 00001PRO  Are you looking to make a difference in a patient’s life? At AmerisourceBergen, you will find an innovative… https://t.co/PN5Etp3iiD https://t.co/8cJ5nj6yrw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[api .net developer: api .net developer Ref No.: 18-32826 Location: jersey city, New Jersey Must have skills: Should be very strong in REST APIs (.Net Web API), SOAP (WCF), JSON, and XML. Comparison of REST and SOAP API, their advantages and use cases.… https://t.co/UkxJsddVu3 https://t.co/YOLXiFVa7B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .NET Developer: Senior .NET Developer | EastBanc Tech – Services – Solutions – Our Approach – Our Work – Tech Insights – About Us – News – Careers – Events – Contact Us – Services – Solutions – Our Approach – Our Work – Tech Insights – – About Us… https://t.co/SRIBD8rVur]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ReactJS Developer: ReactJS Developer Ref No.:18-03382 Location: Irvine, California Position Type:Contract This opportunity is with a multibillion $ Global giant based in United States, Canada &amp; Mexico, with 16 different delivery centers and Regional… https://t.co/o9ijITUFIg https://t.co/9FFCA9yPzR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .Net Developer: Location US-OH-Cincinnati Posted Date 1 month ago(6/18/2018 9:45 AM) Job ID 23422 # Positions 1 Category Technology Position Type Full Time Overview Be Here. Be Great. Working for a leader in the insurance industry means… https://t.co/uxUrVgSNcM https://t.co/q26mmakfTw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer in Washington, DC | CACI International – Small Business | – Suppliers – About Us – | – What We Do – | – Media &amp; Events – | – Investors – | – Careers – | – Contracts – | – Contact Us Join Our Talent Network – About Us – What… https://t.co/eM1KS1cxmw https://t.co/vPHAgfCBPT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Developer/ .NET Developer: Verisk Analytics Job OpportunitiesView Job Careers | Contact Verisk HomeAbout VeriskConferencesPressInvestorsBlog U.S. Job Search Login to Job Section My Candidate Home Help with Job Application Non-U.S. Job Search Careers… https://t.co/r1LoB2BUNe https://t.co/JzdWTBfnmx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer Ref No.:18-13061 Location: Washington, District of Columbia Start Date: 07/24/2018 Position: .Net Developer Location: Washington, DC Duration: 6+Months JD: Microsoft .NET framework 3.5/4.0+/Visual Studio (2008/2012),… https://t.co/hcWh8ZW76R https://t.co/bqfUModqu0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer C# .NET: Software Engineer C# .NET Jobs Description at Cox Enterprises Skip to main content Careers Home Our People Locations Join Our Talent Community Blog Manage Your Profile Cox Enterprises Cox Communications Cox Automotive Cox Media… https://t.co/sH8wgwzYtt https://t.co/YSFPAgzLSm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: MetroStar Systems Careers ========================= .Net Developer Web Development Arlington, Virginia MetroStar Systems is looking for a results oriented Senior .Net Developer that is passionate about designing and developing web… https://t.co/vK5ZfwCuTT https://t.co/3RcKGlTXBP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .Net Full Stack Developer: Senior .Net Full Stack Developer – CAREER HOME – ABOUT US – Culture and Diversity – Benefits – Awards – Community – University Relations – Our Hiring Process – FEATURED JOBS – Engineering – Information Technology –… https://t.co/pp6lK7hpjU https://t.co/uLvpLHTzuy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer : 18-02612 Ref No.: 18-02612 Location: Highlands Ranch, Colorado Akraya is looking for a .Net Developer for one of our clients. If the job description below is a fit, please apply directly or call Somya at ************ If… https://t.co/WbAzlVISdK https://t.co/3fjCpC0FS6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/Zqguck7KPp Developer: ****** Developer Ref No.: 18-31098 Location: Malvern, Pennsylvania Role : .Net Developer Duration : 12 Months Location : Malvern, PA Job Description : MS Windows Desktop Development, ************* Studio 2015, VB-6, OOD… https://t.co/ofHDV1cIcj https://t.co/MxvllnCMUq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Group Manager, Control — Financial and Emerging Technologies Control Team (IT Control Support): Control – M3 Responsible for identifying, analyzing, monitoring and minimizing business risks, and ensures proper control policies and procedures are in… https://t.co/0HdtAQlNGi https://t.co/q95bw1SW40]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software https://t.co/ajsyo2JfPd TS/SCI Tampa, FL: Designs, develops, codes, tests, and debugs complex new software products, and makes significant enhancements to existing software. – Researches and integrates design strategies, product… https://t.co/4Dnoft7dr4 https://t.co/sH8k1L5Abu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer job | Deloitte United States job in Mechanicsburg, Pennsylvania, United States Toggle menu – Deloitte home – About Deloitte – – Location: United States Available in locations and languages – Students – Experienced –… https://t.co/j4vmKYshYU https://t.co/2pIu7IZjQQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PHP and full stack web application Developer in Kenilworth, NJ: Career Portals Job Search Login / Register We are now hiring Req #434 PHP and full stack web application Developer in Kenilworth, NJ Salary FT Tuesday, June 19, 2018 PHP and full stack web… https://t.co/6hqHRhp6Pa https://t.co/NOxBDxqgAM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SDE (C#, .Net, Perl): SDE (C#, .Net, Perl) Ref No.: 18-31830 Location: Redmond, Washington A Bachelor’s or Master’s degree in Computer Science or related field 3 to 8 years in experience in C#, .Net, Microsoft Technologies Experience in Scipting… https://t.co/WYSsEFtPQF https://t.co/kTdfIlvoSz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.net developer: .net developer Ref No.: 18-28649 Location: brookfield, Wisconsin Job Responsibilities: . Provide technical expertise and guidance for best practices . Provide solution for the team after joint discussion with offshore and Client . Analyze… https://t.co/y7fzQAvOvX https://t.co/y4JrPO6BE3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer I, II – .Net: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Fort Worth, TX Job Type: Information Technology Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 7/17/2018 Job Description Primary Purpose: This position is responsible for analysis, codes, tests… https://t.co/bHK0yZKnMp https://t.co/t9JySulfj4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net developer: .Net developer Ref No.: 18-29441 Location: Mountain View, California Position .Net developer Location SFO Job Length W2 Contract Required Skills- *******, MVC, WEB API, Angular JS, WCF, C# Job Description: Design, Development and… https://t.co/rJC8zwwATh https://t.co/OS7FwfWEqU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Product Manager: Irvine Technology Corporation (ITC) is a leading provider of technology and staffing solutions for IT, Security, Engineering, and Interactive Design disciplines servicing startups to enterprise clients, nationally. We pride ourselves… https://t.co/ZjC2OPrkHQ https://t.co/rYO1CzFt1k]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.net Developer: .Net Developer Ref No.: 18-29964 Location: Mountain View, Alaska Proven experience as a .NET Developer orApplication Developer Familiarity with the ******* framework, SQL Server and design/architectural patterns (e.g.… https://t.co/OEsJE8X6jb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Entry Level Software Developer: Company Description . Job Description No Computer Science degree? No problem. We love self-taught developers! LaunchCode offers paid, software developer apprenticeships at one of our employer partners that include Express… https://t.co/lAJSBKt86B https://t.co/OxZyMJlP3D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack .Net Developer: Description HI’s client is adding a Full Stack .Net Developer to its Finance Technology team in the DTC. The role willhelp build the web interface, including visualizations and data collection modals, which are required to… https://t.co/PRYT25S2rJ https://t.co/OTXcUMJWz0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET/REST API Developer: Resource 1 is in need of a .NET/REST API DEVELOPER for our client in downtown Chicago. Selected individual will work with business and technical teams to DEVELOP AND SUPPORT INTERFACES/INTEGRATION to and from the client’s… https://t.co/R3D5GmAWXj https://t.co/k7drGYIww2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer Ref No.: 18-31562 Location: Washington, District of Columbia TITLE: .NET DEVELOPER POSITION TYPE: CONTRACT(W2) LOCATION: WASHINGTON DC SKILLS REQUIRED: Microsoft .NET framework 3.5/4.0+/Visual Studio (2008/2012),… https://t.co/LMK9CdmuRR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Physician: Nashville GI 100% Outpatient with Partnership: Gastroenterology opportunity in the beautiful Nashville Tennessee area. Join an amazing collegial group that is established, professional and respected for quality care. Enjoy a Monday through… https://t.co/BrQuy3a66u https://t.co/UREKnekaxI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net developer: .Net developer Ref No.: 18-29441 Location: Mountain View, California Position .Net developer Location SFO Job Length W2 Contract Required Skills- *******, MVC, WEB API, Angular JS, WCF, C# Job Description: Design, Development and… https://t.co/EAq8hZtkZJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Security Technical Project Manager: Job Description BAE Systems is looking for a System Security Engineering Project Manager to join our team for an exciting opportunity supporting sustainment efforts for the Minuteman III (MM III)… https://t.co/tvgUb014kZ https://t.co/cwCIklbgdH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer- C# .Net: Agilent inspires and supports discoveries that advance the quality of life. We provide life science, diagnostic and applied market laboratories worldwide with instruments, services, consumables, applications and expertise.… https://t.co/dmCdYwYy3O https://t.co/nQ4eIopsYj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Code Quality Assurance Engineer: Mythics Careers – Senior Code Quality Assurance Engineer Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to… https://t.co/oNyrrIAzCQ https://t.co/gpH3oIXNUt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Graphics Software Engineer: Careers Center | 3D Graphics Software Engineer Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome… https://t.co/VEkmQoN7cP https://t.co/15sBqsJumt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (.NET): Job Location US-DC Job ID 10298 Job Location United States Overview American Institutes for Research (AIR) is a leading professional services firm with a growing software engineering and product development team. We design and… https://t.co/jOSjxxfBbV https://t.co/1OcyAftk1S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/itZFk9aFeI developer: ******* developer Charlotte, North Carolina – United States Job Start Date – 07/02/18, Posted Date – 06/13/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview 1. 1. 6-10 years experience developing in ******* 2. MVC, C# 3. SQL 4.… https://t.co/CUlZqqpOfi https://t.co/1wRD7iHMXQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Posting Title Software Engineer / Web Developer: Brand Viacom iCIMS ID 2018-8462 Overview and Responsibilities South Park Digital Studios is looking for a top-notch, driven web developer and frontend engineer to deliver, maintain, and refine dynamic,… https://t.co/Lblbva0yPW https://t.co/G0JMjt4CW2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer Skip Navigation Fiserv Menu – Solutions – Industries – About – Careers – Where you fit in – Technology – Accounting &amp; Finance – Contact Center – U.S. Locations – Alpharetta – Brookfield – Dallas/Ft. Worth – Other U.S.… https://t.co/6SpStKW0vt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer, EnerGov: Software Developer, EnerGov =========================== Developers write code to enhance the product or resolve issues with the product. Understand and apply programming and user interface standards applicable to the product.… https://t.co/kWI2HVsRIQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developers: .Net Developers Round Rock, Texas – United States Job Start Date – 07/09/18, Posted Date – 07/02/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview . Although this role was earlier accepting subs for .NET Developers we have filled the slots for… https://t.co/ZNhsZVojsT https://t.co/OzZ7CkMGOW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Application Architect: Western Union is changing. Yes, we’re the company that moves money around the world quickly and reliably in 200 countries and territories. We are also present in over 510,000 locations bringing immense distribution convenience… https://t.co/FLf0R6mMSC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager – Medical Device Diagnostic Research (Home Based): Are you a seasoned Project Manager with experience in Diagnostics and Medical Device studies passionate about playing a key role in the overall management for global clinical research… https://t.co/MaRaVgktQj https://t.co/vHAcbd9JbF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: Job ********* Developer – ID:32030 Duration12 Months Start DateASAP Job ************, *******, C#, ASP, Visual Basic, JavaScript, COM/COM+ components, Web Services, XML, SDLC LocationTorrance, CA Date Posted06/29/2018 FOR IMMEDIATE… https://t.co/ioiJZzg8Yc https://t.co/GQUKgZTi0F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Application Developer: Job Description .Net Application DeveloperWeymouth, MA Posted: 2/28/2018 Category: Information Technology Job Type: – Minimum Experience: 5+ Required Education: Bachelor (BA, BS…) Branch: Corporate Job Description The .NET… https://t.co/JcKdtHlBXF https://t.co/0eDHWU1H3x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Systems Developer Mobile/.NET: Senior Systems Developer – Mobile/.NET Description at FRESENIUS – Fresenius Fraud Notice As a company with over 60,000 dedicated employees, Fresenius Medical Care North America is quite aware of the many scams that… https://t.co/EEo8kTyYGV https://t.co/bQsWjTolT7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NXP to repurchase $5 billion shares after Qualcomm deal falls through: NXP Semiconductors NV , whose buyout deal with U.S. chipmaker Qualcomm Inc fell through due to lack of approval from China, said on Thursday it would buy back $5 billion worth of… https://t.co/RdJhoecSim https://t.co/hALGzxcyaB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full-Stack https://t.co/BKeTHRUc7v Web Developers: Hiring Full-Stack ******* Application Developers | Invonto 100% Made in America – Solutions – Work – About Us – Insights – Careers – Contact Us – Schedule Consultation – Solutions – Work – About Us –… https://t.co/ynFYyWPKGq https://t.co/A3FqvHIPKO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supply Chain Integration Developer: Description Western Digital We deliver the possibilities of data. YOU define what’s possible. JOB: In this position, the individual will be an individual contributor with responsibilities in design, development and… https://t.co/0P5LFHj3uO https://t.co/yLpehKsoZQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Qualcomm's $44 billion NXP offer deadline passes, no word from China: The deadline for Qualcomm Inc to buy NXP Semiconductors passed at midnight U.S. eastern time without any word on Chinese regulatory approval, likely shutting the door on a deal… https://t.co/iB34wAjvxp https://t.co/wSbIhRnIGA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SDE (C#, .Net, Perl): SDE (C#, .Net, Perl) Ref No.: 18-31830 Location: Redmond, Washington A Bachelor’s or Master’s degree in Computer Science or related field 3 to 8 years in experience in C#, .Net, Microsoft Technologies Experience in Scipting… https://t.co/g9uBhAW3GF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior C#.NET Developer: Great opportunity for strong C#.NET developers from intermediate level all the way up to lead level to join a fortune 500 company located in the Cleveland area. 6 month and 12 month contract-to-hire/permanent positions available.… https://t.co/iVFssjsH9y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Lead (.Net): Technical Lead (.Net) Job Description Are you passionate about building amazing software? Are you constantly pushing yourself to develop better, faster and more efficient applications? Do you have an innate interest in releasing… https://t.co/viL8JWqpmH https://t.co/WhnvndcJBK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Sharepoint Developer: Title Senior Sharepoint Developer =========================== EOE Statement We are an equal employment opportunity employer. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color,… https://t.co/bIS4eJvSO1 https://t.co/DsJ6E9Rut8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Researcher, Solutions Management: Sr. Researcher, Solutions Management (Allscripts Healthcare, LLC. Malvern, PA). Work closely with team Clinical Experts and Business and Financial Analysts to conduct research using academic journals and industry… https://t.co/dRNTNueaMO https://t.co/4rSxYK4PO4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer in Washington, DC | CACI International – Small Business | – Suppliers – About Us – | – What We Do – | – Media &amp; Events – | – Investors – | – Careers – | – Contracts – | – Contact Us Join Our Talent Network – About Us – What… https://t.co/wx4x8uRtFx https://t.co/oODNqcTz1H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Software Developer: Irvine Technology Corporation (ITC) is a leading provider of technology and staffing solutions for IT, Security, Engineering, and Interactive Design disciplines servicing startups to enterprise clients, nationally. We pride… https://t.co/cxgMP4zKUr https://t.co/dRMZOzHpr1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – .Net: Software Engineer – .Net Skip Navigation Fiserv Menu – Solutions – Industries – About – Careers – Where you fit in – Technology – Accounting &amp; Finance – Contact Center – U.S. Locations – Alpharetta – Brookfield – Dallas/Ft.… https://t.co/aTn1cCJpj0 https://t.co/xSaReXTkm1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Systems Developer – Mobile/.NET: Senior Systems Developer – Mobile/.NET Description at FRESENIUS – Fresenius Fraud Notice As a company with over 60,000 dedicated employees, Fresenius Medical Care North America is quite aware of the many scams that… https://t.co/YJEmnVVkdx https://t.co/N4BJhKQhDy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .Net Developer SPARS: Senior .Net Developer – SPARS Ref No.:18-00110 Location: Timonium, Maryland Position Type:Full Time Experience Level: 7 Years Start Date: 06/11/2018 Senior .Net Developer – SPARS FEi is a leading IT company specializing in… https://t.co/qkUXcwo9Bn https://t.co/xyVVTR3Mmu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Software Engineer:   Job Description – .NET Software Engineer (1803519) Job Description  .NET Software Engineer – (1803519) Primary Location : US-CA-Long Beach-Remote Employees Job : Molina Medicaid Solutions Organization : Medical Systems Job… https://t.co/ZP7WglqV47 https://t.co/VH5Be9mVbT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manager, IT Security: Join a Legacy of Innovation 110 Years and Counting! With over 100 years of scientific expertise and a presence in more than 20 countries, Daiichi Sankyo and its 15,000 employees around the world draw upon a rich legacy of innovation… https://t.co/C8qdNWOs7j https://t.co/RCeexqatbF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer: Search and apply for jobs at Piper Companies | Careers at Piper Companies Careers Search Jobs Connect With Us .NET Developer Job Attributes Job Id: 19522Job Category: Software Applications &amp; ERPJob Location: Greensboro, NC 27214Security… https://t.co/unwSXnYgSB https://t.co/x7BQGi1yaj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager: Position: Project Manager – Oracle Applications Job Description: Job Description – Responsible for developing and executing activities related to end-to-end project management, including project plans and budget and resource estimates,… https://t.co/PegcL9pMmb https://t.co/GN5Kcx1146]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/BKeTHRUc7v Developer 16865: Career Opportunities https://t.co/BKeTHRUc7v Developer 16865 Position Location: Washington, D.C. Requisition #: 16865 # of openings: 2 Description Description Huntington Ingalls Industries – Technical Solutions… https://t.co/SHN9VC4YDQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/BKeTHRUc7v Developer: ******* Developer Ref No.: 18-29660 Location: Mount Laurel, New Jersey Position: ******* Developer Location: Mount Laurel, NJ 5+ years of experience in .net 3.5, Csharp, ASP, WinForms Experience in utility design… https://t.co/NSLycKoNc0 https://t.co/1n4CJ67XV2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer with Angular: .Net Developer with Angular Ref No.:18-12363 Location: Torrance, California Position Type:Full Time/Contract Start Date: 07/13/2018 UPS ParcelPro Angular developer GC/USC/L2EAD ONLY SO # *******-1Primary Skills: No. Of… https://t.co/Qvi86alGsv https://t.co/ikiaOX0XPO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Application Developer: Web Application Developer Information Technology Davenport, Iowa Apply Description Position at Lee Enterprises Lee Enterprises, a leading media company in the US, seeks a talented Web Application Developer to join our corporate… https://t.co/JxrwlnyBk6 https://t.co/GxYB9pAzJC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Engineer: Snowflake Computing, Inc. is accepting resumes for the position of Application Engineer in San Mateo, CA (Ref. # SNOCSMIRSN1). Serve as part of Snowflake Computing’s application engineering team. Responsible for requirements… https://t.co/4Ke2wp2QM9 https://t.co/Jg7G9UlEV7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drones and stakeouts: how Tesla 'haters' put pressure on CEO Musk: An online army of skeptics and amateur sleuths that has spent years promoting bets against Tesla Inc senses an opportunity to renew pressure on the electric carmaker after the failure of… https://t.co/SOOIY344xM https://t.co/0EYieLTRaF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Healthcare – Security Systems Specialist: Employee Type: Full-Time/Part-Time Location: 425 Bush Street San Francisco, CA Job Type: Security Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 8/7/2018 Job Description Job Code: *********** Category: General Healthcare… https://t.co/nBKvBWed7c https://t.co/Q0RotpqSk5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net/JavaScript Developer – Wilmington: Skills/Experience: Java 8+ years of web development experience with .NET Framework (4.0+) including C#, *******, and MVC 6+ years of experience with HTML, CSS, JavaScript, AJAX, jQuery, and Web Services 6+ years of… https://t.co/MN8nS9BVXx https://t.co/N3PEFQQru0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer – Data Platform: at Twilio (View all jobs) San Francisco, CA or Mountain View, CA Because you belong at Twilio The Who, What, Where and Why Who? Twilio's Data Platform team is looking for Senior Software Engineer to deliver a… https://t.co/EgwmkcocgE https://t.co/JO4LSJXd9V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .Net Developer: Senior .Net Developer Job Description Job Description Are you passionate about building amazing software? Are you constantly pushing yourself to develop better, faster and more efficient applications? Do you have an innate interest… https://t.co/jzZ3FeTawh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer III: DESCRIPTION .NET DEVELOPER III JOB DESCRIPTION: Must have: * At least 5 years of have solid experience in building and enhancing applications and services using .Net, Angular and Microsoft SQL Server 2012/2016 * 5 years of solid… https://t.co/62jJcRYX3z https://t.co/eaCF56aOUy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst: Overview Job Description: – Responsible for performing the daily operational tasks and ensuring the data quality of the data and reporting deliverables coming out of the team. – Responsible for gathering and assessing business information… https://t.co/nwAtmYpa2e https://t.co/7pLE7gO1Pc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: MetroStar Systems Careers ========================= .Net Developer Web Development Arlington, Virginia MetroStar Systems is looking for a results oriented Senior .Net Developer that is passionate about designing and developing web… https://t.co/HcueqWGqRM https://t.co/mUEqnA4DCs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer: Title .NET Developer ============== EOE Statement We are an equal employment opportunity employer. All qualified applicants will receive consideration for employment without regard to race, color, religion, gender, national origin,… https://t.co/hEgjKFPKYA https://t.co/MG2RNsygsV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft .NET Developer (Healthcare) – Frankfort, KY: Job Ref: ********** Employer: NTT DATA Country: United States County/State: Kentucky Address: Post Date: 09/08/2018 00:31 Req ID: 24673 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on… https://t.co/XzwvtVhW0d https://t.co/GEhKLv91ai]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr./Lead .Net Developer (GIS Environment): Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome page Returning Candidate?Log… https://t.co/iVYoPcrDcR https://t.co/Nk4S1DOED5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET SQL Technical Lead: Job Ref: ********* Employer: NTT DATA Country: United States County/State: Arizona Address: Post Date: 10/08/2018 00:33 Candidate is reposnsible for Creating Functional Specification document and other technical artifacts as… https://t.co/L3U8k5C2hq https://t.co/WtoxhwuUTG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst: Tracking Code RDTE-18-0956-F Job Code 18-0956 Posting Title Data Analyst Post Date 7/16/2018 Full Time / Part-Time Full Time Travel No Travel Required City Dahlgren State VA Country US Description DATA ANALYST (RDTE-18-0956-F) Bowhead is… https://t.co/nAK557zsEY https://t.co/FR7jZINbpI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer-Sharepoint: Job ID : ****** Location : Irving, TX US Level : Experienced Professional Job Category : Information TechnologyDescription : Where good people build rewarding careers. Think that working in the insurance field can’t be… https://t.co/i6IZJiyDHV https://t.co/eakqREOtuA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: Position Summary: The Senior Java Developer will work with the business, technical teams, Architects and middleware engineers to design and implement solutions for Supply Chain Systems. This position primarily focuses on designing… https://t.co/2pPOty6MLW https://t.co/MXgIsqnaHp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer with Azure: .Net Developer with Azure Ref No.: 18-34884 Location: Chicago, Illinois Role: .Net Developer with Azure Location: Chicago IL/Madison, WI Duration: 12 Months Contract Skills Required Strong exp. with .Net technologies with Azure… https://t.co/xdN8cs6oNw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Development Specialist https://t.co/BKeTHRUc7v: Job Ref: ********** Employer: NTT DATA Country: United States County/State: Washington Address: Post Date: 28/07/2018 00:10 Req ID: 26996 At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on… https://t.co/gUQgdV5DEZ https://t.co/t7Ht8PDMJO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Professional Services Mgr: Job Description Description Requisition #: PROFE01647 Job Title: Professional Services Mgr Location: Arlington, VA Clearance Level: Active DoD – Minimum Secret **Selected applicants may be subject to a government security… https://t.co/cZ4JQtXlhs https://t.co/EwhSUUL1V0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer–Need Local Consultant: Job Snapshot Employee Type: Contractor Location: Raleigh, NC Job Type: Health Care Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 8/21/2018 Job Description Role: Net Developer Locations: Raleigh, NC Duration:+6 Months… https://t.co/Bd9bRO70Fc https://t.co/Smdr5BQP79]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.NET Developer: .NET Developer Ref No.: 18-36598 Location: Tukwila, Washington Technical Responsibilities: Participate in application design and reviews Support Functional and User Acceptance Testing Review of design and development Relevant Years of… https://t.co/q7Q1Jb3thR https://t.co/WrfKiTpd5v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .NET Developer: Senior .NET Developer at Conduent Skip Navigation Search Keyword CategorySelectAccountingAdministrative SupportAudit &amp; ComplianceBenefitsBrand &amp; Product MarketingBuck Consulting-ActuarialBuck Consulting-NonActuarialBusiness &amp;… https://t.co/wQMB1Ao6tU https://t.co/WxeIrIVFkZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Expert Developer: Expert Developer in Washington, DC | CACI International – Small Business | – Suppliers – About Us – | – What We Do – | – Media &amp; Events – | – Investors – | – Careers – | – Contracts – | – Contact Us Join Our Talent Network – About Us –… https://t.co/slmGQt8ZXt https://t.co/9SxSKJLRaZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: MetroStar Systems Careers ========================= .Net Developer Web Development Washington, District Of Columbia MetroStar Systems is looking for an experienced ******* Developer that is passionate about developing web applications. If… https://t.co/GEhAxXAcBP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .Net Developer: Senior .Net Developer Job Description Are you passionate about building amazing software? Are you constantly pushing yourself to develop better, faster and more efficient applications? Do you have an innate interest in releasing… https://t.co/pLQmxSF3XE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Director, GMA Project Manager: About Daiichi Sankyo Cancer Enterprise The mission of Daiichi Sankyo Cancer Enterprise is to leverage our world-class, innovative science and push beyond traditional thinking to create meaningful treatments for patients… https://t.co/RI6GSK34tG https://t.co/bFMOqiZJKm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .Net Software Engineer: Job Location US-DC Job ID 10291 Job Location United States Overview Be part of something innovative and cutting edge. Join our team of more than a hundred software engineers, designers, project managers and software… https://t.co/XSO8nNWZVD https://t.co/TIvvuzheFy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Systems Engineer – Rail: Location: Annapolis Job type: Permanent Sector: Manufacturing Category: Engineers Requisition ID: 11014 Want to work with some of the most talented, dedicated people on the planet? Do you value relationships, commitment,… https://t.co/Ud3Q5xs1wW https://t.co/dZlsiQXVcz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Fasttrack Engineer: Microsoft Corporation currently has the following openings in Sunnyvale, CA (job opportunities available at all levels, e.g., Principal, Senior and Lead levels). Technical Solutions Professional Intune: Analyze engineering,… https://t.co/7llaeumPLB https://t.co/NQqeJMFzFY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid level .Net Software Engineer: Job TitleMid level .Net Software Engineer – ID:32239 DurationPermanent Start DateASAP Job SkillsExcellent communciation, Outgoing and personable, .net, Fintech experience LocationIrvine, CA Date Posted07/30/2018 We are… https://t.co/hRC2aGzfz5 https://t.co/udkOLqatPG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mid-level .NET Software Developer: Mid-level .NET Software Developer at EXPERIANSkip Navigation Consumer Small Business Business More…X Experian Site Sections About Experian Consumer Support Credit Advice Global Sites Company Profile Corporate Fact… https://t.co/LxJxuJM4RO https://t.co/ogIiabxoDv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead .Net Developer: Overview At Public Partnerships LLC, a subsidiary of Public Consulting Group, we are passionate about our mission to be the provider of choice of comprehensive financial management for participant-directed services in the public… https://t.co/tNihYeFDFS https://t.co/ZG6mEIBJ2m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: .Net Developer : 18-02612 Ref No.: 18-02612 Category: Software Development Jobs Location: Highlands Ranch, Colorado Akraya is looking for a .Net Developer for one of our clients. If the job description below is a fit, please apply… https://t.co/GKIEb2obfc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .Net Developer: We are seeking motivated, career and customer oriented Sr .Net Developers in the Washington, DC metro area intested in exploring an exciting and challenging career with Unisys Federal Systems. In this role you will gain valuable… https://t.co/nQGXWu8jBf]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>