<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jrsmith73: @EdinburghUni Global Research and Partnership Fund - to build collaboration with colleagues in LMICs. Apply!!! @africanstudi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @talbotrice75: FIRST LOOK: Rachel Maclean #spiteyourface Poster. Exhibition opens @talbotrice75 @eca_edinburgh @EdinburghUni 24 February…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KatieCebula: Families with a child with Williams syndrome OR autism (&amp; intellectual disabilities) and a sibling: If you have free time…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[congratulations @StellaWYChan @ProjectSoothe @BPSOfficial https://t.co/RWec7i17B9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TeresaHacks: Come+work with me on repair, tech, policy, ecology. Full funded PhD. Deadline EOI Feb 9th. Please share @marcgarrett20 @nd…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @talbotrice75: Cards have arrived! David Claerbout &amp; Rachel Maclean open 24 February @talbotrice75 @eca_edinburgh @EdinburghUni #talbotr…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @uoessps: Did you know that over 1/3 of our staff and students @EdinburghUni are international? Join us at #1DayWithoutUs on 19/02 and m…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Athena_SWAN: Are you from an arts, humanities, social sciences, business and law (AHSSBL) department and are interested in being an Ath…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @McRowena: Events to mark #Vote100, including a new dystopian film by artist Rachel Maclean inspired by suffragette protest, and set in…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fabulous cast, production and set for #Rhinocerous @lyceumtheatre https://t.co/3uOlwiib51]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @edintfest: Tickets for most #EdintFest shows go on sale in under 15 mins! Remember that #LightontheShore with @edinburgh_gin will be on…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @UoELawSchool: Don't miss our very own Professor Burkhard Schafer's inaugural lecture on Monday, 26th March! Register via Eventbrite: ht…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@runnyhunny some ideas for your trip?! 10 of the best hacks for happy campinghttps://www.theguardian.com/travel/2018/mar/24/10-best-camping-hacks-tips-advice-tents-campfire-cooking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @UoE_Psychology: Edinburgh International Science Festival: What does your mind tell you? Our researchers from @ccace and @AlzScotDRC fea…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ScottishOpera: VACANCY: fancy heading up the wonderful Scottish Opera in-house design team? We're on the lookout for a new Graphic Desi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @melissaterras: Come and work with me job klaxon! Research Technologist in @EdinburghUni CAHSS Digital Innovation Team developing cuttin…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @stephenckemp: Looking for 4* impact? Here's an extended list from #REF2014 - 91 extra 4* case studies and 7 new UoAs represented! #REF2…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jbralston: a few more weeks to apply for our open and permanent lectureship position in Theology and Ethics @SchoolofDiv https://t.co/A…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KatieCebula: .@theyardscotland Our study looks at how siblings play together at home &amp; listens to their own views on being a sib. If yo…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LSEpublicevents: In her new book 'The Value of Everything' @MazzucatoM argues that if we are to reform capitalism, we urgently need to…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @socialpsychUK: The @socialpsychUK Annual Conf 'Addressing the Crisis' takes place at Keele Hall, 28-30 Aug 18. The 3 day conf invites S…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BPSOfficial: Educational Psychology (Scotland) Qualifications Board - Assessor vacancy for the Qualification in Educational Psychology…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DesignInf: Tickets for renowned interdisciplinary academic Professor Karen Barad's keynote speech at #transimage2018 will be released l…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ScottishOpera: Applications are open for young musicians aged 16-21 who want to take their talent to the next level as part of our #Con…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And watch those armed toddlers.... https://t.co/NrPWMa36dA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Roseberrykate: Please share this picture of my nephew as widely as you can.  He is a student in St Andrews and has been missing since W…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ProfAThompson: We are looking for arts and humanities research that has helped to improve people’s health and well-being as @ahrcpress…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MorayHouseHoS: National Museum of Scotland goes virtual in online first https://t.co/WQyEvWyHmZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@weeartyfarty @genderpol https://t.co/Wu8e355IJD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EdiPhilOnline: Dr. Orestis Palermos introduces @Eidyn1's free Philosophy, Science and Religion course:
https://t.co/NcZPcfTURj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @The_Hoggy: Want to come and work for us? The @UoELawSchool is recruiting a lecturer/senior lecturer in Private Law. Details here: https…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SocSciScotland: In case you missed it... Applications are OPEN for #SpringintoMethods - a programme of research methods training being…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mcintosh2001: Great opportunity for someone wanting to work on U.K. Biobank https://t.co/Ptuu6Wt43B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EdinburghUni: Innovative sound technology is set to reveal how city dwellers might better tune in to the natural world around them.
Sen…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @uoessps: Thu 12 April: Joan W. Scott Professor Emerita, School of Social Science, Institute for Advanced Study will be receiving an hon…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jbralston: We are hiring a lecturer in theology and ethics in Edinburgh @SchoolofDiv https://t.co/AIC2VXy39p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Eavanmac: Can’t recommend this enough knowing the field experience of those delivering the course @erinjessee #runto #wishicouldgo http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @edintfest: Visit our our #EdintFest home @thehubroyalmile in August to see Midsummer – a heart warming love letter to Edinburgh by @Dav…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @sgsahblog: Here's a great opportunity put on in collaboration between @SGSAH_  &amp; @SocSciScotland . Now is the time to apply and registe…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here we go....#edintfest launch https://t.co/y9smlI86Oi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EdinUniHealth: Date for your diary!! Inaugural Lecture of Professor Aisha Holloway 'Complex Alcohol Interventions: the trials, theory a…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ScottishOpera: OPPORTUNITY: Applications are now open for young musicians aged 16-21 who want to take their talent to the next level as…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ScottishOpera: This July, experience opera like never before, with our showstopping immersive production of Leoncavallo's #Pagliacci: h…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many congratulations! https://t.co/yO0kso1dWH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @martincorley: Psychologist? #R #rstats user? Interested in quantitative methods? (Bonus points: #openscience?) We have a job for you...…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pubstrat: This is stonkingly good - and bold - from @JanetHughes. Read and reflect; agree and disagree - put the digital into governmen…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @psychmag: So, has anyone got Jan and Feb 2004, save me buying our own mag off eBay?! Just need a good pic of the covers. https://t.co/K…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LLCatEdinburgh: An original work on myth, identity, citizenship and the refugee crisis, Europa a Lampedusa opens tonight @EdinburghUni.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoyVamvakari https://t.co/eqTXoeiRSj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @claudiahammond: We have a great panel for tomorrow evening's BBC recording of the Evidence @ExploreWellcome on transhumanism &amp; how we m…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SCOmusic: Join us for an afternoon of FREE talks and demonstrations about SCO ReConnect @StCeciliasHall as part of Mad Hatter, Grey Mat…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EdinUniNeuro: 'Music as a Medicine' - a Brain Awareness Week event with @StCeciliasHall on Mon 12 March. Part of our #madhattergreymatt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Urban Analytics public lecture @news_RSE https://t.co/Lymisi5rBK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jennylg go see! https://t.co/ec9ED9BJtJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CarnegieUni: After receiving communication about Edinburgh Uni and Stirling Uni we have decided to extend this deadline further - to We…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EdinUniFUSION: 'Music as a Medicine' - a Brain Awareness Week event with @StCeciliasHall on Mon 12 March. With Dr Katie Overy, @eca_edi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FestofMuseums: Edinburgh Uni @CRC_EdUni are busy bees for #FOM2018 as they focus on artist, poet and gardener Ian Hamilton Finlay. They…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EdinMusCom: Tickets now available: https://t.co/d0FQTl3wwK #MITCAncientMariner https://t.co/OweKd1pcS4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Sarah_C_Burley: Great opportunity to work at the Usher Institute - open to non-clinical applicants and across public health research in…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @socialpsychUK: Very important initiative. Please help in any way you can https://t.co/oxjhU94ixr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/HZ8VQ95ku7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How about brownies?! https://t.co/jhQ1Aqw0vF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Elinor Oliphant is completely fine’.... dry good! Bon voyage https://t.co/NfBEnf0tfW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fabulous performance! Thanks so much for smashing #snowmageddon! https://t.co/WFNil0x8A8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SocSciScotland: Deadline this Friday at noon! With the opportunity to present #Impact posters at our Collaboration Showcase in Edinburg…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EdinburghUni: Innovative designs by students studying fashion design at @eca_edinburgh  will be in the spotlight at a catwalk event on…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DrAileenK: We're recruiting a Lecturer in Mathematics Education to help drive forward our exciting ITE portfolio. It's a great time to…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SchoolofPPLS: Why #PhilosophyofScience matters to science | 21 May 2018 @royalsociety
Our Professor Michela Massimi (@p_realism) is giv…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @talbotrice75: We are delighted to introduce Trading Zone, a new type of student exhibition coming to @talbotrice75 this summer!
Details…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BPSOfficial https://t.co/9jQTQm1vLy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ccace: Knowledge Exchange and Impact officer vacancy @ccace See link: https://t.co/Fn6Vy61Ywx https://t.co/JWGqAqDJv3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LLCatEdinburgh: When #PhDlife involves helping judge Britain's oldest literary awards @EdinburghUni! We talk to English Literature PhD…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @scotlandvenice: We are seeking proposals from experienced curators and/or visual arts organisations to produce an ambitious and imagina…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EdinUniCAHSSres: .@PenFielding explores why we read espionage fiction in @TheScotsman. #SpyWeek2018 – a festival of film and fiction or…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EdinburghUni: Creator of @curiousedi virtual tours exploring Edinburgh’s scientific, technical and medical heritage honoured with @Edin…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SchoolofDiv: 📣 Calling all #students, #staff &amp; recent #graduates apply now for the Inspire Launch Grow Awards! You could win part of £2…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NatGalleriesSco: A huge happy birthday to @EdinburghUni , which was founded today 436 years ago! 🎈

Here is the chap who made it possib…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EdinUniStaff: Book your place at one of our staff roadshows to find out more about the landmark Data-Driven Innovation (DDI) Programme…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @IASH_Edinburgh: The @RCPEdin are offering the 2018 McCarthy Award for History of Medicine in Scotland, open to all researchers in the h…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @IASH_Edinburgh: **POSTDOCTORAL FELLOWSHIP KLAXON**

#Fellowships of 3-10 months are available at IASH. We provide:
*£1,250 stipend pcm…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PaperHazell https://t.co/Jp3jNj4FJJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @paisleyis: Experience opera like never before with an immersive performance of Pagliacci by @ScottishOpera at the ‘Paisley Opera House’…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CCC_Research: Fascinating new research by @PolSettlements identifies the impact of the #GoodFridayAgreement on subsequent peace agreeme…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @UoEArtColl: Our art collection booklet is here! Be sure and pick up your free copy @CRC_EdUni &amp; on campus! Beautifully designed by our…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @royalsociety: Our pairing scheme between policymakers &amp; researchers is open. Apply now for our 2018 scheme https://t.co/7DAruQ30X8 #Sci…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FST_Dir: Subsidised training opp for captioners - keen to make sure we get applications from all over, please pass it on: https://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @StellaWYChan: please RT @EdinUniHealth @EdinUniNeuro @EdinUniBrainSci @ccace @EdinburghUni @ccace @SchoolofPPLS @UoE_Teaching @mcintosh…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CathLoveday: Just a few days left to help with this important experiment. Open to everyone over 16, whether or not you’re lonely. Great…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sorry to be missing this! https://t.co/Fv0Ik4nd8P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @p_realism: We are recruiting! Come and do a postdoc in history and philosophy of science with us @Eidyn1 for the Perspectival Realism p…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SueReviews Oh you’ve got me beaten there.....!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SueReviews I spent a lot of my day doing the same...unearthing and setting up 25 yr old Playmobil....love it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WyevaleGC could your cafe queue be ANY slower in #woburnsands ? Organisation some rethinking...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @geoffcrossick: I agree - this is an excellent corrective and should be widely read by academics alarmed by the briefing from the @Royal…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EdinUniCAHSSres: Wonderful profile of @SchoolofPPLS's very own @fluffycyborg in the @NewYorker. It is mind expanding in every possible…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Au revoir @citizenjoesmith and all the best for your new role...you’ll be fabulous! https://t.co/15xpt1g1ZE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really sorry I had to miss this https://t.co/Bsc2o0JjEI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @fuscowriting: I’m honoured to be making a new work to celebrate our brilliant NHS 70th anniversary! Hoping for at least 70 years more t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BPSOfficial: Applications to join or chair the UK National Awarding Committee for EuroPsy are welcome https://t.co/hhdH4BgCWo https://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @socialpsychUK: ***Have you considered making a nomination for our @socialpsychUK awards? Nominations invited for early career, mid-care…]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>