<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server Database Administrator: Requisition ID 2018-40213 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Secret Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description Responsible for the installation, configuration, administration and… https://t.co/KqjOGNCfFO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL DEVELOPER: Earthjustice is the premier nonprofit environmental law organization. We take on the biggest, most precedent-setting cases across the country. We wield the power of law and the strength of partnership to protect people’s health; to… https://t.co/aV2wjrF4pN https://t.co/RlQC1PbOCg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sources: Cohen sending message to Trump: Michael Cohen, the President's former fixer and ultimate loyalist, is sending a clear signal to President Donald Trump and his attorney, Rudy Giuliani, that "the truth is not you(r) or your client's friend,"… https://t.co/OKS93T7rZA https://t.co/PasYhWGdye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .Net Developer SPARS: Senior .Net Developer – SPARS Ref No.:18-00110 Location: Timonium, Maryland Position Type:Full Time Experience Level: 7 Years Start Date: 06/11/2018 Senior .Net Developer – SPARS FEi is a leading IT company specializing in… https://t.co/xEFooUB2ns https://t.co/ze8k8iIeMF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Software Engineer in Test, Core Technology Group (: PRINCIPAL SOFTWARE ENGINEER IN TEST, CORE TECHNOLOGY GROUP (CTG) DATA ENGINE OUR TEAM The Core Technology Group (CTG) is the innovation hub within Employer that is responsible for delivering… https://t.co/gyE2XLzsnH https://t.co/IIdAYiCYRZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C/C++ SQL Transaction Processing: C/C++ SQL – Transaction Processing at Conduent – What We Do What We DoWhat We Do What We Do What We Do Industries – Automotive, Aerospace and Defense – Banking and Capital Markets – Communications and Media – Healthcare… https://t.co/5acWdTKD89 https://t.co/fjnl9oVc9c]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Queen and Prince Philip miss Prince Louis' christening: Prince Louis, the third child of the Duke and Duchess of Cambridge and fifth in line to the throne, has been christened at a private ceremony in London. https://t.co/ot1mvci7BH https://t.co/WOzPbTrOKO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SDET Integration Testing with Parasoft and SQL Experience: SDET – Integration Testing with Parasoft and SQL Experience in Charlotte, North Carolina, United States | IT Infrastructure at CognizantJob Details | Cognizant – ************* – Industries – – –… https://t.co/PAYWcvaB1f https://t.co/RXbp0QDlp2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior-SQL-Server-DBA: We are hiring a Senior SQL Server DBA (8+ years of experience) who will be responsible for Database administration, data analysis and database management, maintenance, enhancement, designing of data dictionaries, physical and… https://t.co/mG8gLSMquI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beauty queen turns in crown after hearing #MeToo joke at pageant: A beauty queen gave up her title after a skit was performed at the Miss Massachusetts competition that made fun of the #MeToo movement. https://t.co/ybcfbgqYwA https://t.co/2wnPCWQplp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[pl/Sql developer: pl/Sql developer Ref No.: 18-27893 Location: pennington, New Jersey Hello, Kindly review the below position and let me know if you are interested, send me an updated resume along with best time to contact. Title: PL/SQL Developer… https://t.co/INQ66Eu5G2 https://t.co/28Ryd98bFp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Developer, https://t.co/qZglOKK4dO, Visual Studio, SSIS, SQL Server: For BNY Mellon Lead Developer, *******, Visual Studio, SSIS, SQL Server job – Information Technology – Multiple Skip to Main Content – – – – Toggle navigation – Who We Are – What… https://t.co/btxTfMKrAZ https://t.co/pTnuMNXaU1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL/Web Developer: SQL/Web Developer: 18-02230 Ref No.: 18-02230 Location: Plano,, Texas Akraya is looking for a SQL/Web Developer for one of our clients. If the job description below is a fit, please apply directly or call Amit at ************. If this… https://t.co/BNz2WuZIos https://t.co/ASoSb9rAFx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beauty queen turns in crown after hearing #MeToo joke at pageant: A beauty queen gave up her title after a skit was performed at the Miss Massachusetts competition that made fun of the #MeToo movement. https://t.co/nacxJ0QnHn https://t.co/qzUdeQONoS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Administrator (SQL Server/Oracle) South Jordan, UT: Requisition Number 930-14731 Job Title Database Administrator (SQL Server/Oracle) South Jordan, UT Working Hours US 800a-500p M-F Location South Jordan, UT Job Description Database… https://t.co/EYXBVP4woi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java, GOLANG, NoSQL(Couchbase or Cassandra): Java, GOLANG, NoSQL(Couchbase or Cassandra) Ref No.: 18-29403 Location: Phoenix, Arizona Java, GOLANG, NoSQL(Couchbase or Cassandra) Engineer Phoenix, AZ Secondary SkillSet : Java, J2EE Technologies, GoLang,… https://t.co/Qx4Fl8QwM9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Big Bang Theory' actress undergoes surgery: "The Big Bang Theory" actress Kayley Cuoco, who married professional equestrian Karl Cook, posted a video and photos on Instagram after undergoing shoulder surgery on her honeymoon. https://t.co/XYKyo8jpgq https://t.co/wKvoGr9BcN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Engineer/Analyst Microsoft SQL: Excellent opportunity with this industry leading, Fortune 500 Corporation in Dallas, TX. RESPONSIBILITIES: – Participate in development team for mobile and web applications – Provide end user support for a specific… https://t.co/tKNCvs53VP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL/Sql Developer: PL/Sql Developer Ref No.:18-10712 Location: San Antonio, Texas Position Type:Contract Start Date: 06/15/2018 Role: PL/Sql Developer Location: San Antonio, TX Contract Position Description: – Oracle PL/SQL, Procedures, Packages and… https://t.co/jleuL0YpHl https://t.co/1EDGPwQ09I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[4 boys make it out of cave, but rain threatens a planned morning effort to rescue 8 others and their coach: The operation to rescue the remaining boys and their coach from a flooded cave in northern Thailand was expected to resume Monday morning, but… https://t.co/UmBbBP6s87 https://t.co/NZUGcoVqzq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Specialist Developer — https://t.co/qZglOKK4dO, MVC, C#, SQL Server, SSRS: Specialist Developer ‘ *******, MVC, C#, SQL Server, SSRS ‘ Provides application software development services or technical support in more complex situations. May also be… https://t.co/8IyO4SrcEB https://t.co/Lbws21Im0P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stunning turnaround by heroin addicted mom: The words that saved Crystal Champ's life were delivered like a spear into the heart. https://t.co/UYbZCocbZ6 https://t.co/BgrhY6r68Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Conversion Developer: SQL Conversion Developer ======================== The SQL Developer converts client data into Tyler s courts and justice software in a way that meets our clients business needs. Location Plano, Texas Responsibilities * Design,… https://t.co/zX8xpWATxL https://t.co/dSfn5ONlpV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Specialist Developer https://t.co/qZglOKK4dO, C#, SQL Server, SSRS, SSIS: For BNY Mellon Specialist Developer – *******, C#, SQL Server, SSRS, SSIS, DB2 job – Asset Servicing – Jersey City, New Jersey Skip to Main Content – – – – Toggle navigation – Who… https://t.co/4zYXcNMPvR https://t.co/nmcp3Vhfsd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL DBA: SQL DBA: 18-02378 Ref No.: 18-02378 Location: Mountain View, California Akraya is looking for a SQL DBA for one of our clients. If the job description below is a fit, please apply directly or call Dipak Badgujar at ************. If this position… https://t.co/bm10q22lWv https://t.co/PAaETLTJD4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Java Developer — JavaScript, Angular, Kafka, SQL: Principal Java Developer ‘ JavaScript, Angular, Kafka, SQL ‘ The Principal Developer position in the AST Performance, Monitoring &amp; Availability Engineering Team will be responsible for… https://t.co/MYc1XMqxxp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These farmers say tariffs could cause them 'serious damage' https://t.co/stXCw9HY4a https://t.co/TfEn7gsSKG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL DB Developer: SQL DB Developer Weston, Massachusetts – United States Job Start Date – 07/02/18, Posted Date – 06/12/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview Apex has an opportunity for a SQL Developer role in the Weston, MA area. This is a 6+ month… https://t.co/1Wi83GdYnG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETL Data Warehouse Developer (MS BI, MS SQL, SSIS): Job Description The successful candidate will be a part of the team that is responsible for Enterprise Business Intelligence. This position requires that the candidate understands, uses and applies… https://t.co/v8TqRYIab0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Business Systems Analyst — GRS — Strong SQL: Technical Business Systems Analyst’ ‘ GRS ‘ Strong SQL Formulates and defines system’s scope and objectives based on both user needs and a good understanding of the application, business, operational… https://t.co/euZ3dwbHIK https://t.co/9ySVtbJh2f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server: ******/SQL Server Ref No.: 18-29062 Location: Lincolnshire, Illinois DEVELOPER-L3 Job Description(As per hiring manager) Key skills required for the job are: Java-J2EE-L3 (Mandatory) SQL Server-L3 As a Senior Developer, you are responsible… https://t.co/1pNHBp8YGF https://t.co/xIGCnX8N4i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior SQL Database Administrator: Senior SQL Database Administrator – Job Location:Headquarters – Alexandria, VA – Job Status:Full Time – Position Type:IT – Operations – Date Posted:5/21/2018 – Location Address:880 S. Pickett Street Alexandria, VA 22304… https://t.co/G3ONhPO7pG https://t.co/NF81RudGhj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Java Developer — JavaScript, Angular, Kafka, SQL: Principal Java Developer ‘ JavaScript, Angular, Kafka, SQL ‘ The Principal Developer position in the AST Performance, Monitoring &amp; Availability Engineering Team will be responsible for… https://t.co/S29cWhvsfG https://t.co/wMWqxVmhbY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Conversion Developer: SQL Conversion Developer ======================== The SQL Developer converts client data into Tyler s courts and justice software in a way that meets our clients business needs. Location Plano, Texas Responsibilities * Design,… https://t.co/WtqGjG72lf https://t.co/GGDGrigMc3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Data Analyst: SQL Data Analyst Ref No.: 18-28714 Location: Jacksonville, Florida Role: SQL Data Analyst Location:Jacksonville FL Duration:12 Months Contract Skills Required Should have strong exp. with Data Analysis with SQL. https://t.co/gYiNbHGbeH https://t.co/GUslTd7ksk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: System One has a client in the Jacksonville area with an immediate opening for a Mid-Level .Net Developer. This is a full-time/permanent position and ideally looking for those local to Jacksonville or specifically looking to relocate… https://t.co/YlZkErbUqh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woman aims fireworks at people on street: Police are looking for a woman who was caught on camera shooting fireworks on a Brooklyn street. No one was hurt, but police say she could face charges of reckless endangerment and unlawful possession. https://t.co/dTigxojZon https://t.co/LXL2FnzFWg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle EBS Manager: About the position The Enterprise Services and Systems (ESS) organization provides strategic technical solutions for various Actuarial, Financial, and other business groups. Oracle E-Business Suite is a key component of the… https://t.co/rl4W2e6PRI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Report Developer II: Overview Our Developer will design, document, develop, and implement reporting solutions. Uses analytical skills to create reports and database objects. Provides maintenance and troubleshooting of reporting issues identified… https://t.co/OuAlNxiEA0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trucker charged in deadly team bus crash: Charges have been filed against the driver of a tractor-trailer that collided with a bus carrying members of a Canadian junior hockey team, killing 16 people, authorities in Canada's Saskatchewan province said… https://t.co/6hsPaGW6ZB https://t.co/ufR4vcscFh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior UI Developer Engineer Angular JS, Node.js, JavaScript CSS SQL Server: BDC is a clearance and settlement platform handling government securities mandated to replace GSCX as a service provider in this domain. BNYM clearance and settlement platform… https://t.co/Z7Y0yk2WCk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sys Admin-Programmer/PowerShell and SQL: Requisition ID 2018-43237 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Secret Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description GDIT is currently seeking a Sys Admin / Programmer –… https://t.co/bzgAEVIR1t https://t.co/YQK5ALCsEJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Database Developer – SQL – Los Angeles, CA – $140k: Irvine Technology Corporation (ITC) is a leading provider of technology and staffing solutions for IT, Security, Engineering, and Interactive Design disciplines servicing startups to enterprise… https://t.co/owuVRMDwUI https://t.co/cjhxI61zMz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Couple finds hidden message in wall: A couple in California discovered a 23-year-old hidden message in their bathroom wall during renovations. https://t.co/32qIOAXRFS https://t.co/80vSMLEjGF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. PHP Developer w/ NoSQL: SR. SOFTWARE ENGINEER – Permanent (No sponsorship today or in 3 years) AUSTIN, TX DIRECT HIRE – SALARY UP TO $125K – Will pay for relocation IMMEDIATE NEED for a Sr. LAMP Engineer to join our large enterprise client in Austin,… https://t.co/wRVbaACyWZ https://t.co/j8SUpc8e7K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Belgium takes on Brazil https://t.co/BpMpQfTokP https://t.co/PDUPQW6CTL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Database Developer – Corptax: Senior Database Developer CSC Employer is a market leader in leading-edge commercial tax software and process solutions . Through our unique ERP solution, we unlock the value of the tax function, transforming it into a… https://t.co/nAEQeXgbmC https://t.co/Trw0cUHJpO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering Quality Specialist: Quality Specialist for Ariba, Inc (Palo Alto, CA) to to work in a cross functional development or testing team with special focus on quality assurance and test related tasks within the product creation process. Bachelor’s… https://t.co/aPttPzm1zX https://t.co/bWtpHsDnvT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Specialist Developer (T-SQL, PL/SQL, Database design, objects, tuning): Sr. Specialist Developer (T-SQL, PL/SQL, Database design, objects, tuning) ‘ Developer, Application Development and Tools:’ Responsible for designing custom applications and… https://t.co/O3ctTNW8TV https://t.co/3Me5STD3Dk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Data Analyst: Job Description What you’ll be doing… – Work autonomously with Marketing, Finance, and IT to interpret business requirements to SQL code in order to anticipate, investigate, and resolve issues related to new and ongoing projects. –… https://t.co/yPJr4uYKV8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C++, PL/SQL Developer: C++, PL/SQL Developer Ref No.: 18-25330 Location: Charlotte,, North Carolina C++, PL/SQL Developer Charlotte, NC 6 Months Job Description: 1. Should possess strong technical skills to develop software using C++, Oracle PL/SQL and… https://t.co/YivwXFMCrZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Data Analyst: Job ID: ********-10050-LEK Company Name: Argus Description: LCI is an industry leader at analytical and technological services to the financial industry. Founded over 25 years ago, we handle over 1.3 billion accounts a year for the… https://t.co/Jc127hl6dt https://t.co/d1Jj344WOQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL/SQL Developer with .Net Exp: PL/SQL Developer with .Net Exp Ref No.: 18-28361 Location: Santa Clara, California Position: PL/SQL Developer with .Net Exp Location: Santa Clara, CA / Tempe, AZ Experience in coding, designing and testing new web software… https://t.co/DOQHsoFbw2 https://t.co/XHZ3a6yMgA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[School's first black valedictorian can't speak at graduation: Jaisaan Lovett is the 2018 valedictorian at the University Preparatory Charter School For Young Men and after he said he was denied to speak at his graduation, the mayor stepped in to help get… https://t.co/rTYzytqc3Y https://t.co/G2Yw7Qh9gj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Junior SQL Data Developer: Junior SQL Data Developer at Conduent Skip Navigation Search Keyword CategorySelectAccountingAdministrative SupportAudit &amp; ComplianceBenefitsBrand &amp; Product MarketingBuck Consulting-ActuarialBuck Consulting-NonActuarialBusiness… https://t.co/IYzUb9SP8I https://t.co/yUObKiRKaC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Trump's White House, this is the moment that wasn't: When President Donald Trump declared a year ago that "very fine people" were among the Nazi mobs descending upon Charlottesville, Virginia, the reaction was swift. https://t.co/qxdUkWX7JR https://t.co/FutyUmK72y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MySQL Database and Systems Administrator: Requisition ID 2018-44503 # of Openings 0 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Secret Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description MySQL Database and Systems Administrator General Dynamics is… https://t.co/IO95WPuiwr https://t.co/hHKKuovRx4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle SQL Developer: Oracle SQL Developer Ref No.:18-18300 Location: Quincy, Massachusetts Job Title: Oracle SQL Developer (ITS63_APPDEV_EHS_FY 19 – 003) Location: Quincy, MA 02171 Duration: 11+ Months Contract Job Description: We are seeking… https://t.co/nUtCp2uFhB https://t.co/tezBzuXvGo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Senior Database Administrator: The Senior Data Administrator defines and standardizes data used by the firm. This individual also serves as a resource to junior members of the data administration team through establishing guidelines according to the… https://t.co/6gvman1tLe https://t.co/dFdJAGDRWn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network/Systems Administrator – Cisco: Requisition ID 2018-42376 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Secret Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description EACN consists of operational network equipment known as A2G2s… https://t.co/d0pYaqAAAI https://t.co/4Uk6IZ1luU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business System Analyst II: Job Title Business System Analyst II Job ID(Requisition ID):3693 Job Summary Works closely with Development Engineering Technical Program Managers (PMs) and Development Engineering functional management to deliver tools, data,… https://t.co/r7SfkhlFKW https://t.co/l3Sv7xd9yN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server Database Developer: SQL Server Database Developer home About Us – News – Blog – Careers – Resources – Leadership Products – TruCare – Integrations Demo Careers Contact Customer Log In Careers Home Career SQL Server Databa… Careers SQL Server… https://t.co/noJyBFwmAG https://t.co/SQ6s4nc6wr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Musician's odd behavior alarms bandmates: Mark Staudte's bandmates grew concerned when the 61-year-old exhibited unusual behavior during rehearsal. Shortly after, Staudte was dead -- and at the center of a medical mystery. For more, watch HLN's… https://t.co/FydCtBsEsf https://t.co/6JmaeBZOLj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior SQL Developer: Markit Digital is looking for a talented SQL Server Database Developer/Analyst who is interested in working with large, complex data sets. Our growing development team is looking for folks eager to take on the challenge of… https://t.co/2e94n5RD8f https://t.co/swZ7dRjFta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL/SQL Developer: PL/SQL Developer Ref No.: 18-33612 Location: tempe, Arizona Hello, Greetings for the day ! We have an urgent requirement for PL/SQL Developer in Tempe , AZ. Please let me know if you are looking for a new project. You can reach me at… https://t.co/fB8DuuWNG3 https://t.co/gcRlSzN6Ku]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Buzz Aldrin: Space Force is 'one giant leap in the right direction': He was there when man first landed on the moon in 1969 and on Friday, Buzz Aldrin endorsed a new galactic effort -- the Trump administration's Space Force. https://t.co/ig2rkSmBzS https://t.co/ktFFqjypgl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server Database Administrator: Requisition ID 2018-40213 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Secret Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description Responsible for the installation, configuration, administration and… https://t.co/UULv8MJILT https://t.co/R3vI4h2iwU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finally, Nunes admits what his charade is all about https://t.co/A2bw9UDe4v https://t.co/kjLsD59ggw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ICM Developer: Job Title: ICM Developer Location: Seattle, WA Job Number: JO-1805-27058 Description ProKarma currently has an exciting opportunity for an ICM Developer that would like to join our team as a full-time employee in Seattle, WA.… https://t.co/20R35GxmQh https://t.co/geT4EWqM7i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Java Developer JavaScript, Angular, Kafka, SQL: Job Description Principal Java Developer – JavaScript, Angular, Kafka, SQL The Principal Developer position in the AST Performance, Monitoring &amp; Availability Engineering Team will be responsible… https://t.co/eV2plstYDl https://t.co/1mCImxEEpO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Intelligence Developer: Why We Work at Dun &amp; Bradstreet Life here at Dun &amp; Bradstreet is changing for the better. With almost two centuries of experience and a new modern vibe, work at D &amp; B has never been more exhilarating. Our purpose is to… https://t.co/TQ0OwSqYPt https://t.co/OnMUKFYf4n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MySQL Database Administrator: General Dynamics is looking for an experienced MySQL Database Administrator who will be responsible for ensuring the performance, availability, and security of MySQL instances. You will also be responsible for orchestrating… https://t.co/PFZDcdWr5b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: How 'BlacKkKlansman' could help America write a new chapter: Spike Lee's brilliantly provocative film "BlacKkKlansman" (about the true story of a black undercover police officer who joins the Klan with the aid of a white colleague) opens wide on… https://t.co/Z7qsZqDgwv https://t.co/isgz277cFr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lance Armstrong hospitalized after bike crash https://t.co/rjILbF9aHO https://t.co/kBeDbnv77A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst II Purchase to Pay Oracle: Business Analyst II – Purchase to Pay – Oracle – Are you ready to make a difference? School Specialty is dedicated to changing education for the better. That means working closely with educators, sharing… https://t.co/hzQxqOqACB https://t.co/xUOEgpjl66]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ocasio-Cortez: Every other developed nation in the world does this. Why can't America?: Democratic congressional candidate Alexandria Ocasio-Cortez questions why Republicans are happy to pay for tax cuts and "unlimited war" but the GOP, and some… https://t.co/lY85OwB6VH https://t.co/HNZ8LuQ1gs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: ******/SQL Developer Ref No.: 18-31506 Location: Englewood – Colorado, Colorado Description : Develop, implement Stored procedures, Functions, and Triggers using Microsoft SQL Server Review and interpret ongoing business report… https://t.co/uTQkp5uZq0 https://t.co/Ud0RomJo5R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Footage of police shooting released in Nashville https://t.co/UzbXXARqS5 https://t.co/0RIaYF8Zaq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[End of American Era brings chaos: The first major global conflict of the 21st century broke out in the Middle East. It didn't involve Iran. ISIS wasn't a factor. Surprisingly, even Israel found itself on the sidelines. https://t.co/c3JboG7JBm https://t.co/jcdxL4s93U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr SQL Server Data Warehouse Engineer: DESCRIPTION _*background check required_ Reporting to the leader of the Cardiac Rhythm and Heart Failure (CRHF) Data Management (DM) Organization, this role will serve as a data warehouse engineer supporting the… https://t.co/RVQZGjN9G6 https://t.co/PtGkvdCZkE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She has a Purple Heart and tattoos — and is the Democrats' new face https://t.co/shsFxVVH3A https://t.co/bYz1naxrjd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETL Developer/Implementation/SQL Server: Job Description Transforming the future of healthcare isn’t something we take lightly. It takes teams of the best and the brightest, working together to make an impact. As one of the largest healthcare technology… https://t.co/vLKXQRfVvB https://t.co/mt3xZo2u8o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Administrator IV: Job Description Description Requisition #: DATAB01600 Job Title: Database Administrator IV Location: Quantico, VA Clearance Level: Active DoD – Top Secret SCI Required Certification(s): IAT III certification (CISA, GCIH, GCED,… https://t.co/9GVNWYjuCl https://t.co/MpPLRWylhD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst: What We Do: Temenos Group is a market leading banking software provider, partnering with banks and other financial institutions to transform their businesses and stay ahead of a changing marketplace. Headquartered in Geneva and with… https://t.co/QLIcrevtmn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deported parents hug their kids for first time in months https://t.co/YlfHGIitbc https://t.co/TLAqd5wOhe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Functional Analyst: Functional Analyst Ref No.: 18-33385 Location: San Francisco, California o Business understanding on Energy trading, Credit calculation and Market Risk. o Energy Portfolio Management o Commodities – Natural Gas, Power, Renewable o… https://t.co/DsS2qkD7Lc https://t.co/ZPBgnwAFcF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst (SQL): Job Location US-VA-Reston Job ID 10301 Job Location United States Category Information Technology/Software Overview American Institutes for Research (AIR) is a leading professional services firm with a growing software engineering and… https://t.co/QuMOd9jxVN https://t.co/z89nWhqkln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Developer Associate II: Our Lakewood, CO location is currently looking for full-time Database Engineer to be part of a team that is responsible for delivering timely, high quality releases that delight our customers in the upstream oil &amp; gas… https://t.co/h5RAOAJP9u https://t.co/NPiDhstfhR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. SQL Server DBA: Job TitleSr. SQL Server DBA – ID:28818 Duration9 – 12 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsSQL, SQL Server LocationEl Segundo, CA &amp; Las Vegas, NV Date Posted07/18/2018 SQL Database Administrator/Architect As a Sr. Database Administrator ,… https://t.co/wnCxan63TA https://t.co/62s6Uu4ibz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior IT Business Analyst (SQL Server/Integration/Teletrack: DESCRIPTION The position is moderately visible to the hospitals business service lines and functions as a team member responsible for assisting in providing application(s) configuration… https://t.co/8HPrEiuByg https://t.co/Fjv6vAY9Q5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump and Pelosi are keeping the midterms interesting https://t.co/nmUHn5ffbC https://t.co/EgPty3OGKt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Database Specialist: DCCA is a veteran-owned high-technology company specializing in providing information technology services to a variety of government agencies and commercial enterprises since 1982. DCCA is proud to offer a strong, competitive… https://t.co/5T24L6FnJm https://t.co/YfZj2ZbQJw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Record numbers of women are running, but how many can win?: With primary season underway and a record number of women on ballots nationwide, the question now is how many will make it to office after elections in November. The reality is that many of the… https://t.co/uDeGg7qyA9 https://t.co/cdHWBCzrpJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL – DBA: SQL – DBA Ref No.: 18-32877 Location: Dallas, Texas At NTT DATA, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The quality, integrity, and commitment of our employees are key factors in our company’s growth, market… https://t.co/Kn7eh1AVFt https://t.co/5rpdUFoIDK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior .Net Software Engineer: Job Location US-DC Job ID 10291 Job Location United States Overview Be part of something innovative and cutting edge. Join our team of more than a hundred software engineers, designers, project managers and software… https://t.co/6PSWi1PaGO https://t.co/Ru48HpkvBE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: Gates' brutal lesson for Manafort: Rick Gates' testimony in the Paul Manafort trial should teach the rest of the Trump campaign universe an important lesson: Criminals can't trust each other. And there are a number of people in this orbit who… https://t.co/uEPWKf3Z62 https://t.co/S24FIpFQDR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL DBA – Chicago Loop (Great team and Manager!) 100K: We are seeking a SQL DBA who will be responsible for maintenance, enhancement, designing of data dictionaries, physical and logical database models, and performance tuning. This is a great… https://t.co/EurYJO64eC https://t.co/vFiXZiU9k6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could this plate get young kids to eat veggies?: Segmented plates with pictures of recommended foods in each compartment led preschoolers to eat more vegetables, according to a research letter published Monday in the journal JAMA Pediatrics. https://t.co/gJbSXRTW6j https://t.co/zuWSy5g2to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL DevOps Engineer: SQL DevOps Engineer – Clinicient – Login / Support – ************ – Toggle Menu Skip to content – Products &amp; Services – INSIGHT Platform – EMR – Billing &amp; Collection Services – About – About Us – Careers – Contact Us – Resources –… https://t.co/cskZ4ZnVI2 https://t.co/FLKhQOxAgz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETL Data Warehouse Developer (MS BI, MS SQL, SSIS): Job Description The successful candidate will be a part of the team that is responsible for Enterprise Business Intelligence. This position requires that the candidate understands, uses and applies… https://t.co/hmbl705FfO https://t.co/mbg7rzCLM4]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>