<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweatpants are a sign of defeat. You lost control of your life so you bought some sweatpants. --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The History of Rolex Watches – The Start of Something Great  http://t.co/fp76wL8lIt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In my opinion Microsoft is a lot better at making money than it is at making good operating systems. Linus Torvalds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about the Bay Area city of Danville, California http://t.co/eN691aYqJH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Jose Feliciano  http://t.co/axoo6SbTzy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you are thin, don't eat fast. If you are fat, don't eat fast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious Cat Scratch Rapper Music Mixer - Awesome!  http://t.co/d6C7ylKwl3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge a man by how much he does when he doesn't need to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God has no intention of setting a limit to the efforts of man to conquer space. - Pope Pius XII]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some days, you just can't get rid of a bomb! - Adam West, Batman &amp; Robin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The whole fleet knows this man tried to stab me through the neck. And you missed! Butterfingers! - Gaius Baltar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love my crazy girlfriend - hilarious t-shirt - http://t.co/u5Cfg89v1h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter what, the very first piece of social media real estate I'd start with is a blog.  Chris Brogan - New Marketing Labs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inflation is when you pay fifteen dollars for the ten-dollar haircut you used to get for five dollars when you had hair. - Sam Ewing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Before you take somebody's head off be sure you've used yours]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wouldn't feel right wearing clothes covering my body.  Christina Aguilera]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the God Particle – Higgs Boson – On the Run  http://t.co/9106dRaGEM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Are the Major Kinds of Insurance?  http://t.co/TRcigKCXZT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things could be worse. Suppose your errors were counted and published everyday, like those of a baseball player. - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn Baseball Lingo  http://t.co/znknMpyQHR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A shoe has so much more to offer than just to walk. - Christian Louboutin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Thoughts on Baseball Equipment - Its so important! http://t.co/Y2zFRiOY9N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Celiac Disease Requires Gluten Free Foods - Learn More  http://t.co/pWfpiTTWet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Favorite Things for Kids to Review  http://t.co/2WRxryCj3o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A university is what a college becomes when the faculty loses interest in students. - John Ciardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Writing Company Blogs that are Effective  http://t.co/QObhe7XLl8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wal-mart --  do they like make walls there?  Paris Hilton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Harold Melvin and the Blue Notes  http://t.co/5d60OSEjN1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He was born with a silver spoon --  but  never made a stir with it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting Your Creative Writing Degree Online  http://t.co/pJFEpRoSrm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of DC Comics  http://t.co/z9FwMgultV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best use of life is to spend it for something that outlasts it - William James]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You see things; and you say "Why?" But I dream things that never were; and I say "Why not?" - George Bernard Shaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teenagers do everything we did…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the Dos XX Most Interesting Man In the World - Top Quotes!  http://t.co/nbk69bYbke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL - Cool - A Computer Mouse with a Spider in it!   http://t.co/q3ZHWH67hK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just think it's great to show a gown that's $8,000 and a shoe that's, like, $25 - but still look fabulous together. - Christian Siriano]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to find somebody and you want to be married and you want to have children, don't make it a rock star. - Stevie Nicks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His pockets always outlast his suits...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Help with Planning Garage Flooring  http://t.co/a9QD7I5K5A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am truly not one to give advice. I'm divorced and I stole my best friend's husband.  Denise Richards on Love]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to know how your girl will treat you after you married her,  just listen to her talking to her little brother.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Locate Your Garage Space Before Installation Of Cabinets  http://t.co/aH1QKPo5HY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instead of one-way interruption, web marketing is about delivering useful content - David Scott - Author]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We worked 80 hour weeks for 30 years to keep from having to get a real job. - Tom Lemon's comment on the rigors of being a drag racing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The time has come the Walrus said, To talk of many thing’s Of shoes and ships and sealing-wax of cabbages and kings - Lewis Carroll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What really decides consumers to buy or not to buy is the content of your advertising, not its form. - David Ogilvy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Wonderful Canadian Rockies Tour  http://t.co/d06ouxzlIp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Psychiatry is a pseudoscience. You don't know the history of psychiatry. I do. Matt. - Tom Cruise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Media is a Helpful Tool in Connecting with Customers  http://t.co/H15Dz4oEd0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Grand Slam in Tennis – what's the big deal?  http://t.co/fK1sx6zwYN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would you say a parachutist is a fall guy?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips for Using Facebook Pages for Your Business  http://t.co/qSWLL01E8i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool check out this Nerd Kit...  http://t.co/8BvOoS8n6U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The man who remarked that money isn't everything must have gone through a woman's purse.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't tell you what I had for breakfast, but I can sing every single word of rock and roll. - Patty Duke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A toupee is ear to ear carpeting!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seniors Gain from Social Networking Technology  http://t.co/rZnZbseUOy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What fun is it being cool if you can't wear a sombrero? --&gt; Bill Watterson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its better to own the racecourse then the race horse - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your Business Guide for Small Business Internet Marketing  http://t.co/B8wIXMYiff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What we want is to see the child in pursuit of knowledge, and not knowledge in pursuit of the child. - George Bernard Shaw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any government big enough to give you everything you want is big enough to take it away from you, too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making money is a hobby that will complement any other hobbies you have, beautifully. Scott Alexander]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always wear expensive shoes. People notice. - Brian Koslow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I really love this Han Solo iPhone case - may the force be with you! http://t.co/PmChN3hKyA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The purity of a person's heart can be quickly measured by how they regard animals - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The process of growing old is a question of mind over matter. If you don't mind, it doesn't matter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yeah, well. The Dude abides. - The Dude, The Big Lebowski]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women need food, water, and compliments.  That's right.  And an occasional pair of shoes. Chris Rock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pair off in threes. - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These Yoda Lights Must You Have!  Wonderful Geek Gear! http://t.co/Tw0YuJi8wd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We can judge the heart of a man by his treatment of animals. - Immanual Kant]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you tried to give rock and roll another name, you might call it 'Chuck Berry'. - John Lennon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd make a wonderful Lady Macbeth. I'll wear a pair of platform shoes or something - Bette Midler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Tennis – The Sport of Kings  http://t.co/DDb09o0zuz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Habit is habit and not to be flung out of the window by any man, but coaxed downstairs a step at a time. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious Pacifier with a Mustache  - Kids and Adults will love it! http://t.co/9LlkpAMPT5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It gets late early out there. - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 meals a day a roof over my head, two cars, a boat, a power mower and a contented  wife -- why shouldn't I be in debt?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Space Invaders Video Game - Men's Silk Necktie - Cool! http://t.co/XSKqm48sLO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I had learned education I would not have had time to learn anything else. - Cornelius Vanderbilt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't realize how strong a person really is until you see them at their weakest moment. - Unknown Author]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Hire a Strategy Consulting Firm?  http://t.co/AVfj2IszdI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A canter is the cure for all evil. - Benjamin Disraeli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Mac and Katie Kissoon  http://t.co/zzZo3Ajv3f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suitor: A guy who thinks he's throwing a girl a line when all the time he's being roped in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To succeed in business, to reach the top, an individual must know all it is possible to know about that business. - J. Paul Getty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anthony “Tony” Harris, CSECO President and CEO, receives an Honorary Doctorate in Engineering from Purdue University  http://t.co/3JCa4VHoNZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Power of Solar Power - Get Plugged In!  http://t.co/cqNI8QA7Er]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Black Sabbath  http://t.co/3afxfVzexr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dr. Who Blue Tardis Min-Fridge - so “COOL”! - http://t.co/3R9vuBwHYM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Management is nothing more than motivating other people. - Le Iacocca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One deer to another:  "I wish I had his doe"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NASA Unveils a Very Cool New Space Suit  http://t.co/Tj9qjbC0dm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only undertake what you can do in an excellent fashion. There are no prizes for average performance.- Brian Tracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Joe Tex  http://t.co/u9vlmEt0OC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Auto racing is boring except when a car is going at least 172 miles per hour upside down. - Dave Barry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man's health can be judged by which he takes two at a time - pills or stairs. - Joan Welsh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I pretty much try to stay in a constant state of confusion just because of the expression it leaves on my face.  Johnny Depp quotes]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>