<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA["Perseverance is failing nineteen times and succeeding the twentieth." - Julie Andrews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Never mistake motion for action." - Ernest Hemingway]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["He that can have patience can have what he will." - Benjamin Franklin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You cannot change your destination overnight, but you can change your direction overnight." - Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Failure is the opportunity to begin again, more intelligently." - Henry Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["All great changes are preceded by chaos." - Deepak Chopra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Do we need more time? Or do we need to be more disciplined with the time we have?" - Kerry Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Destiny is not a matter of chance; but a matter of choice." - William Jennings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Let me tell you the secret that has led me to my goal. My strength lies solely in my tenacity." - Louis Pasteur]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Happiness is a choice that requires effort at times" - Aeschylus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Efforts and courage are not enough without purpose and direction." - John F. Kennedy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The value of achievement lies in the achieving." - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It isn't what you do, but how you do it." - John Wooden]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Look deep into nature, and you will understand everything better." - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["One is always a long way from solving a problem until one actually has the answer." - Stephen Hawking]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I can accept failure, everyone fails at something. But I can't accept not trying." - Michael Jordan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It is good to have an end to journey towards; but it is the journey that matters in the end." - Ursula Le Guin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It is not easy to find happiness in ourselves, and it is not possible to find it elsewhere." - Agnes Repplier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Things which matter most must never be at the mercy of things which matter least." - Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Happiness is when what you think, what you say, and what you do are in harmony." - Mahatma Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A journey of a thousand miles must begin with a single step." - Lao-Tsu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Excellence is not a skill. It is an attitude." - Ralph Marston]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Life is the art of drawing without an eraser." - John W. Gardner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The key to any game is to use your strengths and hide your weaknesses." - Paul Westphal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["There are only two tragedies in life: one is not getting what one wants, and the other is getting it." - Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Happiness is when what you think, what you say, and what you do are in harmony." - Mahatma Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Management by objective works - if you know the objectives. Ninety percent of the time you don't." - Peter Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The artist is nothing without the gift, but the gift is nothing without work." - Emile Zola]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Don't judge each day by the harvest you reap, but by the seeds you plant." - Robert Louis Stevenson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To climb steep hills requires slow pace at first." - William Shakespeare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Tough times never last, but tough people do." - Dr. Robert Schuller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You will never find time for anything. If you want the time, you must make it." -  Charles Buxton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The greatest mistake you can make in life is to be continually fearing you will make one." - Elbert Hubbard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Hold yourself responsible for a higher standard than anybody else expect of you." - Henry Ward Beecher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["While we are postponing, life speeds by." - Seneca"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Man can believe the impossible, but can never believe the improbable." - Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["This world is but a canvas to our imagination." - Henry David Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A person who never made a mistake never tried anything new." - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The results you achieve will be in direct proportion to the effort you apply." - Denis Waitley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We will either find a way, or make one." - Hannibal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It is a rough road that leads to the heights of greatness. - Seneca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I've failed over and over and over again in my life and that is why I succeed." - Michael Jordan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Freedom is nothing but a chance to be better." - Albert Camus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["All our dreams can come true, if we have the courage to pursue them." - Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We generally change ourselves for one of two reasons: inspiration or desperation." -  Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Great spirits have always encountered violent opposition from mediocre minds." - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Formula for success: under promise and over deliver." - Tom Peters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The true definition of madness is repeating the same action, over and over, hoping for a different result." - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The purpose of our lives is to be happy." - Dalai Lama]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A business that makes nothing but money is a poor business." - Henry Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Enthusiasm finds the opportunities, and energy makes the most of them." - Henry Hoskins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Knowledge speaks, but wisdom listens." - Jimi Hendrix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Try not to become a man of success, but rather try to become a man of value." - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A true critic ought to dwell rather upon excellencies than imperfections." - Joseph Addison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The time to relax is when you don't have time for it." - Jim Goodwin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A goal without a plan is just a wish." - Antoine de Saint Exupery]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Heroes are made in the hour of defeat. Success is, therefore, well described as a series of glorious defeats." - Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Your philosophy determines whether you will go for the disciplines or continue the errors." - Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Wisdom begins in wonder." - Socrates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Sometimes the easiest way is the hard way." - John Finn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Be yourself; everyone else is already taken." - Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["In everything we do, our own thoughts can help us succeed, or they can help us fail. Maintain a positive attitude." - Catherine Pulsifer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I cannot teach anybody anything, I can only make them think." - Socrates]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Life has no limitations, except the ones you make." - Les Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Obstacles are those frightful things you see when you take your eyes off the goal." - Henry Ford]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The only people who never fail are those who never try." - Ilka Chase]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Excellence is the unlimited ability to improve the quality of what you have to offer." - Rick Pitino]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You cannot tailor make your situation in life, but you can tailor make your attitudes to fit those situations." - Zig Ziglar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Until you make peace with who you are, you'll never be content with what you have." - Doris Mortman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you do what you've always done, you'll get what you've always gotten." -Tony Robbins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I'd rather be a failure at something I love than a success at something I hate." - George F. Burns]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Kindness in words creates confidence. Kindness in thinking creates profoundness. Kindness in giving creates love."  - Lao Tzu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Champions are propelled by desire, not compelled by fear." - Denis Waitley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The hardest thing to see is what is in front of your eyes." - Johann Wolfgang von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The best way to cheer yourself up is to try to cheer somebody else up." - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's kind of fun to do the impossible." - Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's not what you are that holds you back, it's what you think you are not." - Denis Waitley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Where the willingness is great, the difficulties cannot be great." - Machiavelli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Success is the maximum utilisation of the ability that you have." - Zig Ziglar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A short saying often contains much wisdom." - Sophocles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I believe that every person is born with talent." - Maya Angelou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Everything should be made as simple as possible, but not simpler." - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Nothing will ever be attempted if all possible objections must first be overcome." - Samuel Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I can resist anything but temptation." - Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It doesn't matter if I don't succeed in something, what matters is that I learn from my mistakes." - Linda Evans]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's not that I'm so smart , it's just that I stay with problems longer ." - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The best way to have a good idea is to have lots of ideas." - Linus Pauling]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Never, never, never give up." - Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Ability will never catch up with the demand for it." - Confucius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Forgive yourself for your faults and your mistakes and move on." - Les Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you do not change direction, you may end up where you are heading." - Lao Tzu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Little by little, one travels far." - J. R. R. Tolkien]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Genius without education is like silver in the mine." - Benjamin Franklin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Take time for all things: great haste makes great waste." - Benjamin Franklin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Love without action is meaningless and action without love is irrelevant." - Deepak Chopra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["While we stop to think, we often miss our opportunity." - Publilius Syrus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Some people grumble because roses have thorns; I am thankful that the thorns have roses." - Alphonse Karr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You can adopt the attitude there is nothing you can do, or you can see the challenge as your call to action." - Catherine Pulsifer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["I love Mickey Mouse more than any woman I have ever known." - Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When I let go of what I am, I become what I might be." - Lao Tsu]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>