<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think you need it more than you need Jesus, it's become an idol regardless of what "it" is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The moments when I least feel like praying are always the ones where I most need it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Such a privilege to hold out the hope of Jesus to a world longing for light. https://t.co/wO8fQXIHyf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LIVE on #Periscope: Sermon Q&amp;A: Money, Power, Intimacy with God and Sovereignty of God https://t.co/wM5YZLC7rc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Going live on Periscope in 10 minutes...invite some friends to join us!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Questions on the last 3 sermons? Jump on Periscope and ask me tonight at 8.30EST.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some of the greatest leaders I know, not because of our power, but because of our confidence in… https://t.co/5mOf5xn20W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sermon Q&amp;A tonight at 8.30 on Periscope. Topics include: money, how we use power, intimacy w/ God &amp; our crazy schedules.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#NationalRefugeeSunday is a reminder &amp; a challenge: the church is called to lead the fight for justice, compassion and hope!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weakness isn’t an obstacle to being used by God. In fact, it’s a prerequisite!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait to encounter Jesus with my Restoration City family tomorrow morning.  Love to have you join us. 10am. Synetic Theater.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Things we learned today: the entire staff of Restoration City fits comfortably in 18 square feet.… https://t.co/tGMS7BdlCY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The church doesn't need your impersonation of a Christian celebrity.  Be yourself - it's the only way to be truly impressive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life changes at the intersection of vulnerability, the gospel &amp; community. Honesty, grace &amp; a good friend are a powerful trio!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is great freedom in knowing you are in over your head and totally dependent on the sovereign power of God.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead with vision.  People who are inspired will always exceed what is required.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's a shameful and dangerous thing when leaders are rewarded for appealing to our fears instead of our potential.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grateful for all God is doing through @LonSolomon and his partnership in the gospel. #sameteam]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our actions, not our words, reveal our priorities.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Realism is good. Pessimism isn't. Lead with vision and hope, not fear and fatalism.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I just wish this city had some inspiring views! #DC https://t.co/AelThDIB9A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tracking with a narrow band of leaders fuels imitation.  Drawing from a wide circle creates inspiration.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're afraid to seek counsel, it's probably because you already know you're planning to make a bad decision!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of the bigger mistakes you could make this week: not pre-registering for #Passion2017! https://t.co/tIGNoIla5d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You won’t see growth where you are unwilling to show grace.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Leaders engage what others are willing to ignore.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greatness is found in service.
Power is found in weakness.
Life is found in death.

Jesus changes everything!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's a spiritual growth that can only come through service. https://t.co/8avTf8MBdS https://t.co/uiApGKNHHo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing day with Restoration City.  Don't miss the chance the serve with our team.  Sign up online: https://t.co/nAEA2QwNwy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is literally nothing in the world that can compete with the local church! I absolutely love it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beyond excited to be back with my @RCChurchDC family tomorrow.  Don't miss what God is going to do!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the inspiration of #Passion2016 comes rushing back every time I listen. Do yourself a favor… https://t.co/GYKdSPb2yv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Holy Spirit IN you is more than enough for everything God wants to accomplish THROUGH you.  He's able!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You will never be able to find in others what you're meant to find only in Jesus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stop looking for a cost free way to live a significant life. It doesn’t exist!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So inspired by what God is doing through my friends at New Hope Initiative. Watch this! https://t.co/o68NksIdNH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only thing that tests our faith more than suffering. Success.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Following God’s plan is the greatest way to unleash God’s power!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to speaking at Spotswood Baptist tonight in Fredericksburg, VA.  If you're in the area, I would love to see you!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Churches don’t need to trade uniqueness for unity! [new blog] https://t.co/eQcjJiMIIA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We stretch, then God supplies.  If He supplied first, we would never learn to trust.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Simultaneously missing #Passion2016 &amp; celebrating all that will now happen as a result.  #Passion2016BlueCG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The height of your leadership will be determined by the depth of your sacrifice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So grateful for @louiegiglio and @shelleygiglio! Amazing vision, faith, love and life. Thank you for leading us all. #Passion2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love that the same God who fills massive arenas meets us in quiet moments! #passion2016bluecg… https://t.co/qqe3R0Qnk6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How we respond when others mess up is a clear indicator of how well we understand the gospel. [new blog] https://t.co/WR69B7OkZ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really believe what God did at #Passion2016 today is going to bear exponential fruit in the weeks and months ahead. Wow!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huge expectation for tonight! #passion2016bluecg #Passion2016 https://t.co/7qtyhYJ9Tg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you're missing the #Passion2016 livestream, you're making a big mistake! Join us 7.30PM Eastern:  https://t.co/oewDQoSrT3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love starting my morning in Romans 11 with the incredible students of #passion2016bluecg @… https://t.co/Cew2tlUzmp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Praying for @dan_iten as he preaches this morning @RCChurchDC.  Love and miss you all!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can't wait for this morning with my new friends in the #Passion2016BlueCG! Come ready for Romans 11.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The stone wasn’t rolled away to let Jesus out. It was rolled away to let us in. -@louiegiglio #Passion2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't miss this! https://t.co/EgbetYf4kr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beyond excited for all God is going to do through #Passion2016. Amazing days ahead!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The world is filled with ordinary reminders of God's glory. We just need to notice. https://t.co/bh8jhDnzNB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Praying the God of all grace will fill you with power, joy and faith for the year ahead.  Happy New Year!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus. He's why we don't need to carry the guilt, fear and regrets of 2015 into 2016. Happy New Year!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy New Year!  What do your resolutions say about you? [new blog] https://t.co/dNA7pfbt4w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, follow a Bible reading plan.  But make sure you avoid these traps. [new blog] https://t.co/HShy6ytMMW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really good!  Thanks @AndyStanley. https://t.co/ymPFUWR5jc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To Do Before Friday: Select 2016 Bible Reading Plan. [new blog]: https://t.co/h090D7bwhY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If we could only see God as He really is, we would never be bored with prayer again. https://t.co/qvewn01DNa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You'll know you're being authentic when it feels a little scary.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huge honor to celebrate the new Mr. &amp; Mrs. Joey Schwartz today. Amazing hearts for Jesus! @ The… https://t.co/tWJPpdQTfM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No Restoration City gathering this morning.  Time to rest &amp; reflect!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our belonging to Christ is confirmed by our bearing of fruit for God. Bearing confirms belonging.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[College students!  We want you to come spend a summer with us in DC: https://t.co/eyo7qBPlvt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Three years ago, this massive gift came into our lives. Jack, you opened the door to parts of my… https://t.co/JzGeCch4RX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don’t avoid the difficult conversations that will ultimately make the relationship stronger!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it doesn't lead you to sacrifice, it isn't the gospel.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God has you at your job for reasons that go well beyond a paycheck.  Be salt &amp; light!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Passion finds a way to become action.  If it doesn't, it's just empty emotion.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Restoration City!  I hope you read this and celebrate with me today! [Today's Blog: https://t.co/nVkmxV9o2h]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunday is the best - loved everything about today at Restoration City!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not a hint of snow!  Can't wait to be back together with Restoration City tomorrow at 10am!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Restoration City, we want you to go from connected to committed.  Join us for our membership class this Sunday: https://t.co/ELYlij3BVE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@jdgreear you're spoiled...RDU is literally the best airport in the country!  It's like a travel spa!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Missed Community Group? Here's the video we showed to catch us up on Mark 13. [Today's Blog: https://t.co/IeScb6LhAN]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Would you be satisfied with God's blessing if it wasn't accompanied by God's presence?" - Chris Gaynor #SummitNetwork]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Is there more longing in you for the promised land or the Promised One?" - Chris Gaynor #SummitNetwork]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So grateful for two days with the pastors of The Summit Network. Amazed by all God is doing! https://t.co/bipWUi6lHk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't need to fly somewhere for a mission trip. Just open your front door! [Today's Blog: https://t.co/dnAyO9K3hj]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know you've been snowed in for awhile when a 4 person trip to the store sounds like fun! https://t.co/9ai9q3PPe7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How's DC doing? This road sign in our neighborhood's the answer!  We've got a long way to go -… https://t.co/CdCM23ayvf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn to be faithful with whatever God has entrusted to you today before asking Him for more tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greatness isn't determined by how much God entrusts to us.  It's determined by what we do with whatever is entrusted.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey, Restoration City!  We've got something special planned for your Community Group this week. [Today's Blog: https://t.co/KLAdvxaSz5]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Headed out in the snow. 30 minutes of prep for 20 minutes of fun! https://t.co/cGrdscOUS9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful morning to dig out! https://t.co/mRgVWVxBjP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We’re not gathering as a church today. But I’m praying we’ll be the church to our neighbors!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blizzard has created a massive opportunity to meet and serve your neighbors. Take advantage of it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RCChurchDC: Restoration City will NOT be gathering tomorrow morning due to the weather. Stay safe and we'll see you next week! https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LIVE on #Periscope: Take it from a guy from Syracuse, there's a lot of snow in DC! https://t.co/nQiq6cgsXI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want to serve and love your neighbors during the blizzard? Here's an awesome tool: https://t.co/4uT8VZQLUX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's going to snow.  Are you going to waste or enjoy the weekend?  Today's Blog: https://t.co/JGPixrywUe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Faith devours fear.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Birthday, Aidan! You've made this past year brighter, more joyful and more chaotic than it… https://t.co/ax780ghzdI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most shocking and transformative thing we can offer the world is grace.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deep irony in Christian leaders bashing the church for ineffectively bashing culture. Both the church &amp; the world need grace!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>