<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[True friends are like diamonds - bright, beautiful, valuable, and always in style. --&gt; Nicole Richie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two things are infinite: the universe and human stupidity; and I'm not sure about the the universe. - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow these Steps to Clean Your Credit  http://t.co/44yYdC09tW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was never interested in being a rock star. I always wanted to be Boris Karloff. - Gene Simmons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beauty, to me, is about being comfortable in your own skin. That, or a kick-ass red lipstick. - Gwyneth Paltrow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Jefferson Airplane  http://t.co/3CbZkm5c5l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can say any foolish thing to a dog, &amp; the dog will give a look that says, My God youre right I never wouldve thought of that! Dave Barry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes are just made from leather, rubber and cloth - read about exotic shoes... http://t.co/e94HVcxIfM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Willie Mays' glove is where triples go to die. - Jim Murray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I consider exercise vulgar. It makes people smell. - Alec Yuill Thornton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Learning Tool for Kids - Snap Circuits Jr - Hands On Learning All About Circuits http://t.co/fH08IVU7XS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is better than poverty, if only for financial reasons. - Woody Allen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Smoking kills. If you killed, you've lost a very important part of your life. Brooke Shields]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read Great Outdoor Camping Equipment Tips  http://t.co/K1L4QrfFmE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reputation is the other fellow's idea of your character]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome kayaking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the paddling lovers in your life!  http://t.co/IMo3bJhp6y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not whether you get knocked down; it's whether you get up. - Vince Lombardi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Personally, I'm always ready to learn, although I do not always like being taught. - Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supporting Adopted Students: Parents and Teachers Working Together  http://t.co/flHGXrxWaa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Chilled Stones to Keep Your Drink Cool - Milled in Vermont http://t.co/NgbnTLWD44]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Using Tumblr for Business  http://t.co/Tc3s9Mj3Wt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One is never over - or underdressed with a little black dress. - Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bring the best of your authentic self to every opportunity.  John Jantsch - Author of Duct Tape Marketing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's so nervous he keeps coffee awake]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of Stargate Universe  http://t.co/xNm2l6HLoJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of State Farm Insurance  http://t.co/t0Tv09aeJJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Bangles  http://t.co/xIrHWPknhp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The law gives a man the right to open his wife's mail, but not the nerve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overheard when the boss returned from his safari in Africa: "He's the first man the head shrinkers ever failed with."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Benefits of Going Green As A Business – Get Certified!  http://t.co/RYHVpmZsqU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How Small Business Can Grow with Social Media Sites  http://t.co/BmWLYrs1qh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to win at golf:  cheat!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just as soon as some people get up in the world they immediately start looking down on others. . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahh nothing like beautiful nerd girls and fun nerd stuff!  Check out Nerd Zing!  http://t.co/phbAvxxmfy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's one small step for [a] man; one giant leap for mankind. - Neil A. Armstrong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of Stargate Universe  http://t.co/xNm2l6HLoJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone has a right to a university degree in America, even if it's in Hamburger Technology. - Clive James]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nolan Ryan is pitching much better now that he has his curve ball straightened out. - Joe Garagiola]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is A Hedge Fund?  http://t.co/gGogSEMQdF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Popcorn Ceiling Removal - A Complex Job  http://t.co/gI8uGYlSX3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rock is so much fun. That's what it's all about - filling up the chest cavities and empty kneecaps and elbows.  - Jimi Hendrix]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't sweep if you don't win the first game, and it's tougher to win two out of three if you lose the first one. - Todd Helton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mama always said you could tell an awful lot about a person by the kind of shoes they wear. - Forrest Gump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome camping t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the camping lovers in your life!   http://t.co/Uf09QEMMyt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL - Cool - A Computer Mouse with a Spider in it!   http://t.co/YBpxhCqIZR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Goonies never say die. - Mike, The Goonies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Design is a constant challenge to balance comfort with luxe, the practical with the desirable. - Donna Karan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about the Bay Area city of Fremont, California  http://t.co/k1LeqAav64]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd just as soon kiss a wookiee! - Princess Leia, The Empire Strikes Back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reputation is the other fellow's idea of your character]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Great Music of Bill Justis  http://t.co/ebYkuVzChg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trust people and they will be true to you; Treat them greatly, and they will show themselves great. - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do something for somebody every day for which you do not get paid. - Albert Schweitzer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Frustrations of Youth Pitching  http://t.co/ksN986mwW5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A classic TV sit-com - the fascinating history of Andy Griffith - they didn’t get along with sweet Aunt Bee?  http://t.co/tWXKIMknUM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Deep Purple  http://t.co/iN1CMwZX0j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read The Story of Traffic the Classic Rock Group http://t.co/p9UV34jbGp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool man a Switch Blade Pocket Comb - look tough!  http://t.co/ludD5kAEWJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Fitness Alternative Energy Devices  http://t.co/9kX8o3A7pL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this gallery of the top 10 Asian beers!  http://t.co/o9MBuvVm58]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome running t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the Running lovers in your life!  http://t.co/hG4lO21GsF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fashion is what you adopt when you don't know who you are. --&gt; Quentin Crisp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is the only major sport that appears backward in a mirror. - George Carlin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Evolution of the Wooden Clog  http://t.co/cem8v8DDb8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So my degree was in political science, which I think was - the closest I could come to marketing is politics. - Steve Case]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blogging Lost – Season 1  http://t.co/gRNGlg7vVB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Mod Showcase: Secret Rooms Mod  http://t.co/MQl4qFKGNF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Some Young People Need Mentoring  http://t.co/2iqV7fg9JC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All of the animals except for man know that the principle business of life is to enjoy it. - Samuel Butler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The kindness planned for tomorrow doesn't count for today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just in time for winter - Touch Screen Texting Gloves  - http://t.co/lgmlBAcwWu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I started racing my father told me, "˜Cristiano, nobody has three balls but some people have two very good ones. - Cristiano Da Matta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 15 - The Cowden Protocol  http://t.co/IDSA1yf7gK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome climbing t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the climbing lovers in your life!  http://t.co/mECUBqw7SA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I live by a simple philosophy: Wear fine shoes and enjoy the best luck. - Qiana Markham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The average dog is a nicer person than the average person. - Andrew A. Rooney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Schools to NOT Get Your Creative Writing Degree At  http://t.co/hJ49fgbz4L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge a man by how much he does when he doesn't need to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where everything is possible miracles become common place, but the familiar ceases to be self-evident. - Eric Hoffer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Assisted Living in Your Own Home  http://t.co/pxdqqI24lA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sign on a barber shop window --  Home haircuts repaired  $20.00]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get A Life? Cool! Where can I download one of those?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Are the Different Types of Web Hosting?  http://t.co/RXNyAgbY5z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mama always said you could tell an awful lot about a person by the kind of shoes they wear. - Forrest Gump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to Douglas Adams  http://t.co/eRcGlhLsTF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The thing about science fiction is that it's totally wide open. But it's wide open in a conditional way. - Octavia Butler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't do any vulgar movements.  -  Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Simplicity is the ultimate sophistication. - Leonardo da Vinci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Joe Simon  http://t.co/ZahyDfsdXt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tennis is a pass time where love means nothing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business has only two functions - marketing and innovation. - Milan Kundera]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to David Bowie  http://t.co/6pVxzKpCNB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips for Using Facebook Pages for Your Business  http://t.co/9mmasNdMa7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We live in a dark and romantic and quite tragic world. --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like to literally put women on a pedestal. - Vivienne Westwood]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Domestic Adoption And Government’s Rules  http://t.co/2tzAOAo9FQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Peter Frampton  http://t.co/tpiuEKD1VS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool Amazing and Mesmerizing SciFi &amp; Space Artwork  http://t.co/zwVoFiZdE7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it's too close to bother to buckle your seat belt it's close enough to walk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Brief History and Introduction to Bitcoin  http://t.co/Ae3PmQTTmE]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>