<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RLadiesGlobal: WOW 1in4 people at the #runconf17 is an #RLady💜! Follow #runconf17 to keep updated on the 2 day #rstats project work htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For those currently on the plan, worried about Public Service Loan Forgiveness. Rest easy: https://t.co/pG5LYjAzDR https://t.co/bYkTpDxvkS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Bencjacobs: Listen to me get body slammed in Montana https://t.co/I8hAUsmuWw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jschwabish: Still a few slots left for my 6/8 workshop on #dataviz in DC. Register and get a free copy of my book! | https://t.co/69f1M…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @zubakskees: Congrats to @not_young, @18F and @FEC https://t.co/AHAUxTX7go]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McCourtSchool @FurongChen ...and natural gas consumption, which is notably higher in western China.  #dataviz https://t.co/QgWiHFXb5F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McCourtSchool @FurongChen ...and petroleum consumption, this is by province, by the way... #dataviz https://t.co/agicGOKDxv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McCourtSchool Starting off with @FurongChen's series of equal area cartograms on fossil fuel consumption in China. Here's coal: https://t.co/xMikg4rmc7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm going to be sharing the wonderful #dataviz work of my @McCourtSchool students over the next week or so.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jbouie: This may rank with LBJ's Howard commencement as 1 of the most honest speeches on race given by a white Southern pol. https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @tpoi: This is false. I hated maths as a teenager. And was awful at it. You can start whenever you want. https://t.co/apqqB7jmLI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @grssnbchr: I made a new map in #rstats: animated commuter flows (here from/to Zurich, CH). #ggplot2 only. Tutorial will follow soon. #m…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interested to learn just now that @USGAO has a new-ish Center for Enhanced Analytics: https://t.co/iQnA3JIMuS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God damnit German. Seriously? 

This is too many pronouns. https://t.co/ViGeRcLlAh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Drawitall: Day506 5/20/17FirstRadioHeadlineS Heard of theDayDrawingProject #HassanRouhani #IranElection2017 #Comey #NewOrleans #confede…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @caragerber: Looking for Stata or R code to conduct analysis on students' educational attainment? Check out #OpenSDP https://t.co/SgYd69…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lotta wonderful @urbaninstitute humans stopped by to wish me well today, and it was very cool of them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Emil_Hvitfeldt: tilemapr, a R📦 for easy tile grid maps (just US now) with ggplot2. Feedback is highly appreciated! #rstats #ggplot2 htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thready threading threadful mc threadster.

Thread. https://t.co/npUVL9QrJu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Saving today's XKCD for the "what not to do" slides in future #machinelearning/#datascience courses... https://t.co/kYesCoN4xw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huh. This combines a lot of interesting aspects. Highly effective #machinelearning algorithm that is scalable and accounts for uncertainty. https://t.co/JctlQlOgoD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @drob: Check out my #rstatsnyc talk:"We R What We Ask: The Landscape of R Users on Stack Overflow" https://t.co/veros57gaC #rstats]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drob 99% of things that look like this in #datascience are terrible and useless. This is the other 1%: Fantastic clustering of #rstats packages. https://t.co/8CNTLOYsj4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lot can go wrong when applying a model built on one dataset (and its data collection process) to an entirely different dataset (&amp; process) https://t.co/dehxvfywfX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great primer on / intro to statistical matching in the first chapter of this book: https://t.co/dhRnRqHlLA https://t.co/sqsCGg7Chg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @alignedleft: Great news: The initial manuscript for the 2nd ed. of the D3 book is complete! Preorder here: https://t.co/iHSDlKQeDO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DataLensDC: Sears, in a drastic move to reverse the decline of department stores and appeal to millennials, expands its payment options…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @hannah_recht: What happens if major insurance companies exit? Story and data via @BBGVisualData https://t.co/hrm2AEESvJ https://t.co/95…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @igorvolsky: Right now at Trump's DC hotel! https://t.co/95cwrUmbmF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@existentialyssa This is more or less my plan. Interactive graphs on GitHub Pages, too. Feedback from me (and classmates) through GitHub Issues.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AlexCEngler: But the latter not so much. Jeff Wu called for use of term #DataScience &amp; Data Scientists in 1997: https://t.co/egX3nEriLZ…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dancy_kim: Students are often ok with using their data as long as it serves to help them succeed not just to write reports - @markmilli…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @vorpalsmith: Do you know anyone who'd be interested in a full-time position at UC Berkeley working on NumPy? https://t.co/zVj0HSKj1N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PostBaron: "Cloak of invisibility": Some federal data gets harder to find. Other data has vanished entirely. https://t.co/TynBWhwOp4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @councilofdc: Every American is represented in Congress by one Representative and two Senators #withfewexceptions https://t.co/5qELDFgXr8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @robinson_es: You don't have to have wanted to be in STEM since you were 5 to enjoy it and succeed. You don't have to look like ppl on S…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NickVeronica: @TreyYingst weird to think that both of these maps represent the same thing https://t.co/c23d95PKVR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@SpiritAirlines I was, in fairness, given the ticket I asked for to another destination after scrapping my original plans. So mixed bag of an experience.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@SpiritAirlines Sent to a hotel without the right voucher. Also was given 'meal vouchers' for $7 that only work in the airport. This slogan feels apt. https://t.co/8GYseALcJN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@SpiritAirlines Ah well this explains some of that: https://t.co/74iiUzSE63]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flight cancelled while I'm sitting on it. @SpiritAirlines]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Phone and computer battery too low to depend on for this flight. Had to buy plastic words for once, tho at the least the topic is the same. https://t.co/zLH4Ks41h3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EricHolder: To the career men and women at DOJ/FBI: you know what the job entails and how to do it. Be strong and unafraid. Duty. Honor…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Nate_Cohn: If there was one thing people would have assumed about Trump, it was probably that he would be good at firing people]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GeraldineAmiel: Bloomberg recalled reporter from Le Pen event. We don't attend events where other credible media are excluded. We belie…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@aedwardslevy Ahem. @t_s_institute]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BecomingDataSci I agree with 1&amp;5 and know this story. Deeply unsettling. For entirely different reasons, would strongly caution away from #3. For everyone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jeffrey_heer: Deeply honored to have ~15 years of visualization tools research recognized by ACM! https://t.co/emwxjQVARl Many people t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GrahamIMac: Like to program in #rstats or #python and care about bringing evidence to policy issues? Come join our team! https://t.co/x…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@McCourtSchool Even better, my @McCourtSchool students got me @xkcd's 'What If?' (spot on gift, srsly) &amp; I am SO full of feels.

Thanks everyone. Hoya Saxa https://t.co/omhTDtu82L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MaxCRoser: Share of the population living in extreme poverty in Indonesia (258 million people)
1984  –  70%
2014  –  8%
https://t.co/UF…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Last class @McCourtSchool after 2.5 years. Definitely won't ever forget the feeling of walking into Healy hall to teach for the first time. https://t.co/gTXRlhBJUD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join @urbaninstitute's excellent webdev team! Contribute to the public dissemination of rigorous policy knowledge! https://t.co/i3Wcnqe8pc https://t.co/rIekOQFHuD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PiotrLe @wb_research @alevergara78 @WorldBank Reminds me of this graph for some reason. Hit play on the treemap: https://t.co/Q44FalYVUN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nytimes: "When he came after me, he’d say that I would get sent back to Mexico and never see my kids again." https://t.co/ftUj8nDuV1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @borjasotomayor: @AlexCEngler @StatStas @UChicagoMPCS @cmgiven Yup, we've used chisubmit in a class with 200+ students and a staff of 10…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@borjasotomayor @StatStas @UChicagoMPCS @cmgiven So I imagine this is particularly helpful for the larger courses with distributed grading w/ TA's - makes a lot of sense.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@borjasotomayor @StatStas @UChicagoMPCS @cmgiven Until someone trains neural networks to identify the misuse of visual encodings... Someone wanna get on that? #deeplearning #dataviz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@borjasotomayor @StatStas @UChicagoMPCS @cmgiven For dataviz all the assignments are totally open ended (students choose data and graph types) so automatic grading seems off the table, hah.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StatStas @UChicagoMPCS @borjasotomayor @cmgiven The automatic grading code sounds interesting, hah. I'm assuming these were not open ended assignments =p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StatStas @UChicagoMPCS @borjasotomayor Understandable. That's what @cmgiven and I did last year, too. We did Git for workflow and submission but then BlackBoard/Email for grading.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PiotrLe @UChicagoMPCS @McCourtSchool Yep. Sadly the GUI won't let you do everything you'll want to with Git over the long term. Others may disagree but it's worth using the CLI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PiotrLe @UChicagoMPCS @McCourtSchool Just try to get used to the add/commit/push cycle. At least then you have an extra copy of your code on GitHub. Then maybe try a branch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PiotrLe @UChicagoMPCS @McCourtSchool Lots of people use git without 'getting' the whole thing. The reality is that if you self teach it might take a while for it to sink in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PiotrLe @UChicagoMPCS @McCourtSchool So fair warning, Git is conceptually trick if you're new to version control. That said, I like this tutorial: https://t.co/GwGZLsoYPb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StatStas @UChicagoMPCS @borjasotomayor I've been strongly encouraging people to put them on their resume - prominently. Turns out it's really easy to say you know R/Python/D3/Spa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@UChicagoMPCS @cmgiven For real though, how much time would this have saved us? My estimate: Oodles.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@UChicagoMPCS @borjasotomayor ...any serious employer in this field will ask for a GitHub account. We need to encourage students to get their work on GitHub early &amp; often]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@UChicagoMPCS Serious H/T to @borjasotomayor. Institutionalizing Git in student workflow is good for the obvious reason, Git. But also]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@UChicagoMPCS Paging #dataviz &amp; #datascience profs - this seems like it solves the dual system problem of feedback on Git and grading in Blackboard/Canvas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[COOL. @UChicagoMPCS has a system for assignment submission &amp; grading entirely through git: https://t.co/leRIyw1YHk https://t.co/MePUYoeAfZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JoshdelaRosa1 @UChicago @qcbigdata Definitely! Would love to come by next time I'm in NYC. Will absolutely keep this in mind.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mbostock: I buried the lede. It’s an in-browser reactive JavaScript notebook for exploratory analysis, visualization, and explanation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mbostock: Introducing d3.​express: the integrated discovery environment. https://t.co/WfwCA9DDoD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ar0r @chihacknight Oh right of course! Added to my calendar. @ChicagoPython and @CruGChicago look pretty active too. Def going to the next Python Project Night]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone know what the most active #data groups in Chicago are? I see @chicagodata and the DataViz Group but feel like there should be more...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dpatil: If you're a Data Scientist &amp; working or being asked to work on this data set, I hope you'll ask look deep in your soul to ask w…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DataLensDC: The Lab @ DC, part of DC gov't, currently has 15 ongoing studies &amp; there's no public info besides what they share in one-of…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@apodkul @GUGovt Did not even notice you taking the photo, but much appreciated!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SloanFoundation @ApacheSpark @GUGovt Regression methods are also much, much better off, but then you have to talk through the calculus, which seems like a questionable choice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SloanFoundation @ApacheSpark @GUGovt Best explanatory example of the power of #Spark over #MapReduce that I can think of is K-means clustering. Much faster, fairly easy to show.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excited to give the first @SloanFoundation-funded @ApacheSpark for Social Science training today - see you soon @gugovt quants. https://t.co/hFRCmQPusm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kwbroman: @timelyportfolio I use table a lot. Also table(table( ))]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SloanFoundation @Wharton WRDS is a subscription repository for business data. Interesting model for policy research. SAS #rstats MATLAB #python #stata all supported.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a @SloanFoundation conference of administrative data for science &amp; research. Bob Zarazowski talking about @Wharton Research Data Service. https://t.co/3PCz985WBj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok this is pretty funny but if you're gonna make fun of R you gotta do it to #rstats https://t.co/522JVrrHoB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dataandme: ICYMI, how-to w/ screenshots abound 🙌: "How to make an RMarkdown Website" by @NicholasStrayer &amp; @LucyStats https://t.co/oNQf…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kenneygm: Here is why @DeanHeller @BrianSandoval are worried: 45% Medicaid enrollment cut &amp; BCRA has deeper Fed Medicaid cuts than #AHC…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RonaldKlain: You know what's better than fact-checking Trump?  Embedding facts in the Trump coverage.  Kudos, @maggieNYT https://t.co/J…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NicholasStrayer: shinysense now has you-draw-it charts a-la @nytgraphics https://t.co/jeAxXyo6io A big thanks to @adamrpearce for the g…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EdwinCBPP: New @urbaninstitute study on children's big coverage gains &amp; improved access since '08. At severe risk w/ GOP bill: https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @drob: The awesome thing about public work (e.g. blog posts) is you never lose it. It's already on your phone and on every computer in t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@urbaninstitute @cmgiven And yes I know it's not working perfectly in this case but I REALLY like saying 'avocados billion'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Important research by @urbaninstitute, translated for millennials by @cmgiven's an-🥑-saved: https://t.co/sKiPQbjSrP

https://t.co/uJtXnqDIE0 https://t.co/eFYsxw07kU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dancy_kim: ICYMI: a large portion of benefits from refinancing would only serve a small number of households. (via @dancy_kim) https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McCourtSchool @FurongChen @austinkabbaz @jimwarycha @smartgunlaws From Tanging Pan - Winter is by far the worst season for air quality in China (more heating needs, I'd think). #dataviz https://t.co/BhRhaNkG48]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How my mom ends emails these days. https://t.co/glMwl4XkcS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DataLensDC: i made a bot that documents and provides remembrance for all the things millennials are killing, a terrifying and vastly un…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @drob: This is statistically illiterate &amp; irresponsible. Correlated errors happen and are essential in interpreting models https://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BenChartoff Oh duh totally read that backwards. Got it.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>