<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DiamondandSilk: Pelosi Dismisses Death of Americans Like Ronil Singh as ‘Anecdote,’ Not ‘Data’ https://t.co/gbVEF0ATAk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mitchellvii: Yep, Dems are lounging on the beach and attending a sold-out play with $1000 tickets to, you know, support hurricane victi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DonaldJTrumpJr: Maybe the Dems will look at these Facts when they get back from their lobbyist sponsored vacation in Puerto Rico. https…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Cernovich Well put.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Cernovich: I want marijuana to be legal. 

I don’t want YOU to use it unless it’s medically necessary. 

That’s why people often confus…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ucchristinme @hrkbenowen Diabetes and cancer many of times are symptoms of sugar addiction]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ThisMomHCN @POTUS @VP @FLOTUS Don't be, I accepted the will of the Lord and carry on as loving mom, my children are a treasure]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @prayingmedic: President Trump vowed to unleash economic destruction on Turkey should its military forces target Kurdish allies when U.S…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @prayingmedic: Even if the border wall problem is solved, other disagreements will likely keep the government shut down.
https://t.co/PV…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @prayingmedic: US Ambassador to Germany Richard Grenell sent a letter to several businesses reminding them that "any company operating i…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @realDonaldTrump: Wish I could share with everyone the beauty and majesty of being in the White House and looking outside at the snow fi…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @realDonaldTrump: ....Likewise, do not want the Kurds to provoke Turkey. Russia, Iran and Syria have been the biggest beneficiaries of t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @prayingmedic: 2 injured, 3 suspects at large in Utah Mall shooting that police say may be gang related.
https://t.co/STwElzaXQ2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @prayingmedic: 1 Dead, 14 Hospitalized After Apparent Mass Fentanyl Overdose in Chico, California. https://t.co/bIFDV3D7ny]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @realDonaldTrump: Starting the long overdue pullout from Syria while hitting the little remaining ISIS territorial caliphate hard, and f…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @prayingmedic: Bad news for Trump haters:
#MuellerTime is going to be let down.

(FakeNews knew that. It was their job to keep your hope…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @prayingmedic: A California judge has blocked enforcement of a Trump administration rule which would allow some employers to opt out of…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @prayingmedic: Lady Rothschild (wife of investment banker Jacob Rothschild) has died. https://t.co/M7xfNNjgrp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @prayingmedic: Russia threatens to retaliate following Defense Secretary Gavin Williamson's prediction that the UK will play a more prom…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @prayingmedic: Mueller has nothing on POTUS.
As that fact sinks in, Max offers another gulp of FakeNews kool-aid to his followers. https…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @prayingmedic: A summary of Hillary and Obama's activities in Libya and Syria with a reminder that General Flynn was privy to everything…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LisaMei62: "People are going to be exposed that no one thought possible." ~ @realDonaldTrump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RepDanCrenshaw: Joined @Foxnewsnight yesterday to discuss border security. Our multifaceted approach includes a wall, but is so much mo…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Jim_Jordan: Tune in! I’ll be talking to @JudgeJeanine at 9:30 https://t.co/akrFJPRT5I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JacobAWohl: In 2008, when the entire country was suffering and unemployment was soaring through the roof, unemployment in Washington DC…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @1776Stonewall: Dukakis rode a tank because he knew how dumb his voters were. Kerry got him a "huntin license" because he knew how dumb…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dbongino: It’s now 1 year 357 days and 8 hours into the Trump presidency and there’s STILL not a scintilla of evidence of collusion. 
O…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @gatewaypundit: Democrat Menendez Spotted Partying with Bikini Girls in Puerto Rico During Government Shutdown https://t.co/WWGEDkpoqh v…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HealthRanger: Sugar is 8 times more addictive than cocaine. #sugar #health #addiction https://t.co/iSX5P1zyMM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DonaldJTrumpJr: Why is @SpeakerPelosi ignoring and refusing to meet with these heroic Angel mom’s? 

The victims of illegal immigration…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JohnFromCranber: #ProgressiveLiberals say the #AmericanFlag is offensive to #Muslims. I could care less.

If the American Flag is offen…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RealKyleMorris: Bernie, in 2017 you made $858,750 in royalties for your book, “Our Revolution.” Combined with your Senate salary, that’…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mitchellvii: I'm embarrassed that roughly half of Americans vote for these lying anarchist America-hating Democrats. Retweet if you agr…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WhiteHouse: “We know what the cost is to families . . . to our families, to our communities, to the country. We are here to serve. And…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @seanhannity: https://t.co/MvmhzLnACb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Barnes_Law: If walls don't work, why does every maximum security prison rely on them?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @hrkbenowen: Which agency or person do you trust the most?

Please retweet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BrianKolfage: I'm a man of my word! I promised to let people back out,  they have 90 days to get a refund. So far we have a 91% convers…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Lrihendry: @realDonaldTrump Former President Ronald Reagan said, “A nation that cannot control its borders is not a nation.“ so true! Y…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JacobAWohl: Where were the MSM tears and sob stories for the millions of people who lost their jobs during Obama’s sad excuse for a pre…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PrisonPlanet: Yellow vests in France trample on EU flag. https://t.co/8X08tfgtpS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DFBHarvard: I have 3 questions tonight.

1. Where the Hell are all the Spineless Republican Senators?

2. Why aren't they speaking out…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DineshDSouza: Should the US intervene to save Venezuela? Here’s how to do it without boots on the ground https://t.co/ppCmqvQcgx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RealMattCouch: Hey Adam, 

Will your team be talking to my team about our Seth Rich Investigation? We'd love to share evidence with you…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JudicialWatch: JW President @TomFitton: Now that President @realDonaldTrump has removed AG Sessions &amp; that Matthew Whitaker is Acting A…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @gatewaypundit: MORE DEEP STATE CRIMES: Rod Rosenstein and FBI Director Wray LIED TO TRUMP and Congress-- Said He Was Not Under Investig…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RealJamesWoods: So would the @FBI consider this child pornography? I’m asking this seriously. If it were a ten year old female child ph…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @johncardillo: 10-Year-Old Boy 'Drag Kid' Photographed With Naked Adult Drag Queen 

I worked on child-protection legislation in 15 stat…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RealSaavedra: Democrat Sheriff refuses to take responsibility for his actions https://t.co/gGtseqZrVF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NevadaJack2: Harry Reid endorsed Mitt Romney as the next Republican presidential nominee in 2020.

Anything Dirty Harry likes ... I HAT…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MarkSimoneNY: Lengthy NY Times article "Why Trump’s Unusual Leadership Style Isn’t Working." Of course, the job of a President is peace…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BrianKolfage: Big names, solid backing to BUILD the Wall! Look who is on our advisory board...a dream team to finally make this happen!…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MsAvaArmstrong: 0bama declared national emergency for Swine Flu.

We have 60,000 illegals a month coming through our southern border.
T…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HealthRanger: What if carbon dioxide isn't the enemy? https://t.co/Um44xoFCkp #CO2 #climatechange]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RudyGiuliani: This is a perfect example of how CNN has become a #FAKENEWS network. They block the truth and substitute anti-Trump venom…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @gatewaypundit: BOOM! President Trump Issues Warning to Deep State: "You'll Be Surprised at the Names of People Involved in the Corrupti…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @marklevinshow: Uh, it’s Sunday &amp; snowing in Washington.The partial government shutdown is a mostly full government shutdown today,  hav…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HealthRanger: Will the vaccine industry stage a false flag outbreak for nationwide vaccine mandates? https://t.co/s2RwnBlULQ #antivax #…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @prayingmedic: Supernatural Saturday - Receiving Your Healing https://t.co/zACirLTLaG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @prayingmedic: Supernatural Saturday Jan 11 – How to Receive Your Healing https://t.co/bPoI9odCHE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KTHopkins: Multiple alternative outlets reporting #ActeIX as the largest #GiletsJaunes protest yet

Brexit Brits could learn a thing or…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @prayingmedic: The world is changing https://t.co/WkY6jURsSE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @prayingmedic: I just uploaded “Qanon January 7 2019 - Follow the Watch” to #Vimeo: https://t.co/EShyat8mYK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @prayingmedic: My Interview With 412Anon https://t.co/d7F8smXQdS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MarkDice: It should be illegal to announce you’re running for president until at least the year of that actual election.  These two yea…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @gatewaypundit: Flashback: Maxine Waters: “Obama Has Put In Place” Secret Database With “Everything On Everyone” (Video) https://t.co/mf…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RepDanCrenshaw: Last night @ShannonBream asked me about reports indicating the Administration is considering using disaster relief fund…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dbongino: Only imbeciles believe in the Russian collusion fairytale. Please, don’t be an imbecile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @camelnubbz: @jerome_corsi I love you Dr. Corsi! You are a good man. I remember talking with you (cbts/dscrd) and you always felt genuin…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @realDonaldTrump: The damage done to our Country from a badly broken Border - Drugs, Crime and so much that is bad - is far greater than…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PressSec: Democrats in Congress are so alarmed about federal workers not getting paid they’re partying on the beach instead of negotiat…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JudgeJeanine: During my exclusive interview with Pres Trump I said Speaker Pelosi was in Puerto Rico with a bunch of her Democrat colle…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @marklevinshow: The border is open, there’s a partial government shutdown &amp; the Democrats take a junket to Puerto Rico. Here’s Menendez…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mitchellvii: Republicans had 2 years in the majority to fund the wall and Ryan/McConnell did NOTHING.  McConnell had a chance to go nuc…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ColumbiaBugle: Senator @tedcruz unveiling the El Chapo Act.

"It says we should take all of the money criminally forfeited from El Chap…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HealthRanger: #WholeFoods pulls off elaborate five-year #GMO labeling hoax; lies to customers and hopes nobody remembers. https://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FiveRights: CNN, MSNBC, ABC, CBS, NBC,
You could help stop horrific beatings like this by exposing non-white bullies the same as if the…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SteveScalise: Democrats are still refusing to come to the table with a serious counteroffer that properly secures America’s border. I’m…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JudicialWatch: JW President @TomFitton: Now that President @realDonaldTrump has removed AG Sessions &amp; that Matthew Whitaker is Acting A…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RealMattCouch: Where are the people that like to scream about racism here? https://t.co/B3zAT4IPVZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SecPompeo: Great to meet with students at NYU Abu Dhabi, who’ve all come here for a first-class American education — one of our most im…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @prayingmedic: Think nothing is happening?

"People are going to be exposed  that nobody ever thought possible."
~ POTUS https://t.co/4e…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mitchellvii: President Trump even offered to take half as much for the wall and the same Democrats who voted $42 billion for the wall i…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @marklevinshow: Does it get any more insane than this stupid post on Mediaite? https://t.co/SEnYrmxLF8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DonaldJTrumpJr: Trump Says Dem Obstruction on Border Wall 'Only Politics' -- 'I Actually Think It's Bad Politics for Them' | Breitbart…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @prayingmedic: 12) Lights on.
Q https://t.co/bbLUjU1yvB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Lrihendry: @realDonaldTrump This is the REAL immorality!  While you work and gov employees work with no pay checks, they vacation in Pu…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @realDonaldTrump: I’m in the White House, waiting. The Democrats are everywhere but Washington as people await their pay. They are havin…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dbongino: Ask this complete zero and failed excuse for a human being to explain Akmetshin &amp; Veselnitskaya’s deep connections to both th…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jerome_corsi: Thank you. In the end, God always wins. https://t.co/jDoLLnn72C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @thecjpearson: People are mad our President cares more about American citizens than illegal immigrants. 

Almost unbelievable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RyanAFournier: The Pentagon recently had to relinquish $27 billion for the simple reason that they were unable to spend it fast enough.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JacobAWohl: Planned Parenthood spent $30 Million to support Democrats in the 2018 midterms 

Who gave them that $30 Million? 

American…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SecPompeo: We denounce the arbitrary detention of #NationalAssembly President @jguaido by Venezuelan Intelligence Chief Manuel Cristoph…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @charliekirk11: Sick:

A statue honoring Saudi Arabia has been placed on the ground zero World Trade Center site

The country that funde…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Jim_Jordan: Judiciary Chairman @RepJerryNadler: “There is no reason to doubt the seriousness or professionalism of the FBI”

Really? No…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @dbongino: Make no mistake, this past week’s “bombshell” report about the FBI targeting President Trump has absolutely confirmed that th…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BrianKolfage: MEDIA IS LYING! Our GoFundme Campaign Is SMOKING HOT! it's not being "cancelled" or "all refunded"

We are BUILDING the w…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jerome_corsi: Now that Mueller &amp; his HATE TRUMP henchmen are attacking my family, my website https://t.co/g9MjyVUWd4  was attacked and…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @washingtonpost: William Barr’s confirmation hearing expected to be a battle over Mueller’s future https://t.co/7rMGgq4HXh]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>