<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Gwyneth Paltrow reveals Brad Pitt's threat to Weinstein: The actress spoke to Howard Stern about the day Harvey Weinstein allegedly sexually harassed her when she was 22. https://t.co/8XIGZhjxk1 https://t.co/Sfu1HH8rsv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Working JavaScript Development Lead: Job Category: Information Technology JavaScript Security Clearance: Secret (or willing to obtain) Clearance Status: Must Be Current Citizenship: Must be a US Citizen IT Partners is seeking a working JavaScript… https://t.co/HzQlqfLbFT https://t.co/jmlyCmsCLn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer with JAVA and PHP: Our Team Informatica Core Metadata Group delivers authoritative and trustworthy data quality to all stakeholders, all projects, and all data domains for all projects and all business applicationson premise or… https://t.co/P1gZdLZpoE https://t.co/Y33hEJDLID]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[15 of the world's best nude beaches https://t.co/XCftfYWBSb https://t.co/lUgCp9UrYE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Java Developer Job in Florham Park, NJ | CVS HEALTH ************* Main menu – About – About – Our Services – Retail Pharmacy – Pharmacy Benefits Management – Clinical Services – Specialty Pharmacy – Digital Services – Leadership –… https://t.co/n9vnKUHuws https://t.co/HAhRj5gvkw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java-JEE-Developer–Journeyman-: We are seeking motivated, career and customer orientedJava/JEE Developer, interested in joining our team in Kingstowne, VA,and exploring an exciting and challenging career with Unisys Federal Systems. Duties and… https://t.co/o1LTav9wwH https://t.co/IekkT04TW6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jr.-Mid Level Java Developer: Seeking a talented Jr. to Mid Level Java Software Developer with Backend skills with Spring Boot, Micro services and Elastic Search. This is a full-time opportunity with a growing group! https://t.co/BET0VjzjbL https://t.co/cge6N3Nchk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nigerian troops accused of raping women rescued from Boko Haram: Women and girls who have fled terrorist group Boko Haram are being raped by Nigerian soldiers, starved and forced to exchange food for sex, according to claims in a new report by human… https://t.co/g4w8y58NEs https://t.co/QvIVvRYVnc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Engineer: Full stack + Angular or React + AWS + NoSQL; CS Degree strongly preferred: Kore 1 Jobs Page ************|************** – Services – Workforce Planning – Software Development – IT Strategy – Staffing Solutions – Technology Staffing –… https://t.co/ZuIKp0VdLj https://t.co/j5eNYwo53B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meghan laughs off Harry's bee encounter: Prince Harry and Meghan Markle's first public appearance since their wedding was interrupted by a pesky bee. https://t.co/P7FkXCyZsJ https://t.co/U0TfVzXgbP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Specialist Developer – Java/JavaScript – APS: For BNY Mellon Sr. Specialist Developer – Java/JavaScript – APS job – Information Technology – Multiple Skip to Main Content – – – – Toggle navigation – Who We Are – What We Do – Who We Serve – Our… https://t.co/UKco3xmvaz https://t.co/zRq61g2j0r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer – Market Risk IT – Market Data: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we want to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them succeed financially. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the center of… https://t.co/hWYGj0Sirm https://t.co/PGiECbrb7N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jr Software Engineer – Java: At Ping Identity, we’re changing the way people think about enterprise security technology. With our innovative Identity Defined Security platform, we’re helping to build a borderless world where people have total freedom to… https://t.co/2EN4krb8QA https://t.co/2Au61iw5rL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: The NFL has never looked more stupid https://t.co/eLD1eoc5Ew https://t.co/JyAvGwGqHf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[# ColdFusion developer w Java Cherry Hill, NJ: TITILE: Senior ColdFusion Developer Type: Contract Duration: 6+ Months Location: Cherry Hill, NJ Key Skills: ColdFusion with Java backend Requirements * BS in Computer Science or related field of study. * 6… https://t.co/j8uBL2mb9q https://t.co/1bLt5xxsqb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: Job Description What you’ll be doing… We are looking for Senior Java Developer to join the Digital Transformation Group. This position represents an opportunity to become an integral part of a talented team helping our clients’… https://t.co/7Li19DDyeQ https://t.co/zmEfMmx41E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Progressive women score big wins in Southern primaries: Democrats will take a step toward settling several intra-party fights with Tuesday's primaries in Georgia, Kentucky, Texas and Arkansas. https://t.co/IeSNC7gfmf https://t.co/2kT46saH8x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer Mid Career C#, C++, or Java TS/SCI in Herndon, VA: Req ID : 423810BR Job Code/Title : E1073:Software Engineer Sr Job Description : Looking for a career with purpose? One that challenges your mind, grows your skills and contributes to… https://t.co/F39Cvpigjg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Architect: Responsibilities: -Develop design specifications, installation instructions and other system-related information. -Verify stability, interoperability, portability, security and scalability of java system architecture. -Select appropriate… https://t.co/ZlZcuUo1Nn https://t.co/jvU1eCUP1V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[F-35 stealth fighter gets first taste of combat: After more than two decades of development and testing, Lockheed Martin's F-35 fighter jet has made its combat debut. https://t.co/BcqQvat63s https://t.co/YDHD4oYgJv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Front End Developer (HTML5, Java, and Java Script): POSITION DESCRIPTION: Front End Developer with extensive experience on enterprise solutions. The candidate must have strong solution design skills and the ability to document, communicate, and implement… https://t.co/Zu0Gddx9y1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The volcano erupted -- but they kept golfing https://t.co/XutjHZDIaC https://t.co/3i7DEmvjCe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NASA will create coldest place in the universe to study quantum physics: It's hard to study quantum behavior on Earth. You can amplify the effects of quantum mechanics by zapping groups of specific atoms (Bose-Einstein condensates) with lasers that drop… https://t.co/JQSLH3yOnH https://t.co/4Bgwrsf5c6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mayor says Trump lied about her: Libby Schaaf, the mayor of Oakland, California, is firing back at President Donald Trump over his suggestion that the Department of Justice investigate her for obstruction of justice. https://t.co/45bTKTgIJp https://t.co/KWSNyA6yor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer (JavaScript): Our development team works on the entire tech stack (from low-level database operations to front-end development) for a large cloud-based enterprise application for the construction industry. Engineers work with all… https://t.co/IsBAG3nfzv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior JavaScript Engineer: The Role:33Across is seeking an experienced software engineer to join our team in expanding our current publisher platform and building innovative products for the mobile web. Our products are already generating 1 billion… https://t.co/aFzZYiTQgy https://t.co/S4sBIAbJYT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Netflix inks multi-year production agreement with the Obamas: The 44th President and First Lady are getting into the entertainment business. According to an announcement by Netflix's Twitter account Monday morning, "President Barack Obama and Michelle… https://t.co/ZoPTVgKLpA https://t.co/QRY70apj0D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java/J2EE Software Engineer: About the Company: Located in downtown Chicago, our client is a digital marketing and creative agency partnering with higher institutions to expand their online enrollment programs. They deliver research, marketing, and… https://t.co/GAFmxf1mhP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[# ColdFusion developer w Java – Cherry Hill, NJ: TITILE: Senior ColdFusion Developer Type: Contract Duration: 6+ Months Location: Cherry Hill, NJ Key Skills: ColdFusion with Java backend Requirements * BS in Computer Science or related field of study. *… https://t.co/IMYidLdcD4 https://t.co/1gCgRCLEs4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior JAVA/JEE Web Developer: Req ID: 21790    At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The quality, integrity, and commitment of our employees are key factors in our company’s growth, market presence and… https://t.co/jEMBg6lzob https://t.co/YF0QsqrDQ4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reliever throws record 105-mph pitch https://t.co/7HGji4FtFm https://t.co/WDkYFLAl6s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: Will Markle become the royal family's silent feminist?: With the upcoming marriage of Meghan Markle and Prince Harry, a feminist is set to become a member of the British royal family. https://t.co/fRGP3Tz9MR https://t.co/3uZdlhQ25d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Software Developer with Full Scope Poly: Req ID: 20883    At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The quality, integrity, and commitment of our employees are key factors in our company’s growth,… https://t.co/1CCfcVyoiY https://t.co/v90POxjgpN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer-Cloud/Microservices: Key Required Skills: Experience with Cloud Deployment, Dockers/container management, node.js, micro services/spring/spring boot, Angular/React, Open shift, Agile Development POSITION DESCRIPTION: Seeking a Sr.… https://t.co/psfS0r3fhy https://t.co/gfS7qSsWGw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: Something important was different about this shooting: This newest shooting seems, sadly, familiar, but it is important that we pay attention to what is different here. https://t.co/Th6beuNKiA https://t.co/LaKjAb4sgP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Senior Developer: Req ID: 3175    At NTT DATA Services, we know that with the right people on board, anything is possible. The quality, integrity, and commitment of our employees are key factors in our company’s growth, market presence and our… https://t.co/QhaS3JLJEg https://t.co/1wYOooPkJG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Serves as a Java developer whose code is clean, efficient, and well documented. Candidate will design and develop solutions to meet the business requirements in support of the Armys mission, ensuring technical capabilities are secure,… https://t.co/AZ9f04Nbwe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['The Fifth Element' director accused of rape: A rape investigation has been launched against one of France's best-known film directors, Luc Besson, the Paris prosecutor's office told CNN on Saturday. https://t.co/xFAY0k1Ald https://t.co/n9R5mJnj2d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch surfers ride $30 million wave: Surfing legend Laird Hamilton saves dozens of people and animals from floodwaters in Hawaii. https://t.co/fTqFW5AJUi https://t.co/ZwqamX4LzP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Java: Req ID : 429706BR Job Code/Title : E1072:Software Engineer Job Description : The CSI Program is looking for world class SW engineers to build an Agile Development Team to support a system's development evolution to today's… https://t.co/x3zKTiiwa0 https://t.co/XocahOMEnE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Java Frontend Developer – Engineer Software 4:   Job Description – Sr Java Frontend Developer – Engineer Software 4 (18005019) Sr Java Frontend Developer – Engineer Software 4 Requisition ID : 18005019 Location : United States-Virginia-Lorton US… https://t.co/QlGIbiqYIG https://t.co/smCtVnDK5D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer 4 (Sr.) – TS/SCI W/Poly:   Job Description – Java Developer 4 (Sr.) – TS/SCI W/Poly (17021306) Java Developer 4 (Sr.) – TS/SCI W/Poly Requisition ID : 17021306 Location : United States-Virginia-Fairfax US Citizenship Required for this… https://t.co/OQBPEbGCIH https://t.co/cVZmXoZi5M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Java Web Developer: 102422BR Full Stack Java Web Developer VA – Herndon 102422BR Raytheon is seeking a Full Stack Developer to be an integral part of a Java Web Application development team to support both Raytheon products and customer… https://t.co/FpgevswIfs https://t.co/MAiarDuUv1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Software Engineer for Microscope Control and Image Analysis: Lab Vision The Discovery Machine Lab led by Loic Royer at the Chan Zuckerberg Biohub will design and build lightsheet microscopy based discovery machines that will not only acquire image… https://t.co/03tzGQ1kCe https://t.co/tBHW0UsbEp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Back-end / Full Stack Developer – NodeJS, Java: Workstate seeks developers with 1+ years of experience in server-side NodeJS development. While this is a server side role, full stack experience will not go to waste. The same goes for multi-platform… https://t.co/odQSmRxS9n https://t.co/nKYpxKxfMG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Specialist, IT App Development – Application Developer (Java &amp; Salesforce): Job ID: 51533 #informationtechnology This position will suport Nationwide Financial. The ideal candidate will have the following: * Degree in computure science or related… https://t.co/KtrQWOZdfL https://t.co/MkRtftnv3V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Platform Services Engineer: The Challenge: Maintain and enhance Java services and API’s related to data privacy for our customers. Interface with multiple product teams across Adobe to help them fulfill regulation requirements and leverage our… https://t.co/8TTXem0Ck9 https://t.co/S7nIIKvGq6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Software Engineer — TS/SCI Required (Java): An analytics and data solutions company that delivers customized solutions to clients, is seeking a qualified Sr. Software Engineer with TS/SCI clearance to join their growing team. This person will be… https://t.co/nqyr5vo3jD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Software Engineer: Java Software Engineer Skip Navigation Fiserv Menu – Solutions – Industries – About – Careers – Where you fit in – Technology – Accounting &amp; Finance – Contact Center – U.S. Locations – Alpharetta – Brookfield – Dallas/Ft. Worth –… https://t.co/avtcTvRbHv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Java Engineer – Top legal tech company: As part of the Engineering Team, you will be given the opportunity to display your creativity and deliver continuous end-user value in an Agile environment. We are self-motivated engineers who like to research,… https://t.co/1styZU9oHk https://t.co/k1L7pTcq8S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best stand mixer: By Lesley Stockton This post was done in partnership with Wirecutter. When readers choose to buy Wirecutter's independently chosen editorial picks, it may earn affiliate commissions that support its work. Read the full article here.… https://t.co/XpyatmEUJ0 https://t.co/JEHvLLSg7N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Backend Java Web Developer: SENIOR BACKEND JAVA WEB DEVELOPER Atlanta technology leader is seeking a senior-level Back End focused Java Web Developer to join the team. In this direct-hire opportunity, you will be responsible for designing,… https://t.co/QpwavE4wVM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Market Risk Java Developer – Quantitative Risk Analytics: Job Description At Wells Fargo, we want to satisfy our customers’ financial needs and help them succeed financially. We’re looking for talented people who will put our customers at the center of… https://t.co/tTj89k6BcQ https://t.co/OolVKD3Syt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who's picking up the tab at the royal wedding? https://t.co/27SyH5m6Xq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer Professional: Search Display Loading Close Your account has successfully been deleted. Close Message deleted. Job has been emailed. Job(s) has been emailed. Send email is not working. Please try again. Close Notifications and Messages… https://t.co/CA7ivi1tJU https://t.co/Hbn4GiHVee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: Join our team of Java Developers and work on dynamic long-term projects. The majority of our team members are long-term employees who enjoy consistent work and a collaborative team approach! * Application Technologies: Spring,… https://t.co/1JvXQSUIwP https://t.co/PDL4uQs8j2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RED's Hydrogen One will be available at AT&amp;T and Verizon this summer: Today, AT&amp;T and Verizon both announced they will carry the first holographic smartphone, the RED Hydrogen One. AT&amp;T is touting a release date of "later this summer," but it should be… https://t.co/M05IQLvQRh https://t.co/eQYTABdVhU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Koch-backed group gives boost to Dems on immigration: An immigration-overhaul advocacy group backed by the influential Koch brothers is sending out a series of political mailers aimed at backing pro-immigration members of Congress -- including a handful… https://t.co/xfz3nhn1tz https://t.co/5ruxAiCFik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Experienced Java Developer: Acadaca is looking for a passionate, smart and articulate Java Developer to help build and support our core software products and services. We are a ~70 person interactive technology company specializing in ecommerce, Content… https://t.co/Z0AZnrmzgI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Whole Foods will help Amazon rule the world https://t.co/aOO9UvbSad https://t.co/AwQMXxdgLv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java UI Developer: Java UI Developer Ref No.: 18-19660 Location: tampa, Florida Role : Java UI Developer Duration : 12 Months Location : Tampa, FL Job Description : JAVA UI – HTML5, CSS3, ANGULAR JS, SQL, UNIX, Core JAVA, Spring, Hibernate, RESTful… https://t.co/l0kQ8csKeX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Acura skips the touchscreen for its infotainment system: It really started with smartphones. Once we started filling our pockets with touchscreens it was only a matter of time before our fingers replaced the touchpad, mouse and stylus on almost all… https://t.co/HtJiixfzIR https://t.co/EQnKUU8rk1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JavaScript Developer – Must have Active Secret Clearance: A data analytics company is seeking a Jr. – Mid Level JavaScript Developer with an active Secret Clearance to join their team. Responsibilities: * Developing custom Analytics applications and… https://t.co/IVN1yGKRVL https://t.co/dxBRSWyvol]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: Join our team of Java Developers and work on dynamic long-term projects. The majority of our team members are long-term employees who enjoy consistent work and a collaborative team approach! * Application Technologies: Spring,… https://t.co/m6qShE1P9O https://t.co/3xgBTyR1yv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JAVA Developer (2018): RSDCGroup, LLC (RSDC) is a Veteran Owned Small Business (VOSB) with a presence in the Washington, DC Metropolitan area headquartered in Arlington, Virginia with offices nationwide. We deliver results for our customers through… https://t.co/3BaorMtXeF https://t.co/ZK4bIGb29W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer (Java): WHO WE ARE _accesso_ is a world-wide software company delivering industry leading virtual queuing, eCommerce and ticketing solutions for the attractions, cultural and leisure industries. The _accesso Passport_ ticketing suite… https://t.co/qr6YyTyir8 https://t.co/QqnunTeNUe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer -Partial Remote: Los Angeles, CA Full-time Compensation Unspecified Posted Today If you are a Senior Java Developer -Partial Remote with experience, please read on! Are you a Senior Java developer that is looking for something new… https://t.co/7xqLTX8cfm https://t.co/E1fNXDhfeh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where the Democrats' fight to retake the House started last night: Democrats' path to a possible House majority starts with several seats in the Philadelphia suburbs, and the party will pick its candidates there in Tuesday's primary. https://t.co/tfRuDB6jb8 https://t.co/GYFGRIyfKe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JavaScript Engineer | React or Angular: San Francisco, CA Full-time $90k – $120k Posted Today If you are a JavaScript Engineer with PROFESSIONAL WORK experience in React or Angular, please read on! Based in the Mission District in San Francisco, CA is a… https://t.co/wJs8zXDGFG https://t.co/HIuzv9iK47]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: UNABLE TO WORK WITH 3RD PARTY AGENCIES LOCAL CANDIDATES ONLY UNABLE TO SPONSOR H1BS AT THIS TIME We are looking for a full stack engineer who feels strongly about delivering good software but also about running software in the real world.… https://t.co/COpteFkA0y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Julian Assange’s protection reportedly cost Ecuador millions: The Ecuadorian government has apparently spent quite a bit of money protecting Wikileaks founder Julian Assange. According to a report at The Guardian, the country had the full assent of the… https://t.co/uch2ZiJ0oL https://t.co/yjL6WePM4L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Engineer: Founded in 2001, ForeSee is the pioneering leader in Voice of Customer (VOC) solutions. More than 2,000 companies worldwide — in retail, government, financial services, and other industries — have transformed their customer… https://t.co/OvboYRzQNt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Lead (Java): Dallas, TX Full-time Compensation Unspecified Posted Today We are a growing tech company with a welcoming culture looking for a Tech Lead with strong Java experience! We provide a number of cloud technology solutions for our… https://t.co/kA1jTQyA2s https://t.co/pgQTCRc42T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[API Development Lead (Java/Grails): We are looking for a Java/Grails Development Lead to steer the development of the APIs powering our successful own-brand and grey-labeled products. The position involves about 30% leadership and 70% hands-on technical… https://t.co/fqXMi4LBE0 https://t.co/sEk7KWlAA2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch State Department react to North Korea reversal: North Korea says the US should carefully consider the fate of the North Korea-US summit in light of "provocative" drills with South Korea, North Korean state news agency KCNA reports. https://t.co/2GI9d1FNb6 https://t.co/Of4PZtelGu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer 3 – Ability to obtain Clearance:   Job Description – Java Developer 3 – Ability to obtain Clearance (18006409) Java Developer 3 – Ability to obtain Clearance Requisition ID : 18006409 Location : United States-Virginia-Herndon US… https://t.co/y6yaone6hV https://t.co/6UTwhOoACS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer Sr – C++, Java: Req ID : 427983BR Job Code/Title : E1073:Software Engineer Sr Job Description : The Enterprise Modeling/Simulation team of LM Space in King of Prussia, PA is looking for talented Software Engineers with recent and… https://t.co/qb6c8Ulkmf https://t.co/WOfMgtIaxZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: MVD Area candidates only! Areeva Solutions, LLC is a fast-growing Information Technology and Project/Program Management consulting firm that works with federal agencies to help streamline their business processes, and develop… https://t.co/c0DwcjWjNF https://t.co/o2lRcioxz6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[LynQ's location tracker helps find your friends outdoors: If you've ever tried to find your friends at a music festival, you know how terrible cell phones can be at tracking them down. Even if you could hear what they're saying over the noisy crowd,… https://t.co/2EwCbMjs8j https://t.co/fuXK0FPEA5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An actress for decades paid $28 a month for a New York City apartment: New York City is hugely expensive. But until March of this year, one woman was lucky enough to occupy a two-bedroom apartment in Greenwich Village -- one of the city's most desirable… https://t.co/pcrITh4xsW https://t.co/XIog3RminR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JavaScript Developer – Simulation: JavaScript Developer – Simulation – Orlando We are seeking a Javascript Developer to help bring the next generation of games technology to the military. Who are we? Calytrix Technologies is a well-established provider… https://t.co/MyZ8IBQgya https://t.co/IKANl78Htl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. JAVA script consultant: We are looking for Sr Java Consultant for our organization – Hands on SOAP API Angular UI/UX JAVA Script – open for performaning presale activities https://t.co/l1W7l47j8v https://t.co/UFmkW24wBU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Assoc Engineer, Software (Java, Open Source, and Network Mgmt.): Job Description Job Description Assoc Engineer, Software (Java, Open Source, and Network Mgmt.) Description The Technology Software Engineer will work with a team of other software… https://t.co/3MDUzfpc1J https://t.co/0VMTmUV2dS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack JavaScript Developer: Full Stack JavaScript Developer Ref No.: 18-20279 Location: San Diego, California Duties: Seeking a full stack developer that has experience developing various aspects of Web and mobile applications using Angular 2/4/5,… https://t.co/hI39QSuemj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Java Developer: Experian offers fraud and identity services for clients in more than 44 countries. Every year we check that 182 million people are who they say they are, and help organizations effectively fight fraud while providing a hassle-free… https://t.co/mdv9xOYDtr https://t.co/JMGKstRE8J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google Drive's new plans bring family sharing and more options: You probably haven't had a huge reason to upgrade from Google Drive's free 15GB service, but Google thinks it can sway you with the right incentives. It's launching a new set of plans,… https://t.co/cwGAnq0eJs https://t.co/fQHCW4f5v0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java/JEE Developer (Entry Level): We are seeking motivated, career and customer oriented Entry Level Java/JEE Developer, interested in joining our team in Kingstowne, VA, and exploring an exciting and challenging career with Unisys Federal Systems.… https://t.co/cHwCPck4Dh https://t.co/4CB4wx1imd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is how much 2018 grads are expected to make https://t.co/jDcFkSW95d https://t.co/J5ri61Wkrj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Architect – (AWS, CloudFormation, Docker, Java 8) – Alpharetta, GA: Cloud Architect – (AWS, CloudFormation, Docker, Java 8) – Alpharetta, GA Optomi, in partnership with a Fortune 500 technology company, is seeking a Cloud Architect to fulfill a… https://t.co/I4MNocYutR https://t.co/SoTeFdG0Gd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Android malware returned to Google Play with just a name change: Google has done a lot to thwart Android malware in recent months, but it's apparent there's still some work to do. Symantec recently discovered seven previously removed rogue apps that… https://t.co/TxYMGgFI0H https://t.co/shoenmTss6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solution Architect – https://t.co/6m4pXZO33Q, JavaScript, Apex: Plano, TX Full-time $110k – $130k Posted Today If you are a Solution Architect with experience, please read on! We are based in beautiful Plano, TX. We are an energetic, innovative, and… https://t.co/bCsOlIglX7 https://t.co/hKuMVQqrS3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Warehouse Developer (JAVA &amp; Informatica): This position will be filled as a Programmer/Analyst based on the skills and experience of the candidate selected. American Century Investment’s Technology Group is looking for a talented programmer with… https://t.co/0rXnzh0uEh https://t.co/g1Ot16lvTg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Javascript Developer: Haven Life is an insuretech innovator at MassMutual that offers a new way to get life insurance online that’s actually simple. We combine the culture of a startup with the stability and backing of a Fortune 500 company to… https://t.co/wjzv2Eh5zz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Software Engineer, Senior: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Falls Church, VA Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 4/16/2018 Job Description Job Number: R******* Booz Allen Hamilton has been at the forefront of strategy and… https://t.co/yk2hiUGe0P https://t.co/6qQqn28vmI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Full Stack Developer (.NET, JavaScript, React, Node): – Services – Training – Careers – About – Thoughts – Contact Menu – Services – Training – Careers – About – Thoughts – Contact – Follow us – Twitter – Facebook – Senior Full Stack Developer… https://t.co/13pzwHCBxx https://t.co/yn1IDbXDb3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Full Stack Developer: Java Full Stack Developer Ref No.: 18-20249 Location: NYC, New York Position: Java Full Stack Developer Location: NYC, NY Duration : Full-time/Perm No C2C/C2H, No Sponsorship, No Remote/Telecommute Job Description: – 4 years’… https://t.co/9WFpgVttoO https://t.co/NyzYZ1oyhe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Google's 'Material Theming' will change your Android experience: This week, Google announced a new set of tools called Material Theming that helps developers implement the Material theme across apps, including mobile and web. App-makers can choose… https://t.co/6wizYldmH8 https://t.co/So951IMpoD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The meteoric rise in the city's housing prices serves as a cautionary tale to others vying for Amazon's HQ2 https://t.co/ntFVWQO855 https://t.co/Xe5SOiSmyB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer (TS/SCI Clearance Required): An analytics and data solutions company that delivers customized solutions to clients, is seeking a qualified Java Developer with TS/SCI clearance to join their growing team. This person will be responsible for… https://t.co/K8JW6rZ3dC https://t.co/oFOb37A841]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: Overview: A successful candidate will have experience developing java based applications as a member of an agile based team, a thorough understanding of software design concepts, database schemas, and AWS cloud infrastructure. The… https://t.co/mQTHtyrQL0 https://t.co/0ilkH2jMTD]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>