<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Have fun and live your life - because things will happen that will just take the rug from under you......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Black Brilliance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Black power is very important to me......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Women: love, respect and honor our men - even if and when they don't always love, respect and honor us!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Black Wealth is not about money - it about a financial disciplined mindset which equals $$ coming....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must empower our children through education.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Build enough business income that you can quit your day job.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be content is to be satisfied.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be grateful is to be happy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WomenOfHistory: Very True https://t.co/ly4Tq8hiHQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Be radical...be crazy" thank you Dave Ramsey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't defend every stance or justify your feelings - just have them!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A budget is vital to your financial success #Dave Ramsey Everydollar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I woke up in appreciation and I went to sleep grateful.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TiffanyHaddish - I read your book in 4 hours - so inspiring - listening to your interviews (Breakfast Club) have so inspired me. DON'T EVER LET HOLLYWOOD CHANGE YOU!!! You are the real deal - may Hollywood be different.....thank you for being such an inspiration new girl crush!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give love, respect and love to all....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Black love
#Black Queens
#Black Kings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Black power
#Black wealth
#Black legacy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am super grateful - thank you Tiffany Haddish]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Black Power
Black Wealth 365 -- thank you Nia Long]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can only imagine...how wonderful this is going to be....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Young people bring so much happiness and fulfillment to my life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GOD is always speaking to us...are we listening is the question.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let GOD soothe your soul.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Show the world the beauty of a smile.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you know what you live for, you know what you live for.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God - Family - Legacy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Focus on the gift GOD gave you - thank you Tracy Morgan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Counter hate with love. Let LOVE rule.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you cannot forgive someone - simply ask, "have I ever been forgiven?".....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When they give hate - give them love.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Make people laugh....and they will do anything for you" - thank you Tiffany Haddish]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Focus on love - then it will be easy to forgive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time for Black Wealth....stay tuned.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is going to be an amazing year....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Speak it into existence....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't compete - I dominate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jamalhbryant: You learn a lot of good lessons from.....bad mistakes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I try not to worry about too much - it all works out!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What kind of life do you really want for you and your children?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't accept excuses - I accept the unstoppable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I cannot stop and I won't stop - thank you Love (P Diddy)....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can teach myself to do anything.
You can teach yourself to do anything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Building anything including wealth - is merely a matter of specific behaviors.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I cannot use "cash" I don't want it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[December 9, 2021 is a very important day to me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only the ones I touch will know me - and I'm alright and ok with that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just imagine yourself becoming all that you are capable of - then live it out in your life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't care what others think of me - I only care what GOD and I think of me!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Respect yourself, love yourself and others will to......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love, serve and bless everyone you can, when you can, with what you can!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you are going to live - live to GIVE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter your passion - always look to serve others often with your passion as well.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't chase money - chase your passions - money always finds those that chase their passions.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am grateful for the truth - become the truth sets us/me free.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Create things that you are proud of.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You cannot be grateful and complaining at the same time!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love don't judge - thank you John Gray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I"m never bitter - just better. 
When GOD lets you off the hook - you must let others off....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cthagod love Breakfast Club man, thank you for never compromising your truth to get to what's real, the truth its so dope. I watch the show daily....success to infinity for you....I have and read your book too!! loved it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TiffanyHaddish - I am so happy for you - you don't know me from a can of paint but I have been watching some of your interviews and your authenticity is so dope. Stay true to you love. Much success to infinity ......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Right now, I'm building an empire - thank you Tiffany Haddish]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Work for 4 hours and sleep for 8 hours and have fun for 12 hours.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It all works out - because I believe. 
Thank you Tamara Braxton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Work short period - have fun longer periods....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twitter is my on-line journal.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greatest lesson from 2017: Boundaries - set them, respect them and make sure others know of them....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank you GOD - for making me amazing, I can be amazing and I can do amazing things.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time to work 4 hours a day only.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live to be happy - doing what you want to do - while giving to others.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've always been outspoken - Tamar Braxton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My definition of success: is making a difference (Through service) in someone else's life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cindytrimm: See your situation from God's perspective.  Everything looks different from his point of view!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My super power is LOVE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Add value to yourself so you can then add value to others......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't always look to receive - have your hands out to give.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just become better people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My super power is found in my love for GOD.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be very quiet Natalie.
Be very still Natalie.
Be very focused Natalie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grateful....Grateful...Grateful....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't be jealous or envious of anyone - its a sickness - and its enough for everyone - believe that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you grind, you reach every goal!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't doubt - just believe.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WrtrStat: "Just leave your mind alone. Your intuition knows what it wants to write, so get out of the way." - Ray Bradbury Writing. #am…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love sitting still and allowing GOD to speak to me - its my favorite part of the day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be intense with all things good: love, faith, diligence, results, family, friends....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jealousy and envy must cease to exist - because we were all created to make our MARK on this WORLD!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am so grateful...
And grateful for many things....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@TheRealDaytime Some action must be made - R. Kelly should do a sincere apology and action change - no judgement but please get some help and stop this please!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you reflect on your life - do you see your legacy unfolding?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can do anything - if you would only do it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Focus brings freedom. Freedom brings focus.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @God_Loved: Do you agree? Comment below. https://t.co/Mq1JEk1xc7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pure_guts_: I'd rather give my life than be afraid to give it. -lyndon B. Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AthIetesForGod: If you put in the work, the results will come. -Michael Jordan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Paula_White: God is sending love to heal your heart!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MotivatedLiving: Experience is a hard teacher, because it gives the test first, and the lesson afterwards.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Paula_White: God will restore everything the enemy stole from you!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Inspire_Us: If you're not making mistakes, then you're not doing anything. -John Wooden]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never lose - because I only see myself winning!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>