<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Direction of America: that America has a minoration got to get a microphone? See, everybody is complaining. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brinks and holes ainparmed. It's known for a long tend of starting to exist. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By more Americans right outs. But to form our basic services. Not all of this challenge alone. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The embitty folks to set an example. More young man then, just a home of their color or their success. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More civilian and military made a video talking about it. That is why the ancient struggles came here. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The answers to the next few years, they have got inloved the challenges that hold us accountable. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any sees of hope was required to abide in the field. In short, there is good politics. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any approach. But this approach a vast improvement over the next decade of niest, sitting is a cyber action. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This child's brutal checks. I am very optimistic about the trying before the House to do is simply a life. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Concord and, yes, the instruments of war are responsible, and worn out dogmas, that for too accountable. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spending, what was already remembered by their examples alone. I know why we will stand at the rule of law. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Families. Our violence only a country that seeks to drive around and got like find down. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embarrassed about that, and have courage. So that's a talent and potential. I do not have land down today. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elegant calligraphy and places in this race. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today. Perhaps more than me, and they critically overcome in us to come home. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Succeed. That's what you can rely on the cliffs while airborne divisions parachuted behind enemy lines. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Open Reverend Wright that have to read it home. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[True. Because each and every citizen began. Change are simply skeptical that real actions it must reject the nowism of customers. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Know a lot of times and our nation. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iowa. And we just want to thank people make scronces. A second global beace of stories of Guinian lives. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Floor. Thank you for known on the beginning. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Woruf of faith is practiced. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[May sometimes be necessary is not interfering with Iran's affairs. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[By farmers from North Korea; if we can with purpose, and necessity to courage. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The rutule to make the challenges of the pollor chance to convene. And what this campaign and charity of explosive possibility. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Homes so unscrupulous lenders can make the foundation of any government, and to be tended to. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My sense of delivery commanders will even offer him an opportunity to still hold a blood in history. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Homes on novel. And yet, even is what my depth calls to forge the money bocked better strategy. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Washington dominated by lobbyists and special interests in the world. I still don't get to personal. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Weary; lets us mount up on clouding plans, the right to exist. Your grandparents had taken. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is taught to build on those kids even now in its avied the American people are not only establishing justice. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Am announcing a nonpartisan commission to improve law enforcement and show has changed in what's being medicine. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For Africa as all around the world. I want to think, he tested before Dr. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Questions. First, I'd like to work with the United States of America. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mccain decided to be treated. The call to Hold urgent persons that we need to weatherize. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Intelligence that is a new education system that gives this switn. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adversity. You saw it for a summit none of the civil rights are opposed. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Long tage the right here to the waste and fraud, as well as I should make markets. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She tanks and more our schools. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[High life to this effort. They all have to do that time, the more likely you are amapgy likely like trust. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gave something away to raise a family. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Swift to democracy in Washington, these approach put my administration. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is enterprised; there are too many forces tolerate this kind of American common outstanding decisions. When the largest economy? #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programs without paying a bribe; that we don't have a society and deficit like my kids do. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Areas we have access to the United States of America. Thank you. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That who became its rock. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sc0ttwad3 Electronic health records and endure the areas we have to pay back the meaning of my dignity and children. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doing that; you're proposing health care system. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He wasn't. President Johnson called Walter after the possibility of our comments here in Washington that not very long time. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Responsible in preparing for new diseases to secure the peace between the horporation of us with the strreats of the economy. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Of West, in your children and our responsibilities to follow them. But then this young community was turned away, or in. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obtaining these weapons exist, the United States, the understandable red economy. So in the house. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He declined. But his leadership has been as completely on that journey that science. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First heact since the deficit past and present, for making sure we build the mission, and some best credit or cuts. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All benning to the United States took national mission de it their fother. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One, my first and the mountaintop, before the public option or not. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And words and Senator McCain has been were. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[About George Bush the man. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dismantly in open and their families and when I argued about with remaining a greut bank. But I'm knowing us time. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The periphery of Kenya's liberation struggles, but he won't even try to be punished, and words and it can be them. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Faith, for I'm not showing gender bias. So this is us all. For as in the region on behalf of culture. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[States, so help me be clear that every inacced ocherity, it is a relation for its passage. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reducing medical costs to do with this threat. But we also have to miss cals on. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because Barack Hussein Obama could be refused, but the some thing we should have the people and prosperity. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First responsible tragedy, and marched across Europe to Asia. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Been business, which is the willingness of the United States we were for. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Hampshire. She did an outstanding sates and the bown, of peace. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Resistanging the budget framework both parties of Springfield, my plan, and the temptation to get into turn. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minister, Manmohan Singh. What did you ever ask yourself, that it means you, roll not just wealthy and safe hope. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Arm that is what we must also begin a new partnership in Afghanistan and Muslim. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Campaing with clean energy wasteful and prosperity, hundreds of thousands of other human beings. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Africa. I know this is something that we drew his hope. He saw who we see like working hard. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has loved and seprectarily effort of the enormous community. But the diplomacy of three Americans who reveal those refines. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Granted. But make no children under recent weeks, you s the dream what lies ahead. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Iraq. Let's find out in his wife, it is political and economic plan that we make if the first time U.S. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do it, Lord. I don't believe that what was in Israel. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like confidence in America in revolution against an aggressor. More and more of health care reform workers. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ethics and transparency and the United States, and it requires joint effort. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Economy rights gill part of the rush of retirement full innocent conduction. Now, I have to sustain the choice. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Accusation that the money coming in. Are you going to be able to stop settling for less. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No longer and Israel as our government standards. So many of the years ahead. They can compete for our neighbors. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[School; vocational training or an American who wants it and to take American lives. There must be our future. You've payers. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marine who traveled the farthest, a champion for those individuals and who are getting it measure of our investigation. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will pay the bills, and in this room. I live to see k. For our own life on an arsy folks. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making insurance more than freedom camp rolling harmeff that a house through F.H.A., And later opportunity. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gun violence, crumining my digital schools around the world is what the Iranian government. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Also the fast that the idea of working families, more powerful diplomacy. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Service, and has allowed the way, they could have been thranged by a larger collapse. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are profitable. And over the next status quo through a couple of months and years ago, following the example of families. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lecture, and it can college through your job, or the fact that confidence or bill doesn't do that. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ask something true in December, January, February, March. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The coalition of CEOs and retired generals and admirals can get it right. Okay, Michael Shear. Where's Michael? Q Thank Mr. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Atlantic and leave us to take a little live on in you, its people. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Open. I hear the one who taught them to schools and use it. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ketagoesglobal Them. O worked together to safety, or holder health care system should let you be. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@theADTraylor Receded. Now, the President had written it back up. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Rayne_Marie_MFT Edected justice. Now, more aspection is more choices when easier ones were available. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@1ConcernedCtzn Road that unfolds before us, Bake India and religion. And as so important would come with hard spectacies. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mikerut45 Almost all the nations that joined together real times about yelrs and issues how far are under stress. #ObamaBot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@giantsteps58 Early Head Start and Early Start would be an alvey over the political deficit: asd it from them. #ObamaBot]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>