<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer Systems Analyst: Quantum Secure Inc (San Jose, CA) F/T positions: Solution Engineer III: Resp for analyze &amp; cust security suite; req Mstr’s or equiv + 2 yr exp + skills. Software Engineer: Resp for dev &amp; &amp; cust security suite; req Bach or equiv… https://t.co/SN9yrGE17U https://t.co/NxDaSB2cYl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Support Specialist: IT Support Specialist $50,722 – $55,795 Hiring Range DOE   Provide first-line technical support to data and telecommunication network systems users. Support services provided by this position include: IT Help Desk coverage;… https://t.co/dvEProUMFS https://t.co/pNdULc3EH3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Application Developer: Capitalogix LLC has multiple openings to work in our office in Coppell, Texas. Sr Data Scientist to translate business needs into data reqs to prototype, develop &amp; launch knowledge-based systems, data mining, machine learning, &amp;… https://t.co/sA2IzP9psM https://t.co/aZoKiRLFSf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Samsung's second quarter profit may flag as smartphone innovation dries up: SEOUL (Reuters) - Samsung Electronics Co Ltd is expected to post its smallest profit growth in more than a year in the second quarter, as lackluster sales of its premium Galaxy… https://t.co/CcZ5thgbat https://t.co/Xbz8lGotoe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Mobile Full Stack Engineer: Los Angeles, CA Full-time $120k – $150k Posted Today If you are a Senior Mobile Full Stack Engineer with experience, please read on! Top Reasons to Work with Us Amazing opportunity to solve some of the industry most… https://t.co/ZwSHWptxIx https://t.co/W3Sqc1ijqH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Afloat Network Engineer (FSET):   Job Description – Afloat Network Engineer (FSET) (PEN000988) Job Description  Afloat Network Engineer (FSET) (PEN000988)  Description   For more than 70 years, Vectrus has been a leader in delivering large-scale IT,… https://t.co/zsjRevD9gs https://t.co/4ZkxY34M0L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Test Engineer: Req ID : 434496BR_3 Job Code/Title : E1784:Sys Integratn/Test Eng Stf Job Description : We are currently seeking a System Integration and Test Engineer to be a part of the team developing hypersonic technology that could forever… https://t.co/OhVPXYgYxq https://t.co/KV8g0JEDD2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ZTE given temporary reprieve from U.S.; removes more executives: NEW YORK/HONG KONG (Reuters) - China's embattled ZTE Corp has received a temporary reprieve from the U.S. government to conduct business needed to maintain existing networks and equipment… https://t.co/sRxI3kgm8a https://t.co/pLzA7Qfagu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cyber Sec Eng Spec, SME pos# 250: Req ID 98639BR Business Title Cyber Sec Eng Spec, SME pos# 250 Group MCIS Location USA VIRGINIA Springfield Clearance Level Needed TS/SCI Category Cyber Job Duties and Responsibilities Currently, ManTech is seeking a… https://t.co/WI4twJzR5D https://t.co/iJ9Mpt1apm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber in talks with Dubai's Careem to merge in Middle East: Bloomberg: (Reuters) - Uber Technologies is in preliminary talks with rival Careem to combine their Middle Eastern ride-hailing services, Bloomberg reported on Tuesday, citing three people… https://t.co/Yz6TcNg6ym https://t.co/UPdJUfJk0f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Naval Supply Business Analyst: Naval Supply Business Analyst ============================= Req #: ******Location: Norfolk, VA USJob Category: Information TechnologySecurity Clearance: SecretClearance Status: Must Be Current Job Description BACKGROUND:… https://t.co/ITCBiVv276 https://t.co/gW4PH0ceB7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-Intel executive departs Google as chipmaker searches for CEO: (Reuters) - Diane Bryant, a former Intel Corp executive who headed the chipmaker's data center unit, is leaving Alphabet Inc's cloud computing unit less than a year after joining and just… https://t.co/WSOIBP9bJK https://t.co/UD1WKq5JmP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Staff Engineer: Staff Engineer Firmware (Mellanox Technologies, Inc., Austin, TX): Develop firmware for Mellanox’s state-of-the-art Host-Channel adapters. Requires: Bachelor’s degree or foreign equivalent in Computer Engineering, Electrical Engineering,… https://t.co/wNrXeBNFtb https://t.co/7Dx1auBIQR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[QA Testing Analyst: Job ID: ********-11637-TL Company Name: Xactware Description: Summary of Responsibilities: Ensure the overall quality and health of the products for which your team is responsible through analysis of design, documentation, and… https://t.co/jO0kBEZ87c https://t.co/VEFTxLd8uK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hyundai invests in Israeli auto tech firm Autotalks: TEL AVIV (Reuters) - Hyundai Motor Co said on Tuesday it was partnering with Autotalks, an Israeli provider of vehicle to everything (V2X) communication technology for improving road safety. https://t.co/T3p8F79X4w https://t.co/bzSHl6Mwkl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Industrial Hygiene Project Manager: TRC Companies, Inc. (NYSE: TRR), a pioneer in groundbreaking scientific and engineering developments since the 1960s, is a national engineering consulting and construction management firm that provides… https://t.co/NJdoKZ1wrx https://t.co/MEpEqLwwq8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Enterprise Architect Chief Job: Date: May 26, 2018 Location:Washington, DC, US Company: SAIC Enterprise Architect Chief (Job Number:425507) Description: JOB DESCRIPTION: Responsible for leading and managing the successful delivery of Enterprise… https://t.co/b3ZhU856rA https://t.co/NtXeNIBF5F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Account Executive: Account Executive Job Location US-NY-New York City Req No. 2018-2340 Category Sales/Presales Overview We have an immediate opportunity for an Account Executive on our Sales team in the New York, NY office. The ideal candidate must have… https://t.co/GU5MPkJ8te https://t.co/EQ8GrmhXY1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer – Junior: Software Engineer – Junior Jobs in El Segundo at Boeing Skip Navigation SearchMenu – News – Investors – Employee/Retiree – Merchandise – Suppliers – Features &amp; Multimedia – Commercial – Defense – Space – Services – Innovation… https://t.co/kys07TW4tK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[User Experience Specialist: Overview AtFOOD SERVICES OF AMERICAwe have a long tradition of providing the highest levels of customer service in the industry. We have a culture that trusts our Associates to act in the best interests of our customers and… https://t.co/XzdYF6vO2t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Security Operations Administrator: Permanent Full time role Prestigious Enterprise Company is currently seeking a Network Security Operations Administrator. Candidate is responsible for analysing, designing, installing, configuring, maintaining… https://t.co/CljLDn7ziV https://t.co/KXKTFpdKCU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Israel's ThetaRay raises over $30 million for money laundering prevention: TEL AVIV (Reuters) - Israel's ThetaRay, which uses mathematics to provide early detection from cyber threats, has completed a fundraising round of over $30 million, bringing the… https://t.co/3rpxhyLybA https://t.co/2z4C2RZe0N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MAC Technical Support Analyst: CONTRACT POSITION FOR A MAC TECHNICAL SUPPORT ANALYST IN LAWRENCE TOWNSHIP, NJ Our client is looking for a Mac Support Specialist with Casper/Jamff policy configuration experience for Mac Application Deployment. CompTIA A+… https://t.co/y3z9r0bpK5 https://t.co/ZDvDwAqYEH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Project Manager: IT Project Manager $73,924 – $103,494 DOE The Project Manager will serve in the implementation of short- and long-range public transportation technology projects within budget constraints, oversight of scope, and technical evaluation… https://t.co/MVyCGhKyO6 https://t.co/VLkMiycNtn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[System Administrator: Develop your career. Enhance your life. Strengthen your future. NOW HIRING! SYSTEM ADMINISTRATOR Seeking an individual with excellent problem solving skills, a strong desire to learn and exceptional communication skills. Knowledge… https://t.co/pWeD1Fe4Fq https://t.co/cCXjKQgtH3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PwC must pay FDIC $625.3 million over bank's collapse: U.S. judge: (Reuters) - A federal judge on Monday said PricewaterhouseCoopers LLP must pay $625.3 million in damages to the Federal Deposit Insurance Corp for failing to uncover fraud that led to one… https://t.co/elmz1FM7VI https://t.co/Nvsbz4a509]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Data Scientist, Data Scientist Assoc, Sr Application Developer,: Capitalogix LLC has multiple openings to work in our office in Coppell, Texas. Sr Data Scientist to translate business needs into data reqs to prototype, develop &amp; launch knowledge-based… https://t.co/JJebgeoB7C https://t.co/unceSrliFy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Randel Solutions LLC seeks SOFTWARE DEVELOPER (full time) in Overland Park, KS: Create, modify, and test codes, write, analyze, and review programs using workflow charts and diagrams, modify and maintain programs, assist in… https://t.co/TolpYbZbaL https://t.co/06gUTnvEad]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Coordinator: Project Coordinator sought by C.M. Architecture PA in Ft. Worth, TX. Prep architectural docs &amp; drawings, build models, &amp; prep construction drawings on REVIT under the direction of a licensed architect. Applicant must have Bach’s deg… https://t.co/t5L6sfesGn https://t.co/2vpHgvcOjt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer / Engineer: Requisition ID 2018-39386 # of Openings 5 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Secret Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description GDIT is currently seeking a Software Developer in Keyport, WA to provide… https://t.co/Z9bnSsKPJq https://t.co/EsBkrFwh9s]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taking Softbank's lead, China, UK managers form $15 billion tech fund: LONDON (Reuters) - A China-backed venture plans to raise $15 billion to invest in technology companies globally, borrowing several pages from the playbook of Japan's Softbank, whose… https://t.co/1qgFef9YER https://t.co/T7cNDCey81]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst-Human Services: Overview Public Consulting Group, Inc. (PCG) is a $400 million, fast growing, for profit company providing management consulting and technology services to help public sector education, health, human services, and other… https://t.co/82ZfzoWZ7A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full Stack Engineer: Full Stack Engineer San Francisco, California – United States Job Start Date – 06/19/18, Posted Date – 06/19/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview Job Overview: ********* Website Application Development develops the highly… https://t.co/TpmQ8lJWwr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mgr Systems Engineering 2:   Job Description – Mgr Systems Engineering 2 (18012858) Mgr Systems Engineering 2 Requisition ID : 18012858 Location : United States-Colorado-Aurora US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation Assistance:… https://t.co/Ng7gvWkYqt https://t.co/Unwnkx2tj1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Analyst: Our team in Winston-Salem, NC supports a very large policy/billing system used by National General Insurance which causes the group to continue growing and adding new headcount. Primary Purpose: This position coordinates and participates… https://t.co/zarRy5DZ9B https://t.co/kUlBMW1RTA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Panasonic would consider additional investment in Tesla's Gigafactory if requested: executive: OSAKA (Reuters) - Japan's Panasonic Corp would consider additional investment in Tesla Inc's automotive battery plant in the U.S. state of Nevada if requested… https://t.co/YIHYm2v6uO https://t.co/93oNXSdKZh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Entry Level Software Developer: Job Postings | Reyrey.comReynolds and Reynolds LogoFacebookLinkedInTwitterYouTubeInstagram Skip to main content [RR – Careers] Careers Super Navigation Careers Menu #ReyReyLife Search Jobs Main navigation [RR – Careers]… https://t.co/9aGMRRFFGP https://t.co/3NrliZk4uh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Java Developer: ******/Java Developer Ref No.: 18-24307 Location: Mt. Loreal NJ, New Jersey Job Description(As per hiring manager) Key skills required for the job are: J2EE architect (Mandatory) Spring Hibernate Angular Usability-L3 (Mandatory)… https://t.co/uxh1d0ahQI https://t.co/l7szXPfBLd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dell near deal to swap out DVMT tracking shares: WSJ: (Reuters) - Dell Inc is close to a deal to combine shares that track its VMware Inc virtualization-software unit in an effort that would result in a public listing for the personal computer and data… https://t.co/BJw4asfIou https://t.co/WbqkGK1qOM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SailPoint Developer: SailPoint Developer Malvern, Pennsylvania – United States Job Start Date – 05/31/18, Posted Date – 05/31/18 Primary SkillsSailpointTax TermsC2COverview Client: Vanguard skype Positions: Multiple Full Name: Full Addresses with Zip… https://t.co/BtzIac8YKv https://t.co/Nd2vAZhlaM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer: Software Developer for Kid’s mobile gaming startup – 77SPARX Studio 77SPARX Studio Digital Toys | 77SPARX Navigation – PUZZINGO Puzzles – PUZZINGO Puzzles Free – PUZZINGO Puzzles Pro – Wonster Words – Blog – Support Software Developer… https://t.co/imiJufR5xw https://t.co/bKux68MQnh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network Engineer, Lead: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Annapolis Junction, MD Job Type: Engineering Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/14/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’ toughest management… https://t.co/HiG2n7R8Fr https://t.co/UyapS9EqqZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JAVA Full Stack Developer: TITLE: JAVA Full Stack Developer DURATION: 12+ Months contract on W-2 LOCATION: Charlotte, NC INTERVIEW TYPE: Phone followed by F2F DESCRIPTION: * Looking for at least 7 years of JAVA/J2EE development experience. * Extensive… https://t.co/8GqbV5A9fi https://t.co/SMOaDJq2py]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst II – Order to Cash / Finance: School Specialty is the industry’s largest provider of educational products, services and programs including Classroom Supplies, Arts products, Special Needs Resources, Math, Science, Reading, Physical… https://t.co/cXb8KAw0tH https://t.co/tIIHSetRYy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teradata Developer: Teradata Developer Ref No.: 18-28272 Location: Sunnyvale, California 6 to 8 Yrs of experience Hands on Teradata &amp; all Teradata utilities Knowledge on ETL process using Informatica, BODS etc. Hands on SQL, PL/SQL. Ability to write… https://t.co/Z5e8dPvcV3 https://t.co/uoPhBD50zV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Administrator: Employer Princeton University Location Princeton, NJ Posted May 31, 2018 Institution Type Four-Year Institution You need to sign in or create an account to save Requisition # 2018-8837 Department Princeton Neuroscience Inst… https://t.co/9XD5AcADeE https://t.co/Abw2j2yFBX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Java Developer: Job Description What you’ll be doing. We are looking for Senior Java Developer to join the Digital Transformation Group. This position represents an opportunity to become an integral part of a talented team helping our clients’… https://t.co/wkarG8QCHh https://t.co/MQKZxUTfu6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Support Representative Part Time: Job Snapshot Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Las Vegas, NV, US Job Type: Technical Support Representative Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 5/14/2018 Job Description JOB FAIR Tuesday and Wednesday, May… https://t.co/QhEU49Xre9 https://t.co/aTpgkiUPTg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Systems Engineer – SDR / Embedded: Req ID : 423202BR Job Code/Title : E1463:Systems Engineer Sr Job Description : At Lockheed Martin Rotary and Mission Systems, we are driven by innovation and integrity. We believe that by applying the highest… https://t.co/Be9YSCuzct https://t.co/fs4kK8q93x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP Basis Administrator: We are currently seeking a Senior SAP BASIS Application Administrator to join our support team at a large Federal Government datacenter located at Hill Air Force Base – Ogden, Utah. This role supports numerous Department of… https://t.co/Kaj8dLCR5s https://t.co/QGmN4zNbUq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior GUI C# Developer: Summary CRD is currently expanding the capabilities of our products in several new areas. The Senior GUI C# Developer is a full-time position, working on developing the user interface and related software. We employ 170+ of the… https://t.co/Y3py2AcooF https://t.co/ROsG2nw8WQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Job Developer: RESPONSIBILITIES * ACTIVELY SOURCE EMPLOYERS USING VARIOUS TECHNIQUES INCLUDING COLD-CALLS AND ONSITE VISITS IN ORDER TO DISCUSS SERVICE OFFERINGS OF CWD * ESTABLISH RELATIONSHIPS WITH EMPLOYERS AND ASSESS THEIR NEEDS IN ORDER TO PROVIDE… https://t.co/zOQA8izq1f https://t.co/qAh6js6yZD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer: Electrical Engineer (MRI): St. Jude Medical, Cardiology Division, in Sylmar, CA seeks qualified Electrical Engineer (MRI). Responsible for providing engineering services to device manufacturing operations &amp; developing &amp; implementing efficient,… https://t.co/KbMWne1oyQ https://t.co/oenCEcnojW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Analyst: Systems Analyst Perform application analysis, investigation, technical support, and liaison role with development team for software utilized for blood bank/transfusion screening applications, using BBX, JAVA, SQL, PROGESA, ePROGESA, PHS,… https://t.co/vkoqh0g9aS https://t.co/gmsRxgtLhd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple rebuilds mapping app, but will still tap TomTom: (Reuters) - Apple Inc is rebuilding the widely used mapping application on its iPhones from the ground up with its own dataset, but Amsterdam-based TomTom NV will continue to be a data provider for… https://t.co/J4xK0urT3Q https://t.co/4CTm1h0nEL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advisory Senior Consultant #XSFH18FA0518AUS1: Advisory Senior Consultant for Deloitte &amp; Touche LLP in Austin, TX to identify and evaluate complex business and technology risks, internal controls that mitigate risks, and related opportunities for internal… https://t.co/sCHUmE1O0i https://t.co/fmmuSBlrRo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AN SAP Basis Administrator II: An SAP Basis Administrator II is needed to support the operation of Dura-Line’s SAP systems in Gainesville, TX. Requires a B.S. in computer science, computer applications or related field (foreign degree equivalent… https://t.co/Zssn7QQSUT https://t.co/BHt1EMYVYC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Creative Designer: Creative Designer Photon Infotech, Inc. Dallas, TX Photon Infotech, Inc. has opening for Creative Designer (Sets visual communication strategies that promote marketing objectives. Apply appropriate metrics and customer insight to the… https://t.co/EqJoySXlZ6 https://t.co/BY79GOU4yv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer I – Distributed Systems: ENGINEERING Mountain View, CA. Couchbase Inc seeks Sr SW Eng’r I-Distributed Systems to create distributed sw srvr infrastructure prods for critical OLTP needs; ensure prods deliver highly avail systs… https://t.co/F15JvemO5b https://t.co/CfJWFfrOxw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China's ZTE shakes up board in bid for U.S. ban lift: SHENZHEN, China/HONG KONG (Reuters) - Chinese telecoms giant ZTE Corp announced a new board on Friday in a radical management shakeup as part of a $1.4 billion deal with the United States, moving it… https://t.co/HRYskW0sNa https://t.co/DW2HaiuQUS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Scientist: Department23300 SSD-Administration About the UnitConsistently ranked among the top ten social science research universities in the world, the Division of Social Sciences is at the vanguard of inquiry and impact. Whether through the… https://t.co/3upr2megpn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[KM Firm Solutions Project Analyst: KM Firm Solutions Project Analyst – Morristown NJ | Ogletree Deakins – Contact Us – Media Center – Extranet – Careers – Alumni Germany UK Mexico French Canada – Who We Are – Overview – Client Pledge – Our Leadership –… https://t.co/LiXMtuCT5Q https://t.co/f4RQnIgwY9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sales Specialist IV: About Avaya Avaya enables the mission critical, real-time communication applications of the world’s most important operations. As a global leader in delivering superior communications experiences, Avaya offers a complete portfolio of… https://t.co/bxnnuyASxR https://t.co/YkNj5kNwNt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Manager, Center for Nursing Education + Professional Dev: Project Manager, Center for Nursing Education + Professional Dev (46470) Job Type: Full Time FTE/Bi-Weekly Hours: 1.0/80 Shift: Days Hours in Shift: 8 Location: Palo Alto, CA Req: 46470… https://t.co/NDKjCKISGO https://t.co/381RCExGlU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[French startup Syntony takes geolocation underground: PARIS (Reuters) - French startup Syntony, which has designed systems to locate mobile phones in tunnels and subways, is raising 10 million euros ($11.6 million) to fund its international expansion. https://t.co/hReToCeAcF https://t.co/Mldyz9ZSHn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer: COMPUTER/IT SuccessFactors, Inc. seeks a Development Expert at our South San Francisco, CA loc to be responsible for development focusing on concept, design, coding, testing, quality assurance of complex product features in a development team… https://t.co/Xh6ezspORJ https://t.co/ESYFnQAh1g]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Bridge Project Manager: AECOM is actively seeking a creative, highly talented Senior Bridge Project Manager for immediate employment in the Raleigh, NC office. AECOMs Transportation Group Southeast Region is growing again! With 100,000 people in… https://t.co/GPhonZYnk4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Systems Engineer/Programmer: BNY Mellon is looking for talent to design, manage and monitor of virtual networking solutions in container-based environments. The environments are being orchestrated by technologies like Kubernetes, Mesos, Nomad,… https://t.co/FtXw0SzpdV https://t.co/ValD6CBn6A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr Network Engineer – TS/SCI required: Requisition ID 2018-41815 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Top Secret/SCI Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description Contract: I2TS 3 Position: Sr Engineer, Network –… https://t.co/FRLV6ZnSgZ https://t.co/C7Kaw8OvE3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. ISR Systems Integrator/ Knowledge Management: Sr. ISR Systems Integrator/ Knowledge Management ================================================ Req #: ******Location: Tampa, FL USJob Category: EngineeringSecurity Clearance: TS/SCIClearance Status:… https://t.co/Ieje5ePjz0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Novogratz's Galaxy invests $20 million in virtual reality platform: NEW YORK (Reuters) - Hedge fund manager Mike Novogratz's investment fund has invested $20 million in a blockchain-based virtual reality platform called High Fidelity, the project's chief… https://t.co/iNhvUFYlXp https://t.co/u627kKD0Nt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Safety Engineer 4:   Job Description – Software Safety Engineer 4 (18009466) Software Safety Engineer 4 Requisition ID : 18009466 Location : United States-California-Woodland Hills US Citizenship Required for this Position: Yes Relocation… https://t.co/BY4IsPB0ci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ground Software Engineer Orion LabVIEW: Req ID : 436088BR Job Code/Title : E1072:Software Engineer Job Description : This Software Engineer position is with the Electronic Aerospace Ground Equipment (EGSE) team on the Orion Program. The position requires… https://t.co/Eu7W0o7Ual https://t.co/FI7cpXeWcI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SAP S/4 Hana Project Manager: SAP S/4 HANA PROJECT MANAGER 12 months NYC, NY JOB DESCRIPTION Strong knowledge of end to end S/4 Hana Fulfill commercial process &amp; tools knowledge is critical to success. Must have extensive experience in dealing with… https://t.co/eR7ELy8dpF https://t.co/p7miasrfcP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Developer: I am working with a fantastic client located in the Houston area that is looking for an Application Developer. The client offers an excellent compensation and great benefits package. RESPONSIBILITIES: * Serve as a Project Manager… https://t.co/rz9tVsLXf9 https://t.co/UoPgEAwocx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Panasonic flags battery shortages as Tesla Model 3 output picks up: TOKYO (Reuters) - A senior Panasonic Corp official on Friday said a pickup in production of Tesla Inc's Model 3 cars, after earlier delays, has resulted in occasional battery shortages. https://t.co/LBYr5N7k9b https://t.co/Qvw7jnzl8A]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lyft raises $600 million in funding at $15 billion valuation: (Reuters) - Lyft Inc said on Wednesday it raised $600 million in a new funding round led by Fidelity Management, valuing the ride-hailing firm at $15.1 billion. https://t.co/ilglDpt9XQ https://t.co/zurwQG2OXO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering: ENGINEERING: Samsung Austin Semiconductor LLC has multiple openings in San Jose, CA: Sr. Engineer; Principal Engineer and Sr. Staff Engineer to research, design, develop, and/or optimize operating systems-level software and/or compilers to… https://t.co/Cfsnhn9Lu6 https://t.co/yRIJqEsBRG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Estimator/Project Manager- North Wasatch Area, UT: Back to search results Search by Keyword or Job ID More Search Options Search by Location or Country Search by Postal Code (US ONLY) Search by Location or Country Search by Postal Code (US ONLY) Distance… https://t.co/GBJT9K9Jfn https://t.co/yrLXIHlZhh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principle Network Engineer / Tech Lead: Job Description BAE Systems has a job opening for a Principle Network Engineer in Charlotte, NC (Ballantyne). Design and implement complex networking solutions over a large enterprise level network. The person… https://t.co/gvyPs1wqoH https://t.co/0BlftAcIxw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Power Developer: Data Power Developer Ref No.: 18-24277 Location: Richardson, Texas Role : Data Power Developer Duration : 12 Months Location : Richardson, TX Job Description : – Experience in designing, developing and maintaining IBM Datapower and… https://t.co/pa4ZFvu3hl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/qnMiKeGOPZ Developer: ************** Developer: 19-02110 Ref No.: 18-02110 Location: Burbank, California Akraya is looking for a ************** Developer for one of our clients. If the job description below is a fit, please apply directly or… https://t.co/YQE270ZQLW https://t.co/94Vhp0eA4U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior DevOps Engineer: Senior DevOps Engineer in Washington, DC | CACI International – Small Business | – Suppliers – About Us – | – What We Do – | – Media &amp; Events – | – Investors – | – Careers – | – Contracts – | – Contact Us Join Our Talent Network –… https://t.co/HFl0LYZYr4 https://t.co/ZbO3FnDHnh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineer Payments / Payouts: Description At YapStone, we approach payments with the same startup mentality that we had when we launched our first payment solution in 1999. We are now focused on combining our entrepreneurial spirit with… https://t.co/N7h9XLBtho https://t.co/kcgJWmxPFd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Cyber Software Engineer:   Job Description – Principal Cyber Software Engineer (18008892) Principal Cyber Software Engineer Requisition ID : 18008892 Location : United States-Maryland-Annapolis Junction US Citizenship Required for this… https://t.co/zSLNEYS1pU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer / Embedded / C++ / Orlando, Fl: Req ID : 419354BR Job Code/Title : E1073:Software Engineer Sr Job Description : Develop and maintain embedded software applications and/or desktop applications for Lockheed Martin Missiles and Fire… https://t.co/zzUu89BUFh https://t.co/VXiawoUFL6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google retires DoubleClick, AdWords brand names: NEW YORK (Reuters) - Alphabet Inc's Google announced on Wednesday the biggest-ever rebranding of its advertising software, retiring the DoubleClick and AdWords brands to streamline entry points for… https://t.co/34dnw6LZ0d https://t.co/R6KsB0yTuj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineer II: Engineer II – Embedded sought by DISH Network, LLC in Englewood, CO. Design, develop, &amp; test STB software modules; create software running in a multithreaded environment; design &amp; implement new software features; debug &amp; production support.… https://t.co/OE4Zuf2mF5 https://t.co/RnvxeL5yWS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. senators want Trump to reconsider lifting ban on China's ZTE: WASHINGTON (Reuters) - Two U.S. senators urged President Donald Trump on Tuesday to reconsider his agreement with ZTE Corp , saying lifting a ban on China's second-largest… https://t.co/lSoL9VtRru https://t.co/OPlgDwNsgM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uber granted new, shorter, license to operate in London: LONDON (Reuters) - Uber was granted a new, shorter, license to operate in London on Tuesday after a judge said it had made the changes required to be deemed fit and proper, after its earlier… https://t.co/kIUEYpYUhO https://t.co/UiWopiMF2x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Software Engineers- Research Systems: The University of Chicago seeks Senior Software Engineers – Research Systems for Chicago, IL to design, architect &amp; deliver solutions for the scientific computation &amp; workflows community. Masters in Computer… https://t.co/Q6BE1vxDQ3 https://t.co/5k81p9WrHj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Orlando ends facial recognition program with Amazon: (Reuters) - Orlando has stopped testing Amazon's facial recognition program after rights groups raised concerns that the service could be used in ways that could violate civil liberties. https://t.co/xYfffTgBi9 https://t.co/p7ifDC1Bgk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Platform Engineer (SAP): The SAP Basis Engineers role is to support the administration, planning, for all the systems in the SAP landscape. The SAP Basis Administrator will perform all SAP Basis related activities and collaborate closely with SAP… https://t.co/rH8zBNXfg0 https://t.co/iNNuxd4F6O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HPC Systems Administrator: Job Description Candidates shall have a Bachelor’s degree in Computer Science or related field, and have ten years of demonstrable experience in system administration and support of a large client-server based IT enterprise. Or… https://t.co/NcnrY19VvP https://t.co/P9hhJ1D4fb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sailpoint Developer: Sailpoint Developer Ref No.: 18-26061 Location: Atlanta, Georgia – 2-3 years Sailpoint IIQ Support/Upgrade experience with total 6 to 8 years experience as IAM Technical Lead Experience – Relevant experience in Analysis, Design,… https://t.co/YDaEiLJUVJ https://t.co/9PlYzVaWbo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Construction Project Manager: Job Description ******** JOB SUMMARY The purpose of this position is to lead individual, multi-disciplined real estate project solutions for clients, with direct accountability for project delivery. Characteristics of… https://t.co/rrFXfT2IN1 https://t.co/gdHbITTte9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Installations and Facilities Data Analyst: Employee Type: Full-Time Location: Arlington, VA Job Type: Strategy – Planning Experience: Not Specified Date Posted: 6/17/2018 About Us At Booz Allen, we harness our collective ingenuity to solve our clients’… https://t.co/YAtnxI5vGc https://t.co/NVWwxPjFOG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.Net Developer: Careers Center | .Net Developer Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome page Returning Candidate?… https://t.co/sq5rvpq8dZ https://t.co/YhSJrCjd3B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Indonesia's Lippo Group says invests $44 million in China's Tencent: JAKARTA (Reuters) - Indonesian conglomerate Lippo Group said on Tuesday it had invested 628 billion rupiah ($44.35 million) in Chinese internet giant Tencent Holdings Ltd through shares… https://t.co/6N1p6IFQsA https://t.co/5LdzgK5Qoc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technology: TECHNOLOGY NextEV LLC (now known as NIO USA Inc.) has the following job openings in San Jose, CA: Staff Engineer BIW Underbody (ID #400): Responsible for all studies, development and engineering activities for the underbody structural… https://t.co/FJWtLTbmAJ https://t.co/isG3iQj5aZ]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>