<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ccjones13: Just so we’re all caught up: Incumbent @MiaBLove illegally raised $1 million (+ then refused to give it back), launched atta…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @matthewjdowd: This should be a huge story.  Wow.  Whelan knew ford’s name before the public. https://t.co/pV4TRiEs24]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Zac_Petkanas: My statement on the Rosenstein NYT story: https://t.co/wSSGX9CYW4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JoePerticone: It’s strange how silent Ben Sasse has been on Kavanaugh allegations. Statements, interviews, nothing. He’s both on Judici…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Lawrence: McConnell says he has the votes to confirm Kavanaugh.

So we must now ask @JeffFlake @lisamurkowski @SenatorCollins if they a…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This—-&gt; https://t.co/ohRvbuafqf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ByCommonConsent A college professor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @bri_provenzano: Since the president is glibly tweeting about how Ford surely would have filed charges if her alleged attack was "as bad…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@isaacweiner27 @mjcressler @HLuceFdn @ADeRogatis Congrats!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DrCurtisFreeman: Today I described the 1637 examination of Anne Hutchinson as a #MeToo moment. The all male General Court refused to be…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @shannonrwatts: Watch video of @KimsMom3 confronting Ted Cruz who tells her that SROs are the answer to school shootings like the one th…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NBCNews: Yale Law School dean: Reports that a prominent professor at the school groomed female clerks for Judge Kavanaugh are "of enorm…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And, Emily you rock.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope Plotz listens again to the episode, not only to better hear French’s insincerity, but mostly to hear his colleague’s quiet and steely righteous anger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Emily, one of the strongest and smartest public intellectuals working today, can stand up for herself, of course. But that doesn’t mean she should be expected to take such implicit abuse in the service of a “debate.”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And @davidplotz, with whom I almost always agree, from this listener’s perspective your job wasn’t to act as chair umpire—Emily brought her own painful experience and expertice on sexual assault, French brought his hackery—your job was to stand up for your colleague and friend.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As a weekly listener for years, I was disgusted by the choice to bring Fench on. The idea that he is some kind of “woke” or reasonable conservative just because he opposes Trump baffles me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Props to @emilybazelon for calling bs on @DavidAFrench’s predictable hack and misogyny on this week’s @SlateGabfest’s discussion of Kavanaugh.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kaitlancollins: Not sure this is the support Brett Kavanaugh wants.
https://t.co/zhuVuefFBW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @casey_connects: To the man who assaulted me in the basement of that house decades ago:
I learned this week that there is no statute of…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @joycemaynard: In today's Yale Daily News: what Brett Kavanaugh was up to back in his school days, when he belonged to a secret society…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CJPatruno: I hope someone has informed @OmahaPolice that one of thier members in the front row is throwing a white power symbol. https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JRubinBlogger: On MOnday in front of cameras she can say: Mark Judge allegedly witnessed the attack, but Republicans refuse to call him…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ANNELAMOTT: This does it: I am coming after @senatorCollins no matter how she votes on Kavanaugh. She’s talking about Dr. Ford like she…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GlennKesslerWP: New #FactChecker --&gt;  Brett Kavanaugh’s unlikely story about Democrats’ stolen documents https://t.co/kyz2u0UHrv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read this. .@jbouie is kind of the perfect political exegete for the political moment we are in. https://t.co/v3vEq53W3y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ljoywilliams: The Gullah-Geechee People Called Carolina’s Coast Home for Centuries. Then Florence Came. https://t.co/5fGB2nCV3X #CivicD…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @publicroad: Focus on the Family just issued an email asking supporters to contact their senators to support Kavanaugh. https://t.co/Xvw…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @peterbakernyt: Blasey lawyer says "the Committee's stated plan to move forward with a hearing that has only two witnesses is not a fair…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Lawrence: People who make up stories don’t ask the FBI to investigate those stories.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ClaraJeffery: “As of Tuesday evening, the Twitter account posting Ford’s address was still active, and another account had posted what…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Sifill_LDF: Not sure that this has gotten enough attention. Let's not forget that even with the catastrophe this confirmation is facing…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @NatashaBertrand: Wow. Blasey Ford says that Grassley scheduled the public hearing expecting her to testify “at the same table” as Kavan…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@andrewheiss JHC. Gotta go back up EVERYTHING.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheLeadCNN: By reopening the investigation of Vince Foster's suicide Kavanuagh "tormented the Foster family in the most vicious, cruel,…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @VirginiaScharff: Aw, that's so sweet.  Meanwhile Dr. Blasey is in hiding and hiring security for her family. https://t.co/7QlBgJ6alz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KevinMKruse: Why Didn’t She Speak Out Sooner?™️ https://t.co/HpaF87Y6DF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SenatorLeahy: .@RealDonaldTrump just claimed that re-opening Kavanaugh’s official background investigation isn’t something the FBI does…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheRickWilson: So I've had a couple conversations this morning with some former and current IC people. 

The line crossed on this decla…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mikedebonis: King today said visiting Auschwitz  was a “very, very powerful experience” then described wanting to get a “Polish perspec…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KristenClarkeJD: NEW- The Court just issued a final Temporary Restraining Order in our case challenging Georgia’s mass rejection of abs…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ShireenGhorbani: My opponent wants to equivocate on domestic terrorism. These acts are an attack on our institutions and ideals. Full s…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Classical_Ideas: Chicago folks! This is a SUPER opportunity, put on by John Camardella @KnightsofPHS. Definitely go if you can! https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JohnKasich: I gave him every chance, but I've come to the conclusion that @realDonaldTrump is simply incapable of being a unifier or ac…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @emmaogreen: '@jackmjenkins takes a look at Cory Booker's possible presidential run -- and how he could become a symbol of the religious…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ProfIRMF: so, uh, have some work on terrorism in the US and its ties to white nationalists...
https://t.co/rs12SA4APw https://t.co/gYcy…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @janekleeb: Go @JaneRaybould! "The position she occupies lands at a pertinent intersection of agriculture, health care, taxes, trade, im…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @davidfrum: Worth stressing: Gingrich said this at breakfast TODAY https://t.co/bhMpishLyZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @insuregoodlife: ✅ Health coverage for 90,000 hard-working Nebraskans
✅ A stronger economy
✅ 11,000 new jobs
✅ Keep rural hospitals runn…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DavidAstinWalsh: I'm sorry I had to hit you, honey, but you just made me so angry. https://t.co/bvH2ormHUs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @anamariecox: Imagining what the coverage of serial murder attempts on Republican leaders would look like. Imagining what Trump's respon…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ClaraJeffery: The bomber attacked:
two former presidents
two former first ladies
one former Secretary of State
one former US Senator
on…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Sifill_LDF: I don't understand this headline @thehill. Mr. Miller did not "advance." He had a hearing. Democrats did not attend. Neithe…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AndrewGillum: As my grandmother used to say — a hit dog will holler. https://t.co/kC34Ldd0is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drhonor Keep up the word count! Though I'm jealous (it's hard to write anything with a six-week in one hand and two new preps in the other!)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @markmobility: .@FoxNews has to interrupt another important piece on @senatemajldr being harassed at a restaurant for breaking news on b…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JeffFortenberry You have no self awareness. You should resign.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @feliciasonmez: Trump in Wisconsin: "By the way, do you see how nice I'm behaving? ... We’re all behaving very well. And hopefully we ca…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drjmftspeaks @maggieNYT “I believe!”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kaitlancollins: Aides used to joke about the president's multiple phones, calling them "Trump 1" and "Trump 2." NYT now reporting that…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @maggieNYT: Officials take solace that Trump has always been comparatively guarded on the phone and that he doesn’t really dive into sec…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AnandWrites: The people targeted by terrorists today had one thing in common: being targeted by Donald Trump. https://t.co/31mYqbjTJt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DavidJollyFL: Hard to suspend disbelief and not recognize the context that repeated @realDonaldTrump statements like this provide on a…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CharlesPPierce: Profiles In Marshmallow
Thanks for the next 40 years, pal. https://t.co/FHGYaDQRa3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ChrisDunkerLJS: Spent most of the last two days trying to figure out who is paying for the television ad opposing Initiative 427 to exp…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kylegriffin1: The Garland County Election Commission left Susan Inman, the Democratic candidate for secretary of state, off the electio…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @paulkrugman: I'll be curious to see the GOP response to the assassination attempts against Soros, the Clintons, and Obama (because that…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jackmjenkins: CNN anchors now continuing their show from out in the street after evacuating their building, using phones to broadcast t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @maggieNYT: Not really sure the purpose of this media tour. https://t.co/OohDyYkYwX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks, in large measure, to @UNLCivicEngage! https://t.co/qtulVMME0Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @UnionSeminary: Migrant caravans are not new. https://t.co/qr8bMUxgDS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HC_Richardson: This comes straight from Reconstruction, when white southern Ds said black voters were stealing tax dollars. https://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ashava2: Don Bacon did not speak up for civility when Trump led a cheer of “lock her up” regarding Diane Feinstein at a local rally he…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @thehill: Georgia GOP governor candidate caught on tape expressing fear that residents will "exercise their right to vote" https://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cjane87: A reminder that the Stars and Bars were ADDED to the Georgia state flag in 1956. 

I wonder why. https://t.co/Kj0hcC198O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JesseFFerguson: BREAKING from FOX 5 (Georgia) --

"Brian Kemp owes more than $800,000 in insider loans to bank he helped start" 
 
#GAG…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Unexpectedactiv: A reminder that @RepDonBacon @DonJBacon was one of the laughing hyenas in this group. He will NOT protect healthcare.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @kendallwilcox: @sltrib @BenMcAdams @REPmIa What a pathetic abdication of your civic duty @sltrib 
Your Huntsman bias is showing...
@Rep…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DennisPCrawford: @karaforcongress https://t.co/4JMCFUOzeX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @karaforcongress: American politics can be different. We can have civil debates, get money out of politics so that negative ads are not…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LCDP_NE: Vote Jessica McClure for Congress, #Nebraska District 1 ! #LNK #NE01 https://t.co/DhrdsKFljK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ReligPolitics: Howard Divinity Dean @YNPierce reviews the final work of James Cone, the late black liberation theologian. https://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ChrisMurphyCT: Need a ride to the polls on election day? Uber and Lyft will take you there for free. https://t.co/kmBIQU9cjZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jananamirah: So much love &amp; hard work went into making this film. Films like this don’t get made very often. If you’re in Utah, please…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nycsouthpaw: It’s not Republicans vs Democrats. It’s Republicans vs democracy itself. Media should cover this as a conspiracy against A…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RollingStone: New leaked audio offers insight into Georgia Republican Brian Kemp's gubernatorial campaign, which has been plagued by vo…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jbouie: I thought this might have been an exaggeration, but no, Megyn Kelly is really doing a “I don’t see what’s so offensive about bl…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jnpearce: So very sad: https://t.co/HKaoFg0a4Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nprfreshair: 24 states have implemented new voting restrictions disproportionately affecting minorities — ranging from requiring voter…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JLWeisenfeld: Morning shout out to the historians of religion who uncover buried histories, reorient our understandings of familiar his…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JoyAnnReid: Read the whole thread if you care about healthcare. https://t.co/EgZoufwZZy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @peterbakernyt: Trump at Houston rally: "You know what I am? I’m a nationalist, okay? Nationalist. Use that word, use that word."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @matthewamiller: Trump’s midterm campaign strategy is just a full on blitz of lies, and 90% of the press hasn’t figured out how to cover…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @page88: .@JaneMayerNYer : "A meticulous analysis of online activity during the 2016 campaign makes a powerful case that Russia's target…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HailVarsity: "If you can't see we're building something special here, you'll just have to be on the other end of it.”

#Huskers QB Adri…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Alyssa_Milano: This. Is. Everything. 

I cried ugly tears after watching this. Turn up the sound. Pass it on. Vote. 

(Thanks for inclu…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MichaelStanger1: Utah friends, go see this amazing film in theaters! Send a message that there is a place for LDS film that doesn't mak…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey, @Uber. I hope you follow suit. (Actually, I expect it). https://t.co/qtyx09rYsT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey, @PreetBharara. Are we going to see the beard? https://t.co/oPJyqPKvpO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats, @FarinaKing, on the book! https://t.co/mNf1xaAhMg]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>