<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Nevada Democratic Senate Candidate: "Offensive" To Suggest I'm Not Mexican Enough https://t.co/lgufJ7osYQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Son Of Nevada GOP Senate Candidate Made Sexist, Racist Comments On Reddit https://t.co/2zTWj4ORsH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Jr. Claims Children In Europe Are Being Raped By Migrants Daily https://t.co/Iih3VkSkSU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On Campaign Call, Clinton Latino Supporters Air Concerns On Youth Support And Ads https://t.co/4UuyYNfRk3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bobby Knight: I've Been Trying To Get Trump To Settle Down https://t.co/dtsiUvBkO9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Evan McMullin: Trump’s Stop-And-Frisk Proposal Talk A “Cocktail Of Racism” https://t.co/fSuuUeWOky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GOP Rep. Steve King: Congressional Black Caucus Is The "Self-Segregating Caucus" https://t.co/7fnExYSojz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rand Paul: Clinton Should Be Examined For Health Problems Other Than Pneumonia https://t.co/84fInHb23p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Jr: "A Lot In A 12,000-Page Tax Return That Wouldn't Make Sense To Open Up" https://t.co/RK9sAdqvAl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Lewis: Civil Rights Movement Discriminated Against Women Members https://t.co/kpU0WvwXnT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump On Why He Stopped Being A Birther: "We Want To Get On With The Campaign" https://t.co/4RxJr8SCR3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge Who Struck Down Stop-And-Frisk Policy Pushes Back Against Trump https://t.co/1Nfb0p7n5N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump In Crazy 2011 Interview: “I’m Very Proud” To Be A Birther https://t.co/Z6o6esapjy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are You Ready For The Big Debate Immigration Clash Between Trump And Clinton? https://t.co/nJETINGwWG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Appears With Pastor Who Questioned If Obama Was Muslim https://t.co/xtepm7KlSv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christie: Clinton's Comments On Tackling Systemic Racism "A Disgrace" Like Her https://t.co/uQ30QssFZv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Evan McMullin Turns Racist Voicemail From Trump Suppporter Into Campaign Ad https://t.co/tZZMwBFE0r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Vicente Fernandez Came Out Of Retirement To Drop A Corrido For Clinton https://t.co/CArXTDR7fd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RosieGray: .@SenMikeLee on Kaepernick: "that is his right to send that message in whatever way he deems appropriate" but finds approach…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @darrensands: .@CoryBooker doesn't agree with @Kaepernick7's methods, but concerned folks have more to say Kap's protest than #TerenceCr…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chrisgeidner: Here we go! #BuzzFeedBrews returns to DC! https://t.co/kt8KJYOT4Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Latina And Black Operatives Join Clinton Transition Team In Key Roles https://t.co/oYWubRUugC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[13 Times Donald Trump Was Not The First To Campaign In Front Of A Plane https://t.co/Rid8F1YTjy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mike McCaul Goes After Ted Cruz For Not Backing Trump https://t.co/oeDyQPKU3P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bowl Of Skittles Photographer Says He Doesn't Approve Of Trump Jr.'s Tweet https://t.co/VgaJ13PheB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Initiative Looks To Fuel Next Administration's Latino Political Appointments https://t.co/TgETbs0zTk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Carrasquillo: Smart one from @darrensands: What’s The Matter With These Young Voters? Black Democrats Want To Know! https://t.co/FL14Fs…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People Are Pointing Out That Refugees Are Not Skittles After Donald Trump Jr. Posts Meme https://t.co/dBnZVovg1Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What’s The Matter With These Young Voters? Black Democrats Want To Know! https://t.co/0s3Inlzdlw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What’s The Matter With These Young Voters? Black Democrats Want To Know! https://t.co/09FIOBKKOF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Cites Latest Attacks In Renewing Calls For Tougher Immigration Controls https://t.co/RJ5fS0VApb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pro-Trump PAC "Liberty Action Group" Responds To FEC Inquiry Amid Lawsuit https://t.co/LLTiCTFz9f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hillary Clinton Tries To Introduce Herself To Skeptical Young Voters https://t.co/mPsi4MiS0R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anti-Defamation League Boosting Presence In Silicon Valley https://t.co/VWCnw1yulp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Book Pushed Birther Conspiracy Months After He "Finished" Birtherism https://t.co/oRPuPitBR5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Says Police Know Who Terrorists Are, Don't Do Anything Out Of Fear Of Profiling https://t.co/a1bxnctxbr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is The Supreme Court Ever Actually Going To Be An Election Issue? https://t.co/E8h7pIXtFF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Surrogates Are Spreading False Claims To Defend His Birtherism https://t.co/NRqzcHeKkC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RNC Chair Says Candidates Who Don't Back Trump Could Be Punished In The Future https://t.co/EXMIC7j8Vl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama Jokes: "I Am So Relieved That The Birther Thing Is Over" https://t.co/dtIoRwPBiq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clinton: People Have Thrown "Hateful Nonsense" At The Obamas https://t.co/I4Iz7fQY5z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rubycramer: Clinton at #CBC16: People Have Thrown "Hateful Nonsense" At The Obamas https://t.co/T8TQ71yDBi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Says Clinton's Security Detail Should Disarm: "Let's See What Happens To Her" https://t.co/eHZB0UCIT5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why It's So Hard For Trump To Give Up His Birther Crusade https://t.co/PbMYLwXkIJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Latino Voter Registration Efforts With Mexican Rock Band Hit A Snag In Las Vegas https://t.co/eX1zfKOPlR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Black Lawmakers Say Trump's Birther Issue Fueled His Candidacy https://t.co/OpySbTWmg5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democratic Senator Blasts Clinton Over "Basket Of Deporables" Remark https://t.co/cFzP7OSGr7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump Executes Very Trumpy Media Stunt https://t.co/y3SVfKTwmv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @rubycramer: Three Lies About Birtherism To Look Out For In Donald Trump’s Speech  https://t.co/H835nuRV6J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Said In 2015 And 2016 He Didn't Know If Obama Birth Certificate Was Real https://t.co/RHWwnEDnih]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Questioned Obama Birth Certificate In 2014, Despite Campaign Statement https://t.co/kCJySte54F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Donald Trump Let Jimmy Fallon Mess With His Hair https://t.co/Fo2RBPyvVc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clinton Turns Back The Focus To Charges Of Trump Racism In Speech To Latinos https://t.co/wUxJMRd8ks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Refuses To Say Obama Was Born In The US https://t.co/aNBS1Adu8O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hillary Clinton Won't Say When She Disclosed Pneumonia To Running Mate https://t.co/0m4ETNRuN0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alabama Sets Execution Dates For Two Inmates For Later This Year https://t.co/1iY4EJ1rvr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ivanka Trump Responds After Cutting Off Interview With "Cosmopolitan" https://t.co/F5iN88TZSL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hillary Clinton Returns To The Campaign Trail After Illness https://t.co/p84m4leP1d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clinton Aims To Use DREAMer Program Model To Get Florida Puerto Ricans Out To Vote https://t.co/u4GusXYQ5u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aide Shuts Down Local TV Interview With Trump Jr. When Charity Issue Is Raised https://t.co/OCGqAViRSj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mike Pence: Trump Accepts Obama Was Born In US https://t.co/pmsRV4y62u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Jr.: Media Would Be "Warming Up The Gas Chamber" If GOP Did What Hillary Did https://t.co/GJ2ATyZ0Xt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Poll: Hillary Clinton Still Struggling To Win Over Young Voters https://t.co/XM2WU39MiK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Bill Clinton's Voters Wouldn't Vote For Him Today, As Told By Bill Clinton https://t.co/BwwkBkJ2KO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Questions Clinton's Physical Stamina After Pneumonia Diagnosis https://t.co/yDgpJgFLWr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hillary Clinton Releases Additional Information About Her Health https://t.co/4ioMvJHwnV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Pastor Shut Down Trump When He Tried To Bash Clinton At A Church https://t.co/lcQ3oq1N6V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Campaign Co-Chair: "We Will Have A Lot Of Self-Deportation" In First Term https://t.co/9HIvnRRP1w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RNC Chair: Clinton "Cold-Hearted" And "Cruel" For "Deplorables" Comment https://t.co/cqjCSDOgru]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rice: If Rumsfeld, Pentagon Had Done Their Job, Iraq Might Have Turned Out Different https://t.co/88IORnUAyx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New York Attorney General Opens Investigation Into Donald J. Trump Foundation https://t.co/xo0qE95F3H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lawyers For Transgender Student Ask Supreme Court Not To Take Case On Anti-Trans School Policy https://t.co/8pRR6BsMuv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Libertarian Gary Johnson Makes Presidential Ballot In All 50 States https://t.co/veXChxqSFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Supporters Say Both Candidates Should Release Their Medical Records https://t.co/ew2wcHFfFv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chelsea Manning Told She Will Receive Gender Transition Surgery, Her Lawyer Says https://t.co/AalQ5WwV3G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats Worried Young Latinos Are Cool To Clinton Ahead Of Key Stretch https://t.co/WWdenOcsmm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Founder Of "Black Men For Bernie" Launching Pro-Trump Effort https://t.co/Qo1Igz7SVA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @katherinemiller: Would pneumonia have been shared if not for video? Longtime Clinton ally: “Never. Never ever, ever, ever."  https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @katherinemiller: Notably: Not including USSS, Hillary Clinton's traveling party is actually smaller than Tim Kaine's. https://t.co/PYPq…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @darrensands: The founder of Black Men for Bernie is launching a pro-Trump effort to get black voters behind him. My story: https://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Jr. In 2014 Praised His Dad's "Moral Conviction" On Obama Birtherism https://t.co/rrsBm3E9vx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supreme Court Denies Request To Restore "Golden Week" In Ohio https://t.co/fHozfQWMsF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pneumonia Episode Highlights The Protective “Cocoon” Around Clinton https://t.co/4S9SOGQOes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It’s Not Clear Which Abortion Ban Exceptions Mike Pence Supports https://t.co/otjNmD2Raz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republicans Privately Panic At "Terrifying" Prospect Of Trump Win https://t.co/tgYgeCE3GO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Supporters Fire Back At Clinton Over "Basket Of Deplorables" Label https://t.co/ptsQHCD86K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RNC Chair: Reasonable For People To Not Accept Clinton's Health Explanation https://t.co/882FYHIJZ7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David Duke: "Good To See" Mike Pence Reject Media's Game https://t.co/fyGBSE4Kqq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mike Pence Refuses To Call Former KKK Leader "Deplorable" https://t.co/Xv09X84s3t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[GOP Congressman: Something Else "Is Plaguing" Clinton Beyond Pneumonia https://t.co/7HZ5Fjjuqx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Former Top Bush Official, World Bank President Says Trump Is “A Dangerous Man” https://t.co/VLkX1Odf1L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Veterans For Trump" Co-Chair Claims Clinton Has Parkinson's Disease https://t.co/NPgp4dMxLD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Rise And Fall Of Trump's Hispanic Advisory Council https://t.co/m9neGO8au2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Calls On Clinton To Drop Out For Not Retracting "Deplorables" Comment https://t.co/0cW7kqdail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Pushed For US Action In Iran, Libya In 2011 Fox News Appearances https://t.co/LT4LFSKTJ6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alabama Congressman: I Have "Serious Doubts" As To Whether Clinton Has Pneumonia https://t.co/znwTm9PCxR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ben Carson: Clinton Should Release Specialized MRI https://t.co/PciSWHfAJa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump In 2011: "When Obama Gets 95% Of The Black Vote, Is That Racist?" https://t.co/H82FbqgyJq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump Says He'll Release His Physical Results https://t.co/MaFyn8Kim8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RosieGray: icymi, my profile of Sean Hannity may make a good Sunday night read https://t.co/3j1blLjesS]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>