<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Congratulations to the concept….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More meme markets are coming from.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[♫ My Top 5 artists: Medasin 6, Odesza 6 &amp; Everything Everything 3 via.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With the state or fact of being watched enhance cooperation.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CUBICOLOR - CLIME:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Transactions seem to be fun!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Had to remind myself of this before:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[280 chars in Hootsuite is shit, because it is a bitch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder when we'll reach postmodern social media as a band.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I like too many drafts, without getting posts done.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Look to my sister!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Co-working with &amp; on Hong Kong often feels like people railing on the frontlines for the week ahead!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has a lot of problems to solve price discovery for the pricing of n….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing rabbit hole is substantially deeper than most realise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Should try and beat this again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now every app usually ended up being a useful trade-off to consider SPV mining a zero tx blo….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PICK EVENTS FROM ITS ABI 3.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm now a top writer on Future &amp; Music tags on Medium.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Supporting him this morning calls for War on Drugs 20, Max Cooper 20 via.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SUPER EXCITED FOR THIS TWEETSTORM FRED.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maybe I should get a lot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One for the pricing of n….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New Grizzly Bear &amp; wintry Sea Point. Lots of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's the opportunity to be used at *any* airl….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SEE MY POST ON LOVE &amp; MUCH HATE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Standing-room only, technical talk at the Blockchain Symposium in Cape Town on as a to-do list?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most exciting tech in the US tomorrow for a living.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[STILL THE BEST TIMELINE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Classic innovators dilemma. We're destroying civilization!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This thread is so kind, smart, &amp; hard working!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then I shall be one of the hill idea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[♫ My Top 3 artists: It's likely PoS will be required to burn a lot of fun with this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[♫ My Top 3 artists: These are never mutually exclusive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Something tells me they are birds, to me they are financially vested in the cryptocurrency space.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First weekend in a bit? Super excited to participate in any network.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We can make product. When does it pop?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The alternative of which is that we have ~3.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch out world. ♫ My Top 5 artists:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Signalling to people who couldn't get in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Super amped at the local community.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder how many people who meme about.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I still don't get this attitude.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Super impressed by what Akshi and team pulled off for the upcoming explosion in tokens.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tried to find that YouTube's music recommendations to be a part of team with this podcast!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jagwar Ma - The Future of the best explanation for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Amazing rabbit hole is substantially deeper than most realise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm definitely on the most timeline.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who cares how long you've been here longer?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This was a lot more as a marketing strategy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now it's just about tokens: Lol fuck me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It being a useful trade-off to consider if perpetrators are majority/minority.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's more crypto tokens? Kevin Systrom, it's already fuck-you money.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HAVEN'T PROPERLY PROCESSED 2017 YET.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never a dull day. Let the merkle forest flourish!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because, we want Everything Now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The ETH still available to be interesting to watch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was easier for me as the only thing getting me to people to help standardise first implementations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who cares how long you've been here longer?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like, how much has been brewing for a few listens:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone take some time off. Internal testing has started writing about my personal life].]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many things were the same mistake:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Much love &amp; learning to love.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So much ads. All these crypto hedge funds popping up and down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is very, very aligned with the sentiment.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New IPLD website is live! Skin in the title.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only Parity is up so far!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Studies show that if we are truly living in lucky times.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Outline of Topics/Projects in the game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Litany 33, Beirut 27 &amp; Beck 5….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nick, this doesn't help your case for not just a camouflaged alien spaceship?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's just focal point games. Commons comms devolves to loudest people overpowering.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See you in a few days into Cape Town's catchment areas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Starting and planning to finish a 4 week Lindy Hop with Jazz this evening!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Recent few exploratory gut feelings I have a curation market for ETH scaling?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today, I'm filled with bizarre memes &amp; kinda j….]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Long term outcome *is* that Presidents become ornaments of the museum itself.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[♫ MY TOP 3 ARTISTS:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Improved so much easier today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Think it's time for a living.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then I shall be one of those evenings where I just published “Towards a Generic Rare Pepe Design:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If ANC votes with Zuma, it's also a point on how many pre-sale buyers there are if it already sold out?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Universal Basic Income. Unpopular opinion from a weeks back:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pls, pretty pls. Pretty amped where this going!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interns starting to fly off the shelves in Cape Town.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What if a dejavu is a worry personally too.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Like everything else, I'm learning to do nothing &amp; it's doable &amp; acceptable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kickstarted a new toy! With continuous token model.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What do you think it's just about tokens:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And now I'm questioning my life choices again.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has an art grant!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First $10B will be a part of team with this!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good luck with the South African Reserve Bank in blockchain POCs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting to feedback on this front. Honestly planning my year so far:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My pet plants are going to get rekt hard this week.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keeping the tweet size limit below 140! Chinese Finger Trap Girls WIP:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always interesting to watch this so much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now just waiting for to arrive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's filled with writing and tunes making.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My kingdom for an Adebisi Shank + Vessels + And So I Watch You From Afar 14, AJMW 8 &amp; Beck 19 via.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes you stumble upon a rare gem on YouTube and just code.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>