<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Work expands so as to fill the time available for its completion. Cyril Northcote Parkinson/Parkinson's Law.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju While You Were Offline: Boycott McDonald's! Boycott Hawaii! Hell, Boycott Eve.. #technology #geek https://t.co/ZeLRvgaJ3Q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Man livestreaming on Facebook fatally shot by Tennessee deputies - KETV Omaha #facebook #internet https://t.co/mij08jr1Iq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju What Is the Internet of Things? -- The Motley Fool - Motley Fool #internet #web https://t.co/ccuznkMVRv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju After Chuck Berry's Death, Bruce Springsteen, Ringo Star and Other Legends Pay Tr.. #entrepreneur https://t.co/S6EBLzLgHu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Buccaneers sign veteran competition for second-round kicker Roberto Aguayo - CBSSp.. #competition https://t.co/7rZyNG41eh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Unilever prepares 6 billion pound sale of food brands: newspapers - Reuters #branding #brands https://t.co/nfjM494DUv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Incorporated Built an Incredible World. Then Syfy Nuked It #technology #geek https://t.co/7oGHfNNqHY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Facebook is so thirsty for comments it created a new pop-up window - Mashable #facebook #internet https://t.co/CTIFf5LTli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[”Talent is formed in solitude, character in the bustle of the world.”- Johann Wolfgang von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Apollo Box is applying AR to drive lifestyle ecommerce - TechCrunch #ecommerce #tech https://t.co/amyOvqvzjH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Katonah sex offender had just gotten off Internet ban - The Journal News | LoHud.. #internet #web https://t.co/HvS1xXw46G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju 4 Secrets to Building Your Own Empire #entrepreneur https://t.co/1KqAVm6tJL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Trevin Kennedy participates in SAEA Quiz Bowl competition - Bureau County Republican #competition https://t.co/dc7N3PdmlD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Google Vows More Control for Brands Over Online Ads - Wall Street Journal (su.. #branding #brands https://t.co/0xkKtp0keQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most of the important things in the world have been accomplished by people who have kept on trying when there seemed to ….. Dale Carnegie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju The Stream Dream #technology #geek https://t.co/RPg1Zx50wP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Facebook's new features like Messenger Day are distracting and obtrusive - .. #facebook #internet https://t.co/pUSK0PqzAc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Deeds not Words" via Bernord Hor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju eCommerce Merchandiser - Charlotte Agenda #ecommerce #tech https://t.co/GJt3LHuQQa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju This is what life was like before the internet - The indy100 #internet #web https://t.co/ypqbJclyrH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Why You Shouldn't Confuse Comfort With Safety #entrepreneur https://t.co/f8ll4jegZz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Social Commerce Innovators 'Btab' Seek To Raise $100 Million To Support New Ent.. #socialcommerce https://t.co/ZSmWy0ZCcN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Drone company wins $1M grand prize in Genius NY business competition in Syracuse -.. #competition https://t.co/wWDtrhtarx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Seattle education technology company Ravenna Solutions acquired by Education .. #branding #brands https://t.co/y3N9NHOEV7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Gold Company Manager Charged in Vast Peruvian Smuggling Plot - Bloomberg #manager #leader https://t.co/Zs9DJbrVo8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A budget tells us what we can't afford, but it doesn't keep us from buying it. William Feather]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju That Deleted McDonald's Tweet? Too Surreal, Even For Fast-Food Twitter #technology #geek https://t.co/gZlOKWGqTi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Facebook is the only thing standing between us and a face-reading nightmare.. #facebook #internet https://t.co/pCpaTzsJU2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many great ideas go unexecuted, and many great executioners are without ideas. One without the other is worthless.- Tim Blixseth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju 6 Mistakes Your Ecommerce Store Must Avoid - Entrepreneur #ecommerce #tech https://t.co/ZcQfZ3HytJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju 7 tips for lowering your internet bill - MarketWatch #internet #web https://t.co/7kiQd6BLA9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Why Some Prices Are More Right Than Others #entrepreneur https://t.co/qXUyrPCbxk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Are Missionaries Decent to Do Social Commerce? - China Christian Daily #socialcommerce https://t.co/ycg19kOUk0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Gorham Savings taking applications for LaunchPad competition - Press Herald #competition https://t.co/u1Zjju88YC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Pentland Brands Takes Majority Stake in SeaVees - Footwear News #branding #brands https://t.co/pWLwRQFoOq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you don’t know what to do with many of the papers piled on your desk, stick a dozen colleagues initials….Malcolm S. Forbes quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju The social commerce revolution is coming. Is your brand ready to mobilise? #socialcommerce https://t.co/qAadWu2RMf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju A Robot Ear Surgeon Drills Into the Future of Medicine #technology #geek https://t.co/j9Z1YfTc2v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju This new app can identify total strangers and Facebook isn't happy - The Bo.. #facebook #internet https://t.co/q3G5mN1i63]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The problem with the rat race is that even if you win, you're still a rat. Lilly Tomlin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju REFILE-China e-commerce confusion catches Australian retailers on the hop - Na.. #ecommerce #tech https://t.co/QoGWZ7PMnw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju China Is Tightening Control Over The Internet To Stop New Threats Against Its Ru.. #internet #web https://t.co/3gRGWo04XQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju 9 Revolutionary Companies to Watch #entrepreneur https://t.co/xcHtDBfXxh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Ways Competition Makes Your Business Stronger - ValueWalk #competition https://t.co/VJnJnk0SUT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju China's Name-and-Shame TV Show Puts Household Brands on Edge - Bloomberg #branding #brands https://t.co/WO86gnqyq4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The only place where success comes before work is in the dictionary." Vidal Sassoon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju The incredible growth of the internet over the past five years – explained in d.. #socialcommerce https://t.co/GkRYkMFLgW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Intel's 15 Billion Reasons Why an AI Chip Revolution Has Arrived #technology #geek https://t.co/B1hqqnr2d8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Facebook will not let anyone use its data to spy on you - BGR #facebook #internet https://t.co/talEL6I7N7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“You gain strength, courage and confidence by every experience in which you stop to look fear in the face.”- Eleanor Roosevelt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju This S'porean Is Breathing New Life Into Her Family's 95-Year-Old Bookstore Wi.. #ecommerce #tech https://t.co/npW1BvUJKx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju How to live a fulfilling life on the internet - The Week Magazine #internet #web https://t.co/apzqL22uie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju 7 Tips for a Stellar Company Retreat #entrepreneur https://t.co/cj70tlkHRx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Brands, Listen Up: Influencers Striking a Pose is the New Normal - Adweek #branding #brands https://t.co/WBXcAdwVmA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“When I hear somebody sigh, ‘Life is hard,’ I am always tempted to ask, ‘Compared to what?’”- Sydney Harris]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju We Are Social's Monday Mashup #345 #socialcommerce https://t.co/3HyXPsr0e9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju No, Microwave Ovens Cannot Spy on You—for Lots of Reasons #technology #geek https://t.co/HwmPcEMivv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Facebook tells developers not use data for surveillance - TechCrunch #facebook #internet https://t.co/VcH24y4iSq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eagles soar, but weasels don't get sucked into jet engines.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Ecommerce in the Nordics was worth 21.9 billion euros in 2016 - Ecommerce News #ecommerce #tech https://t.co/Ml5RRIv5Vk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Why Facebook tracks internet outages around the world - Mar. 12 ... - CNNMoney #internet #web https://t.co/P7Sta4Xf9d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Fixing the ROI Problem with Influencer Marketing #entrepreneur https://t.co/hAsG0DwCNr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju 4 Keys to Creating Cause Marketing That Benefits Both Brands and Nonprofits -.. #branding #brands https://t.co/cNP6rrN5Wv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The road to success and the road to failure are almost exactly the same." Colin R. Davis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju We Are Social's Tuesday Tweakup #29 #socialcommerce https://t.co/j31fNiyPmA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Facebook Messenger's Plot to Be the Only App You Ever Need #technology #geek https://t.co/OSpr89d6FI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju A Murder Posted on Facebook Prompts Outrage and Questions Over Responsibili.. #facebook #internet https://t.co/RiLPqu97qW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are two ways to face the future. One way is with apprehension; the other is with anticipation. Jim Rohn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju SATS' new 'Airhub' to triple e-commerce capacity at Changi - Air Cargo World (.. #ecommerce #tech https://t.co/lWgJJutzyq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Lawmaker: Using the internet is a choice - WTSP 10 News #internet #web https://t.co/B9HtIokcLm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju You Are Your Best Investment #entrepreneur https://t.co/7E8FZQafpE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Constellation Brands Is a 'Best in Class' Growth Star - Barron's #branding #brands https://t.co/82okTDzZ38]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Failure is the condiment that gives success its flavor. - Truman Capote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Let's Model Radioactive Decay to Show How Carbon Dating Works #technology #geek https://t.co/d5qM1seK2z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Police cast wide net in search for suspect in Cleveland Facebook killing - .. #facebook #internet https://t.co/RNYWH6gyaN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Fall down seven times, get up eight times" – Japanese proverb via Tina MiModels]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Donald Trump's Multi-Pronged Attack on the Internet - New York Times #internet #web https://t.co/TunRdSZ7rl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Why CEOs Need to Embrace Social Media (and How to Do it) #entrepreneur https://t.co/Ho4rpBFBTV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Boutique gin and whisky boom spooks big spirit brands - The Guardian #branding #brands https://t.co/nSrIHtvqMC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Granada manager Tony Adams puts on brave face after defeat - Daily Mail #manager #leader https://t.co/3ilepbDJIy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She should go far. The sooner she starts, the better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Hack Your Pearly Whites With These High-Tech Toothbrushes #technology #geek https://t.co/FRmsukRzwM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Facebook's new features like Messenger Day are distracting and obtrusive - .. #facebook #internet https://t.co/bZMlDxx3wT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Congressman tells constituents that nobody has 'got to use the internet' - Sacra.. #internet #web https://t.co/Gmj3wW2EsI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju 5 Essential Steps to a Great Job #entrepreneur https://t.co/wZ8n9SUGdp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju THS BPA students do well at state competition - Tallmadge Express #competition https://t.co/B6ZzQ8Tdtk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Stop Asking Brands To Give You Free Stuff For Retweets - Huffington Post #branding #brands https://t.co/Xl5cdMbf2j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Tony Adams gets down to business as Granada manager with some hilarious traini.. #manager #leader https://t.co/nvn7s80wyv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Security News This Week: Nasty Microsoft Word 'Booby Trap' Loaded PCs With Ma.. #technology #geek https://t.co/2enYjYVWe5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Facebook knocks down massive spammer network - CNET #facebook #internet https://t.co/K3fdjAb5kP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The harder you fall, the higher you bounce. Unkown Quotes Author]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Washington state House committee approves internet privacy ... - The Seattle Times #internet #web https://t.co/7SZcMEHgW1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Tell Your Startup's Story and Captivate Your Audience. Here's How. #entrepreneur https://t.co/5WOONvc6QP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju One broadband choice counts as "competition" in new FCC proposal - Ars Technica #competition https://t.co/qMu8lUfnL8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Wellmann's Brands is going big - https://t.co/79wmCW3a2d #branding #brands https://t.co/A8xGdv3c6a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make sure you have a vice president in charge of your revolution, to engender .…………….. David Ogilvy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Fear Not, Superfans: Netflix's Mystery Science Theater 3000 Reboot Nails It #technology #geek https://t.co/Lb9AhlLeH6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[sharing #suaju Facebook ramps up efforts to quash fake accounts - USA TODAY #facebook #internet https://t.co/DYaEDeNbpG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Capital isn't scarce; vision is." Sam Walton]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>