<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA["Nothing will ever be attempted if all #possible objections must first be overcome." ~ Samuel Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Some #training days u don't feel like u have it, but u still do it, which means u got it.” via @ncjack]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In dreams and in #love there are no impossibilities. -Janos Arany]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In every walk with nature one receives far more than he seeks. ~ John Muir ---&gt; experience your #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Kind words can be short and easy to speak, but their echoes are truly endless.”
― Mother Teresa via @CharityIdeas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Courage is the discovery that you may not win, and trying when you know you can lose.~ Tom Krause]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope that I may always desire more than I can accomplish. Michelangelo #determination]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am fine but am in search for the Doctor who has a solution other than 'Don't run for 60 days' ~ Macon on getting injured” via @RunToWin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I hope to die in the saddle seat. ~Albert Ellis #run #live]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love recognizes no barriers. It jumps hurdles, leaps fences, penetrates walls to arrive at it destination full of hope. Maya Angelou #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“The race is not always to the swift... but to those who keep on #running” via @TheTrailJogger]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["One mile at a time" #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your #fears are not walls, but hurdles. - Millman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Each of us has a fire in our hearts for something. It's our goal in life to find it #reach #change #passion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret of Running is......Running via @runaddicted]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Some #hearts do not need speed training, they were just simply made to give life everything" RQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will #persist without exception. ~Andy Andrews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To #live is the rarest thing in the world. Most people exist, that’s all.~Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["#Dreamers are not people disconnected from reality. Dreamers are people fully connected to reality's potential.” via @AffirmationSpot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If everything seems under control, you're just not going fast enough." ~ Mario Andretti #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["My 1st thought on my birthday 'One more year until I move into another age group!' I guess I'm a #runner." -- Karen Austin via @RunToWin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Without #ambition one starts nothing. Without work one finishes nothing. via @Kcancer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People ask, "But what if #positive thinking doesn't work?" Better to ask, "What if negative thinking does?" via @AffirmationSpot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never stop dreaming, ever!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You were never created to reach a certain level and then plateau. You were created to #excel.” via @coacheye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["It's not what you are that holds you back, it's what you think you are not." - Denis Waitley #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Find the fire in you, find what excites you, find your inner #passion AND go for it!" #run #give]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Run happy, Run strong, Run free]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I believe in #can. I believe in #do. I believe in #dreams. I believe in the #impossible.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He #can who thinks he can, and he can't who thinks he can't. This is an inexorable, indisputable law. ~Pablo Picasso]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["When you have the enthusiasm and the #passion, you end up figuring how to excel." Deena Kastor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whatever you want to do, do it now. There are only so many tomorrows. ~Michael Landon #life #live #love #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I run because they said I couldn't #Motivation @RunningQuotes via @elliall]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I run to find emotional healing #whywerun via @shanda_lynn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I run because I can prove my willpower with each step.  #whywerun via @marcdasharc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I run because I can't possibly think of a good reason NOT to! #whywerun via @soschlongltsrgt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I run because I CAN! #whywerun via @jimmykinney1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I run to prove that I can. #whywerun via @chicagolandrun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I run because I really like dessert! #whywerun :) via @bethinmadcity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I run because people have told me I am too big to run #whywerun via @bigluto]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I run because I can't fly #whywerun via @dontslowdownyet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I run to see how far I can push myself. #whywerun via @abkills]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I run because it is one of the greatest feelings in the world. #WhyWeRun via @_benzino]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#whywerun i run to breathe, i run to release stress via @_just_jayr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I run because running helps me give back to others #whywerun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love running because when I run I feel free.  #whywerun via @magas_larock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I run for the love of running #whywerun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Nothing matters except life and the love you make" — Coldplay #run #love #life #live]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["People moving all the time inside a perfectly straight line. Don't you wanna just curve away? When it's such a perfect day." Coldplay #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["if you never #try, you never know, just what you're worth" — Coldplay]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“I have learned to use the word #impossible with the greatest caution.” - Wernher von Braun]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[But I know no matter how fast we are #running..Somehow we keep..Somehow we keep up with each other." — Dave Matthews Band]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["if you give, you begin to live." — Dave Matthews Band #charity #runners]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["If you're going to make it, your desire for your #dreams has to be greater than your fear of failure." via @JoshCox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["A runner must #run with dreams in his heart." - Emil Zatopek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is short, surround yourself with kind people. via @CharityIdeas #run #friends #charity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["#Goals are not only absolutely necessary to motivate us. They are essential to really keep us alive." -Robert Schuller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Never underestimate the miles you run, and the people you run them with. -- via @runtowin #friends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Take what you can from your #dreams Make them real as anything, It takes the work out of the courage" Dave Matthews Band]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only thing you can't teach in life is passion]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Fast girls have better times" -- #running shirt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“No matter how slow you are...you're still lapping everyone on the couch.” via @411Fit #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whether you come in first, in the middle of the pack, or last. You can say, 'I have #finished' There is a lot of satisfaction in that~Lebow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I believe the most important single thing, beyond discipline &amp; creativity is daring to #dare. -Maya Angelou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Train where your fitness is NOW, not where you want to be.”~ Scott Jurek #ultra #marathon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["The greatest achievement is to outperform yourself." -Denis Waitley #running #marathon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So, what's your excuse? #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["We all have different paths to the start, but what is important is to start" #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winners, imagine their #dreams 1st. They want it with all their heart &amp; expect it to come true. There's no other way to live ~Joe Montana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to run, run a mile. If you want to experience a different life, #run a #marathon. Emil Zatopek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is meant to be lived, live it! Body is meant to be used, use it! #run #truth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get out there]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Life is short, live it. Love is rare,grab it. Anger is bad, dump it. Fear is awful, face it. Memories are sweet, cherish it via @freakyfact]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The one that finds a way will win in #life and the #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["You can't wait for inspiration. You have to go after it with a club." ~Jack London #charity #run #giveback]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The gun goes off and everything changes... the world changes... and nothing else really matters. ~ Patti Sue Plummer #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Most people would rather be certain they're miserable, than risk being happy." - Robert Anthony #change #run #happy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Favorite sign at #RnRLV "Nut up, Princess." Really helped last miles via @CGIprguy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Does 24 hours in a day control you or do you control the 24 hours in a day #getyourrunin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The trouble is, if you don't #risk anything, you risk even more. -Erica Jong]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Each one of us has a fire in our #heart for something. It's our goal in #life to find it &amp; to keep it." Retton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Because there's no way you're not crossing the finish line. It's a misery that non-runners don't understand~ Costello #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the #love]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do the work. Do the analysis. But feel your run. Feel your race. Feel the #joy that is #running.~Kara Goucher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can't imagine living and not #running ~Paula Radcliffe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only passions, great #passions, can elevate the soul to great things. -Denis Diderot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your purpose in #life is to find your purpose &amp; give your whole heart and soul to it. ~Buddha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to do it because I want to do it.~ Amelia Earhart #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adventure is worthwhile in itself.~Amelia Earhart #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Never interrupt someone doing what you said couldn't be done."-Amelia Earhart #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most people have the will to #win, few have the will to prepare to win. -Bobby Knight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["To get through the hardest #journey we need take only one step at a time, but we must keep on stepping"~Chinese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Patience, persistence and perspiration make an unbeatable combination for success. ~ Napoleon Hill #run]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Run, live, change, train, focus, help, care, laugh, friends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Remember, your worst #run is always 100% better than the person who never tries." via @JoshCox]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We all have #possibilities we don't know about. We can do things we don't even dream we can do. ~ Dale Carnegie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Run after your #dreams, you don't have to accept mediocrity, you can have the stars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't #run away from what you really want]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being the underdog just gives #you something to work for. ~ via @iheartquotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Others can help, but you need to be the one that says "let's go" #run]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>