<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[@CuriosityLiquid would this only be suitable for beginners?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@arielhelwani @offtheball nice one, just listened, you forgot to mention Joseph duffy was irish though :p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@metalmanbrewing this glass needs metalman in it! #comeoncans http://t.co/t5rVPWznoB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kenearlys oh yeah, will do. Didnt think you guys liked it that much]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@kenearlys hello ken, love the diego torres book and ibras. I felt they were kind of similar. Any more books like these?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BierhausCork does she come with the beer?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CapitalBrewers @beerwhiskeyIRE @8degreesbrewing @whitehagbrewery i just kayne wested that didn't I, enigma is great too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CapitalBrewers @beerwhiskeyIRE @8degreesbrewing @whitehagbrewery on my second one and 3 other @CapitalBrewers with me agree its fantastic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CapitalBrewers @beerwhiskeyIRE @8degreesbrewing @whitehagbrewery coffee infused chocolate milk stout beats its though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beerwhiskeyIRE tense atmosphere http://t.co/nYuZznD9LK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@MacIvorsCider @BeoirFinder @beerwhiskeyIRE @majakristek have you had your dose of macivors yet today?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MacIvorsCider: @adamski8 @BeoirFinder @beerwhiskeyIRE #pieman a star as always. Chilli beef and #macivorsdry goin' down as we speak!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@whitehagbrewery #blackboar is awesome and neil at the bar cuts a mean pizza]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beerwhiskeyIRE @MacIvorsCider any winners yet?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BeoirFinder @beerwhiskeyIRE food at #pieman is must too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @majakristek: Favourites at @beerwhiskeyIRE today: @whitehagbrewery chocolate oatmeal stout and @8degreesbrewing Enigma! Ready for more …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @flightradar24: Friday 17.00 -&gt; 19.00 UTC is the time of the week when most flights can be tracked on Flightradar24. Normally 11-12k htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @whitehagbrewery: We're gonna have a very special Black Boar porter cake in the RDS! Only RT's get a slice... http://t.co/PmkotqckwU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SMSPopDown: Ready for the weekend? RT&amp;Follow for a chance to win dinner for 2 in our #SexyBooth tonight! http://t.co/qhEMyasmnI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @publinie: RT to win a pair of tickets to Irish beer and whiskey fest in RDS which starts today. http://t.co/gOpqTeFjNS http://t.co/wTw6…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BeoirFinder: The Irish Beer &amp; Whiskey Fest kicks off today!
RT and follow for a chance to win 2 passes. http://t.co/ar0mpX9MCd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LovelyDubley: Love beer and whiskey? We have 2 tickets for the @beerwhiskeyIRE this weekend! Retweet this for a chance to win! http://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @publinie: RT to win a pair of tickets to Irish beer and whiskey fest in RDS which starts tomorrow. http://t.co/zZo8O1dU4C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @clevermanbeer: The wait is over...Clever Man Atractor Beer can now be found in Simon Lambert &amp; Sons Pub &amp; Brewery in… https://t.co/bmbG…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @beerwhiskeyIRE: COMPETITION @LongMeadowCider have a mixed case of medium and sweet cider up for grabs. Simply RT to win! Cheers http://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @martinsfairview: To celebrate our  website going mobile we are give away FREE tickets to this weeks @beerwhiskeyIRE Simply RT to be in …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @clevermanbeer: Exciting Day for Clever Man Beer. Our Atractor Beer can now be found in @PettittsSuperV St.Aidans #wexford#cleverman htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LovelyDubley: Love beer and whiskey? We have 2 tickets for the @beerwhiskeyIRE this weekend! Retweet this for a chance to win! http://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BaggotStWines: RT to enter! #Win a pair of tickets to this weekend's @beerwhiskeyIRE: 5 days, 100+ #craftbeer &amp; 20+ #whiskey http://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @beerwhiskeyIRE: @MacIvorsCider have given us a case of cider and a branded glass to give away. Simply retweet to be in with a chance of…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @beerwhiskeyIRE: @BlackDonkeyBeer are giving a bottle of award winning"Sheep Stealer",USB flash drive/bottle opener and glass RT 2 WIN h…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Miro_zlikovski i haven't been able to get my hands on some yet, sold out. Ill keep looking though]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HomebrewClubIrl @AlfieByrnes @majakristek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stewarding at The final table #BOS @HomebrewClubIrl @AlfieByrnes http://t.co/tC9g3UHKFP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @majakristek: Judging beer in progress. Tough job! Stewarding with @adamski8 and @brk3 @HomebrewClubIrl @AlfieByrnes http://t.co/PPumRXk…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrownPaperBagP @LMulliganGrocer sweet, any of that gose knocking about?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BrownPaperBagP so where the fuck can i buy this shit?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brk3 @drinkstore yeah i cant see anything!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@galwaybeer none on @againstgraindub any in @AlfieByrnes for the comp tomorrow?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@irishbeersnob @TasteTheBrew  @StMelsBrewing whats the story there wayne, is it open late? Cost anything?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Miro_zlikovski i could but im not sure when ill be back over, you planning a trip to eire soon?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@irishbeersnob @BrewDock any price?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@irishbeersnob @BrewDock but i think they said the other bars tomorrow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@galwaybeer draught tomorrow in ATG???]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@irishbeersnob ao whats the story, will it be on draft in all their pubs tomorrow or is it just bottles? Ill be in ATG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cara_eire hey you, when will your beers be flowing @SLambertSons i want some!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@8degreesbrewing @majakristek @Boojum_Dublin @MacIvorsCider the night was complete with some full irish]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SLambertSons @cara_eire beat of luck guys, i know there will be great brews coming from ye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@majakristek @Boojum_Dublin always goes well with @8degreesbrewing @MacIvorsCider http://t.co/rHpKMlWTrM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Food and drink in ample supply @SeanMoncrieff @AlltechBrews http://t.co/PSrIl1I9VK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IBDHQ are you still accepting distance learning candidates for 2015 diploma in brewing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@irishbeersnob @MrsBeerSnob @Pmacspub @TodayFMSunday @missflannery rewarding your drinking with drinks, classic!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SportsJOEdotie: **WIN** We have a €200 Apple Store voucher up for grabs. To be in with a chance of winning just RT &amp; follow! http://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Caught @majakristek  tweeting about @RascalsBrewing new Kiwi Pale Ale and @onthebackpage pizza! Tasty stuff]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @againstgraindub: Nearly 4k followersTo Celebrate when we hit 4k some lucky follower wins this full of @galwaybeer  RT  and Win !! http:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@onthebackpage is your pizza and pint deal on everyday?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[17 Things Everyone Must Eat In Dublin http://t.co/gHiEDBCNCb @majakristek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@RascalsBrewing: NEWSFLASH! We are launching our brand new beer in @onthebackpage next Thursday the 19th! More info to come!!"@majakristek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BeoirFinder: In case you missed last night. Beoir's Beer of the Year went to http://t.co/bPGiEQTE4M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BeoirOrg @8degreesbrewing congrats to the full irish, it got my number 1 vote]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Doing the Bermondsey beer mile today! 6 breweries and 5 hours to do it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thelinden ok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @IrishTimes: First pub dedicated to craft beer to open next week in Dublin http://t.co/JU36g3DTu0 via @IrishTimesBiz http://t.co/xqSmn4D…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@PouringInDublin @Oblivious_ @McHughsBeers @WWolfBrewery @majakristek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ufc: RT if you're w/ Mirko Cro Cop in his rematch against Gonzaga this Saturday at #UFCKrakow | LIVE on @UFCFightPass http://t.co/G4YXm…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thebeernut @BeoirFinder 'even nudist  sex'  i think you know drinks are being consumed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Themottlybrew @DubBeerLadies you might want to avoid the 9th+23rd brewcon&amp;belfast abv fest....then again you might not! :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SecondCaptains @30.42 of the football podcast you can hear some of the notification sounds that litter your podcasts, can u turn them off?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @entertainmentIE: Win tickets to a preview screening of #JohnWickMovie in Dublin on Tues evening.
RT+Follow to enter.
#eiWick http://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Ryanair #RyanairEasterBunny molly malone statue dublin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@brk3 @majakristek @Joeydecourcey @HomebrewClubIrl very good!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Coffee bean infused apollo smoked stout. #goodhomebrewfriday @majakristek @Joeydecourcey @HomebrewClubIrl http://t.co/DcqbuBsJlH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HomebrewClubIrl: We're proud to officially announce the 1st annual NHC brewing conference: #BrewCon2015
See http://t.co/Usc5BACFg8 http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LovinDublin: RT to win 2 tickets &amp; pints for Easter Sunday's @Irishpubfilm w @EnsembleEriu @sugarclubdublin http://t.co/I6FTQ9MrAH http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BeoirFinder: Introducing the new AVOID marker for the app. Designed for those bars who have "taken the 12 pieces of silver"... http://t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @uglyducklingdub: Rt any of our tweets this morning to be in with a chance of winning a free lunch for you &amp; a friend. 2 winners announc…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thebeernut i loved Sideways!  Drinking Buddies was a poor beer version]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thebeernut don't worry there is no craft beer invloved. Would have been great if it was a Sideways like film]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WGMADave @majakristek must have been a good session yesterday, sore and stiff for the first time post training!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@beerwhiskeyIRE @MacIvorsCider still no winner?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dublinbusnews i just wish i didnt have to leave an hour earlier everytime i need to get somewhere important in case a bus doesn't show up]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dublinbusnews well thats understandable but it shouldn't be up on the RPTI then. 83 is so infrequent its frustrating when 1 doesn't come]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dublinbusnews another Saturday another huge wait for the 83 bus at stop 1443, dissappearing act from the RTPI again. Total wait 40mins!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Themottlybrew: @CapitalBrewers @HomebrewClubIrl @BeoirFinder @NorthCoBrCapital 
 Capital brewers are back tomorrow from 12pm for an all…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@sidlowe how hard would it be for a tourist to get a ticket? Do they go on general sale at all?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why was the commentatory shocked that the french didn't kick it out at the end?! France werent winning &amp; aren't ireland last time i checked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McHughs_Aidan @McHughsBeers @WWolfBrewery its a dangerous but good rule]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dublinbusnews but why display it then! Its inaccurate enough normally with Phantom buses weekdays too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dublinbusnews thanks for the none existent 83 service today from the city, nice that it was on the display all the time though. #phantombus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@57theheadline yeah had the misfortune to give them money last year at your pub, scum.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mcginnc13 yes there are six teams in it, its kind of in the name]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@McHughsBeers @MCollinsDublin @lagunitasbeer @HookerBrewery @8degreesbrewing @troublebrewing whats the shelf life without opening?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fuck you #waterprotest made me stranded in the city again. #payyourfuckingbills]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SecondCaptains @kenearlys can you ask sid about this next time he is on? http://t.co/caqW2uhooR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @57theheadline: RT to win beer for u+1 for @KinnegarBrewing Tap Takeover
https://t.co/TADNaARVGu …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @57theheadline: RT to win 2 places @the5LampsBeer Brewery Tour Mon 23rd
https://t.co/QkOIgmqvde …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @57theheadline: RT to win 2 places @the5LampsBeer Brewery Tour Mon 23rd
https://t.co/QkOIgmqvde … …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SevereMMA: Video - UFC 189: Jose Aldo vs Conor McGregor Staredown http://t.co/UdLpLksQkl #IrishMMA #UFC189 http://t.co/1eXvkbwQRF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Themottlybrew cheers Ian, you saved me with some emergency yeast for @majakristek first brew]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@cara_eire @SLambertSons you doing another one soon? Didn't know about this one and my mate would be interested]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>