<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding the Right Fitness Gadgets  http://t.co/AxB1SGe7rU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bird does not sing because it has an answer...  It sings because it has a song. - Chinese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The whole fleet knows this man tried to stab me through the neck. And you missed! Butterfingers! - Gaius Baltar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can a guy win a game if you don't give him any runs? - Robert Bo Belinsky after Losing 15 - 0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, I'm from Iowa. I only work in outer space. - Kirk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clarity trumps persuasion.  Dr. Flint McGlaughlin - Director MECLABS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Rolling Stones  http://t.co/qa0jKw8cBH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making the Most of Twitter for Your Business  http://t.co/5Nq5ZGOlJN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sweet - very cool mechanical pin clock - very unique - http://t.co/tUhzndmqQT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seniors Gain from Social Networking Technology  http://t.co/Xy3wFXXrdc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can lead a boy to college but you can't make him think. - Elbert Hubbard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these lovely Dos XX Most Interesting Main the World Commercials!  http://t.co/EUIA9yjNOq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My little dog -- a heartbeat at my feet. - Edith Wharton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Tsingtao Beer  http://t.co/tbVz48ckww]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Music of Hot Chocolate  http://t.co/SFhx7sIV5E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Star Wars  http://t.co/vHDM2btZlX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Lobo the Classic Rock Group?  http://t.co/DGHiAXIthY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ray, if someone asks you if you're a god, you say YES! - Winston, Ghostbusters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Using Instagram for Web Marketing  http://t.co/RdenrdTz1x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Peter Cetera  http://t.co/h4YCEDAA8m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The secret of toe cleavage, a very important part of the sexuality of the shoe; you must only show the first two cracks. - Manolo Blahnik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future's got a million roads for you to choose, But you'll walk a little taller in some high heel shoes - Hairspray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spring is when you feel like whistling even with a shoe full of slush. - Doug Larson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Very Unusual Hamburgers  http://t.co/PreZm8LdK2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The law gives a man the right to open his wife's mail, but not the nerve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cricket is basically baseball on valium - Robin Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I knew the words to 25 rock songs, so I got in the group. Long Tall Sally &amp; Tutti-Frutti, that got me in. - Paul McCartney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The blunt people make the most pointed remarks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The Music of L.T.D.  http://t.co/vIErxO0L11]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Heineken International  http://t.co/io0b9V5Rkg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of Artemis Fowl By Eoin Colfer  http://t.co/JKfVdUP54P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Marmalade Insurance: Selecting The Right Insurance  http://t.co/MvHUiRuL2M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is not the filling of a pail, but the lighting of a fire. - William Butler Yeats]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We live in a dark and romantic and quite tragic world. --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opportunity is missed by most people because it is dressed in overalls and looks like work - Thomas Edison]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't cross a sea merely by standing and staring at the water. - Rabindranath Tagore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The groundwork of all happiness is health. - Leigh Hunt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Review of the The Burning Bridge by John Flanagan  http://t.co/hYMdc9M76r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To err is human, to forgive, canine - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever wonder about the history of the coffin?  http://t.co/PFlPWKX0Sq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your culture is your brand.  Tony Hseih CEO, Zappos]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can an EMP really wipe us out?  http://t.co/V1kfkodQF1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The key to wisdom is a knowledge of our own ignorance.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It isn't the mountains ahead to climb that wear you out; it's the pebble in your shoe. - Muhammad Ali]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can never be overdressed or overeducated. --&gt; Oscar Wilde]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Motown, Motown, that's my era. Those are my people.  Hillary Clinton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Jackson Five  http://t.co/zw8BfkkqAE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Adversity causes some men to break; others to break records. - William A. Ward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is the ability to listen to almost anything without losing your temper or your self-confidence. - Robert Frost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education costs money, but then so does ignorance. - Sir Claus Moser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So my degree was in political science, which I think was - the closest I could come to marketing is politics. - Steve Case]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of David Gates  http://t.co/LIR3sblI3t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I grew up in a world that told girls they couldn't play rock 'n' roll. - Joan Jett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you drag your shoe a bit those plastic spikes or rubber spikes can be almost as bad as metal spikes. - Bernhard Langer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You must be the change you wish to see in the world. - Mahatma Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you ain't making waves, you ain't kickin' hard enough - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He ran out of talent about halfway through the corner. - Buddy Baker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome disco t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the disco lovers in your life!   http://t.co/oAX3oXoQ0J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never hit a man with glasses. Hit him with a baseball bat. - Author Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Successfully Use Other Websites for Link Building  http://t.co/ATYkux9CNm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like wrestling a gorilla- you don't quit when you're tired, you quit when the gorilla is tired - Robert Strauss]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think MTV should consider using subtitles. Half the time, even I can't understand what the **** I'm talking about.  Ozzy Osbourne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Harness The Power of Twitter for Business to Business Internet Marketing  http://t.co/tycW8r2fmG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only point in making money is, you can tell some big shot where to go. Humphrey Bogart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I make Jessica Simpson look like a rock scientist.  Tara Reid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The aim of marketing is to know and understand the customer so well the product or service fits him and sells itself. - Peter F. Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Kansas  http://t.co/OD18WUBNty]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you can look in the mirror and smile at what you see, then there's hope for you]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is where you &amp; I are different. Because this is all I want to talk about. Letterman to Paris when she didn’t want to talk about jail]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn from yesterday, live for today, hope for tomorrow. - Albert Einstein]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overheard in hollywood: "You said their marriage wouldn't last! They left the church together, didn't they?"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excellent Blue LED light stemmed Umbrella - a unique take on the Umbrella! http://t.co/jMADti8Xhc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There are so many emotions involved that I would like to wait until I know I'm with the right person &amp; married. Britney on virginity]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Kool and the Gang  http://t.co/JW8Jyt9WrP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That guitar is okay but you'll never make a living with it - John Lennon's Aunt Mimi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trying to sneak a pitch past Hank Aaron is like trying to sneak a sunrise past a rooster. - Curt Simmons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Aerosmith  http://t.co/7hP4VdvHaT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[80% of the final exam will be based on the one lecture you missed and the one book you didn't read.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How To Find The Right Gluten Free Foods  http://t.co/2BkGrIg5mz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Overheard when the boss returned from his safari in Africa: "He's the first man the head shrinkers ever failed with."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love the Lava Lamp - so retro and so cool --&gt; http://t.co/ZCazxOebHJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seriousness is stupidity sent to college. P. J. O'Rourke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Old age means realizing you will never own all the dogs you wanted to. - Joe Gores]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the History of Adobe Photoshop  http://t.co/lTold5EtC4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Caring for Pet Teeth – Ways to Keep Your Pet’s Teeth Clean  http://t.co/gDPxrjYd04]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think education is expensive, try ignorance - Derek Bok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You may have to fight a battle more than once to win it. - Margaret Thatcher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome kayaking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the paddling lovers in your life!  http://t.co/BHaURDkuUb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The lead car is absolutely unique, except for the one behind it which is identical. - F1 commentator Murray Walker.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Use SEO on Multiple Websites to Drive Traffic in Your Direction  http://t.co/czrBMs2FjZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sign on a barber shop window --  Home haircuts repaired  $20.00]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A cat is a puzzle for which there is no solution. - Hazel Nicholson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you ain't making waves, you ain't kickin' hard enough - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A women with good shoes is never ugly. They are the last touch of elegance. - Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The first thing you lose on a diet is your sense of humor. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Christian Louboutin  http://t.co/QvyOIioFsQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The worst examples of snap judgment are usually found in the old family album]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nobody remembers the guy who finished second but the guy who finished second. - Bobby Unser]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Play is the only way the highest intelligence of humankind can unfold. - Joseph Chilton Pearce]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Pat Benatar  http://t.co/g3MY0X30um]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>