<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you heard ‘Lost Cells’ by @Brasik_UK on #SoundCloud? https://t.co/WXmMxuhNvd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Have you heard ‘Sacarine’ by @Brasik_UK on #SoundCloud? https://t.co/lDJWTPZVC5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BBCiplayer has the Kooks on the John Peel stage @ Glastonbury Eh WTF @BBC6Breakfast WTF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DanKennett: Last 9 #ENG matches LLWWDDLLD #Hodgson #NoOneEvenCares #Suarez]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Savage there giving his opinion on playing clean good football.... FFS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All this talk bout Suarez &amp; Barca and I thought they had a ban on buying players for 2 years?? #LFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BeardedGenius: When I say 'most confused fan at the World Cup', I obviously mean after Columbian Nazi Weed Pope. Obviously. http://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TerraceLife_: Funniest thing of the World Cup so far... https://t.co/xYjZ2Z9r2V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BowersWilkins: Sports loving dog watching the #WorldCup2014 flanked by Bowers and Wilkins. http://t.co/v7rKkTVYuF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could you image J Pearce and Gary Neville commentating together. FFS that would be great wouldn't it!!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You know... I posted about phil Neville's commentating skills because I thought I just thought it was shit but it turns out..........]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just watched the match on BBC2 and please please please @BBCSport don't use Phil Neville to commentate again!! It was painful.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GeneralBoles: Harrison Ford rushed to hospital following #StarWars accident http://t.co/uDstBKgdOS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do they always market #yogurts at girls in adverts #sexism Men eat yogurt too ya know]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's coming together nicely, we have power now and a water tight roof. Now just inside to do!! #logcabinmusic http://t.co/lSCtLosN6b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The beginning http://t.co/eOxfLTB7gr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So this is the start of my log cabin build and the floors been an absolute bugger! My knees are fooked....... http://t.co/JIvOghEWzl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBC6Music after this tho http://t.co/FBEihHs2hI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBC6Music so it begins http://t.co/PUlaNnY06z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBC6Music the pressures on then !]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBC6Music ok will send updates haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBC6Music it's just bits of wood at the mo but when it's built I will! It's going to be my creative zone painting and music/noise making...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBC6Music you can come and help ;) I will need it! O look eldest daughter Martha 's up still wearing Halloween make up. Looking good....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sunshine Boiled egg and soldiers tea &amp; contemplating building the Log Cabin in the garden with daughter Lyla @maryannehobbs on radio. Lushxx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @vonstrenginho: Therapy
https://t.co/HmKOYXHjoU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not been to Whitby since the soul all nighters at the pavilion. Messy times haha @CCfunkandsoul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On holiday in Whitby in a little smugglers cottage and 3 yr old daughter dancing to @CCfunkandsoul good times! Lyla, Martha, Del &amp; Gareth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RealBobMortimer: It's Friday!.. Let's Skank! http://t.co/Blg4gHvVe8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@BBC6MorningShow and we're off haha 808 state..... Not heard this in ages]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Blooming heck I forget my daughter now sees my tweets damn n blast..... I don't swear normally honest.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You won't believe what happened next or you can't believe what this person saw. So fucking sick of seeing them words. The Internet is fucked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JamesEdwinKing: Great speech Mr Osborne. Keep punishing the bastards we all know caused the financial crash - the young, the poor and t…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[All the goalies will want reactolight contacts.... Tremendous idea yeah!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gonna invent reactolight contacts then I can move to a desert island and walk around naked eating mango.... #invention #theworldneeds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Simple, beautiful &amp; ad-free. Read the manifesto: http://t.co/PipsZfKSdr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@roof_shingles can I email you a picture of my roof I need shingles for and can you let me know how many I need? Thanks Gareth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AnyoneButUtd: Louis van Gaal looks like he's had a rough night. http://t.co/Dw6SHbwnzL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really looking forward to @BBC6Music tonight and the @WarpRecords Now Playing show should be a good one!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@97MDE you were lucky... !!
Well played you deserved it..... LFC had another nightmare game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Another Poor game. You think we miss Sturridge and dare I say Suarez?? YNWA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I see Lamberts beard is scared of his neck!!! @LFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jesus fkin Christ WTF !!! Can't swear now as my daughters following me ..... Come on Liverpool....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JCC saying Fashion in a slight transatlantic voice there mate on the @BBC6Music infomercial...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And we're off top desert island disco haha @BBC6MorningShow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheTweetOfGod: Thank you for praying. All available angels are currently assisting other prayers. Please stay on your knees. We will be…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/cee580YfE8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really Liking the @derrickmayday 6Mix. Good mix of stuff from Techno to House vibes just the ticket for the first night off in soo long....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @occupythemob: Palestinians launch #RubbleBucketChallenge to create awareness for suffering in #Gaza http://t.co/tmtU3bpaLg http://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Traveling through hyperspace ain’t like dusting crops, farm boy. But  the first time in for ever I finally understand....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dazbroomhead yeah we got 3 whole inches but these are not the droids your looking for!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dazbroomhead we managed a snow ball fight on boxing at 10.00 at night, not enough for snowman tho ;( Luke I am your father]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dazbroomhead do you wanna build a snow man....? Lyla loves it all the time "I'm Elsa" this "I'm Elsa" that... Now Star Wars that's a film..]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Massive Attack kind of a night here.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to the match today, hopeful of another good performance and 3points... Come on Redmen #LFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@IamStoneyBen thanks man you too! Hope 2015 gets you closer to seeing your boy.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Working at this time NYD  never mind at least @BBC6Music is too...... :)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ya Bitches]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy New Year Everybody]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Guardians of the Galaxy gets a big thumbs up from my daughter and I. Wasn't sure if it was her sort of thing but she loved it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#neighbours #noise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to deal with a noises neighbour? I've contacted council we'll see what trouble that brings........]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@thisisanfield any decent streams gonna be available?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mary Christmas one and all, even atheists like me. Hope Santa brings all you desire. Proper confused tweet this one, Have a great Yule y'all]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Martial Arts Master Fail! http://t.co/NqLEx7khvV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Something's wrong when the loo paper at work is better than what you have at home... Where did she buy it from FFS.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get in skirtel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bloody Hell!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For God Sake.......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes yes Fkin Yes!!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@D_Sturridge this games set up for you Daniel, any idea when you'll be back??]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking forward to this and nice to hear @sleafordmods behind the music...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@IamStoneyBen: Wow i have 4G for the first time ever! Norfolk is getting with the times!” I get 4G in the kitchen but nowhere else in house]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ELF TIME!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Epithemiou: Well now you cocomamie sons of bitches, the new potcast is out now. Recorded live you know at MI5.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#AddMeOnBebo
My username is: 'garethmclark' http://t.co/bUHKRnotbt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Muppets most wanted!! #family #movie #Night]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @fatherscontact: #LightaCandle for alienated families worldwide! We circumnavigate the globe! #PASAwareness #PASCollage http://t.co/UV3x…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdamBuxton shed of Xmas was great thnx. That is all. Merry Christmas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@destroyeddad @fatherscontact @UndervalueDads it was a long journey but it shows how things can change for the better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I left Facebook a week ago and I'm still Alive! Yeahaw.....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just found this and it made me smile... http://t.co/fb8b1Zq2pn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@fatherscontact @AmandaBrooks8 @UndervalueDads until I got custody that is.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@fatherscontact: This pretty much sums it up! #PAS Dad @UndervalueDads http://t.co/5W1LOBm0go” had all these thrown at me pretty much....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just got my @ThreeUK #CalendarMe its most excellent and I'm sure my GF will love it! Haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Battling_joshua @Bham_Childrens keep strong YNWA X]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I made it phew]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Expecting a delivery but need a No2 Do I chance it!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@97MDE: Just caught the end of what sounded like a cat being strangled on Radio 2. #radio2 #samsmith” ooooft condolences man!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or songs that sound like that....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think if you sing "ally ally ally ally ooooo ally ally ally ally aaaa"repeat.then you'll win everything just like the Spanish teams. #LFC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think a game like this might do us good. Able to pass it around a bit get some confidence back #LFC #LFCFamily come on reds....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I seriously cannot get my head around how someone can do this. What is going on in their head?? #Peshawar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The news from #Peshawar is sickening. I can't get my head around it. So Sad that these things are happening in our world, heartbreaking....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@DrAliceRoberts: @marcusbrig I nearly broke my ankle last night trying out the skateboard I've bought for my daughter... Gr8 present!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@NTStoneacre @BBCSpringwatch saw one at work yesterday!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @scotwilliams: Seriously, go to http://t.co/4j0lVY25Jj
• Enter your twitter @name
• Click 'Search'

it's hysterical.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So I picked the coldest day of the year so far to get new windows put in!! #bimf #freezing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Tim_Burgess: #timsadventcalendar DAY 12! 3 winners Signed copy of Oh No I Love You More with your name on. RT to win. Winners 11pm http…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So just #deleted my #Facebook account. Bye bye Facebook hello the future!!! Haha]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“@IamStoneyBen: How can Torres go from one of the finest strikers in Europe to worthless?” Chelsea FC.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>