<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Oooo, sick burn! https://t.co/f4zxVpCHqu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MYSADCAT: My cat is sad because he's remembering a time long ago when he still had friends &amp; didn't have to play Twister alone https://…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @birbigs: Suicide Squad has machine gun killings and bombings and got a PG-13 rating. @Dontthinkmovie gets an R because adults smoke pot…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MYSADCAT: My cat is sad because he tries his best to hide from his problems but he is always massively shit at doing so. https://t.co/m…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nooMcinaP You've got me there. Two of my (many) favourite actors.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nooMcinaP Re: "Josie &amp; the Pussycats": The product placement was satire by the movie-makers, and they received no payment (Wikipedia).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @stevecavers: 47 years ago today, Neil Armstrong planted the 1st human foot on the moon. Today, that foot has grown to be a healthy crop…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This dead-baby joke comes to us from "Cyanide &amp; Happiness": https://t.co/Ea6ygqDneg.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Interesting look at "What Types of Low-Budget Films Break Out?" (Hollywood level): https://t.co/rPPW1SXE2O.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AlbertBrooks: R.I.P. Garry Marshall. A great, great  guy and the best casino boss in the history of film. #lostinamerica]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Scammerhead: THE BERKELEY TIMES calls @scammerhead "One of this years' most
intriguing movies". https://t.co/kx1jvuShEm #noirish https:…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@benjaminluk That's a strange thing for him to boast about, but okay ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @playwrightnow: Conflict is all. Watching combat—dialogue back and forth—transfixes an audience like a tennis match. They won't have tim…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @playwrightnow: In a good scene, every relationship is different at the end from what it was at the beginning. #amwriting #2amt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @irmadesmond: "To shoot a film is to organize an entire universe." Happy birthday Ingmar Bergman! (July 14, 1918) https://t.co/1FiUUULbbz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson Whew!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @stevecavers: Many Bothans died to bring us this information. Many Bothans also died playing frisbee golf yesterday. They're dangerously…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @leonardmaltin: 'Cafe Society' is unfortunately one of Woody Allen's weakest films https://t.co/H3PmAp1Azq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow, Facebook has become pretty much unusable on my computer. Its unresponsive scripts keep hanging my whole browser.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Number10cat: People seem to be making quite a big fuss about me replacing my butler...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And those "actors" in these flickers! If they had any real talent they'd be on the stage, right? https://t.co/m58bLsU9OG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I thought I was wrong once, but I was mistaken.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @playwrightnow: Just the fact that you can read a play in half the time you can see it should tell you that there's a lot of stuff you'r…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SnarkySteff: ISTHMUS: (noun) A narrow landbridge with flanking water bodies either side... ALSO: word invented to torture people with l…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Stan_And_Ollie: #LaurelAndHardy with Hal Roach pictured at the Oscars after The Music Box won best short film. Friday, November 18, 193…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OnePerfectShot: THE MALTESE FALCON (1941) DoP: Arthur Edeson | Dir: John Huston | https://t.co/9T4holNI2R https://t.co/7ZZZCoOOiS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OnePerfectShot: THE CONVERSATION (1974) DoP: Bill Butler | Dir: Francis Ford Coppola https://t.co/5L06iPtWzl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @_daveharrison: @JohnCleese. Yes, the last time I flew into Helsinki the airline lost my bag. I mean, it was as if it had just vanished…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MarcSnetiker: sad: in six states it is still illegal for wonder twins to activate https://t.co/h6sYXUvJh1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OnePerfectShot: THE GREAT PIGGY BANK ROBBERY (1946) Dir: Bob Clampett | See IMDb for artist info | https://t.co/Lcnqlvgl8i https://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @AlanWattsDaily: This thing that you are feeling is your own life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@evanjstern I'm afraid @jonvoight has been a right-wing-authoritarian bonehead for years. "Midnight Cowboy" is still a good movie though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsAdamCanuck I'm afraid @jonvoight has been a right-wing-authoritarian bonehead for years. "Midnight Cowboy" is still a good movie though.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson Ah! Thank you. My knowledge expands -- I love when that happens.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson Aside: What means "ARCs"? Google is not helpful, alas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JamillaTamera: You work better with a clean desk, but cleaning your desk is no excuse not to work.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @alyankovic: From the archives - my first press coverage! https://t.co/h1yngRUlJv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson "Oh, my!" (George Takei voice)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @cox_tom: *Awoken at 3am in rural cottage by scary noise*

*Creeps downstairs with shoe-as-weapon*

Cat (bashing chicken bone against ra…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson Handsome beast!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@HopeLNicholson Very Jem!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ItsAdamCanuck "I have magic breasts!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @evanjstern: I feel like we've cycled back around to the dark ages. That or (more likely) they've always been here but now we've got vid…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RealEOC: Director Jacques Rozier w/ cinematographer René Mathelin &amp; crew filming ADIEU PHILIPPINE (1962). #filmmaking #bts https://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Criterion: Storyboarding BLOOD SIMPLE: Get a fascinating glimpse into the Coens’ creative process https://t.co/tKL157yIfp https://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BCFerrys: Regards, acquaintances. Today is articulate as would a maritime criminal day. #ITLAPD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Emmy Awards are tonight! I'm sure the mothers of the winners and nominees are all very proud.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RobCottingham: #BatmanDay is way too commercial. Should go back to its roots: a celebration of parents killed in filthy alleys by mugge…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Dam3ian: "US playwright Edward Albee dies aged 88": https://t.co/x3gABW0yqX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dammit! https://t.co/wiBxPsJwOx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@StacieBee Ah, whenever I hear someone say that, I think to myself, "Boy, that Bowie song holds up pretty well."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattdagley Blu-ray player might not recognize exFAT, but will recognize NTFS, which MacOS can use (but beware of creeping file corruption).]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@mattdagley Yeah, that's the well-known filesize limit on FAT32. Reformat as exFAT for use on both MacOS and Windows.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @ClassicMovieHub: Cinema is the most beautiful fraud in the world. -Jean-Luc Godard #quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow, when did @eBay become so ugly and hard to use?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LeVostreGC: Alreadye blockinge off the David Bowie anniversarye on my datebooke: CRYINGE ALL DAYE, THEN DAUNSE PARTYE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[*Everything* needs a grim 'n' gritty reboot -- even (especially!) Lassie! https://t.co/7tlHCLAfu3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OnePerfectShot: BLOW OUT (1981) DP: Vilmos Zsigmond | Director: Brian De Palma https://t.co/8wqEi6jm1o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @SeeBeeWhitman: Sure, that's how a normal cat sits https://t.co/aglEbLK16V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OnePerfectShot: RAIDERS OF THE LOST ARK (1981) DP: Douglas Slocombe | Director: Steven Spielberg https://t.co/eHLQauneNN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @LeVostreGC: LYFE YS A CAT BALLET, OLDE CHUM
COME TO THE CAT BALLET]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevecavers These Germans are crazy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevecavers Germanic tribe? Where?! Invading Germanic hordes aren't here again, are they?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@stevecavers Vandal? Where?! Vandal Savage isn't here again, is he?!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @freyburg: This shot is about as Vancouver as it gets. https://t.co/gDosEV7EQo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: A school photo of a 9-year-old Mick Jagger at Wentworth Junior County Primary School in his home town of Dartford, 1951.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OnePerfectShot: OCEAN’S ELEVEN (1960) DP: William H. Daniels | Dir: Lewis Milestone https://t.co/gut6oy8Hy1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Criterion: Director Barry Jenkins (@BandryBarry) on his enduring passion for the films of Wong Kar-wai: https://t.co/0YgRZAVavj https:/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OnePerfectShot: RADIO DAYS (1987) DP: Carlo Di Palma | Director: Woody Allen https://t.co/Cu7UCUPw8O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey @Adobe! Now Dreamweaver CC 2017 crashes only 50 percent of the time I open it. This is, alas, a great improvement.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@corbett I have observed "force of nature" applied to women and men. I have not tallied how often to whom; might be interesting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Criterion: Did you know that Jacques Tati came to the set of ONE-EYED JACKS just to watch Marlon Brando direct? https://t.co/YMwCaWopO0…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @pattonoswalt: Doing stand-up while Trump readies himself for the White House is cathartic but I can't shake feeling like The Emcee in C…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OnePerfectShot: To Kill A Mockingbird (1962) DP: Russell Harlan | Director: Robert Mulligan https://t.co/JNNOUB7bPy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@tarakjpratt Perhaps you're bursting with fruit flavour.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BisqaMusic: Hewey Lupus and the news

#sickbands @midnight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @BCFerrys: @bcferrys is seeking a qualified Kraken-whisperer. Fluency in Heptapod-A an asset.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @STORYHIVE: “We should always be willing to sprinkle a little nonsense into the work we do.” - 
Tina Roth Eisenberg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Grover: WHAT DID THAT SAY? https://t.co/DhtQKZKCI6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OnePerfectShot: UNFORGIVEN (1992) DP: Jack N. Green | Director: Clint Eastwood https://t.co/31mmlDJBHJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @stevecavers: “An anagram” sounds like a French message from a pineapple. #badbilingualjoke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OnePerfectShot: BOOGIE NIGHTS (1997) DP: Robert Elswit | Director: Paul Thomas Anderson https://t.co/QX6ILYo49S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@shanebee "There there, little bunny."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: Gregory Peck reading 'To Kill A Mockingbird'. Photograph by Cliff Donaldson. https://t.co/dI7WCsG9pK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And he still looks the same as he always did: embalmed. https://t.co/3TffCQDNMC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A few minutes ago on The Crescent, Vancouver, BC, an @Amazon truck pulled out without looking or signalling and almost ran me off the road.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Huh. Apparently somebody named @PiersMorgan has more Twitter followers than comedy legend @EricIdle. Well, well, well. https://t.co/iAgmfSHlUO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching Butterscotch Candygram on "Saturday Night Live". Gad, the man just drips charisma.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@dreamweaver Exact steps: Open Dreamweaver. Create new HTML file. Try to type anywhere on screen; nada. Program crashes. Repeat as needed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So apparently it is not possible to enter text in @Adobe Dreamweaver 2017. Bit of a drawback, that.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I press "Record" on the camera. https://t.co/jT1rod3Mji]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DoctorJeph: *puffs on a cigarette* "Thomas? I haven't heard that name in years"

https://t.co/jBe9KrxyDf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColleenDoran ... yet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ColleenDoran Enjoyed this series of posts. One day, when you have some spare time (ha!) readers might be interested in seeing some entries.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Aww, "Luke Cage" -- what a disappointment. They rushed it into production, and it shows; godawful second half. Such a shame.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdobeCare So you are saying that your own software does not work, and your own update procedures do not work. Good to know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdobeCare No. My fault, trusting your software to do what it claims it will. Why is the default to delete the old version if that's bad?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdobeCare No. Both. The app displays the welcome screen ... and goes no further. Eventually Windows 10 reports, "... has stopped working."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AdobeCare "If it did not install correctly"? How do I find this out, pray tell?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Luke Cage" continues to dribble away after the halfway point. Stryker and his whole plotline should have been amputated root and branch.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>