<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History Of Samuel Adams Beer  http://t.co/ub2JeDlYYA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you haven't got it, fake it! Too short? Wear big high heels, but do practice walking! - Victoria Beckham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He didn't believe in flying saucers until he tickled the waitress]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your Attorney Search: The Advantages of Flat Rates  http://t.co/vqHvChB0lM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Major Shoe Retailers  http://t.co/d9K38eLWzL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You will never change your life until you change something you do daily. - Mike Murdock]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was a pretty good coach and working with marketing was like coaching. - Bernard Ebbers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A teacher affects eternity; he can never tell where his influence stops. - Henry Brooks Adams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A comparison and History of Game Consoles  http://t.co/fwFJWG3gUY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Creating Beautiful Gardens with Butterflies - Easy Steps  http://t.co/lhMnUEJFvz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Follow these Steps to Clean Your Credit  http://t.co/heu7NZL96i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Introduction to Dallas, Texas  http://t.co/DyFEZymakg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A hamburger by any other name costs a lot more.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It isn't necessary to blow out the other person's light in order for yours to shine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We never repent of having eaten too little. - Thomas Jefferson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read The History of the Beau Brummels  http://t.co/i4j63I7vZS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You have enemies? Good. That means you've stood up for something, sometime in your life.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of McDonald's  http://t.co/9v90XK03vE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If my uniform doesn't get dirty, I haven't done anything in the baseball game - Rickey Henderson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These Yoda Lights Must You Have!  Wonderful Geek Gear! http://t.co/Nx2bXBqfqs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How To Find Best Supplies For Gardening  http://t.co/PaaD1ku1im]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The truest test of moral courage is the ability to ignore an insult]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You cannot dream yourself into a character: you must hammer and forge yourself into one. - Henry D. Thoreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes you can play 3 Man Chess - Check It Out! http://t.co/bpCWL6HSIX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When you go to buy, don't show your silver - Chinese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is a very easy way to return from a casino with a small fortune: go there with a large one. - Jack Yelton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips To Draw More Traffic With Quality Link Building  http://t.co/1MPh3wLO76]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rock and roll is here to stay. - Neil Young]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Molly Hatchet  http://t.co/oMGNrwmb7Y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our Review of Amazon’s Popular Kindle Reader  http://t.co/FNvfSBmPTt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious Pacifier with a Mustache  - Kids and Adults will love it! http://t.co/5PfXnjOlJi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this very cool bed fan - cools right under the covers! http://t.co/zNPTaGJ119]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's so timid he wouldn't open an oyster without first knocking on the shell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never dance in a puddle when there's a hole in your shoe (it's always best to take your shoes off first). --&gt; John D. Rhodes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can You Really Make Things Invisible?  http://t.co/284csHEx2w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His head is getting too big for his toupee...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Are the Different Types of Web Hosting?  http://t.co/RXNyAgtzdD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for great resources on Beer?  Check out our top 10... http://t.co/Y6X9gb8cnE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kate Austen: So what, I'm your prisoner? James 'Sawyer' Ford: If that sort of thing turns you on.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Blue Oyster Cult   http://t.co/pvENSpXMaj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Peter Cetera  http://t.co/NOFo2jf0re]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Ramones  http://t.co/2ZfaFgs7Q2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is the best deodorant. - Elizabeth Taylor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating History of American Idol   http://t.co/bGCxCG5TGL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[His pockets always outlast his suits...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Redrum. -  Danny, The Shining]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Overview of Bluetooth Enabled Watches  http://t.co/prlGfklsRv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahh Fond Memories of San Antonio  http://t.co/ADIKvsi2yX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm sorry. You are right. Those pants don't make you look fat. - Jin-Soo Kwon  The only three things a woman needs to hear! - Sawyer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heredity:  what makes the father and mother of a teen-ager wonder about each other]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not wait to strike until the iron is hot; but make it hot by striking - William B. Sprague]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is what you get from reading the small print in a contract. "experience " is what you get from not reading it]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About How Technology Has Helped Seniors to Make Great Strides in their Lifestyle  http://t.co/suYLE856Jv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man with a lot of money may be a bad egg, but folks seldom take offense until he is broke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn about the History of San Francisco, California http://t.co/HjQMvsUkCs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Dells  http://t.co/E4LlwVzUFK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The less a man knows --  the more he tells it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Judge a man by how much he does when he doesn't need to.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to The Knack  http://t.co/o4IwOFwKYl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool check out this Nerd Kit...  http://t.co/YiB9bFE9s0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Fun! BANG! Turn it off this Lamp with a gun, and it "plays dead". Then bring it back to life with another shot! http://t.co/FYEzri9Duc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fellow who rocks the boat is never the fellow at the oars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Rufus  http://t.co/RECIuToccI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only way to prove that you're a good sport is to lose. - Ernie Banks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great History of the Rolling Stones  http://t.co/pfBQS8j4ZX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you wish to grow thinner, diminish your dinner. - Henry Sambrooke Leigh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Always wear expensive shoes. People notice. - Brian Koslow]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A college is a place where pebbles are polished and diamonds dimmed. - Robert Ingersoll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Christian Louboutin  http://t.co/gtKPE8GE5U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to Tumblr Blogging  http://t.co/dF9CbTwcZ3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Leif Garrett  http://t.co/sb0qy8SQbl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's behind you doesn't matter. - Enzo Ferrari]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The pessimist sees difficulty in every opportunity. The optimist sees opportunity in every difficulty. - Winston Churchill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Very Unusual Hamburgers  http://t.co/7yZdrMK9As]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the dressing room, I always put on my right shoe first. Same thing for my right wristband. -  Mary Lou Retton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Kiss  http://t.co/4tlBZ9yi1K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See you in another life, brother. - Desmond Hume, Lost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Awesome BookBook for iPhone- Combine Wallet and Phone and Style  http://t.co/LpsyiDfdyt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would rather entertain and hope that people learned something than educate people and hope they were entertained. - Walt Disney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love Minecraft?  Check out the hot new video blogger Crimson Mine - http://t.co/cRFKJCcPpY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Profiles of Major Watch Designers  http://t.co/43cJjGEo4R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I pretty much try to stay in a constant state of confusion just because of the expression it leaves on my face.  Johnny Depp quotes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Cooking – An Effortless Way to Bond with Kids  http://t.co/7TfiIEC0EV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seniors Gain from Social Networking Technology  http://t.co/e8dpeXalYW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They just couldn't live without each other --  so they got married and discovered they could]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Grand Slam in Tennis – what's the big deal?  http://t.co/nQhSBBjAI3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[80% of the final exam will be based on the one lecture you missed and the one book you didn't read.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Laser Tag anywhere - cool guns and app make it easy to play anytime!  http://t.co/0dbhpgHx2x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trust people and they will be true to you; Treat them greatly, and they will show themselves great. - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is one AMAZING Kate Upton poster - gorgeous http://t.co/cmNrXQKSpL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A patient man is one who likes slow catsup.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Home is where -- . You hang your head]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The aim of marketing is to know and understand the customer so well the product or service fits him and sells itself. - Peter F. Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can an EMP really wipe us out?  http://t.co/Ms2qjMh68B]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Redrum. -  Danny, The Shining]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minecraft Minigame Turf Wars: Such Rage; Much Death  http://t.co/xPk71NEaAY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the shoe fits, you're not allowing for growth. - Robert N Coons]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Kool and the Gang  http://t.co/y15sQEyWLS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Drill sarge to recruit:  "wipe that opinion off your face!”]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The 7 ages of a woman are the right one and 6 wild guesses!]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>