<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[A Life? Cool! Where can I download one of those?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips for Effective Use of LinkedIn for Your Company  http://t.co/ynd8alIRy8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it's too close to bother to buckle your seat belt it's close enough to walk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh, give us the man who sings at his work. - Thomas Carlyle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Small Dogs Can Make Great Pets - Picking the Right Breed  http://t.co/IsUdF1fMSy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I never wear the same shoe twice. - Dion Sanders]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live the Thug Life with These Temporary Tattoos! http://t.co/fU5ubZFq0V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science fiction is not predictive; it is descriptive. - Ursula K. LeGuin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Alice Cooper  http://t.co/ncT1PO3DwW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome camping t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the camping lovers in your life!  http://t.co/kIRHX0DzMk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Mets have found ways of losing that I never knew existed. - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In science fiction, you can also test out your own realities. - Theodore Sturgeon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Finance Trade Secrets  http://t.co/uwIMqHxXJW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One Family’s Adoption Stories  http://t.co/ztMzWQjTtN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes are the quickest way for women to achieve instant metamorphosis - Manolo Blahnik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Julius LaRosa  http://t.co/VlSCJXLJJN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fall seven times, stand up eight. - Japanese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Locate Your Garage Space Before Installation Of Cabinets  http://t.co/3vpcQ3R7W6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We thought you was a toad! - Delmar, O Brother Where Art Thou?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips for Using Facebook Pages for Your Business  http://t.co/xnQLJ9jAES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wal-mart --  do they like make walls there?  Paris Hilton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Interesting History of Dos XX Beer  http://t.co/GJtagV4ikk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Product Reviews Through the Eyes of a Child  http://t.co/k10Oa3CIbE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Eagles   http://t.co/ZQHhgUfc7V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must accept finite disappointment, but we must never lose infinite hope. - Martin Luther King, Jr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Star Trek  http://t.co/U96Z5NZdBq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The absolute fundamental aim is to make money out of satisfying customers. - John Egan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Use SEO on Multiple Websites to Drive Traffic in Your Direction  http://t.co/uCMsNnpXgQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not lose courage in considering your own imperfections. -  Saint Francis de Sales]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I accidentally forgot to graduate from college.  - Anne Lamott]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Inflation is when you pay fifteen dollars for the ten-dollar haircut you used to get for five dollars when you had hair. - Sam Ewing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I make Jessica Simpson look like a rock scientist.  Tara Reid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome kayaking t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the paddling lovers in your life!  http://t.co/pGN5jeAJHJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A house is not a home without a pet. - Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the first place, God made idiots. That was for practice. Then he made school boards. - Mark Twain]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Superhero caped glasses - totally cool!  http://t.co/Fo5Maa7zj0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the fascinating history of that classic baseball park - Wrigley Field - http://t.co/AfLipvSP0D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you are thin, don't eat fast. If you are fat, don't eat fast.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the The Early History of Beer  http://t.co/55wwnSrEjI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be successful, the first thing to do is fall in love with your work. - Sister Mary Lauretta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Dale Hawkins - The Father of Swamp Rock Boogie  http://t.co/lx6vt5Kgw8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Spock. This child is about to wipe out every living thing on Earth. Now, what do you suggest we do? spank it? - Dr. McCoy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Review of The Little House on the Prairie Episode Called "Four Eyes"  http://t.co/9OKMKHWTl7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Profiles of Major Watch Designers  http://t.co/pzFVMSJ1w3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Evolution of the Wooden Clog  http://t.co/LeBL259dpt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Never dance in a puddle when there's a hole in your shoe (it's always best to take your shoes off first). --&gt; John D. Rhodes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're either making money or you're not. If you're not making money get out of the business. Meredith Whitney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Book... The Shapeshifter  http://t.co/lHISB5egI4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[10-Light Star Wars Plastic Yoda Light Set - may the force be with you! http://t.co/jx5lp9Hbzi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did You Know this About Blackbeard in Pirates of the Caribbean 4  http://t.co/nY8SNODZl4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Staple Singers  http://t.co/lDb78K4JFk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Radiation Detection Equipment - Providing the Equipment Necessary to Protect Those That Protect Us  http://t.co/k55507BjXE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[History of Blogging  http://t.co/FTeDmh53ei]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Your attitude determines your altitude! - Denis Waitley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flattery, like perfume, should be smelled, not swallowed]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My wife is such a terrible cook the police made her register her stove as a deadly weapon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I went to college for four years. - Kim Kardashian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ever wonder about the history of the coffin?  http://t.co/QagTZVOHKv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hiring Strategy Consulting Firms: The Importance of Competitive Analysis  http://t.co/eUDxLYOA1I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would give a million bucks to have seen my mother say "cute shoes" to a naked Ashley Judd. --&gt; Brian Fies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not let what you cannot do interfere with what you can do. - John Wooden]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Very Unusual Hamburgers  http://t.co/KAOSs3ZPCm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The entrepreneur always searches for change, responds to it, and exploits it as an opportunity. - Peter F. Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 1 - What the heck do I have????  http://t.co/XqOB2WArOe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only undertake what you can do in an excellent fashion. There are no prizes for average performance.- Brian Tracy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you ain't making waves, you ain't kickin' hard enough - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Driving a car is like playing baseball. The object in both is to get home safely. - Joe Moore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bright light! Bright light! - Gremlins]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Bob Marley  http://t.co/rWzize6TEi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Cool Batman Comfy Throw - Stay Warm and Cool :&gt;)  http://t.co/CGGgvtwWyK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The thing about science fiction is that it's totally wide open. But it's wide open in a conditional way. - Octavia Butler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read The Life and Music of Rupert Holmes  http://t.co/yFxSKKocDV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Amazing Nappy Brown  http://t.co/SkNBnaURAY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Giant Squids - Hunters of the Deep  http://t.co/9SU6bBw15Z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really &amp; truly you can never have 2 many pairs of shoes. You need a pair for every mood &amp; everyone knows women have lots of moods. Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome camping t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the camping lovers in your life!  http://t.co/kIRHX0DzMk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Cool History of Science Fiction  http://t.co/BrZrIPpD8U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Skeeter Davis  http://t.co/bwRFczDb76]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Be not afraid of growing slowly, be afraid only of standing still. - Chinese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only way to prove that you're a good sport is to lose. - Ernie Banks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[End Of Line - The MCP, TRON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Greetings, programs! - Flynn, TRON]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Miss Toni Fisher  http://t.co/KAptnryaS3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are going to turn this team around 360 degrees. Jason Kidd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who will wear a shoe that hurts him, because the shoe-maker tells him 'tis well made? - Algernon Sydney]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Barbara Acklin – “Love Makes a Woman”  http://t.co/9SFujXJboa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Who Invented the Modern Watch?  http://t.co/nx7hol7CLb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Rose Royce  http://t.co/zXDKuQ0Xa4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give a girl the correct footwear and she can conquer the world. - Bette Midler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About GPS Technology and Fitness Watches  http://t.co/ks5hHqVt66]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Awesome BookBook for iPhone- Combine Wallet and Phone and Style  http://t.co/DZvlvvzRDH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Ohio Players    http://t.co/g7mdCDshrr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I make Jessica Simpson look like a rock scientist.  Tara Reid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My little friend that I only I can see is wanting me to warn you that he thinks you have serious mental problems He He He!!  :&gt;)]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Mountain Climbing from Novice to Experts  http://t.co/UFUfjPo6pn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Poets are like baseball pitchers. Both have their moments. The intervals are the tough things. - Robert Frost]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL - Cool - A Computer Mouse with a Spider in it!   http://t.co/OHQJvRtNc9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't realize how strong a person really is until you see them at their weakest moment. - Unknown Author]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bring the best of your authentic self to every opportunity.  John Jantsch - Author of Duct Tape Marketing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Guide - Four ways to keep your printing environmentally friendly  http://t.co/oLWv93iTDh]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>