<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Some cool new insights into the Future of HR. https://t.co/wzQWVmQ937]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool insights on HR 2020: &lt;br&gt;HR 2020 http://t.co/iJ6CFInpd8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HR Magazine - Business leaders unable to collaborate effectively https://t.co/JEFqiqDI1q via @sharethis]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice profile of 3M CHRO (SVP of HR Marlene McGrath) by CEB on how they drive employee engagement http://t.co/9c4Eyz1J2U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEB_HR: 32% of #HR execs would replace members of their leadership team at the 1st opportunity via @HRmagazine &amp; @briankropp http://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good news: More workers are quitting April 03 - CNNMoney http://t.co/qJPiFVBXoJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Employees globally prioritized vacation over other benefits when considering a new employer in 2014 https://t.co/swWfXoqCwt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[interesting read on how google manages employees http://t.co/3NF0xtUP3T]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deloitte has an interesting take on the performance reviews they conduct http://t.co/7tPbZS0QAH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Google CFO retires with a candid memo about work/life balance http://t.co/336HX5FLIH via @mashable]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEB_HR: @briankropp quoted via @globaleditor "Workers still want money but people aren't just chasing the biggest pay check" http://t.c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[great to see #walmart raising wages, they also need to make sure the communication is right to get maximum results  https://t.co/sBc7TIEA77]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great conversation last week re career pathing.  Managers focus on absolute progress, employees care about relative progress =misalignment]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[participate in our leadership effectiveness survey and receive your own leadership effectiveness report http://t.co/ylBhwNsPf5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are HR business partners a dying breed? - People Management Magazine Online http://t.co/vzL90whh8u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Being stressed makes you work harder for rewards, but you don't feel greater pleasure http://t.co/5AMHVKMziE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[good take on work world becoming less vertical and more horizontal -- need for #enterprisecontributors http://t.co/LN9DSW1ghD via @forbes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@AgtInEngagement @washingtonpost EE helps, but only if aligned against right goals.  Otherwise just effort without impact.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[join me at an upcoming event outside boston on how CHROs are working with the board http://t.co/1qW5uhSK5z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I found the gov of VA at the movies! http://t.co/aPSzEQreyl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEB_HR: According to @briankropp, orgs with effective collaborators saw revenue increase 5% more between 2012 &amp; 2013 http://t.co/qgb2pD…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEB_HR: Our very own @briankropp was mentioned in @SHRM's article "Taking the Dread out of #Performance Reviews" http://t.co/TRhVG95Unz…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Share an update. Type a name to mention a connection or company... http://t.co/0gFHVryaG6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Performance reviews don't really matter: Four ways to get improved performance http://t.co/0gFHVryaG6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An additional viewpoint on the Accenture performance review news http://t.co/zxurAJJl9v via @YahooFinance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nikibeth wonderful.  my colleague cartina Parks-Williams will reach out and find a time for us to talk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nikibeth as the person that wrote the CEB study on performance -- would love to here more about what you guys are doing re collaboration]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[cool new idea from #tasktorch  about teamwork http://t.co/3tLMzS3Td9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In big move, Accenture will get rid of annual performance reviews and rankings http://t.co/26VLMYirD4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Accenture changing performance review process, likely a good move http://t.co/FcMJPB5QKt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The careers of today fail employees and employers http://t.co/FSlupmeEyj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Organisational 'paradoxes' compromise productivity.  http://t.co/3HUm6dztcR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@SteveRattner CEB viewpoint on how to improve employee productivity -- drive collaboration, not more technology https://t.co/wcKelNgHcW?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[https://t.co/4ohCL7z7Oi https://t.co/HNzNgqMXo6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Companies are preventing the productivity increase Wall Street so desperately wants http://t.co/HLXU9XlJUw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to Establish a “One-Company” Corporate Culture https://t.co/iXEnm0lfz4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See our new Executive Guidance on how to dramatically improve employee productivity. https://t.co/8UeXKY7JRJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Want better performance?  Have fewer individual stars http://t.co/d5AQcN5NEc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["State of the C-Suite: Is Collaboration Stalling Your Business Plans?" on @LinkedIn https://t.co/21TXQfhh2i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some new thoughts from Google CHRO on diversity @Stitcher  http://t.co/PGCwn22cyE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[congrats @donnacmorris great work from #adobe on rethinking the performance review process http://t.co/QXfygHudu4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nice overview of enterprise contribution across the years  http://t.co/wnEQoVIKpd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[false modesty worse than bragging http://t.co/QZQ2bUa5Fn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to go fast, go alone. If you want to go far, go together -- how enterprise leaders lead  http://t.co/ih5XoUvvwr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[how to get performance reviews better, check out this podcast:  http://t.co/5XJKM77w6U from @RadioTimes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[better collaboration --&gt; 10,000+  £ revenue per employee http://t.co/OWVVD5JYJE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Michael_LukeUK: How effective are #PerformanceReviews in motivating workers? [Podcast] http://t.co/yWRRCM7GOM   - from @whyyradiotimes …]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @whyyradiotimes: 11-12, we talk performance reviews: why we hate them &amp; how to improve them w. Sam Culbert @UCLA &amp; @briankropp @CEB_HR h…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Join me on NPR to talk about Reviewing the Performance Review https://t.co/jMjcqdTIPQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[see our new work on enabling enterprise contributors   https://t.co/3kPzQAfYHf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @joshdavisphd: What we eat has important implications for our mental energy—and what we drink does as well. #TwoAwesomeHours http://t.co…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Downside of Being Competent http://t.co/vURZDnx3fz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @chiaracokieng: Reading @matthewxdixon 's book The Challenger Sale. Super useful and highly recommended for complex SaaS products... htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[how the military could benefit from #enterpriseleader behaviors http://t.co/4wd6pNufnH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[powerful to see google's investment in gender diversity  http://t.co/STVmg0c3Dt.  Here is how to make it work https://t.co/3Zh1u4YoF9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Wunmi_CEBNews: @CEB_HR's @briankropp will be @neuroleadership #2015NLS in 4 week. Talking about #compensation and #motivation http://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very cool picture of our latest insight run on managing change http://t.co/e8sjLXZuwT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[U.S. workers staying put, despite improved economy http://t.co/cSZvfkEEcv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Number Of U.S. Workers Actively Seeking Jobs Declines  http://t.co/vcraoFq92L via @TheStreet]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@workforcejames thanks for the conversation about the future of HR. http://t.co/qXsfO8sPSL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEB_TlntMonitor: Thx @alexiaer for using @CEB_TlntMonitor and @CEB insights from @briankropp in your story U.S. Workers Staying Put htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@WorkforceJames @CEB_HR thanks of the opportunity.  Great fun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Number Of U.S. Workers Actively Seeking Jobs Declines Significantly, http://t.co/Sei8tKs0bC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CEB_News 2 days to go until #ReimagineHR can't wait!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A court has ruled that time spent traveling to and from work is "work" http://t.co/OLDFdELOnC via @qz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How to motivate ambitious staff as flat-structured firms become more common - People Management Magazine Online http://t.co/Rnx0GU7LUK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@bertranddussert not only managers, but leaders.  Important to design work as a whole to be engaging -- and then make sure employees know.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bernanke misses re vets; forgets they are more engaged, loyal @dan4vets 
http://t.co/CEjKoscmeZ  http://t.co/BHk8oM4Kr0 via @BusinessPundit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[lack of layers in an organization often = lack of perceived opportunity for employees  http://t.co/i7xHnQjucr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@CEB_SHL @hrreview @HRTechAdvisor focus on employability and experiences critical to driving engagement with flatter organizations]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[do heroes and enterprise contributors rely on instinct or value? http://t.co/HtVrys3mPB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@drshow great conversation today on the future of the workplace on the diane rehm show   https://t.co/u492VbieYu http://t.co/yOXaFe7ysR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why big business is falling out of love with the annual performance review http://t.co/iUwYEnhHW1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Even with all the news  21% of companies still using forced rankings http://t.co/PMhMrsnvDJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Congrats @dcmorris @adobe smart decision for employees and the company http://t.co/posZf5Fy2p via @nbcnews]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[what is your hr partnership style?  https://t.co/VuTVE3Iern]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America's persistent problem: Unskilled workers August 07 - CNNMoney http://t.co/LcalM0T1Sz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[companies in the UK rethinking their approach to performance as well https://t.co/MUT4ByRUGK via]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could the federal government transform their performance reviews as well? http://t.co/8Ra9se9B89 via @govexec]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[great insights from anne sample on future of HR https://t.co/6tncEwz6uU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[95% of managers dissatisfied with performance mgmt. process http://t.co/pECdCtZuio via @PeopleMatters2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes performance reviews take a lot of time, but getting rid of scores will not save time http://t.co/p3PvLMTkXp via]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To Increase Corporate Productivity, Reduce Dependencies on Star Performers http://t.co/VuIYusXFMc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK workers switch off whilst 19% look for new career https://t.co/iGTGj4oCqD via @RecruitmentGV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OrganiSolutions: Besides birthday, ees most likely to make career decisions over holidays as spend time w friends/family @briankropp ht…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No Holiday Party?  No problem.   https://t.co/ETvSUdtfDS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Talent Matters: If the job market is improving, why are so many people staying put? https://t.co/PwThAUuHm0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[academic study showing that the hot air that leaders (sometimes) fill the room with actually lowers employee IQ. https://t.co/lv2BZsFlTu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@changemblog and based on CEB research, more than half of these will fail to achieve their goals https://t.co/wDtpYlq21P]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[how to create better careers for employees in the UK https://t.co/4t68hgB9Lo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According+to+CEB,+SEVEN+IN+10+EMPLOYEES+UNHAPPY+WITH+CAREER+OPPORTUNITIES https://t.co/UR2s0Kpp06 via Market+Research+Bulletin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Charles_Cotter: One unhappy staff member can cost an organisation £16,000 finds CEB https://t.co/yqH04x041k @GeorgieR30 @CIPD @CEB_HR @…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One unhappy staff member can cost an organisation £16,000, finds CEB - People Management Magazine Online https://t.co/owThF0xAA8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks for the nice words  @PattiClifford        https://t.co/oJPVrZHwxV    https://t.co/SCEA8dgi4D]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @OrganiSolutions: Employers/ees need to start thinking about careers in terms of continuous growth &gt; focusng on promotions @briankropp h…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CEOs with daughters are more responsible https://t.co/dMXJxZALxU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Enterprise Leaders are changing the workplace https://t.co/e5G5TnC2GM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ways to identify the next hot jobs https://t.co/oILjHsgTMs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HR: How to Close the Growing Productivity Gap | CEB Blogs https://t.co/VV7z6wKgWi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CEB_HR: Watch @briankropp give a sneak peek into the future of HR with @Workforcenews https://t.co/mdbJyJiLwN https://t.co/Hwn9qfJiex]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>