<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Charles Phoenix's Cherpumple: The "Monster" Pie-Cake:  http://t.co/MYHTvlHe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Petition to save the Vancouver Playhouse:  http://t.co/FN0kAz8v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chalk one up for theatre playwright:  http://t.co/YAYpWbEL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Closure of Playhouse affects other theatre companies:  http://t.co/qn3QxjKr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Author writes play in chalk in response to theatre closure:  http://t.co/HplOCMBw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicksartore @jessierelephant @joelgrinke @pitheatre @stephanietkong Next time!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For a very good, if somewhat predictable, romantic comedy, see Salmon Fishing in the Yemen.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yesterday, I read aloud excerpts from The Exquisite Hour with @RachelAberle as we walked from @VanPlayhouse to City Hall. @CityofVancouver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessieRelephant @AnthonyFloyd Ah, the romantic power of dressing like an opera-loving psychopath.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@nicksartore @jessierelephant @joelgrinke Indeed!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @thezoocrew: Still can't believe that Vancouver will be without a regional theatre. That is so not ok. #ILoveThePlayhouse]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @alinsenharbc: Vancouver Playhouse Theatre company to shut down http://t.co/yuzuRea7 How many theatre companies would the $$ of a ret ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jcritty: The more we say "no one supports the arts" the fewer people will.  #ILoveThePlayhouse #Rebuild #YVRTheatre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @jcritty: @VanSunArts Rally tonight @VanPlayhouse at 7:00pm. Many people available to comment on the social and economic loss as the  ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thanks to Max, Chelsea, Katie, John, Melanie, Dan and staff at @VanPlayhouse for their support: http://t.co/d0c5Xx2i https://t.co/zyZ9UTDt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@FirehallArtsCte @volcanotheatre @ChutzpahFest @TouchstoneInVan I did indeed!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@volcanotheatre 's Goodness at the @FirehallArtsCte is excellent! @ChutzpahFest @TouchstoneInVan #Vancouver #theatre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Catalyst__ca You're most welcome!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RachelAberle @jessierelephant What?  Didn't they know that it was time for your breakfast-lunch-dinner?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RachelAberle Yeah, they are most definitely contradicting their anti-consumerism message by creating a tonne of tie-in merchandise.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@alisonroberts12 Great to see you too!  It went well, thanks.  How about yours?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JessieRelephant: I just had a small heart flutter. So soon! “@VanPlayhouse: @jessierelephant #ExquisiteHour in the Recital Hall in j ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DannyZuker: As a parent I often wonder if there's anything I could've done differently to prevent the jealousy between my twins Lisa ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excited to see @volcanotheatre's Goodness at the @FirehallArtsCte ! @ChutzpahFest @TouchstoneInVan #Vancouver #theatre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessieRelephant Bosses of what?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Although it feels a bit like the poor man's WALL-E, and pales in comparison to the children's book, the The Lorax musical film is excellent!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@Catalyst__ca 's Hunchback at  @VanPlayhouse is amazingly unique! Go see it! @TheCultch #Vancouver #theatre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Musicals have the power to change minds:  http://t.co/xmzsF7zq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessieRelephant @nicksartore @moniqueepearson Oh, right.  Much more acceptable.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just received a phishing e-mail apparently from "a 59 years old widow diagnosed of coloratura cancer.". Yup!  You read that right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really?  Really really?  EXCLUSIVE:  Honey Boo Boo Child To Get Her Own Show!:  http://t.co/ILEDur09]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disney's Jungle Book, Crafted by Mary Zimmerman, Will Premiere at Goodman:  http://t.co/AFtamhs3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessieRelephant @nicksartore @moniqueepearson And for once the bad words weren&#39;t directed at me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessieRelephant @jonathanwinsby And baseball.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WonderettesVan: @customersright Yes there are still some tickets left at the door!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessieRelephant Well, it is now!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@yangjustinc Thanks for coming!  Glad that you enjoyed it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessieRelephant @jonathanwinsby And Charlie Brown isn't a baseball movie now?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @travisbedard: Take a moment every time you're having a "state of the industry" talk & separate "how do I get a job?" from "how do I  ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @gayvancouver: Your final chance this afternoon to see @WonderettesVan a show packed with pure fluff and four marvelous performances  ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @stopbcartscuts: BC arts people: Pls send us names +/or stories of artists/art workers forced to leave province for other cities/coun ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WonderettesVan: Last chance to see The Marvelous Wonderettes!! Only a few tickets left.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessieRelephant @jonathanwinsby Wait a minute! I fail to see how a viewing of A League of Their Own will butch me up!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Marvelous Wonderettes closes today at PAL Theatre. 1 chance left to see it! Limited amount of tickets left! Get yours ASAP! #Vancouver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WonderettesVan: Marvelous Wonderettes is sold out tonight!! Only a few tickets left for tomorrow so act fast!! #Vancouver #arts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Marvelous Wonderettes plays at PAL Theatre 'til Feb 26. Two chances left to see it! Tonight's show is sold out! Get your tickets ASAP!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A review of The Marvelous Wonderettes: http://t.co/nStH2HAO @WonderettesVan  #Vancouver #theatre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lose the squares at The Marvelous Wonderettes! Only 2 chances left!  Tonight: sold out! Get tickets ASAP! http://t.co/YpWY3zpZ #Vancouver]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @RyanInVancouver: See this show for those of us who can't... MT: @greenfieldsteve: The Marvelous Wonderettes @palvancouver 4chances l ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @intimateTHEATRE: Couldn't get a ticket to see #ILoveYouBecause ?  Check out @WonderettesVan , Lost Girls of Neverland or #Drood with ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WonderettesVan: Only 3 chances to vote for prom queen!! Check out this great blog via GVPTA http://t.co/KdR1V3I8 #Vancouver #theatre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WonderettesVan: Only a few tickets left for tonight and 2 for tomorrow!! Get your tickets fast...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Exquisite Hour is enjoying a production in Toronto at the same time as Vancouver's.  A review of that production:  http://t.co/zTBzKxSi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TELUS: Today is #EarthDay! We’ll donate $3 dollars to @TreeCanada for every retweet of this message http://t.co/OQd9nxK5 #TELUSCSR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It feels like summer in Kamloops today.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating to watch Radiohead's "Creep" performed by Broadway actor Carrie Manolakos:  http://t.co/lnNchbbJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Western Canada Theatre's The 25th Annual Putnam County Spelling Bee opens this evening at the Pavillion Theatre! #Kamloops #theatre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exquisite Hour Photos:  http://t.co/65MpHOQW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[First preview of Western Canada Theatre's production of The 25th Annual Putnam County Spelling Bee went excellently!  #Kamloops #theatre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Exquisite Hour is enjoying a production in Toronto at the same time as Vancouver’s. A preview for that production: http://t.co/pqlfE2t1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mary Philips Award Nominations:  http://t.co/jCB5AZkp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @straightarts: UBUNTU (The Cape Town Project) crosses a myriad of boundaries http://t.co/Prx4IUzW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In Q2Q for Western Canada Theatre's The 25th Annual Putnam County Spelling Bee. Exciting! #Kamloops #theatre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessieRelephant @titanicrealtime Fascinating!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Colin Campbell Award for Excellence in Technical Theatre:  https://t.co/XH5ZFwUW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[John Moffat & Larry Lillo Award:  http://t.co/HXfOP8qw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[33 Animals Who Are Extremely Disappointed In You:  http://t.co/aLZEhmE0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Theater groups chosen for Capitol Hill complex:  http://t.co/JfLQ34Kv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The show must go on:  God of Carnage to continue despite theatre closing:  http://t.co/g9KHozfZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can you name the Disney characters from their eyes?:  http://t.co/3nKJv52a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Exquisite Robots Work for the Fringe:  http://t.co/vmdf6QgP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessieRelephant  arrives soon!  Yay!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Excited to see Ubuntu at Western Canada Theatre this evening!  #Kamloops # theatre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Relephant Theatre:  The Exquisite Hour:  http://t.co/wEUNyEoX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Catch Me If You Can:  Frank Abagnale 10 Years Later:  http://t.co/Srr0Yn9q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ben Cameron:  The true power of the performing arts:  http://t.co/kkiwQsFp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessieRelephant For now . . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessieRelephant @littlemscant @christinequinty Of course I do!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessieRelephant How'd day two go?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[World Theatre Day Message 2012 | Stratford Shakespeare Festival:  http://t.co/LpqKS3DM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A new home for The Exquisite Hour:  http://t.co/rcEMFblV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The show must go on:  God of Carnage to continue despite theatre closing:  http://t.co/g9KHozfZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A review of The Great American Trailer Park Musical:  http://t.co/ZUPWGs8N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@JessieRelephant @gayvancouver Yay!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@christinequinty Maybe, but I still think that it's very good; and, IMHO, better than the other popular musical theatre-based T.V. program.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@djkeng Enjoy!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @F_C_Productions: Go see some theatre this weekend... FCP Alumni appearing in FLOP! (Studio 1398), The Great American Trailer Park... ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @gayvancouver: Lots of updates to our theatre listings. Contrary to popular belief theatre does not appear to be dead in Vancouver! h ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ghostlightpro 's The Great American Trailer Park Musical is at @palvancouver 'til Apr 1. Only 5 chances left to see it! #Vancouver #theatre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[$20 billion a year cannot buy us another Alberta:  http://t.co/wpvSIlMX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7 Reasons Why Theatre Makes Our Lives Better:  http://t.co/h2VkxjcE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@djkeng The Hunger Games was amazing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@christinequinty Smash is awful?  How figure you?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GVPTATheatre: World Theatre Day may be over but the list of "Special WTD" Offers is still happening. Check the Listings  http://t.co ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CityofVancouver: Volunteer for Vancouver’s Civic Agencies. Deadline for applications: tomorrow (March 29) @ 5pm http://t.co/WbFtAMsc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@ghostlightpro 's The Great American Trailer Park Musical is at @palvancouver 'til Apr 1. Only 6 chances left to see it! #Vancouver #theatre]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @VancouverFringe: The Great American Trailer Park Musical Mar 23-Apr 1 at PAL Studio Theatre http://t.co/UNaPZFhj Sounds rowdy doesn' ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Live_Vancouver: The Great American Trailer Park Musical - Musicals about spray cheese, road kill, strippers, flan and disco?  http:/ ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@RachelAberle You're most welcome!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[@djkeng @palvancouver It's just me trying to be serious.  :)]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>