<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Christian Louboutin  http://t.co/ksBoH0nqeD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The crashes people remember, but drivers remember the near misses. - Mario Andretti]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Make the customer the hero of your story.  Ann Handley - Chief Content Officer - MarketingProfs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I am not a glutton - I am an explorer of food. - Erma Bombeck]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Put on your red shoes, and dance the blues. - David Bowie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is but one game and that game is baseball.  - John McGraw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You may have to fight a battle more than once to win it. - Margaret Thatcher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stevie Wonder  http://t.co/wEPHfCmuO8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Favorite Things for Kids to Review  http://t.co/SptzzoBwUe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One Family’s Adoption Stories  http://t.co/hZycfoWHa0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the top science fiction movies of all time!  http://t.co/Vek7FQJYk8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Who Invented the Modern Watch?  http://t.co/eFv9GmhpxF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Having Fine Wine with Dinner - learn more! http://t.co/YHsNGYNMKI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The iPaperPad is not magical or revolutionary. It's a paper pad. A poor man's iPad LOL http://t.co/cmAfpN2oIX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would give a million bucks to have seen my mother say "cute shoes" to a naked Ashley Judd. --&gt; Brian Fies]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Motivation is the art of getting people to do what you want them to do because they want to do it. - Dwight D. Eisenhower]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Lovin' Spoonful  http://t.co/7dIhITdZsa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Barbara Mason  http://t.co/VTX88nHAYx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The time has come the Walrus said, To talk of many thing’s Of shoes and ships and sealing-wax of cabbages and kings - Lewis Carroll]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Horse! A Horse! my kingdom for a horse! - Shakespeare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One Person’s Musings on Elvis  http://t.co/5sdAfDOVZK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Allman Brothers Band  http://t.co/33bykVzqlz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only thing that ever sat its way to success was a hen. - Sarah Brown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The man who is old enough to know better is always looking for a girl who is not quite old.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of James Brown  http://t.co/y5QHG5xdNn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sex and the City changed New York - New York's become a big shoe store now, unfortunately. -  Chris Noth]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For the math geek in your life - the math clock... http://t.co/dUIINvb4TA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How much do you weigh? "Well, according to the charts, I should be six inches taller."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These Yoda Lights Must You Have!  Wonderful Geek Gear! http://t.co/1Pn1jnpUAf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's no secret. You just press the accelerator to the floor and steer left. - Bill Vukovich]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apollo: I will not serve under a man who questions my integrity. Adama: And I won't have an officer under my command who doesn't have any.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About James Taylor - his biography  http://t.co/kueMA6H4Ez]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why do elephants have trunks? - they don't have glove compartments]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Visiting  relatives are like fish. They begin to stink after 3 days!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Beverly Hillbillies is an American sitcom classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/wo4qn2a0C4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The great difficulty in education is to get experience out of ideas. - George Santayana]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Better to be a geek than an idiot.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is not a rock opera. This is not Tommy. I can write songs that emote, and that's it. - John Mellencamp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatness of a nation and its moral progress can be judged by the way its animals are treated.- Mahatma Gandhi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Everyone has a rock bottom.  - Prince]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A tax collector has what it takes to take what you got]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oh this is cool - a remote control spy plane with a mini-viewer - COOL http://t.co/R9MRDTV2vK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Review of The Little House on the Prairie Episode Called "Four Eyes"  http://t.co/6jV5JXaZo4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fall seven times, stand up eight. - Japanese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honeymoon:  A vacation before going to work for a new boss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think education is expensive, try ignorance - Derek Bok]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A shoe without sex appeal is as barren as a tree without leaves. - Rita De Acosta Lydig]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Ramones  http://t.co/2WRrWfPPeL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Getting Your Creative Writing Degree Online  http://t.co/iVRxSEaAkf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You maniacs! You blew it up! Oh, damn you! Damn you all to hell! - Taylor, Planet of the Apes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I looked and looked but I didn't see God. - Yuri Gagarin, 14 April 1961]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Really &amp; truly you can never have 2 many pairs of shoes. You need a pair for every mood &amp; everyone knows women have lots of moods. Anonymous]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dammit, man! I'm a doctor, not a physicist! - Leonard 'Bones' McCoy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In a meat-eating world, wearing leather for shoes and even clothes, the discussion of fur is childish. --&gt; Karl Lagerfeld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I didn't have a big fat Greek wedding, but I have a lot of fat Greek friends. Pete Sampras]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No one really knows who created Bitcoin - read about the fascinating history of Satoshi Nakamoto... http://t.co/qdhOc8v0mM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Frustrated at Cleaning Your Keyboards and Other Electronics?  Check Out Cyber Clean - Fast and Simple! http://t.co/eyXCLiZQ9V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A bird does not sing because it has an answer...  It sings because it has a song. - Chinese Proverb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read How to Use LinkedIn for Your Company   http://t.co/IB5FhAAU0C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cross Fit is a growing fitness craze - find out about its history here - http://t.co/uEnBxKVbCv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He's always itching for money, but he never scratches for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman's dress should be a like a barbed-wire fence: serving its purpose without obstructing the view. - Sophia Loren]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome basketball t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the basketball lovers in your life!   http://t.co/ysCZtMQMHR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hilarious Pacifier with a Mustache  - Kids and Adults will love it! http://t.co/c50rkGz80I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Kinds of Strategy Consulting Firms to Avoid  http://t.co/fQE8RYK5ld]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of LA Gear  http://t.co/dz8LZXRP0G]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Maxine Brown  http://t.co/JoHKwc4GCS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Alana's Lyme Journey - Part 3 - My Visit With Dr. McFadzean  http://t.co/JAZ5KQsizq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A philosopher is someone who knows what to do until it happens to him]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the History of Heineken International  http://t.co/OgkjDIAL21]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What is Fiverr Exactly and Why All the Buzz?  http://t.co/cHh3SVzmFA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Awesome Sword Umbrella - Eye Catching http://t.co/hZPuSazHl0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Finding the Right Fitness Gadgets for Better Health http://t.co/c90hjAge6C]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Schnauzers  http://t.co/QUIrhq2Dzz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Planning Beach Camping Tips  http://t.co/6uuc9vLoX6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[E.T. phone home - E.T.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So my degree was in political science, which I think was - the closest I could come to marketing is politics. - Steve Case]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If opportunity doesn't knock, build a door. - Milton Berle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of The Jackson Five  http://t.co/V3MZqLrXpH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What really decides consumers to buy or not to buy is the content of your advertising, not its form. - David Ogilvy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out the Top 10 Burger Chains in the US  http://t.co/A9YjpU2GkW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have no use for bodyguards, but I have very specific use for two highly trained certified public accountants. - Elvis Presley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DC Comics Ultimate Character Guide http://t.co/6vV8MJ1NU1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How To Grow Your Business With Twitter  http://t.co/flRCI8H2tj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My shoes are special shoes for discerning feet. - Manolo Blahnik]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Lynyrd Skynyrd  http://t.co/NdkEnx0TOB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd make a wonderful Lady Macbeth. I'll wear a pair of platform shoes or something - Bette Midler]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Very Unusual Hamburgers  http://t.co/swS3MbKC4x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Building Experts - Get Some Free Tips  http://t.co/dCtfZ7Odui]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to that hilarious sit-com Three’s Company - http://t.co/IuZ0Ywc14x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The quickest way to get a doctor today is to turn on your television set. . .]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Domestic Adoption - A Helping Hand To A New Life  http://t.co/2o2OVrNkDX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Utilize Strategy Consulting Firms: Gain a Competitive Advantage  http://t.co/L4J1R9N30M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Awesome Nintendo Wall Graphics! http://t.co/h1QH2zrYtd]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The trouble these days is there's no arrest for the wicked]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sawyer: You versus Sun - hot oil death match - my money's on you, Sheena. Kate: Thanks for your vote of confidence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd just as soon kiss a wookiee! - Princess Leia, The Empire Strikes Back]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The Top 10 European Beers  http://t.co/escQDqkPgv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips for Using Facebook Pages for Your Business  http://t.co/f8DIgvi2xD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn How To Invest In Penny Stocks  http://t.co/eGLR0c2KAg]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>