<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn the Keys to Using LinkedIn for Your Company  http://t.co/MNXrJ1TBo2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is 90% mental, the other half is physical - Yogi Berra]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cinderella is living proof that a pair of shoes can change your life…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating history of Wrigley Field!  http://t.co/KdGZTVZt2x]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feed sparingly and defy the physician. - James Howell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our Review of Amazon’s Popular Kindle Reader  http://t.co/rBdfci22ln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beautiful Women Prefer Nerds! A Real Man's Guide on How to Find, Date, and Romance the Perfect Woman! http://t.co/KIbUteY7yr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What people forget is that every movie that gets made keeps making money for somebody FOREVER. Dave Thomas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I live by a simple philosophy: Wear fine shoes and enjoy the best luck. - Qiana Markham]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lie travels around the earth while the truth is putting on its shoes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honeymoon:  A vacation before going to work for a new boss.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The less a man knows --  the more he tells it!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is Horology?  http://t.co/HWEipgqM5w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[History of Blogging  http://t.co/L2WSRoGd88]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Seniors and Social Networking  http://t.co/rV7q1XhOnI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Making money is a hobby that will complement any other hobbies you have, beautifully. Scott Alexander]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yep NFL Football Is Here To Stay!  http://t.co/VVYT620LQK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tips on Getting the Cheapest Car Loan  http://t.co/PjMu8tDCC4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most serious mistakes are not being made as a result of wrong answers. The truly dangerous thing is asking the wrong question P Drucker]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Most games are lost, not won! - Casey Stengel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why Some Young People Need Mentoring  http://t.co/8ID1EpetJ5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life begins when we first realize how soon it ends]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of France Joli  http://t.co/qxOvs3RO3L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sawyer: Son of a . . .! What's a head doing back here? Hurley: Oh, that's just Roger.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Its better to own the racecourse then the race horse - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An extravagance is anything you buy that is of no earthly use to your wife]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Jedi Dressing Gowns &amp; Star Wars Bath Robes! http://t.co/oD6FFnRNCT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Staple Singers  http://t.co/jM7d6FHfwN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3 meals a day a roof over my head, two cars, a boat, a power mower and a contented  wife -- why shouldn't I be in debt?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have ways of making money that you know nothing of.   John D. Rockefeller]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't care how long you've been around, you'll never see it all. - Bob Lemon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A lie travels around the earth while the truth is putting on its shoes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome ping pong &amp; table tennis tshirts &amp; gear - get something for the paddle lovers in your life! http://t.co/vLWpd2IMmO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About the Top 10 fitness gyms  http://t.co/Jwcy96LVXg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nothing makes a woman more beautiful than the belief that she is beautiful. - Sophia Loren]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Can You Really Make Things Invisible?  http://t.co/v86p3JAX04]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Totally Cool 80s Retro iPhone Case http://t.co/ZfT7vY0k4M]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helpful Tips for Web Marketing  http://t.co/2OtrL9zG3y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good pitching will beat good hitting any time, and vice versa. - Bob Veale]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like flying jet fighters in a gymnasium - Dick Trickle was asked what racing at Winchester Speedway was like.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Dan Fogelberg  http://t.co/rq52yzAoDg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball is a skilled game. It's America's game - it, and high taxes. - Will Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hello again, everybody. It's a bee-yooo-tiful day for baseball. -  Harry Caray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I went to college for four years. - Kim Kardashian]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can't sweep if you don't win the first game, and it's tougher to win two out of three if you lose the first one. - Todd Helton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Cool Pixie Espresso Maker - Compact and Cute! http://t.co/KieVlsvIjl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Modern Homesteading  http://t.co/Fu0bHnAKxn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Aretha Franklin  http://t.co/BNsqxSH1ek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Human sacrifice, dogs and cats living together --  mass hysteria! - Dr. Peter Venkman, Ghostbusters]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shoes transform your body language and attitude. They lift you physically and emotionally. - Christian Louboutin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've been carbo loading for the last 20 years in the off chance I have to go on a 4000 mile run across the US!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Men of lofty genius when they are doing the least work are most active. - Leonardo da Vinci]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Frustrated at Cleaning Your Keyboards and Other Electronics?  Check Out Cyber Clean - Fast and Simple! http://t.co/xd3SQq3ONc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Dan Fogelberg  http://t.co/rq52yzAoDg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[London Weight Loss Salon sign: "We value the pound."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Finance Trade Secrets  http://t.co/uD8qQeM6f8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Giant Squids - Hunters of the Deep  http://t.co/w035X7o2Fp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Review of Skylanders: Spyro’s Adventure  http://t.co/IetMVrkxx9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yesterday our troubles seemed so far away, I believe in yesterday. - The Beatles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greater your capacity to love, the greater your capacity to feel the pain.  Jennifer Aniston]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canada has Great Tourism Just Across the Border  http://t.co/kMx6ehO5Sn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out this gallery of the top 10 Asian beers!  http://t.co/4ohGh8MluV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Guide - Four ways to keep your printing environmentally friendly  http://t.co/OcwvOTT6bj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Strangers passing in the street, by chance two separate glances meet and I am you and what I see is me - Echoes - Pink Floyd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eat, drink and be merry, for tomorrow ye diet. - William Gilmore Beymer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China has blocked Twitter!!  Now 2 billion people will have no idea what I'm having for lunch.  Bummer!!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Fascinating History of Schnauzers  http://t.co/wc1EWIcW7w]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating History of American Idol   http://t.co/IRk8u5o9Qv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The probable reason some people get lost in thought is because it is unfamiliar territory to them]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The roots of education are bitter, but the fruit is sweet. - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome soccer t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the soccer lovers in your life!   http://t.co/X4JYxxFHlT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest thing in this world is not so much where we stand, as in what direction we are moving. - Oliver Wendall Holmes]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Some people are born on third base and go through life thinking they hit a triple. - Barry Switzer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where everything is possible miracles become common place, but the familiar ceases to be self-evident. - Eric Hoffer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel like punching the boss' jaw again  "Did you say again?" "Yes, I felt like doing it once before today!"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Small Dogs Can Make Great Pets - Picking the Right Breed  http://t.co/yie6s5nEFd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The law gives a man the right to open his wife's mail, but not the nerve]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was a pretty good coach and working with marketing was like coaching. - Bernard Ebbers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Mindy Carson  http://t.co/AlumrzlJg7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My life is an open book. With illustrations.  Hugh Hefner]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lassie is an American TV classic - read all about its history - http://t.co/uBmDuO09UQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consider the Tuba an Amazing Instrument  http://t.co/BNbmDVHqkE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think too little, you are sure to talk too much.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read a Short Introduction to ABBA  http://t.co/ci50JZYdSg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Auto racing is boring except when a car is going at least 172 miles per hour upside down. - Dave Barry]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WOW - Very Cool A Sticky Note Wrist Watch! http://t.co/JXTIBNC2dG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out The Top 10 European Beers  http://t.co/BXR2uA1c46]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Apple has great marketing, among the best PR and marketing in the world. - Ron Johnson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out This Very Cool Hand Juicer http://t.co/3RNO5dKkyB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thats the way Baseball go - Ron Washington]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If I have any beliefs about immortality it is that certain dogs I know will go to heaven, and very very few people. - James Thurber]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A toupee is ear to ear carpeting!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If it's too close to bother to buckle your seat belt it's close enough to walk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here Kitty Kitty Kitty! - Tony Stewart]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My wife is such a terrible cook the police made her register her stove as a deadly weapon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Dave Mason  http://t.co/Thz7gWWUMl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Advertising is the life of trade. - Calvin Coolidge]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Choosing To Use Solar Power  http://t.co/bghgpfAPnh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Planning Beach Camping Tips  http://t.co/o70xhgsLrR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Play is the only way the highest intelligence of humankind can unfold. - Joseph Chilton Pearce]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>