<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[A book is a device to ignite the imagination. - Alan Bennett]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you are irritated by every rub, how will you be polished? - Mawlana Jalal-al-Din Rumi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No matter what happened yesterday it is insignificant when compared to what lies within the core of your being today. - Sandy Brewer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't be afraid of enemies who attack you. Be afraid of the friends who flatter you. - Dale Carnegie]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/R8D3iLi8hK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listen to Inspiring Classics on your Android phone http://t.co/IdgWyxixu3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Zen_Moments: When you come right down to it, the secret of having it all is loving it all. ~ Dr. Joyce Brothers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheGodLight: In the end you get what you deserve, the amount of effort you put in determines the amount of joy that you receive.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Keep in mind to be kind. - A. Volta]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The most wasted of all days is one without laughter. - e.e. cummings]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[iPhone and iPad Apps for Quotes about life: http://t.co/kEEvDKp48S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Inspire_Us: Men are disturbed not by the things that happen, but by their opinion of the things that happen. - Epictetus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/gINSIWDGdq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any writer overwhelmingly honest about pleasing himself is almost sure to please others. - Marianne Moore]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And in the end it is not the years in your life that count. It is the life in your years. - Abraham Lincoln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is only one way to happiness and that is to cease worrying about things which are beyond the power or our will. - Epictetus]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which of theese 10 quotes is the best? http://t.co/68aMIPjbyc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What if love wasn't the act of finding what you were missing but the give-and-take that made you both match? - Jodi Picoult]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @motivational: We are progressing or retrograding all the while; there is no such thing as staying stationary in this life. -JF Clarke]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I know because I read...Your mind is not a cage. It's a garden. And it requires cultivating. - Libba Bray]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which of theese 10 quotes is the best? http://t.co/7gEFxYY3cE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The seventh quote here is a killer... http://t.co/tDgNPOhfXo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DavidRoads: Two things define you: Your patience when you have nothing, and your attitude when you have everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listen to Classic Books http://t.co/DlZFTQXyNz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GreatestQuotes: "Tact is the art of making a point without making an enemy." - Isaac Newton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Zen_Moments: Those with the biggest ideas can be shot down by those with the smallest minds. Think big anyway. ~ Dr. Kent M. Keith]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who can not adjust to change will be swept aside by it. Those who recognize change and react accordingly will benefit. - Jim Rogers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Live in moment, every day is the new beginning of life and every night is the end of life. - Santosh Kalwar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This Android Quotes app refreshes quotes, so you always have new quotes to enjoy: http://t.co/j1BWcu9554]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What's right isn't always popular, and whats popular isn't always right. - Sharon M. Draper]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listen to Inspiring Classic Books on your Android device http://t.co/YjFRv3KeYW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I would rather make mistakes in kindness and compassion than work miracles in unkindness and hardness. - Mother Teresa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheGodLight: Only that which you put your whole heart into stays forever, everything else will come &amp; go with the winds of change.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Get Quotes About Life app on iTunes: http://t.co/xPkVppwEsI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fiercest anger of all, the most incurable, Is that which rages in the place of dearest love. - Euripides]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Inspire_Us: Count your rainbows, not your thunderstorms.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @motivational: Wicked people are always surprised to find ability in those that are good. -Marquis De Vauvenargues]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you don't have the time to do something right, where are you going to find the time to fix it? - Stephen King]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DavidRoads: Time you enjoy wasting, was not wasted. -John Lennon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There's an old saying that applies to me: you can't lose a game if you don't play the game. - William Shakespeare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Life is not a matter of holding good cards, but of playing a poor hand well. - Robert Louis Stevenson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Which of theese 10 quotes is the best? http://t.co/bcnFXSOBd3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GreatestQuotes: "The longer we dwell on our misfortunes the greater is their power to harm us." - Voltaire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I believe that every single event in life happens in an opportunity to choose love over fear. - Oprah Winfrey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To live a life is to live with struggle because life is to live and to live we struggle. - Santosh Kalwar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I prepare for the worst, but hope for the best. - Jackie Chan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[People are just as happy as they make up their minds to be. - Abraham Lincoln]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reality provides us with facts so romantic that imagination itself could add nothing to them. - Jules Verne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you see these 10 Inspirational Quotes? http://t.co/p59kJN0jNV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need your support, please get and rate our Quotes app: http://t.co/1RXAwv62as]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DeepLifeQuotes: Know your worth. Know the difference between what you're getting and what you deserve. - Unk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Inspire_Us: A lion doesn't concern himself with the opinions of a sheep.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The seventh quote here is a killer... http://t.co/gEynIZoe8i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listen to Classic Books while you work http://t.co/IqaW2WAB34]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Time flows away like the water in the river. - Confucius]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fate is nothing but the deeds committed in a prior state of existence. - Ralph Waldo Emerson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @motivational: In order to win, you must expect to win.  -Richard Bach]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listen to Great Classic Motivational Books on your Android device http://t.co/PNFYf79rmV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And yet,to say the truth, reason and love keep little company together nowadays. - William Shakespeare]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DavidRoads: If you want to feel rich, just count all the gifts you have that money can't buy.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sometimes, the way you think about a person isn’t the way they actually are http://t.co/2wdh8wxhaZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I believe in the ability to choose. I believe this life is made up of our choices and their consequences-the good and the bad. Kelseyleigh R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Need new quotes to share? Get this iPhone app http://t.co/BGHAKjo80h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you see these 10 Inspirational Quotes? http://t.co/Cjb3VTmD06]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You will like this Quote app, get it now, thank us later: http://t.co/lBpvQBOq9O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These 10 Inspirational Quotes is a must to read http://t.co/9F3kHwzT9o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GreatestQuotes: "Deal with the world the way it is, not the way you wish it was." - John Chambers]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love is like a virus. It can happen to anybody at any time. - Maya Angelou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Writing is not lying, nor is it theft. It is a journey and search for transparency between one's words and one's soul. - Richard Flanagan]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listen to Classic Books while you work http://t.co/ydDQQFYxgj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need your support, please get and rate our iPhone app: http://t.co/4pOPNJUC13]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DeepLifeQuotes: Bad things happen when you trust the wrong people. - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WomenOfHistory: My kids are my heart and soul. They will always be my babies, even when they grow old.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[http://t.co/WeSk4Gr5SM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As long as we draw breath, we owe it to the ones we loved and lost to live out our lives without wasting them on regrets. - Sharon Sala]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It does not matter how long you live, but how well you do it. - Martin Luther King Jr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listen to Great Classic Motivational Books on your Android device http://t.co/Bcdq5Jp1gZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One word frees us of all the weight and pain of life: That word is love. - Sophocles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are not called by God to do extraordinary things, but to do ordinary things with extraordinary love. - Jean Vanier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Inspire_Us: The best thing about the future is it comes one day at a time.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listen to Inspiring Classics on your Android phone http://t.co/lnXllNxaeL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A friend is someone who knows the song in your heart and sings it back to you when you've forgotten the words. - Donna Roberts]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You might like this: Quotes About Life Android app! http://t.co/Z01tcqjUw0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need your support, please get and rate our Quotes app: http://t.co/KQIX1NF4YS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @motivational: Through seeking and blundering we learn. -Johann Wolfgang Von Goethe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DavidRoads: Let love win.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Let men tremble to win the hand of woman, unless they win along with it the utmost passion of her heart! - Nathaniel Hawthorne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listen to Great Classic Motivational Books on your Android device http://t.co/WyduZeLndb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[war grows out of desire of the individual to gain advantage at the expense of his fellow man. - Napoleon Hill]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I can chase you, and I can catch you, but there is nothing I can do to make you mine. - Morrissey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GreatestQuotes: "A bird doesn't sing because it has an answer, it sings because it has a song." - Maya Angelou]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So many believe that it is love that grows, but it is the knowing that grows and love simply expands to contain it. - William P. Young]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow, these yoga pictures will actually inspire you! http://t.co/5QmoGjHLlw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Seeing is not believing. Believing is seeing! You see things, not as they are, but as you are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Age does not protect you from love, but love to some extent protects you from age. -Jeanne Moreau]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These 10 Inspirational Quotes is a must to read http://t.co/z6PoavV7Vy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A man who dares to waste one hour of time has not discovered the value of life - Charles Darwin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One becomes a beginner after one thousand days of training and an expert after ten thousand days of practice. - Masutatsu Oyama]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you see these 10 Inspirational Quotes? http://t.co/D0HWcKeuqL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't be afraid to take a big step if one is indicated. You can't cross a chasm in two small jumps. - David Lloyd George]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>