<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch this quadrotor turn into a trirotor and keep flying: In a video that similar to those videos where humans push around ATLAS, researchers at Delft University of Technology have created a system that will let a quadrotor drone keep flying even if one… https://t.co/AD3SWepktg https://t.co/HCQnHTJqXY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Helpdesk Analyst: Premier Work Solutions is looking to recruit an experienced Helpdesk/Service Desk Analyst on behalf of our prestigious client based in Manchester/Cheshire. Job Summary: Working within the Service/Help Desk environment administrating and… https://t.co/cFa6JSFwZ8 https://t.co/nVUF73I0IL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CAFM support/administration: CAFM support Our client, an FM services provider has identified a requirement for a CAFM administrator. This is a great opportunity to become part of their Software Solutions Team which will aims to deliver and maintain high… https://t.co/y8Yc6y6DjR https://t.co/M5ji47LSk6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AllTrails gets $75M to keep hikers happy: Spectrum Equity is making a big bet on AllTrails, that app for outdoorsy folk. https://t.co/wfCCvvTLOQ https://t.co/paoW50j7gl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BI Developer: BI Developer Location – Northampton Salary – £40,000 to £50,000 A well-established, fast paced company are looking for an experienced Business Intelligence Developer to join the growing team. You will be working within a highly capable,… https://t.co/BEp65RBZZ5 https://t.co/B76I7jyj1E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Contract Business Analyst – Imm Start: Business Analyst – Immediate Start – City Centre – £350pd Being part of a large-scale digital project is always interesting, especially if you become involved at an early stage. So, if you are a Business Analyst… https://t.co/sc5ilerVA1 https://t.co/LJhFUuQqrD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The £50 note is changing and here's why https://t.co/8czv2ORtUC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook prototypes Unsend 6 months after Zuckerberg retracted messages: In April, TechCrunch broke the news that some of Mark Zuckerberg’s Facebook messages were deleted from recipients’ inboxes in what some saw as a violation of user trust and abuse of… https://t.co/pTqbNQltl4 https://t.co/KTnn8iONA0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer: A growing business that aims at facilitating the movement of vehicles across the UK is looking for an experienced Developer to join its team in Birmingham, in the heart of the city centre, walking distance from Snow Hill station!    The role… https://t.co/oZQKgRelUB https://t.co/0DoeTTHXUD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Application Analyst: An exciting opportunity for an Applications Analyst (MS Dynamics – CRM) has become available for our client in the North West. North West Based Contract length – 9 months An exciting opportunity for an Applications Analyst (MS… https://t.co/4GKnH5mjbO https://t.co/qpLpYDl1X9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Developer (JavaScript): Avanti Recruitment is currently partnering with a leading Digital Software company based in the Centre of Manchester who are recruiting for a JavaScript Developer to join their technical team. The purpose of the role is… https://t.co/mIxK3uDAat https://t.co/GT3lPNVGA0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stephen Hawking’s final paper about black holes is now online: Stephen Hawking passed away earlier this year at the age of 76, but his incredible intellect isn’t yet done contributing to the scientific community. The acclaimed physicist’s final paper is… https://t.co/bNemvHiiG2 https://t.co/evhIGCZW9a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python SQL Developer – (Retail Tech): Python SQL Developer – (Retail Tech) If you are a Python SQL Developer who wants to work in the Centre of London within a tight-nit dynamic team on a software of platform that uses AI and algorithms to support… https://t.co/HUYRVWpoZp https://t.co/wdDts5IQP5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software / Hardware Asset Manager / SAM: Software Asset Manager / Software Asset Management Lead / SAM £(Apply online only)/day – Bristol onsite SNOW Asset Management A Software Asset Lead / Software Asset Manager is required to join an organisation in… https://t.co/2VNhVSnTG3 https://t.co/z6b1VRgKO6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PHP Developer (Backend): We are searching for a talented and skilled Back-end, PHP driven Web/Web Application Developer for our client, a well-respected and very successful digital business located in Somerset. You will be working on new and existing… https://t.co/XkIUl6APGu https://t.co/kKbrR1mGej]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elon Musk: Teslaquila tequila is ‘coming soon’: Tesla CEO Elon Musk confirmed Friday in a tweet that the Tesla-branded tequila called “Teslaquilla”—the bottle of liquor that co-starred in his April Fool’s Day joke about the automaker filing for… https://t.co/kiFfIs0KLu https://t.co/orhbMXgguj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Operations Manager: Becoming an Operations Manager with Capita Workplace Technology (London/Birmingham): The role of Operations Manager will sit within the Professional Services team with a direct report to the Head of Post Sales. The position will be… https://t.co/WnJVwcREjG https://t.co/83EWvAFRaG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PPC Executive: PPC Executive Chester £25,000 ShortList Recruitment have a brilliant opportunity for a PPC Executive to join a market leading Chester based company. The right PPC Executive will be a savvy and credible individual who can work with a range… https://t.co/jyxsEITb7m https://t.co/rpUR9nu8yY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer, SpatialOS: Software Engineer, SpatialOS London Engineering – Engineering Full-time Permanent Our Purpose Improbable is dedicated to building powerful technology designed to help solve previously impossible problems and enable the… https://t.co/gaCPcvGQWS https://t.co/ba29DmZr2e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Venmo bumps up instant transfer fee to 1 percent of the total amount: If you’re a frequent Venmo user, you might want to double-check your settings because the company just changed up their fee structure for instant transfers and it may result in more of… https://t.co/5tWzEszPHl https://t.co/9MlEJrC43W]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Associate Dir Product Manager: Associate Dir Product Manager Job Title: Associate Dir Product Manager About IHS Markit IHS Markit harnesses deep sources of information, analytics and expertise to forge solutions for the industries and markets that drive… https://t.co/4onXjWpLYg https://t.co/gadkVS5mqh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FCC resorts to the usual malarkey defending itself against Mozilla lawsuit: Mozilla filed a lawsuit in August alleging the FCC had unlawfully overturned 2015's net neutrality rules, by among other things "fundamentally mischaracteriz[ing] how internet… https://t.co/blcM71sYem https://t.co/f2Cgk4kUiQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[iOS Developer – Nottingham: iOS Developer – Nottingham A fantastic opportunity has arisen to join a leading digital agency in the heart of Nottingham as an iOS Developer. This role can offer up to £35,000 DOE + benefits. The company are experts at… https://t.co/a7J16I3Hmu https://t.co/573gs8h4oF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Graduate JavaScript Developer: Graduate JavaScript Developer – London – Machine Learning/Ai – £32,000  One of London’s most exciting start-ups with an exceptional global reputation are looking for the best graduate engineers from the top tier… https://t.co/1an4YvFjOe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Games Producer – Mobile Games – Central London: Games Producer Mobile Games Central London • Flexible office hours • 25 days of annual leave + 8 UK Bank Holidays + Christmas • Competitive pension plan • Profitability Bonus • Private healthcare •… https://t.co/Y7Gm7lAojD https://t.co/tFYvdylc6N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New wave founders are headed to Startup Battlefield Latin America: TechCrunch is thrilled to announce that Rappi co-founder Sebastian Mejia, Enjoie founder Ana McLaren and Konfío founder and CEO David Arana will be joining us on stage at Startup… https://t.co/O44PRGzMrA https://t.co/HsjeSiwfYF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Test Application Engineer – Belgium: Role of Test Application: * Working on real customer environments * Work in a small team * Learn new technologies * Work in simulated and artificial environments * Performing tests at customers sites * Prototype… https://t.co/sa3JtWtCFQ https://t.co/dDyDnrspnd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[China car sales slump ripples globally https://t.co/tXkyWqpyzq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Infrastructure Support Engineer: Infrastructure Support Engineer – Nottingham Up to £35k + Bonus + Fully Funded Microsoft Certifications One of the Midlands fastest growing and successful IT services business with both a managed IT and Professional… https://t.co/L1D2AtO93L https://t.co/rz34NFCNPB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook bans hundreds of clickbait farms for ‘coordinated inauthentic behavior’: Facebook has announced a relatively small but significant purge of bad actors from the platform: 810 pages and accounts that have "consistently broken our rules against… https://t.co/krha8PlhjR https://t.co/hdBGkC1yTT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Service Desk Support Analyst: Service Desk Analyst The position An opportunity is available for a Service Desk Analyst to join an established and lively support team within a leading healthcare marketing business. This is a very successful organisation… https://t.co/l6RvVqk5gF https://t.co/ZpCbyT8Omi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Service Desk Support Analyst: The position An opportunity is available for a Service Desk Analyst to join an established and lively support team within a leading healthcare marketing business. This is a very successful organisation in a continually… https://t.co/1lFDJf9b8x https://t.co/nwume1TdKB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Software Engineer: A global leader in marketing performance analytics are looking to expand their Newcastle-based software team rapidly with a talented mid/senior Software Engineer (there are multiple positions available). They have offices all over the… https://t.co/LzRt9mmZVV https://t.co/HwKvNw56Rr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CoD: Black Ops 4 is available today: CoD: Black Ops 4 is available today, marking yet another chapter in the franchise’s history. The Black Ops series, developed by TreyArch, tends to be one of Call Of Duty’s most popular, and Black Ops 4 doesn’t show… https://t.co/s3vA6gdH7Q https://t.co/UmIAdMnJLL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Quality Assurance Tester: We have an exciting opportunity to join a reputable and dynamic company in the heart of Berkhamsted as a Quality Assurance Tester. As a Quality Assurance Tester you will support and advise on the infrastructure set-up, help… https://t.co/YPkC0tQiZg https://t.co/AMhF9n3xek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mulesoft Developer: Mulesoft Developer required to join on a 6-12 month initial contract opportunity for a leading company based in Liverpool City Centre. Key skills required: * Mulesoft * Utilising and applying enterprise integration patterns * Source… https://t.co/7asKw5WeU1 https://t.co/mj9eSDcymX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Regis hairdressing group seeks rescue https://t.co/Dp3o3IctLN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hamley's reports toughest year since 1760 https://t.co/3y0oOph1jC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps Engineer – Cloud &amp; Blockchain: DevOps Engineer – Cloud &amp; Blockchain! Contract Role – Great Day-rate Location – Dublin City Centre Description Do you want to work with one of the most innovative Fintech/Blockchain companies based in the heart of… https://t.co/eRdpa7aKa4 https://t.co/efaCAui822]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch Boston Dynamics’ humanoid robot leap up massive steps like it’s nothing: Two years ago, Boston Dynamics’ humanoid robot Atlas needed a big ol’ safety tether to shuffle its way down a flat hiking trail. Five years ago it needed a big, bolted-down… https://t.co/YhcWu6R34F https://t.co/izG2GFNPMQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Scrum Master: Scrum Master, Permanent, South Dublin My client an International Bank is undergoing a period of rapid growth are looking for an experienced Scrum Master to join their expanding team in South Dublin. The Role: In this role you will leading… https://t.co/Y8kSU4HGmX https://t.co/jtSL7oRw1j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sports Direct buys iconic Glasgow Frasers building https://t.co/I0hXrRcD7m]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C++ Software Engineer: C++ Software Engineer My client, a global company operating within the transportation industry are seeking to hire several C++ Software Engineers at all levels to join their rapidly expanding team based in West Dublin Due to their… https://t.co/S0YvbF5AN1 https://t.co/yZbDWxBWR7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why missing Saudi journalist’s Apple Watch is an interesting, but unlikely, lead: Police investigating the missing Saudi journalist Jamal Khashoggi are searching for his Apple Watch to obtain his health and location data before his disappearance. But… https://t.co/rL3JqRX0ZP https://t.co/KuBLx0stvG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Graduate Systems Support (Air Traffic): Are you a recent Computer Science, Networking or Software Engineering graduate? Do you have an interest in state-of-the-art technology? We have a truly rewarding opportunity for you! Systems Support Engineer – Air… https://t.co/G5g3LYmIyQ https://t.co/8R27nqubbn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Patisserie Valerie says finance chief arrested https://t.co/gGCZHgFiSv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hammond expects 'better economic outcomes' from Brexit deal https://t.co/axYZgypIhM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud Security Engineer: Cloud Security Engineer (Move into DevSecOps) Are you a Security Engineer who is keen to own the Security function for a FTSE 250 company? What to help drive best practice through the development team? All of this whilst working… https://t.co/MnJWTi5let https://t.co/QUKCYK4yeI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jamal Khashoggi: Branson halts $1bn Saudi investment talks https://t.co/h4gW8DLPwO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trainee Web Developer: Would you like a job in Web Developer? Are you an ambitious and enthusiastic techie, looking to change their life by becoming the next Bill Gates or Mark Zuckerberg? Well now is your chance to become a Web Developer! The Training… https://t.co/QZflJSIUGC https://t.co/MNjQbyE3PD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[YC-grad Papa raises $2.4M for its ‘grandkids-on-demand’ service: Alexis Ohanian's Initialized Capital and Ashton Kutcher's Sound Ventures participated in the round for the Y Combinator graduate. https://t.co/k6IjoahFWm https://t.co/0ZhJSYksVT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Graduate IP Analyst: Graduate IP Analyst – Computer Science / Engineering/ Physics / Maths / Data Science / Chemical Engineering Job Location: Winchester (Relocators Welcome) Job Type: Full Time, Permanent Start Date: Flexible Salary: Negotiable… https://t.co/aJApNBLlWT https://t.co/e9ekXuu7Rm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trainee Web Developer: Trainee Web Developer With us you can learn in your own time, whether you are unemployed or work full-time you can find the time to study when it suits you. We provide you with all the tools you need to succeed and get you… https://t.co/4KPpgHhaXV https://t.co/BWOZ9aHTT0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Engineering Manager, SpatialOS: Engineering Manager, SpatialOS London Engineering – Engineering Full-time Permanent Our Purpose Improbable is dedicated to building powerful technology designed to help solve previously impossible problems and enable the… https://t.co/bXI8q4tkL6 https://t.co/PjS2prlGVZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook mistakenly deleted some people’s Live videos: This time instead of exposing users’ data, a Facebook bug erased it. A previously undisclosed Facebook glitch caused it to delete some users’ Live videos if they tried to post them to their Story and… https://t.co/9IMud2OzkS https://t.co/AKcgQcJGu5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Contract Administrator M/F: General information Entity Bouygues Energies &amp; Services operates in over 30 countries globally. Using the expertise of our 2,640 UK employees, we provide engineering and service capabilities committed to designing, building,… https://t.co/wiA0duTGcH https://t.co/SZyMr5HXs2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Part Qualified Accountant: Part Qualified Accountant REF. BAW5274 MASS COMMODITIES|Production, Operations and R&amp;D PLEASE NOTE THIS IS A TALENT ACQUISITION OFFER This position is in high demand in the market and it is likely this offer will be active… https://t.co/DErmfyossv https://t.co/dhPjEVEHQP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce Functional Consultant: Salesforce Functional Consultant / Manchester A market leading consultancy are looking to hire a Salesforce Functional consultant to expand their Salesforce practice in Manchester. You will bring good Salesforce… https://t.co/s6ZvpEfkRO https://t.co/whCSkKFJER]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sky battles: Fighting back against rogue drones https://t.co/n03OHZhmXd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[G2 Crowd, a business software marketplace, raises another $55M at just under a $500M valuation: G2 Crowd, a platform that lets businesses search for, compare reviews and pricing for, and then buy software and other IT services — it likes to refer to… https://t.co/HIqJJMrNko https://t.co/sn2qA1g8LW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Car groups condemn grant cuts for electric and hybrid vehicles https://t.co/CLhlJtOCdd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Entry-Level Consultant (STEM graduates only): Job Title: Entry-Level Consultant (STEM graduates only) Location: Bracknell Salary: £32,250 REF: J2521:M4:GJ:GC:BRA Sector: Technology Our client: An innovative, dynamic technology company are on the lookout… https://t.co/7lzeQ9o16K https://t.co/2mBotrBj3l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pub industry in plea over Budget tax rise https://t.co/ItEktZY0rb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Release Automation Engineer: Build and Release Engineer Location: Staffordshire 3 Month Contract MAIN RESPONSIBILITIES My clients Build and Release team are looking for a Build and Release Engineer to join this exciting and vital part of their business.… https://t.co/yChX3RBb3q https://t.co/9okFtHEKW6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook rolls out 3D photos that use AI to simulate depth: What if you could peek behind what’s in your photos, like you’re moving your head to see what’s inside a window? That’s the futuristic promise of Facebook 3D photos. After announcing the feature… https://t.co/q60mL1hExM https://t.co/0E8pCacZdV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Python Developer (FinTech): Python Developer – (FinTech) If you are driven Python Developer who wants to be involved in shaping the direction of this business as well as playing a crucial part in the core platform of a FinTech company then this might… https://t.co/4AjEcOs2em https://t.co/3mrWekRxS2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Analyst – £50,000: Business Analyst – £50,000 Key skills: Business Analyst, Business Analysis, Business Consultant, Requirements Gathering, Stakeholder Management, Agile Business Analyst wanted by a major UK employer. This company is going… https://t.co/ZVGijSNXqA https://t.co/OMGtT3DaeX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pocket’s reading app won’t sound so robotic now: Last year, Mozilla made its first acquisition by snatching up Pocket, the Instapaper competitor that helps you save longer articles for later reading. Today, this popular reading app is getting a major… https://t.co/GmOEnDuetY https://t.co/T4hjE73AZf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump says Chinese 'lived too well for too long' https://t.co/E0bWkalbxj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Infrastructure Engineer: IT Infrastructure Engineer Our client is a world leader in the defence and security systems based in South Wales, providing security to critical infrastructure including government clients. They are currently recruiting for an… https://t.co/NVnVgRI2SB https://t.co/TxW0mcDw5r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[iOS Developer: This is a fantastic opportunity for an iOS Developer to work for this global financial organisation. This is a fantastic opportunity for an iOS developer. Due to the market, leading success of this organisations mobile channel including… https://t.co/Js9tat2UQA https://t.co/dqGoqdb0Ee]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Audit Facebook and overhaul competition law, say MEPs responding to breach scandals: After holding a series of hearings in the wake of the Facebook -Cambridge Analytica data misuse scandal this summer, and attending a meeting with Mark Zuckerberg himself… https://t.co/DN36XtfQVo https://t.co/jAsukfoyrp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Network Engineer: Senior Network Engineer / 3rd Line Network Engineer – Peterborough £38,000 – £45,000 + on-call + benefits I'm looking for a Senior / 3rd Line Network Engineer for a major client based in Peterborough. The Senior Network Engineer… https://t.co/2GYLV67xMm https://t.co/Ege4DR9D2f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Brexit: No deal brings risk of stockpiling says watchdog https://t.co/zNdAIVHB5n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SC Cleared Network Architect – 12 month contract: CCIE / CCNP / Network Architect / Network Engineer / Cisco / ACI / Cloud / Azure / Design / Layer 3 / 12 Month Contract My Manchester-based client are currently recruiting for a SC Cleared Network… https://t.co/kc1Ur1vIqe https://t.co/fVXdUACXyv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[eBay tax bill rises after HMRC review https://t.co/Zaufq4H15p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is the FTSE 100? https://t.co/CjC8YSDhJN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft adds 60,000 patents to the Open Invention Network: Microsoft announced today that it’s joined open-source patent group Open Invention Network in an effort to help shield Linux and other open-source software from patent-related suits. As part of… https://t.co/HXg2qvgNRD https://t.co/QxVAnqSSY2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Agile Delivery Manager / Agile Coach – £60,000: Agile Delivery Manager / Agile Coach – £60,000 plus excellent package (see below) Key Skills: Agile Coach, Agile Delivery Manager, Agile Evangelist, Release Manager, Scrum Agile Delivery Manager/Agile Coach… https://t.co/2OVkXizS8b https://t.co/XQwgZrYRVa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Content Creator: Amazing full time Content Creator opportunity, working as part of a growing Southampton based development team delivering quality content to clients and internally, on a permanent basis. The Company was established over 10 years ago and… https://t.co/YYwuw06TXl https://t.co/ZJp2J4i4D0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gogoprint raises $7.7M to expand its online printing business in Asia Pacific: Gogoprint, a startup that is aiming to disrupt the traditional printing industry in Southeast Asia, has pulled in a $7.7 million investment as it prepares to expand its… https://t.co/p1evZRmOHo https://t.co/bzUa29L1mc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DevOps / System Administrator: A leading global consultancy have an immediate requirement for DevOps / System Administrator to join them at their offices on the outskirts of Belfast in Northern Ireland. Key Skills: DevOps, System Administrator, Linux,… https://t.co/MpzD6lyoD9 https://t.co/sYExweLoHD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Standing desks 'boost work performance' https://t.co/JcEwT1CNoO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Telesales Executive (Part Time): Are you an experienced Telesales Executive with a bubbly personality who is seeking part time hours to maybe fit around other personal commitments then this role could be just what you are seeking. You will be required to… https://t.co/OT6JmsxgS2 https://t.co/KP1kY0G847]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Support – 1st/2nd Line Support – Birmingham: IT Support – 1st/2nd Line Support – Birmingham Title: IT Helpdesk Support – 1st/2nd Line Support Location: Birmingham Start date: ASAP Salary: £21,000 – £23,000 + Bonus + Excellent Package IT Support –… https://t.co/ZipVfVB21W https://t.co/lDIL4nTEHW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Origin launches protocol for building cheaper decentralized Ubers &amp; Airbnbs: The sharing economy ends up sharing a ton of labor’s earnings with middlemen like Uber and Airbnb, and $38 million-funded Origin wants the next great two-sided marketplace to be… https://t.co/giLHeUOZBu https://t.co/SK2Jo5gBM4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Project Engineer: Project Engineer REF. BAW5294 MASS COMMODITIES|Production, Operations and R&amp;D PLEASE NOTE THIS IS A TALENT ACQUISITION OFFER This position is in high demand in the market and it is likely this offer will be active shortly. Thus, we are… https://t.co/x1Vx4UR0o2 https://t.co/CsXulW5Iwq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[FP&amp;A Manager:   Job Description – FP&amp;A Manager (40874) Job Description  FP&amp;A Manager-40874 Description   EMEA Financial Planning &amp; Analysis Manager – £65,000 to £75,000 Hitachi Consulting is the global management consulting, solutions and IT services… https://t.co/kN0TkNeh9F https://t.co/eltRyyz6hX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Product Marketing Manager: Product Marketing Manager London Marketing – Marketing Full-time Permanent Our Purpose Improbable is dedicated to building powerful technology designed to help solve previously impossible problems and enable the creation of new… https://t.co/Rbu4bYwDxS https://t.co/FkRI3KaJoc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Self-driving car startup Aurora becomes Pennsylvania’s first ‘authorized’ tester: Aurora, the buzzy self-driving car startup, has become the first company officially authorized by the Pennsylvania Department of Transportation to test its vehicles on… https://t.co/Upcdwrry01 https://t.co/T96fUZspqP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Salesforce Solution Architect, Marketing Cloud (London) – Bluewolf: 167471BR Job Description We are Bluewolf, an IBM company. We help organizations come up with simple solutions to their customer experience problems through customization across the… https://t.co/Gyp9Cc3eyL https://t.co/34x17565KK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior Front End Developer: Senior Front End Developer- London- £65000 My client is looking for a Senior Front End Developer to join an ever-growing development team. Working closely with the whole Product team you will help create an environment of… https://t.co/8iXvj4DPB6 https://t.co/Vgj9jYFsBR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chinese man charged with US aviation 'espionage' https://t.co/mV7spuYmhb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US shares suffer sharpest drop in months https://t.co/H84tpQuxho]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[James Murdoch tipped to lead Tesla board https://t.co/pC1DluhXvA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tyre firm plans to cut 300 jobs at Melksham factory https://t.co/ASiWVZ2y82]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[NET Developer: Full Stack .NET Developer – Sussex – Contract A well distinguished client of mine is looking for a Full Stack .NET Developer based in Sussex on a contract basis The role will include carrying out development tasks, hands-on application… https://t.co/lPt7ef4JxK https://t.co/yuxn7WOaK9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kahoot, the educational gaming startup, has raised another $15M, now at a $300M valuation: School’s back in session and a startup that’s building games to help students learn has moved to the top of the class. Kahoot — the educational gaming startup out… https://t.co/YfYBP7Fy5k https://t.co/TVAsnw3Hud]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Europe stocks sharply lower after US and Asia sell-off https://t.co/VCKEDHRECE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dynamics 365 CRM: Dynamics 365 CRM Consultant Turnaround project The system is built but it is clunky and the workflows don't function properly. Currently the system has no data and is on the test bed. They will be using the CRM for tracking finance,… https://t.co/nPN2qHy013 https://t.co/yX8rwwcGAV]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>