<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Why isn't @Target's #grocery offering helping to pull in more shoppers? https://t.co/C93pPdCcUW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Choosing #GMO crops helped 1 #farmer reduce nitrogen &amp; phosphorous loss, cut erosion &amp; decrease use of #Pesticides https://t.co/SuqwOZhRiS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[For #snack bars is it better to be in the #breakfast bar or #nutrition bar set? @EatBobos says the latter: https://t.co/FNLmLqr4UC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@CampbellSoupCo shares best practices to disclose #GMO in a way that is informative, not frightening for shoppers https://t.co/F42O8678iX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Sunwarrior CEO chats about changing competitive landscape for #protein &amp; where it is headed in this wk's podcast: https://t.co/KpCShmDZqu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clean ingredients and #plantbased proteins help fuel @pinnaclefoods growth: https://t.co/cgOicJmzjB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Mexico's sugar tax responsible for the closure of 30,000 mom and pop stores? https://t.co/wgltZFiz2O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If #kombucha is a bit much for you, drinking vinegar might be an easier option to swallow: https://t.co/6uvgUeLbmC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is it realistic to expect ppl to show receipts to prove they are part of a class action suit against a company? https://t.co/CW4sGRDRB3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New mustard from @ChupsItUp uses apple cider vinegar for more mellow taste. https://t.co/cdWE0bLAcx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ok. Wait for it. ... #vegan pork rinds from @snacklins. Whaaaat?! Showcased at @unionkitchendc meet the makers event. https://t.co/262VESi9EW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@elementshrub launches a ready to drink option further illustrating the rise of drinking vinegar and shrubs. https://t.co/u1EpMwTZ7n]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Designer blends of stevia are here https://t.co/zrEWB0C2RN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids' water brand AquaBall is now less ball-shaped: https://t.co/UC07KKQQAC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out how some retailers are blending brick-and-mortar with ecommerce to drive sales https://t.co/5mOHvlKJtC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#organic is not the niche product of the past, @GeneralMills' organic ambassador says https://t.co/dK4qvbDnen]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HPP #juice is hot, but crowded. Find out from @misfitjuicery where there is white space @ our free forum March 22 https://t.co/BP0MYDaU4L]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out how @Range_Me is like the common university application for food and beverage product placement at retail https://t.co/F9x3wGzlZM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Much-needed funding for #agriculture is on #organic industry's wish list for next Farm Bill https://t.co/agA0yQVuLz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Snackapade's SmashMallows are so hot that a 50-case display at Fred Meyer sold out in 3 days: https://t.co/499cPfD1Po]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Those who grow #GMO crops are not "the devil with horns," #farmer says as he shares their #sustainability benefits https://t.co/SuqwOZhRiS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[As the halfway mark nears for USDA to create national GMO disclosure @CampbellSoupCo's approach could be a blueprint https://t.co/F42O8678iX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@Target is stuck between a #grocery destination &amp; place where to buy food when you are there for something else https://t.co/C93pPdCcUW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CSPI: We @CSPI are known for highlighting the worst foods.  But here's a list we put together of ten of the best foods: https://t.co/5p…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoodNavigator: Pleasure without the guilt: seaweed bacon from @SeamoreFood @sodderland #FoodVision https://t.co/M2joZnaTfG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EWatsonWrites: In this David v Goliath trademark dispute between @uponafarm &amp; @AbbottGlobal David has pretty good odds, say experts htt…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No denying #protein is hot, especially #plantbased But what comes after powdered protein? Find out in this #podcast https://t.co/KpCShmVAP4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@pinnaclefoods predicts #mergers and acquisitions will be afoot and says it is ready to participate: https://t.co/cgOicJEaIb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To what extent is a drop in soda sales in Mexico actually related to the country's sugar tax? https://t.co/wgltZFA9Um]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tart and vinegary drinks rise in popularity as consumers turn sour on #sugar: https://t.co/6uvgUeLbmC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manufacturers are getting sweeter on stevia as #sugar reduction becomes a top consumer priority https://t.co/zrEWB0ks0f]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What should be required to certify a "class" in class action lawsuits? https://t.co/CW4sGRmgJv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The maker of AquaBall scores $3.6M to expand distribution https://t.co/UC07KL8rsa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baldor Specialty Foods makes it easier for consumers to find exotic ingredients and by doing so driving foot traffic https://t.co/5mOHvlt8C4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@GeneralMills spells out the business case for supporting transitioning @organic farmers: https://t.co/dK4qvblMmP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is the next 'it' beverage? Find out at our free online forum March 22 https://t.co/BP0MYCTiGb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Product discovery is a "messy process" -- find out how @Range_Me does it: https://t.co/F9x3wGQXom]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is on the #organic industry's wish list for the next Farm Bill? https://t.co/agA0yQVuLz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marshmallows arent just for hot cocoa &amp; campfires, now they're for snacking - a concept growing at "explosive" rate: https://t.co/499cPfD1Po]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there still meaningful growth in #glutenfree? https://t.co/cgOicJmzjB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#sugar taxes discourage soda sales in Mexico: https://t.co/wgltZFiz2O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is the difference between #kombucha and drinking vinegar? @LIVEBeverages chimes in: https://t.co/6uvgUetzY2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @FoodNavAsia: WATCH: Find out why probiotics, functional diary and natural colours are top growth drivers in APAC. https://t.co/9QEUH3iQ…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @frankyiannas: Another marketing label. 'Clean food' doesn't mean it's 'safe food.' Remember 'food w integrity?' https://t.co/jgZ9gDLO1h]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Are 'natural' claims legit if they are for products made with #GMOs? The Supreme Court could weigh in: https://t.co/CW4sGRmgJv]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not one day of one person's life has been added bc of implementation of #prop65 but we are stuck w/ it says James Coughlin says #GMASciForum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are living in a post factual world where fact &amp; science are not winning the day w food/beverage shoppers, says Randy Burt #GMASciForum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Demand for foods "free from" undesirable ingredients represents a $63B market that is growing 20% annually, says Randy Burt #GMASciForum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fresh &amp; local food &amp; beverage trend is growing 9% annually. That is 4 or 5x faster than industry as whole, says Randy Burt #GMASciForum]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CStoreNews_: #hotchocolate:this flower shaped marshmallow blooms in your hot chocolate. this is so awesome https://t.co/3oN9qzHlDX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#peanuts account for 25% of food allergies, but there are problems beyond peanuts: https://t.co/OnyLJ8xG9S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[While consumers what healthier food in general, they will trade health for indulgence when it comes to #chocolate https://t.co/sKNzLoF9h7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How @Hellmanns is helping #farmers move to #cagefree eggs https://t.co/7zL0hpXuek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How much lactose is in Lifeway's kefir is basis for lawsuit https://t.co/PEw7V0T8cN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Under Trump, nutrition policy will be like a swinging pendulum going to the far extreme of where it was under Obama https://t.co/hqPyXnbm3F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Could @FlowWater be the next Fiji or Evian? https://t.co/ZlAZe6kapX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Will FDA push back the deadline for the new Nutrition Facts label? https://t.co/gmFO5T3IFy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Has Whole Foods Market lost its mojo? https://t.co/IfMjYyJa3y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What is next for #glutenfree: https://t.co/mkXiHL4dXn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cutting funds for #foodstamps is short sided and could lead to higher long term health costs, suggests @RepMcGovern https://t.co/vBzSyqqfaQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grasshoppers have more #protein than crickets and are #kosher giving them an edge in race for protein from insects https://t.co/vScHSDbKbm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[According to @CDCgov the incidence of food #allergy is up 50% from 1997 to 2011 https://t.co/OnyLJ8xG9S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hippity-hop! Seasonal sales of #chocolate (like that #bunny in your basket) are keeping the category afloat https://t.co/sKNzLoWKFH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The high cost of switching to #cagefree #egg production https://t.co/7zL0hqf55S]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Small, local food &amp; beverage #startups could find distribution gains through community supported agriculture https://t.co/VKfUJfswAp #CSA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out what companies can do to boost struggling frozen food sales https://t.co/YUJehsV6xB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Partially hydrogenated fats linked to trans fats could soon be banned in Canada https://t.co/P83dLQCMqR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sen. Roberts says higher school lunch standards for lower sodium, more whole grains &amp; low-fat dairy are "egregious" https://t.co/VK7cDNp79l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@themapleguild thinks Americans  will love light colored #maple syrup. Do you? https://t.co/UgRAmIsCjd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The #blacklivesmatter movement isn't appropriate fodder for advertising campaigns, critics of @pepsi ad say https://t.co/PWZWjFj1C6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Snacks are most frequently targeted food in class action #lawsuits. Find out why in this wk's Soup-To-Nuts #podcast https://t.co/nx3ahszoEL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CEO of @WholeFoods refuses to participate in a "race to the bottom" https://t.co/IfMjYz0Ls8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DYK: Sesame seeds have 10x #calcium as cream cheese, more #protein than tofu and more iron than broccoli: https://t.co/80Ib6L7WVq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Grasshoppers offer a whopping 72% of #protein by dry weight https://t.co/vScHSDtl2U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@BEFOREBrands wants to head #allergies off at the pass: https://t.co/OnyLJ8Ph1q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Find out how #chocolate's status as a treat is actually holding back sales https://t.co/sKNzLoF9h7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What will it take to meet the rising demand for #cagefree #eggs? https://t.co/7zL0hpXuek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is there a safe level of #glyphosate https://t.co/k4jwJIHYLO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[More people are signing up for a #CSA to get their produce, and other staples, direct from farmers https://t.co/VKfUJfaVbP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The future is bleak for frozen foods according to @packaged_facts https://t.co/YUJehsV6xB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Health Canada takes aim at remaining partially hydrogenated fats in foods https://t.co/P83dLQCMqR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sen. Roberts says fewer kids eat school meals bc of higher nutrition standards for more fruit, veggies, whole grains https://t.co/VK7cDNp79l]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do consumers want a lighter colored #maple syrup? https://t.co/UgRAmIKdHN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why was @StacysPitaChips' women's movement marketing strategy successful &amp; @pepsi's protest-themed ad not? https://t.co/PWZWjF1qKy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Political efforts to rollback school nutrition standards would be laughable if not so tragic says @RepMcGovern https://t.co/vBzSyqHQzq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Class action #litigation against #food, #beverage cos is up 750% since 2008. Find out the targets in this #podcast https://t.co/nx3ahshNNd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Cstore channel enters period of growth thanks to healthy snacking trends https://t.co/nJM6bdUWto]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Activist investors pressure @WholeFoods to address chronic under performance https://t.co/IfMjYyJa3y]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No pressure but #innovation exec at @MDLZ says if you don't have a kick-ass product, you might as well go home now https://t.co/SljyCyfj2O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stereotypes that people on #foodstamps are lazy is a major hurdle holding back America's ability to feed the hungry https://t.co/vBzSyqqfaQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It would be an economic disaster and political disaster to get rid of undocumented workers in America says @MaxwellSU at #CFAFPC2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[#Crickets are not the only game in town for insect-based #protein. Grasshoppers also are full of potential: https://t.co/vScHSDbKbm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @megsharm: If we do not regulate based on sci, we subject food policy to the volatility of politics - Chuck Conner @FarmerCoop #CFAFPC20…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[An ag sector that does not embrace technology and science is not sustainable @FarmerCoop says at #CFAFPC2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@FarmerCoop compares yuck reaction of some to food sci to 3yo saying yuck to veggies. Cos must advance sci just like kids must eat veggies.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[California takes aim at #glyphosate   by potentially adding it to #Prop65 list https://t.co/VKfUJfswAp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CSPI: At #CFAFPC2017, @MarsGlobal talks of support for Nutrition Facts updates &amp; added sugars labeling, as well as sodium reduction eff…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Top elements ppl look @ on Nutrition Facts: calories, sugars, srvg size, total fat, sodium, carbs &amp; protein, says @ncl_tweets at #CFAFPC2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[21% of consumers buy food &amp; beverages bc they are labeled as #nonGMO, says @Danone's Caradec #CFAFPC2017]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @KathyM_PMA: @RepMcGovern: Hunger is a political condition. Issue is polarizing and shouldn't be. #CFAFPC2017]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>