<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Others went to war so that I didn't have to.   Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump protesters just rolled by. https://t.co/arP5EGKNZb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[11:11]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Though shalt not panic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @TheLOAWorld: The only energy you can attract is the energy you are in harmonious vibration with. Change your perception. Change your re…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hillary is going to bed?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @nationalpost: Air Canada bans flight crews from wearing poppies, then immediately regrets the decision https://t.co/0KFLvFbFPL]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone's night just got worse. https://t.co/DkGFlELhD8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today was the most amount of daylight we are going to see for months.   #hack]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When is last call tonight? #DST]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[There is going to be a new President in the United States on Tuesday.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @georgiastraight: #Burnaby's Michael Bublé puts career on hold after three-year-old son diagnosed with cancer https://t.co/ojKjQesvVd #c…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hard to believe that we are about to lose an hour of daylight this weekend. Do we have an hour to lose?   It's dark enough already.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mondinion: Congratulations @BenKielb, you are 68 on #MondREACA the Canada toplist of real estate agents. https://t.co/9m2vUdUP0x #MondR…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WhatTheFFacts: Louisiana is the prison capital of the world. 1 out of every 86 adults is in jail.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The baseball season ends tonight.  Isn't it a summer sport?   And isn't it November?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EdibleCanada: We all know a “Ben." Help support those working hard in the #hospitality industry! #BuyBenABeer @BCHospitality https://t.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beer league game tonight. Lost 4-2. We had a great start to the season.  Now on a skid. #Canucks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Is Movember still a thing?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's November.   Good luck to all this month.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @GlobalBC: Vancouver fire crews are battling 2nd alarm fire at 4838 Belmont Ave. in Point Grey. Neighbours say home is vacant.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wanted to have a 30 minute nap.   It turned into over 2 hours.   Woke up groggy. Then saw Wonder Woman and a dinosaur together.   #Halloween]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beer league hockey league update.  Had a game last night. 10pm start. Should have had 2 goals and 3 assists. Ended up with 0 points. L 4-1.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It feels like a Friday to me.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @globeandmail: Mulroney plans institute bearing his name at St. Francis Xavier University https://t.co/P8kIQ4aTye @GlobePolitics #cdnpoli]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MMorton980: Head of the Wallonia legislature Andre Antione says the free trade deal between Canada &amp; the EU can not be met by today's d…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watching the Canucks game in Punjabi.   It's kind of interesting. It's like being in a foreign country. #CBC #HNIC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fur protesters just wrapping up another protest.   Ridiculous.  And they are all wearing leather shoes. https://t.co/XtHPg3ut31]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big shout out to my mother.    She's celebrating the completion of 78 years of existence on this planet tomorrow.   I adore her. #KeepGoing]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beer league game update.   Played last night. We were down 4-1.   Climbed back to 4-3 but lost. I had a goal and a helper. #McDavid]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's 12:12 on 12/12.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The new https://t.co/oiQhFU8aqW is out.   Compliments are welcomed.   Insults...not so welcomed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wonder what people in Alberta, Sakatchewan, Manitoba, Ontario, Quebec, N.S., N.B.,  P.E.I., NFLD and Labrador think of our 'snow storm'.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Big snow, little snow.   Little snow, big snow.   #Snowgate]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @JillSlattery: Ok everyone needs to calm down. 20cm of snow is not a #snowpocalypse or #snowmageddon. This is what WINTER is. #rantover]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not a snowflake to be seen as of yet.   #BCStorm2016]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryInPics: Today marks the 75 anniversary of the attack on Pearl Harbor. A day that will live in infamy. #PearlHarbor https://t.co/…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Yukon has tremendous potential.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flew back from the Yukon tonight. The airport is so simple.  Went through Gate 1.  Flight left 15 minutes early. Great people at Air North!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WhatTheFFacts: Billionaire Warren Buffet still lives in the house he bought for $31,500 in 1958.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very excited to head to the Yukon tonight. Tomorrow I will be attending the swearing in of the new Premier @klondike_silver   #InGoodHands]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WhatTheFFacts: There's only 11 minutes of actual game play action in an average NFL game.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cool. https://t.co/Ra1nQaljSJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beer league game update.   We beat The Outlaws 4-2.   I had to hit the showers early with a game misconduct.   #Canadian  #OhWell]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Under 10 days until the launch of the new https://t.co/oiQhFU8aqW.   I'm half excited and half nervous.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Carrier: We are pleased to have reached a deal with President-elect Trump &amp; VP-elect Pence to keep close to 1,000 jobs in Indy. More de…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@Scorpio_F6: #Scorpio spread joy and laughter wherever they go." As a Scorpio I have to whole heartedly agree.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where I was this past weekend.   A winter wonderland. #BirkenheadLake https://t.co/NHIdilV2hO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beer league hockey game update. Quite the tilt last night. We won 6-2.  There was also 121 PIMs. Shout out to Nick for representing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's like hurricane winds out there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She's a windy one out there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MotivatedLiving: Stop running away from your problems because that only increases the distance from the solution. Make it right today,…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @MetroVancouver: Attention hikers: #GrouseGrind is closed for the season due to unstable weather &amp; hazardous conditions. Stay safe! @gro…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HistoryHit: #OnThisDay 1963: JFK Assasinated https://t.co/Ocplf4Lsh1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@Cowboycerrone: Hey @arielhelwani https://t.co/tkQtAvg39E". What did the other guy look like?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's it for daylight today?  Really? Now dark until tomorrow morning?   C'mon.   It's only 4:40pm. #harsh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Was flying in this thing earlier today.   Great ride. https://t.co/EzSpItGjSY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At Tsawwassen Mills mall. This place is huge.   I feel like I just walked 18 holes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@HuffPostCanada: Toronto luxury home sales soar almost 100% in a year https://t.co/G5CoN3QHYI https://t.co/HDvNmKSAWu" Ya.The ex YVR buyer.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WhatTheFFacts: An atom is about 99.999% empty space, making everything in the universe mostly nothing.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Currently getting reflexologized.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Correction:   It does NOT feel like spring out there.   If you don't like the weather wait 10 minutes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Feels like spring out there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Fact: Having at least one "lazy day" per week can reduce stress, high blood pressure and the chances of having a stroke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[B.C. real estate data show sharp decline in foreign investment after tax https://t.co/DZkW9AeHw4   Brutal news.  Harsh stats.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @bobproctorLIVE: It is important to understand your paradigms because I guarantee your paradigms are controlling the results you are get…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @CTVVancouver: Home sales in Vancouver dropped 5.6 per cent last year, prices slide. #VancouverRE https://t.co/JwYUgPqgxq https://t.co/H…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["@MlNDBLOWINGS: Sushi relieves stress."  So does prime rib medium rare  @TheKeg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[11:11. @mauroranallo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Yaletown salted sidewalk.  No ice.  No snow.  That's messed up. https://t.co/w0JlEINGnw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OK 2017.   Look out.   I'm serious.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heading to Big Feet for an hour and a half major league rub down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I actually noticed a real difference in the amount of daylight we got today.  Seems much longer than just 7 days ago. #RightDirection]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HealingMB: The body Heals when we Sleep - 10 Health Benefits #sleep #healing #health #mindfulness #wellness https://t.co/jg3laVLvFQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm having a hard time believing that it's December 30th, 2017.   I remember the millenium like it was yesterday.   Time is flying.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[En route to see @KaseyMicaela @Kendall_Titch and @J_Titchener.   Good times ahead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Reflecting on the death of George Michael I remember when the video for Freedom came out.   It had all the top models of the era #straight]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[George Michael was Greek.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @PMPDcat: Boxing Day does not mean it's time for fisticuffs in the parking lot at the mall. Let's look after each other and be courteous…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy Holidays y'all.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's Christmas Eve day.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The shortest day of the year is almost over. From here on in we gain a minute of daylight per day. This is a good thing for many. Me too!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very happy with my haircut. If you want the same magnificent results go see Nancy at Black to Blonde in Kits.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Currently getting my ears lowered.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beer League update. Playing later tonight. Same team where we tallied up between us 121 PIMs in a 39 minute game.  I'm prepared.  #tinfoil]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Beer League hockey update. Down 3 zip last night.   Ended up tying it up at 3.  Lost 4-3 with 1:20 to go. #FirstWorldProblems]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @steeletalks980: BC Coroners Service:  128 people died as a result of illicit drug use in November, an average of more than four a day.…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @globalnews: Oldest water on earth found in Timmins, Ont., by University of Toronto researchers https://t.co/NPS9DVnj18]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I feel like poutine right now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Impromptu hip hop freestyle session last night with musical guest @ShaiMate.   He's still got it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @VancouverSun: Warm spell coming to Metro Vancouver after wild winter weather https://t.co/ucJ5pZhk1F https://t.co/YNdxDXgn4j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Love it when people are hijacking someone else's Internet WiFi and then complain because it's slow.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @VancityBuzz: Pricey parking put through.. #Vancouver approves 400% rate increase for #WestEnd parking permits https://t.co/arCfZsF0wU h…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @HuffingtonPost: BREAKING: Appeals court rules against Trump; travel ban remains suspended https://t.co/7AdHEeocQL https://t.co/p7ZqXEZT…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me and my nephew Sam.   He's awesome. https://t.co/nptsVNIdRj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[BC storm.  #Yaletown #WhatStorm? #WhatsAllTheRuckusAbout? https://t.co/3xalR35kqp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @vancouvermetro: Vancouver to consider 350% street parking cost increase in West End https://t.co/rVAVyZtchY https://t.co/tl1PcKATzz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @gerrydee: 1. In my 1st hockey game for @stfxuniversity I had 4 points in a 4-3 win over UPEI. I was on the 4th line 2 months later &amp; cu…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A snow plow taking charge.  What a donkey. https://t.co/DkPtIqCXbQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The streets downtown seem fine.   Are they fine where you're at? https://t.co/Yryma5LLpB]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>