<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Showtime refutes Palin's claim that Cohen posed as disabled vet: Showtime says comedian Sacha Baron Cohen did not claim to be a disabled veteran to secure any interview subjects for his series "Who Is America," despite claims from former Alaska Governor… https://t.co/A4kXVniz3E https://t.co/NJ2rzJmgUH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[C/C++ SQL – Transaction Processing: C/C++ SQL – Transaction Processing at Conduent – What We Do What We DoWhat We Do What We Do What We Do Industries – Automotive, Aerospace and Defense – Banking and Capital Markets – Communications and Media –… https://t.co/EVO5eJPadA https://t.co/7Yxmdhkdmr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Business Systems Analyst – GRS – Strong SQL: Job Description Technical Business Systems Analyst – GRS – Strong SQL Formulates and defines system’s scope and objectives based on both user needs and a good understanding of the application,… https://t.co/jZUUjkR3Q9 https://t.co/PoxRgxhh4R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MySQL Database Administrator: Requisition ID 2018-40977 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Secret Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description General Dynamics is looking for an experienced MySQL Database… https://t.co/Q7rqtw283M https://t.co/rtwM2DMB7e]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Developer, https://t.co/qZglOL1FCo, Visual Studio, SSIS, SQL Server: Lead Developer, *******, Visual Studio, SSIS, SQL Server ‘ Provides application software development services or technical support in situations of moderate complexity. May also be… https://t.co/hNzbKgvgWN https://t.co/GFdi1REAu7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Taylor Swift 'third wheel' in proposal: Their "Love Story" started at a Taylor Swift concert so it just made sense that they would get engaged there. https://t.co/66639t2bFY https://t.co/k8KfgJzS6i]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ETL Data Warehouse Developer (MS BI, MS SQL, SSIS): Job Description The successful candidate will be a part of the team that is responsible for Enterprise Business Intelligence. This position requires that the candidate understands, uses and applies… https://t.co/ARggNPnVOk https://t.co/C5BsIOB4lK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: SQL Developer Ref No.: 18-27433 Location: Jersey City, New Jersey 5-9 years exp.Reviewing query performance and optimizing code. Writing queries used for front-end applications (websites, desktop applications, or cloud apps) Designing and… https://t.co/W47dK6DhW0 https://t.co/SCqmIDEuJu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Equine-assisted therapy works. Why isn't it used more? https://t.co/Rs9mhv3hOr https://t.co/yvgDJQkE6p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Database Developer III: S &amp; P Global – SQL Database Developer III Job in Charlottesville, VAplay S &amp; P Global Careers – – – – – – – Careers Home &gt; – Job Details SQL Database Developer III JobDescription : Role: SQL Database Developer III Location:… https://t.co/sWh1uNxWF7 https://t.co/jFgVWaKHuJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Specialist Developer NET, C#, SQL Server Exchange Traded Funds: Sr. Specialist Developer – .NET, C#, SQL Server ‘ Exchange Traded Funds The Exchange Traded Funds Technology Team creates application-layer solutions to streamline and improve the… https://t.co/EU9rGyWBdz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server: ******/SQL Server Ref No.: 18-29062 Location: Lincolnshire, Illinois DEVELOPER-L3 Job Description(As per hiring manager) Key skills required for the job are: Java-J2EE-L3 (Mandatory) SQL Server-L3 As a Senior Developer, you are responsible… https://t.co/BfD6HCx6fN https://t.co/TjAPH1Rxpu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL BI Developer: SQL BI Developer Ref No.: 18-28074 Location: Redmond, Washington Role: SQL BI Developer Location: Redmond, WA Duration: Full Time Permanent Job Description Proficient in SQL BI Advanced knowledge on SSIS/ETL Packages and SSAS Knowledge… https://t.co/IICgKQpOuS https://t.co/KNYDpfbPCI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Performance Metrics Analytics SQL Architect/DBA: Performance Metrics &amp; Analytics SQL Architect/DBA in Hermitage, Tennessee, United States | Information Technology at Deloitte Toggle menu – Deloitte home – About Deloitte – – Location: United States… https://t.co/twOTBAArMC https://t.co/Zfk23kLKjZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Technology Senior Consultant – 3rd level support – VMware/Netapp/MS SQL: IT Technology Senior Consultant – 3rd level support – VMware/Netapp/MS SQL Job Close By continuing to use and navigate this website, you are agreeing to the use of cookies.… https://t.co/gxwtftmi0x https://t.co/OD0eWwbBVH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Conversion Developer: SQL Conversion Developer ======================== The SQL Developer converts client data into Tyler s courts and justice software in a way that meets our clients business needs. Location Plano, Texas Responsibilities * Design,… https://t.co/Lte4G1d34b https://t.co/9rW1YGzlV1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Specialist Developer — https://t.co/qZglOKK4dO, MVC, C#, SQL Server, SSRS: Specialist Developer ‘ *******, MVC, C#, SQL Server, SSRS ‘ Provides application software development services or technical support in more complex situations. May also be… https://t.co/RuPsX5ZBKC https://t.co/VrnkFxUkPs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[UK's May: Trump advised me to sue the EU: UK Prime Minister Theresa May says President Donald Trump advised her to sue the European Union -- rather than go into negotiations with them. https://t.co/jic1XlMdmy https://t.co/zzM4GsQnkO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Netanyahu: No ceasefire with Gaza if arson attacks continue: Israel's Prime Minister Benjamin Netanyahu has made clear that Israel will now consider arson attacks from Gaza in the same way that it considers launches of rockets and mortars. https://t.co/58z4vlkptW https://t.co/9Lu9lzKqX9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server Database Administrator: Requisition ID 2018-40213 # of Openings 1 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Secret Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description Responsible for the installation, configuration, administration and… https://t.co/rME3Hv3mrf https://t.co/PW6BSCNm6t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL/SSIS Developer: Search and apply for jobs at Piper Companies | Careers at Piper Companies Careers Search Jobs Connect With Us SQL/SSIS Developer Job Attributes Job Id: 19145Job Category: Software Applications &amp; ERPJob Location: Durham, NC… https://t.co/YRBqJ0YQdc https://t.co/lxu3IpCABm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer (For XML): Job TitleSQL Developer (For XML) – ID:31282 Duration12 Months Start DateASAP Job SkillsXML, SSIS, XML Stored Procedures, SQL Queries, Consumer Facing web sites LocationTorrance, CA Date Posted05/14/2018 FOR IMMEDIATE DETAILS… https://t.co/NrKS4j80L8 https://t.co/fxbT7WkHoI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Microsoft SQL DBA: Requisition ID 2018-42777 # of Openings 0 Job Function Information Technology Security Clearance Level Secret Full/Part Time Full Time Job Description GDIT is seeking a MS SQL DBA to support our newly awarded Army Analytics Group (AAG)… https://t.co/e15rLQmlJK https://t.co/vpzbXgM3IH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teradata and SQL Developer: Teradata and SQL Developer Ref No.: 18-29976 Location: Charlotte, North Carolina Position: Teradata and SQL Developer Job Location: Charlotte, NC/ Plano, TX Job Title: Full time permanent The ideal Candidate is an expert… https://t.co/9WwGlDTZpV https://t.co/DXmpelC1Mn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ODI/SQL Developer: ODI/SQL Developer Ref No.: 18-29151 Location: Seattle, Washington ODI/SQL developer Seattle, WA Contract – Bachelors Degree or equivalent work experience required- 4+ years of prior professional experience in software engineering… https://t.co/7jmaeLEaxz https://t.co/aImY7dr6ye]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. PHP Developer w/ NoSQL: SR. SOFTWARE ENGINEER – Permanent (No sponsorship today or in 3 years) AUSTIN, TX DIRECT HIRE – SALARY UP TO $125K – Will pay for relocation IMMEDIATE NEED for a Sr. LAMP Engineer to join our large enterprise client in Austin,… https://t.co/CBduGQRkDG https://t.co/vQlwQUxQ6o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Operations Data Analyst (SQL, Excel, large data sets): Job Description Job Title: Operations Data Analyst (SQL, Excel, large data sets) About the Opportunity: A client of ours is a leading integrated marketing solutions is looking for an Operations Data… https://t.co/MK0H7To452 https://t.co/u0IDmpFKqH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cops called on 11-year-old on his paper route: CNN's Don Lemon speaks to an 11-year-old boy who was stopped by police on the first day of his paper route in Ohio. https://t.co/PemfmgfLi7 https://t.co/yPWmzqN176]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Production Support Analyst with SQL Exp.: Production Support Analyst with SQL Exp. Ref No.: 18-28056 Location: Louisville, Kentucky Position: Production Support Analyst with SQL Exp. Location: Louisville, KY Rate: Market rate Duration: 12+Months Ability… https://t.co/HYr0yIfDPg https://t.co/xCAeCm9NS0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Data Analyst (Truckload Pricing): Job Description The Business and Data Analyst (Truckload Pricing) will be responsible for creating, supporting, and communicating unique truckload pricing analytical perspectives to empower decision makers… https://t.co/LjHMwTyQVk https://t.co/7ub4MTYBIb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Specialist Developer (T-SQL, PL/SQL, Database design, objects, tuning): Sr. Specialist Developer (T-SQL, PL/SQL, Database design, objects, tuning) ‘ Developer, Application Development and Tools:’ Responsible for designing custom applications and… https://t.co/Kr2rCpQ9og https://t.co/qGyXYA3Tyj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud SQL Server DBA/Developer: Cloud SQL Server DBA/Developer in Baltimore, Maryland, United States | Management Consulting at Deloitte Toggle menu – Deloitte home – About Deloitte – – Location: United States Available in locations and languages –… https://t.co/0AVwsU6n3I https://t.co/Q4Rm82pClf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MS SQL-DBA/ Developer/Analyst: MS SQL-DBA / Developer / Analyst About the Job Duration: Long term contract Location: Greenville, SC Pay rate: Hourly Job ID: GVLSQL Overview Datasoft Technologies, Inc. is seeking a MS SQL-DBA / Developer / Analyst for a… https://t.co/eF9WCXowgZ https://t.co/t5ZiXG1Bh2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Full-Stack Java Developer: Eagle Creek Careers Email: ******************** Phone : ************ – Home – Careers – U.S. Technology Centers – Employee Success Stories Careers – Search Current Openings – Update Your Profile – Create a Job Agent – Update… https://t.co/8FfR8Hh5nk https://t.co/nnHcDl0BUO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Systems Engineer/Analyst Microsoft SQL: Excellent opportunity with this industry leading, Fortune 500 Corporation in Dallas, TX. RESPONSIBILITIES: – Participate in development team for mobile and web applications – Provide end user support for a specific… https://t.co/hYbntOqhvo https://t.co/KQ7eeJfdyy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Conversion Developer: SQL Conversion Developer ======================== The SQL Developer converts client data into Tyler s courts and justice software in a way that meets our clients business needs. Location Plano, Texas Responsibilities * Design,… https://t.co/tMvI62xFWb https://t.co/LkvTB37jNo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst (SQL): Job Description – Data Analyst (SQL) Job LocationUS-VA-Reston Job ID10301 Job LocationUnited States CategoryInformation Technology/Software Overview American Institutes for Research (AIR) is a leading professional services firm with a… https://t.co/9ivqqIw9rM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Software Engineer: Lead Software Engineer with Cox Enterprises Skip Navigation – Careers Home – Early Career – Tech Careers – Join Our Talent Community – Blog – Manage Your Profile – Cox Enterprises – Cox Communications – Cox Automotive – Cox Media… https://t.co/Gj4LMiG6sS https://t.co/IrbvhiRVo2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cloud SQL Server DBA/Developer: Cloud SQL Server DBA/Developer in Baltimore, Maryland, United States | Management Consulting at Deloitte Toggle menu – Deloitte home – About Deloitte – – Location: United States Available in locations and languages –… https://t.co/SmWAwSIkYz https://t.co/zrzRtkdiQC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Justice Dept just drove a stake through the heart of Comcast's bid for Fox https://t.co/2gcWjfgcUc https://t.co/y2AqHgQ7WJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL/SQL Developer with .Net Exp: PL/SQL Developer with .Net Exp Ref No.: 18-28361 Location: Santa Clara, California Position: PL/SQL Developer with .Net Exp Location: Santa Clara, CA / Tempe, AZ Experience in coding, designing and testing new web software… https://t.co/d8DmAL30Cg https://t.co/hAd8uD53Em]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MySQL Database Administrator: General Dynamics is looking for an experienced MySQL Database Administrator who will be responsible for ensuring the performance, availability, and security of MySQL instances. You will also be responsible for orchestrating… https://t.co/qkGYa8CFZJ https://t.co/w9UFX4Ydxd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server Developer: SQL Server Developer Ref No.: 18-27483 Location: Jersey city, New Jersey Position : SQL Server Developer Duration : Full Time Permanent Location : Jersey City, NJ. Description: Reviewing query performance and optimizing code.… https://t.co/iOJDFiGsXx https://t.co/63xO16gS5t]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. SQL Developer: Sr. SQL Developer Sunrise, Florida – United States Job Start Date – 07/09/18, Posted Date – 06/27/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview Day to Day Responsibilities/typical day look like: Day To Day: * Actually looking at SQL code… https://t.co/k0q4PuHZ7o https://t.co/MWEcVergQC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Technical Business Systems Analyst GRS Strong SQL: Technical Business Systems Analyst’ ‘ GRS ‘ Strong SQL Formulates and defines system’s scope and objectives based on both user needs and a good understanding of the application, business, operational… https://t.co/1REmQMG3wi https://t.co/Z2IdeSn3EN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[500 zipline visitors sick in stomach illness outbreak: An investigation continues into what has caused hundreds of visitors to a Tennessee zipline destination to suddenly develop gastrointestinal illness. https://t.co/v94br0lWxl https://t.co/0OPmv5j6Cg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Data Analyst: The MSR Portfolio Management team is currently searching for a Technical Data Analyst with associate level experience with relational database structures, SQL, Visio, Excel and/or MS Access skills. Business Objects or Reporting tool &amp;… https://t.co/1jvr9WAsaQ https://t.co/b0x5MIj4wV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Avocados as big as your face https://t.co/Hvw3Rp5GG1 https://t.co/mpmJQQOqoh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oracle Forms and Reports Software Engineer: General Dynamics IT has an opening for an Oracle Senior Software Engineer in New Orleans; LA. Successful candidate must be able to obtain and retain a Department of Interior background investigation. Candidates… https://t.co/bZ64OhdeC9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pelosi: 'Jim Jordan had a duty to protect' Ohio State wrestlers: House Minority Leader Nancy Pelosi said Thursday that Rep. Jim Jordan had a "duty to protect" the Ohio State wrestlers who have alleged sexual abuse by the team's doctor. https://t.co/iEpsRSTqJr https://t.co/OVlicpLG1q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Report Writer/Report Developer SQL/SSRS: Report Writer/Report Developer – SQL/SSRS – FirstPRO 360 Toggle navigation Menu Close – Specialties – Accounting &amp; Finance – Information Technology – Life Sciences – Medical Device Sales – Project Services –… https://t.co/k49hGNHbjz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Systems Analyst SQL/Agile: Job ID ******* Date posted 03/20/2018 Category Information Technology Organization Centene Corporation Schedule Full-time Description: Position Purpose: Contribute to in the entire implementation process. – Contribute… https://t.co/KgLAGMcv3z]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL/SQL Developer: At least 4years of experience in Oracle PL/SQL development. At least 4 years of experience in software development life cycle. At least 4 years of experience in translating functional/non-functional requirements to system requirements.… https://t.co/X2f6zVyuaq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's spiritual adviser: Jesus was not an illegal immigrant: President Trump's spiritual adviser Paula White said, "people have taken biblical scriptures out of context" on immigration. https://t.co/CMTUXnpebH https://t.co/NqGHIYJEqI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sys Admin-Programmer/PowerShell and SQL: GDIT is currently seeking a Sys Admin / Programmer – Powershell &amp; SQL at Lackland AFB to support the IAFNOS contract, which supports the 690th Cyberspace Operations Group performing 24/7/365 Air Force Information… https://t.co/H65XkRdncF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MSSQL Database Administrator: Do you like to work and explore multiple, complex IT technologies? Are you a customer-focused team player, who would like to become part of a large global organization? Would you like to take an opportunity to drive your… https://t.co/yzhuaIItbw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lead Developer, https://t.co/qZglOKK4dO, Visual Studio, SSIS, SQL Server: For BNY Mellon Lead Developer, *******, Visual Studio, SSIS, SQL Server job – Information Technology – Multiple Skip to Main Content – – – – Toggle navigation – Who We Are – What… https://t.co/XY6aVVwktu https://t.co/MwmPORMgW8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL/SQL Oracle Developer | experience writing highly optimized functions, procedures, and complex queries: PL/SQL Oracle Developer | experience writing highly optimized functions, procedures, and complex queries – CareWorks TechCareWorks Tech CareWorks… https://t.co/vXCrcA6zJF https://t.co/VhK9S91rYY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump criticizes British PM Theresa May over Brexit deal: US President Donald Trump touched down in the United Kingdom Thursday and spoke with a major British tabloid where he differed with British Prime Minister Theresa May on her approach to Brexit. https://t.co/m72QcbSvFW https://t.co/NR05JzYgbd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Integration Engineer: Costa Mesa, CA Full-time $90k – $120k Posted Today YOU ARE A passionate SQL Engineer that loves solving problems! In this role you will be analyzing and integrating data from many sources with minimal documentation. We are… https://t.co/iiwJUhHZir https://t.co/jsjDnDZ69K]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server Admin/Developer: SQL Server Admin/Developer Ref No.: 18-28320 Location: Torrance, California Role: Sql Server DBA Location: Torrance, CA Duration: 12 + Months primary skill : DBA SQL secondary skill : Microsoft SQL Server Database Developer… https://t.co/7HtGO40Y4D https://t.co/Ag5nZ0BfJ0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Marlins cut ties with Papa John's https://t.co/1DqiUnNPaf https://t.co/kFq631KLvn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL-DBA-Architect: SQL Server DBA/Architect Location: Chantilly, VA Currently looking for a SQL Server DBA with Architect experience for great new role supporting the HRSA. Provides database support by verifying databases associated with network tools… https://t.co/s7wNlzYOaN https://t.co/DxVHvHkU8R]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL DBA: SQL DBA: 18-02378 Ref No.: 18-02378 Location: Mountain View, California Akraya is looking for a SQL DBA for one of our clients. If the job description below is a fit, please apply directly or call Dipak Badgujar at ************. If this position… https://t.co/CAEj9aMXxU https://t.co/vK7FS5Nca3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CNN pundit cries during racism debate: In a discussion about racism in the Republican party, panelist Angela Rye thanks former congressman David Jolly (R-FL) after he tells CNN's Don Lemon that he believes President Trump has racist tendencies. https://t.co/j1Ll6I9vD9 https://t.co/nmbPK1OZ2q]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL DBA: SQL DBA Dallas, Texas – United States Job Start Date – 07/03/18, Posted Date – 07/03/18 Primary SkillsSQL DBATax TermsC2COverview SQL DBA CO-OP Financial Long Term Contract Dallas, TX RESPONSIBILITIES: * Develop and maintain new and existing… https://t.co/mPnxYTd5aN https://t.co/6goaWbqMzV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior UI Developer Engineer Angular JS, Node.js, JavaScript CSS SQL Server: BDC is a clearance and settlement platform handling government securities mandated to replace GSCX as a service provider in this domain. BNYM clearance and settlement platform… https://t.co/Yk5vdHAbRm https://t.co/SKVPeaxnfT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Backlash: Forbes dubs Kylie Jenner 'self-made': You know it's something when a dictionary feels the need to weigh in. https://t.co/IpFysOxXof https://t.co/FEpKlaKXVz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Members of the alliance 'stepped up today like they have never stepped up before,' the President says https://t.co/L6eVYS489K https://t.co/9Cfe4r9prI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Business Intelligence- ETL / SQL Developer II: Business Intelligence- ETL / SQL Developer II at PATTERSON COMPANIES Skip Navigation – Corporate Site – Company Overview – News and Events – Working at Patterson – Environmental Impact Sign In Search Jobs… https://t.co/KiMz8dK9PC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Power rankings after semifinals https://t.co/BvlJM39xwo https://t.co/VUKG5a4sHC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SSRS – SQL Server Reporting Services: SSRS – SQL Server Reporting Services Ref No.: 18-27583 Location: columbia, Maryland Key skills required for the job are: SSRS – SQL Server Reporting Services-L3 (Mandatory) As a develoer, you are responsible for… https://t.co/Jpbl2ZFs6U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ODI/SQL Developer: ODI/SQL Developer Ref No.: 18-29151 Location: Seattle, Washington ODI/SQL developer Seattle, WA Contract – Bachelors Degree or equivalent work experience required- 4+ years of prior professional experience in software engineering… https://t.co/AkPSwqigTG]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Data Analyst Lead: Irvine Technology Corporation (ITC) is a leading provider of technology and staffing solutions for IT, Security, Engineering, and Interactive Design disciplines servicing startups to enterprise clients, nationally. We pride ourselves… https://t.co/0lnLvdcToL https://t.co/za6KuetvAR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boosler: A 'joke' is no excuse for offensive behavior https://t.co/QzdQoa8Sx4 https://t.co/ZNQc9YCts8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Informatica and SQL Server Developer: *Primary Skills: Informatica, SQL Server Developer, CRM Expertise, SSIS Duration: 6 Months Contract to Hire Contract Type: W2 Only* Job Description: Informatica and SQL Server Developer – The Informatica and SQL… https://t.co/DvM1vd8fRD https://t.co/wUHtTcd79r]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[JAVA – MySQL Developer: JAVA – MySQL Developer Ref No.: 18-28163 Location: Columbus, Ohio Foundation : MySQL, Assurance : Java Unit Testing Frameworks (Junit, *Unit, *Mock, Cactus, etc), Foundation : Java EE – EJB 3.0/JPA, Spring MVC https://t.co/bvPlP7y99t https://t.co/ylKiqoe3QR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Data Analyst: Job Description What you’ll be doing… – Work autonomously with Marketing, Finance, and IT to interpret business requirements to SQL code in order to anticipate, investigate, and resolve issues related to new and ongoing projects. –… https://t.co/covm8RpSle https://t.co/IMzOQT6lmU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[PL/SQL Developer: Careers Center | PL/SQL Developer Please Enable Cookies to Continue Please enable cookies in your browser to experience all the personalized features of this site, including the ability to apply for a job. Welcome page Returning… https://t.co/cSSbmq5cfv https://t.co/w5QdCtA4uq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[pl/Sql developer: pl/Sql developer Ref No.: 18-27893 Location: pennington, New Jersey Hello, Kindly review the below position and let me know if you are interested, send me an updated resume along with best time to contact. Title: PL/SQL Developer… https://t.co/zen51xww3k https://t.co/j2aC1Q0oeV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Database Developer – SQL – Los Angeles, CA – $140k: Irvine Technology Corporation (ITC) is a leading provider of technology and staffing solutions for IT, Security, Engineering, and Interactive Design disciplines servicing startups to enterprise… https://t.co/71ngR4EvuF https://t.co/qFUTjehPzj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Engineer (Full Stack – VertX, No-SQL, Cloud, React): *At American Express we place an enormous emphasis on users and usability. We sit at the intersection of commerce and experiences and are rare in our business model where we are one of only a few… https://t.co/B6XKty7sLO https://t.co/bPS7zmspFo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kim Jong Un snubbed Mike Pompeo, source says: CNN's Michelle Kosinski reports that Secretary of State Mike Pompeo's trip to North Korea went "as badly as it could have gone," according to a CNN source familiar with the discussions. https://t.co/Z0jAifZ8tw https://t.co/Ksf78NQOg5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Developer – SQL/Informatica: Responsible for the analysis, design, development, testing, and documentation of information management systems. Contribute in defining and maintaining development standards and development best practices, and will… https://t.co/flvlEOzsLh https://t.co/S07onbjU2U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL BI Developer | experience testing data treatment processes from data ingestion to output to reporting: SQL BI Developer | experience testing data treatment processes from data ingestion to output to reporting Columbus, OH, Dublin, OH 06-13-2018… https://t.co/yJttoq7Zvh https://t.co/hGXppQxevW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Java Developer — JavaScript, Angular, Kafka, SQL: Principal Java Developer ‘ JavaScript, Angular, Kafka, SQL ‘ The Principal Developer position in the AST Performance, Monitoring &amp; Availability Engineering Team will be responsible for… https://t.co/JwIN8v5GS6 https://t.co/XLiMpIg346]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pence: Trump has opportunity to evaluate Putin: Vice President Mike Pence tells CNN's Dana Bash that President Trump's upcoming meeting with Russian President Vladimir Putin is an opportunity to evaluate if Putin is a friend or foe. https://t.co/OTOjrk0QVY https://t.co/q0fGuLBTOt]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: SQL Developer Overland park, Kansas – United States Job Start Date – 06/27/18, Posted Date – 06/27/18 Primary SkillsSQLTax TermsC2COverviewThis is a 12+ months contract. Phone and Skype. Candidate must have atleast 1 real time project in… https://t.co/dVZzl2agbo]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Principal Java Developer JavaScript, Angular, Kafka, SQL: Principal Java Developer ‘ JavaScript, Angular, Kafka, SQL ‘ The Principal Developer position in the AST Performance, Monitoring &amp; Availability Engineering Team will be responsible for developing… https://t.co/hEvCO0cDeO https://t.co/p9YvPkdzT0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server DBA: SQL Server 2012 DBA Ref No.: 18-29328 Location: Loveland, Colorado SQL Server DBA: Bachelor’s degree required, preferably in computer science or a field closely related to computer science. Individuals without a degree may be considered… https://t.co/p4vVbMpqdZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Server: ******/SQL Server Ref No.: 18-29052 Location: Lincolnshire, Illinois LEAD-L1 Job Description(As per hiring manager) Key skills required for the job are: Java-J2EE-L3 (Mandatory) SQL Server-L3 As a Lead, you are responsible for managing a… https://t.co/ntEGQLJpJx https://t.co/HkVqrCMMqf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL / ETL Developer: SQL / ETL Developer – VanderHouwen 1-************ – About Us – Meet The Team – Join Our Team – Employers – Technology Job Placements – Accounting &amp; Finance Job Placements – Engineering Placements – Job Seekers – Technology Jobs –… https://t.co/oPZwtUjDs6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[SQL Developer: SQL Developer Miami, Florida – United States Job Start Date – 06/08/18, Posted Date – 07/03/18 Primary SkillsN/ATax TermsN/AOverview We have an opening down in Miami for an SSIS developer for one of our Fortune 500 clients. This candidate… https://t.co/VJ9mFfVuEB https://t.co/vR2EhdOlnW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[IT Technology Senior Consultant – 3rd level support – VMware/Netapp/MS SQL: IT Technology Senior Consultant – 3rd level support – VMware/Netapp/MS SQL Job Close By continuing to use and navigate this website, you are agreeing to the use of cookies.… https://t.co/zjrxRqDNyk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sr. Specialist Developer (T-SQL, PL/SQL, Database design, objects, tuning): Sr. Specialist Developer (T-SQL, PL/SQL, Database design, objects, tuning) ‘ Developer, Application Development and Tools:’ Responsible for designing custom applications and… https://t.co/EzKJPPCfWz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Programmer Analyst Entry Level: Location: Missouri Job type: Permanent Sector: Operations Category: Analyst Jobs The Boeing Company Business &amp; Supply Chain Systems (B &amp; SCS) Run organization is seeking a highly motivated and adaptable individual with… https://t.co/rOvr1oEIsX https://t.co/qRRgEBFBRZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ODI/SQL Developer: ODI/SQL Developer Ref No.: 18-29151 Location: Seattle, Washington ODI/SQL developer Seattle, WA Contract – Bachelors Degree or equivalent work experience required- 4+ years of prior professional experience in software engineering… https://t.co/duVRIDNx3F https://t.co/XE8A47a4Kl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Senior SQL Developer: Senior SQL Developer – (SSD) This details all the information about the job posting. Job Title Senior SQL Developer Organizational Unit Ashley Furniture Industries , Corporate , Information Technology Location Advance, NC 27006 US… https://t.co/J7Frq59OQd https://t.co/brQUg0AxCR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Photos: All the boys are out: All 12 boys and their soccer coach have been rescued from a flooded cave in northern Thailand, ending an 18-day ordeal. https://t.co/VdLhXANHJl https://t.co/2Ps1C9xneS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[pl/Sql developer: pl/Sql developer Ref No.: 18-27893 Location: pennington, New Jersey Hello, Kindly review the below position and let me know if you are interested, send me an updated resume along with best time to contact. Title: PL/SQL Developer… https://t.co/arPqeBcGOT]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>