<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Mars is suddenly more interesting https://t.co/pzvBGuie61 https://t.co/VXOLozfjXC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CNN anchor tears up honoring Bourdain: CNN's Kate Bolduan remembers Anthony Bourdain. https://t.co/2hrGjsFcyu https://t.co/iVDD3X3fYe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Golden State beats Cleveland to win 3rd title in 4 seasons https://t.co/QQCYINmL8H https://t.co/I3AAF4Ldgk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Missing Florida woman may be victim of alligator attack, authorities say: Authorities believe a woman who disappeared Friday morning while walking beside a lake died after being bitten by an alligator, according to the Florida Fishing and Wildlife… https://t.co/BCn3mEiUJp https://t.co/dVwQBjkigE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The story behind Berlin's forgotten places: "Germany's history is pretty unique," says Ciarán Fahey. "I don't think you have the same level of waste and destruction in other countries in Europe." https://t.co/RUc5y8rWpC https://t.co/CpMUAnhQds]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Famed conservative columnist says he has only a few weeks left to live https://t.co/b2h4DGW9t2 https://t.co/U7Q4fr52eZ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Listening to gut 'rumbles' may help to diagnose IBS: Based on a device designed to listen to termites, researchers create a belt that can diagnose IBS by analyzing the sounds made by the gut. https://t.co/iGNENQp255 https://t.co/8Im1ZwGCDI]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kim Kardashian shares joy of how she told Alice Johnson she would be freed: Six months ago, Kim Kardashian West first saw a story come across her Twitter feed about Alice Marie Johnson, a nonviolent drug offender serving a life sentence, and "felt this… https://t.co/ri7n5Td43G https://t.co/XcPBDMk1YH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[State trooper pulls over the cop who delivered him 26 years ago: A traffic stop led to a surprise reunion between a New Jersey state trooper and a retired police officer who delivered him as a baby. https://t.co/9H2WKeZN8k https://t.co/dNrtqpwTIV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Freed inmate: I never gave up hope: Alice Marie Johnson, the woman whose sentence President Donald Trump commuted, said she is "just so thankful" to Trump. Johnson was a first-time nonviolent drug offender, who had already served 21 years of a life… https://t.co/y1Noq5lFcY https://t.co/izC7H7OBn4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What a US-North Korea friendship would mean https://t.co/ZQL1OmXks8 https://t.co/qP1gcOaTVV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Papadopoulos' wife asks Trump for a pardon: The wife of Trump campaign aide George Papadopoulos, who pleaded guilty to lying about his Russian contacts, asked President Donald Trump to grant him a pardon in a CNN interview on Wednesday. https://t.co/8zMSXamaLr https://t.co/yGLg3SaxMP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Court: Woman's forced labor was material support of terrorists. She must leave US.: She was kidnapped by Salvadoran guerillas three decades ago, watched her husband be killed and forced to cook and clean for the militants. Now she can't stay in the US. https://t.co/IxF6VQg1ZF https://t.co/6TexWX82l0]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysis: Another day, another clemency. What Trump's pardons are really saying: Since being sworn in as President 16-plus months ago, Donald Trump has pardoned or commuted the sentences of six people, a pace that could pick up rapidly in the… https://t.co/N66KysTMIO https://t.co/DDQ8O7sise]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Van Jones: It's 'beyond insulting' for White House to lecture black people on patriotism: CNN's Van Jones on Tuesday responded to President Donald Trump's decision to disinvite the Super Bowl champion Philadelphia Eagles from the White House, saying he… https://t.co/5Elu7nP8P8 https://t.co/BYWI6X5ke4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One slogan made this company millions https://t.co/homhnt11vB https://t.co/h55mln5dul]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[WH aide who mocked McCain is out: Kelly Sadler, the White House communications aide who made a imprudent comment about Republican Sen. John McCain's health last month, no longer works in the administration, three sources with knowledge of the matter said… https://t.co/DcIuu8KBaj https://t.co/XeqZm3W8jK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Polls closed in eight states. Democrats want to take back the House, but they have reason to be worried. https://t.co/2zDduXZIes https://t.co/v1CzOdRSqK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cruz pauses for 18 seconds after question: Sen. Ted Cruz (R-TX) was speechless for 18 seconds before sidestepping a question from a reporter about whether Trump can pardon himself. https://t.co/kcxueLe1rb https://t.co/y6JfbjsTDB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David Koch steps down due to health: Republican megadonor and billionaire David Koch is stepping down from his role at Koch Industries and other organizations due to declining health, his brother, Charles, announced on Tuesday. https://t.co/4BFhLfC0in https://t.co/lh24YOBuVK]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: My only crime was being a black man: In recent weeks, Americans have read headline after headline chronicling near daily accounts of racism -- from a public figure's racist tweet toward a former Obama administration official to the profiling of… https://t.co/ACF9Z9aQYJ https://t.co/RXWVLhDS0N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sara Gilbert reacts to 'Roseanne': Actress Sara Gilbert, who played Darlene Conner in 'Roseanne,' said she stood by the network's decision. https://t.co/NjQXA1kZvZ https://t.co/VRS5DgPQeD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sea level rise is pushing them to higher ground: Despite the apocalyptic drumbeat from climate scientists, most Americans remain skeptical that climate change is the "most urgent threat facing our entire species," as actor Leonardo DiCaprio argues.… https://t.co/8xM5qq3XIi https://t.co/PmNKtnpkUj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Supreme Court's 7-2 ruling is not the wide-ranging decision on religious liberty some expected: The Supreme Court ruled narrowly in favor of a Colorado baker who refused to bake a cake to celebrate the marriage of a same sex couple because of a… https://t.co/HZwZ8FRnRM https://t.co/T9erIB7kJO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Eat like Bourdain in Hong Kong https://t.co/3rrqYP9ptI https://t.co/A7kU4N2h2J]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Corker says GOP senators are working on plan to 'push back' on Trump policy: Sen. Bob Corker said Saturday that he is working with other Senate Republicans on an effort to "push back" on President Donald Trump's use of authority "in ways never intended… https://t.co/d8lfmU8GEG https://t.co/yp5TEYuqQq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whale dies after swallowing 17 lbs of plastic: A pilot whale died in Thailand after swallowing more than 80 plastic bags. https://t.co/zG1fHRpCJa https://t.co/GY4ngIhZV5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US customs seizes Ohio family's life savings at airport: Members of an immigrant family in Ohio say US Customs and Border Protection seized $58,100 of their life savings. Now they want it back. https://t.co/KRWlHxS7jt https://t.co/MpDui8EAgs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: Germaine Greer's dangerous ideas about rape: For someone who's spent most of her life advocating for other people, Germaine Greer appears to have very little interest in other people's feelings. https://t.co/stqWjZhCGg https://t.co/Wg8OVmIJ4F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US car tariffs: Which countries have the most to lose? https://t.co/VrAhekA4rH https://t.co/zz6krh5Ucf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michael Avenatti's firm was forced into bankruptcy by a minor debt. The timing let him avoid being questioned in an $18 million arbitration dispute.: Even before he became famous as the fast-talking, trash-talking, in-your-face attorney representing… https://t.co/27TLJL5Lge https://t.co/hpbq5zQWO5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Americans left waiting and wondering as new hurricane season starts: Sitting outside his one-room home, Miguel Angel Vera Gonzalez admits he may get old, but the view does not. https://t.co/YNzpoFF7aD https://t.co/HjONvzMyOq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[EPA paid $1,560 for 12 fountain pens, emails show: A close aide to Scott Pruitt last year ordered a set of 12 fountain pens that cost the Environmental Protection Agency $1,560, according to agency documents. https://t.co/O3FcoxlVvw https://t.co/LAvhRBFbw1]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Golden State star Stephen Curry defies critics https://t.co/ZXoRrtdvhy https://t.co/W6mOQPp2c2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[See rockfall threaten church: Watch the moment a stunning rockfall consumes a church in a dust cloud in northern Italy. https://t.co/vs9tMrsv81 https://t.co/vRl9i65lhf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Samsonite CEO quits after short seller allegations https://t.co/Zes6DBdWfc https://t.co/duHgyKvEIq]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How Trump has weakened America https://t.co/O7VdBdgj9x https://t.co/DrURSrhHa9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[To be herself, she needs to change her body. But first comes the battle with insurers: Jasmine Glenn's friends remember late-night phone calls from her, sobbing and saying she was ready to kill herself, knife in hand. https://t.co/JJHSh1rUcM https://t.co/6jBtkhRSYb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Officer to beachgoer: 'You're about to get dropped': New body camera video shows what police in Wildwood, New Jersey, say happened before an officer tackled and punched a woman at the beach. https://t.co/jGHG3FRJEC https://t.co/VKfJZO7j6V]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysis: How Giuliani and Trump win: He is ridiculed as ridiculous. He is attacked as around the bend. He is maligned as morally bereft in his unwavering defense of his old friend and client, President Donald Trump. https://t.co/0WfyTjsVWo https://t.co/erytmhFoTV]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forget selfies -- you need a drone pilot https://t.co/EDj3maelyM https://t.co/SWEg1T34ro]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tom Arnold says he knew 'Roseanne' reboot 'would not end well': Tom Arnold, actor and ex-husband of Roseanne Barr, said Wednesday he was not surprised by the cancellation of ABC's hit sitcom "Roseanne" after the show's star went on a racist Twitter rant. https://t.co/87hsXccL0x https://t.co/NFIr4gCzI4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Grey's Anatomy' actor: 'Whites Only' spaces exist: For a few hours on Tuesday, thousands of Americans will suffer. They will be without their morning jolt, afternoon pick-me-up and end of day treat from corporate giant Starbucks coffee. People around… https://t.co/sTbvvtvXQz https://t.co/76rb1Tkuv5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why journalist's death was faked -- and why he couldn't tell his wife: A Russian journalist and Kremlin critic, reported to have been shot dead in Ukraine, has appeared alive at a news conference. https://t.co/P1qGCMHu0q https://t.co/wUd0CXevQg]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Televangelist: God says I need a $54M jet: Televangelist Jesse Duplantis told his congregation he needs roughly $54 million for a private jet. https://t.co/beajzcseP0 https://t.co/Y56GnW691I]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bolton adds two loyalists to his team: National security adviser John Bolton has added two loyalists to the National Security Council, according to a source familiar with the hires.  https://t.co/6UlcJaMzKb https://t.co/qCvwjOhjfd]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fewer babies were born in Brazil due to the Zika outbreak: An increase in birth defects associated with a 2015-2016 epidemic of Zika virus in Brazil caused widespread concern, fear and in some cases hysteria throughout the Americas. Now, research… https://t.co/olY1F0oqVF https://t.co/9motsBZ4fE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fareed Zakaria: Trump desperate for North Korea summit: CNN's Fareed Zakaria tells Anderson Cooper that President Donald Trump is almost too eager for a summit with North Korea. https://t.co/qunTy4Rr8J https://t.co/mXkBVLLoO4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's what's really happening with the 1,500 'missing' immigrant children: In the past few days there's been a flurry of emotion, and misinformation, regarding child immigrants in the United States. https://t.co/wRaj59q66j https://t.co/ro5hW7r8jH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[America Ferrera welcomes first child: Welcome to the world, Sebastian Piers Williams. https://t.co/Zw1GcrFsgR https://t.co/GsgsrUlJn3]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Father of child in Paris rescue was playing Pokemon Go: The father of a young child dramatically rescued from a Paris balcony was out playing Pokemon Go when the incident happened. https://t.co/D1hwGFOZHp https://t.co/yH5HEE03vS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elon Musk: 'Who do you think *owns* the press?' https://t.co/1OkKfkzOYb https://t.co/RTC8LSzuBH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flash floods ravage Maryland town: A state of emergency was declared in Howard County, as a massive storm drenched the Baltimore region, triggering flash floods in Ellicott City and leaving one person missing. https://t.co/KAiRWIWvmd https://t.co/cDrOIApItM]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Summer travel from A to Z -- in two minutes: No need to feel overwhelmed with the virtually infinite options for summer travel destinations and activities. https://t.co/eff8VwAYr8 https://t.co/1wHvqp2HCE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They weren't going to play the National Anthem, so fans started singing: Fans at a California softball tournament weren't happy when an official announced that the National Anthem would not be played before Friday's game, so they took matters into their… https://t.co/NNMoXvdawq https://t.co/Y0WiWNDoPn]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch 4-year-old take her first steps: This is the moment when 4-year-old Maya Tisdale, who suffers from cerebral palsy, takes her first steps. https://t.co/gL4VlhXoqu https://t.co/RjLPxcCjLc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Two shocking exits from Wimbledon: There was a double shock at Wimbledon, as Maria Sharapova and Petra Kvitova were upset by a qualifier and player who had lost her last five matches on grass, respectively. https://t.co/gGwmXUA27N https://t.co/ymXn4cqf7v]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Embattled FBI agent may ignore House subpoena: Embattled FBI agent Peter Strzok may not comply with a House Judiciary Committee subpoena requiring that he appear for a second round of questioning early next week, his lawyer told CNN's Chris Cuomo on… https://t.co/JkCpPOxCqv https://t.co/149imQqRwY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[She could be the first Muslim woman in Congress: Rashida Tlaib pulled her brown hair into a ponytail and changed into silver sneakers, a safari hat and a blue T-shirt that said "Rashida for Congress." https://t.co/YKDQiS5w6K https://t.co/OiX2DELWMU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Soccer team may need to learn to scuba dive to escape: The initial relief that greeted the dramatic discovery of the trapped Thai soccer team has given way to concern, as rescuers begin the difficult task of attempting to free the 12 boys and their coach… https://t.co/1EvmoQdJDb https://t.co/iMv7UPDSF7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What Justice Kennedy's retirement means for affirmative action: The Supreme Court was often called the "Kennedy Court" because Justice Anthony Kennedy cast the deciding vote on so many politically salient cases, especially on abortion and gay rights. https://t.co/Oi5WH3apon https://t.co/9VrYO5HgUk]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Thank Tony Soprano and Omar Little for today's bingeworthy TV: The roots of the current Golden Age of Television run deep, but its seeds can be traced to a pair of HBO dramas that left their mark in the 2000s, for shared reasons as well as two very… https://t.co/3pAbVlATcs https://t.co/dKUecHSazE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The reinvention of traditional thobes: Saudi Arabian fashion designer Hatem Al-akeel is making his name by giving the traditional Arab thobe a makeover. Called a dishdasha in Oman and Kuwait, and a kandoura in the United Arab Emirates, the thobe is a… https://t.co/GKhlVMRb0z https://t.co/9r3auuOmct]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[California passes strictest US online privacy law https://t.co/SXZDie7KPc https://t.co/8NO2miarj6]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[3-year-old girl stabbed at birthday party dies: A 3-year-old girl who was stabbed at a birthday party in a Boise, Idaho, apartment complex has died from her injuries, the Boise Police Department said. https://t.co/Den64CSoHR https://t.co/OSJnEHwmcF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Road collapse caught on camera: A 50m section of road in Sichuan province, China collapsed following days of heavy rain. https://t.co/B9wrSgcNuk https://t.co/3GM1KOOMG4]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[He saw kids sleeping on the floor, so he quit his job to build these: A simple project to help a family in need stopped Luke Mickelson in his tracks. https://t.co/8gi55IfsB2 https://t.co/chfQjRmNUl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Andy Murray withdraws from Wimbledon https://t.co/d9SOi3IcJP https://t.co/k2MY17vw8d]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How deaf and blind man experiences World Cup: A deaf and blind man experiences World Cup games through a special form of communication developed by a friend. https://t.co/uhuOt3SJNp https://t.co/UdVwDbkxnP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Elizabeth Warren sounds like a candidate: Our weekly roundup of the news, notes and chatter about the prospects for the next Democratic presidential race: https://t.co/WLSoMWbhZr https://t.co/GZpoxgBXIX]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Demonstrators march across the country to protest US immigration policies https://t.co/MZGK5rq3zE https://t.co/nJjyxx87IA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You're probably washing your hands all wrong, study says: Hand-washing seems pretty simple, but a recent study shows that 97% of the time, we're still doing it wrong -- which can lead to contamination of food and surfaces and result in foodborne illness. https://t.co/Tf5rQVJhNE https://t.co/itM4jTrS3U]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Actor on sexual assault: He held the power: Actor Terry Crews describes his alleged sexual assault by a Hollywood executive while speaking at a Senate hearing for the Sexual Assault Survivors' Bill of Rights. https://t.co/PQTXlD6BqM https://t.co/V2D3jlfVXf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Trump's pick for UN job voted down: The UN migration agency on Friday voted down Ken Isaacs, the Trump administration's candidate to lead the International Organization for Migration, a US official told CNN, leaving it without an American at the helm… https://t.co/3cXLVNEcUS https://t.co/qPlQXio7nD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Just be a kid, OK?': Inside children's immigration hearings: As each immigrant child took their seat in his courtroom for their hearing, Judge John M. Bryant started the same way. https://t.co/UwukGDraZR https://t.co/NUWh1jFoYW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why you shouldn't pay for Amazon Prime: If you were looking for proof that Amazon is leveraging its ever-expanding shipping and distribution capacity to clobber every last competitor and become the go-to seller of everything, here is some: The tech giant… https://t.co/5X8I1BQx7m https://t.co/Yx9I56BBZs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[One of them could replace Kennedy: Justice Anthony Kennedy, a longtime member of the Supreme Court and frequent swing vote, announced Wednesday that he will retire, giving President Donald Trump the chance to fill his seat. https://t.co/GNMIZSA5UP https://t.co/mU5CTsbuKx]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The royal family made even more money last year https://t.co/lK7ijETB58 https://t.co/1xsqJdfrHQ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What will happen with the 700 empty Toys 'R' Us https://t.co/l3511BBsAV https://t.co/J8reLeu9RP]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[New planets found forming around star: Researchers using the ALMA telescope in Chile have discovered three infant planets orbiting a young star in the constellation of Sagittarius. https://t.co/GY0jgKvQSK https://t.co/tHeXstwhQl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Japanese-American protesters weigh in on travel ban ruling: Outside Supreme Court on Tuesday, many protesters held signs that read "No Muslim Ban" and "We Will Not Be Banned" as they disputed the court's decision to uphold President Trump's travel ban. https://t.co/fTjs1z8avC https://t.co/iiaNp0iwXc]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Man berated in racist rant caught on video: Esteban Guzman was doing a landscaping job when a woman approached him and his mother to verbally attack them telling them to "go back to Mexico" and calling him a "rapist" and a "drug dealer." https://t.co/SQ5fxDBRfm https://t.co/CdBtC2ez8o]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A large streak of 'blue' was found on Mars: Mars is often referred to as the Red Planet, but pictures from one of NASA's orbiters showed what appeared to be a striking blue sand dune. https://t.co/qChgNo4dZK https://t.co/2fj05B5hgR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ex-Secret Service agent's warning: Over the weekend, Rep. Maxine Waters -- a vocal critic of President Donald Trump -- directly called for her supporters to publicly confront members of the Trump administration over a "zero-tolerance" policy that… https://t.co/NOvFaV32kJ https://t.co/UvTiIbLSFb]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Meet Walgreens: The Dow's newest member https://t.co/oT6hbM546n https://t.co/aqRg55X9vC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Sen. Booker: We need to reclaim our values: In an interview with CNN's Manu Raju, Sen. Cory Booker reacted to the Supreme Court's decision to uphold President Trump's travel ban, saying "if it was really about our safety, it would be a different list of… https://t.co/NssuJu8zxT https://t.co/pmEKk4DI0O]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[6 things to know before the opening bell https://t.co/wKGtrEFVSa https://t.co/z68PvaY7Zi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook caves in to pressure from conservatives: It has been just a few months since Mark Zuckerberg was dragged before Congress to answer for his company, but Facebook has been put in the hot seat again — and is falling for a faux scandal cooked up by… https://t.co/gZkhcLSBZC https://t.co/UeYtmp2tIA]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Minority leader pushes back after Rep. Waters calls on supporters to confront members of the Trump admin. https://t.co/jRuQOBaMaf https://t.co/22Jl38oe5b]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Firefighter shot and killed responding to call: A 17-year veteran of the fire department in Long Beach, California, was shot and killed Monday morning while responding to a call of an explosion at a senior residential facility, Long Beach Fire Chief Mike… https://t.co/Bb7dBY7QJ0 https://t.co/AZaaNdGu01]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prosecutors cancel Stormy Daniels interview, attorney says: Federal prosecutors have canceled their planned interview with Stormy Daniels Monday, according to Daniels' attorney. https://t.co/oB8Ldqi45T https://t.co/yBEczkeCq5]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pride celebrated around the world: See images from this weekend's Pride celebrations from around the world. https://t.co/E5KoHLN4kt https://t.co/3d3hFmhP5j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[9,000 barrels of bourbon fall in Kentucky distillery building collapse: Pardon bourbon lovers for crying in their beer after half of the barrels being aged at a Kentucky distillery building fell to the ground when part of the structure collapsed. https://t.co/uKBcH2DByN https://t.co/tcJaa0g9Xp]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fox News commentator apologizes for racist remark https://t.co/RNK9pEYWar https://t.co/Vd8BUeS81N]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Opinion: 'Zero tolerance' makes zero sense: Pregnant and fearing for her unborn's life, a woman fled a death threat from a drug cartel in Honduras and made her way to America, delivering her baby girl, Andrea, along the way. https://t.co/S6AjIV5KVW https://t.co/h2r6OCn0RR]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Almost 350 migrants stranded in the Mediterranean: Almost 350 migrants are stranded on two boats in the Mediterranean, including a Danish cargo ship, as a standoff between nearby European countries deepened on Sunday. https://t.co/nbG3rAYPVk https://t.co/yzFnXFqAHN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[US suicide rates have increased, CDC says: Suicide rates increased by 25% across the United States over nearly two decades ending in 2016, according to research published Thursday by the US Centers for Disease Control and Prevention. Twenty-five states… https://t.co/xYmMP2O2Xz https://t.co/wbpJuAp02j]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Artist Christo unveils major new work in London: On the opening day of 83-year-old artist Christo's new exhibition and large-scale installation in London he stands defiantly in front of his new floating artwork, constructed with 7,506 oil barrels in Hyde… https://t.co/dBDLxTeWQV https://t.co/PoohzzgEsj]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Rock star's widow: There were warning signs before his suicide: Now, nearly a year after Linkin Park lead singer Chester Bennington took his own life, it's clear to his widow that in the days before he died, there were warning signs. https://t.co/bMTBePgv4O https://t.co/4FfUsp6kW7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Analysis: A disastrous week for Trump: Fresh off one of the best -- or, at the very least, most consequential -- weeks of his presidency, Donald Trump just experienced one of his worst weeks in the White House. https://t.co/hO58N0JOuK https://t.co/FcQU7dwTWR]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>