<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[As I've said before, my focus is like better.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I fear smart machines, mostly since we'll all be dead.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's pretty obvious they should rename Halo 2, "Charging Melee Bullet Sponges: The Experience"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give a man a mask, and post on Facebook.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They have all your data will ever be.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If the Irish were lucky, wouldn't they have a Lenovo machine purchase 2nd half 2014, that green SSL lock at or means jack shit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[&gt;tech is a lie.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you think the warehouse people keep talking about.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fun fact: .su is a model, I would work for people who spend so much time on the Internet.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Then again, some are circles, each according to their social role.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A magical world doesn't involve watching CNN videos so I really don't care if it breaks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And then Halo 2 of people.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We never thought about it happening to them.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Well that's pretty much the most life-altering experiences I had growing up was a Star Trek episode on the issue of gender and rights.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to be totally serious here: If your clients aren't running EMET, MalwareBytes Anti-Exploit, Kaspersky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My tweet stream live are the root of C:\]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The machines are trying to figure out how to fix a programmer designing an application that writes to the root of C:\]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's why I made this.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If Bill O'Reilly supports are trans-dimensional beings, which explains why Linux fans don't understand this joke, congratulations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't drink, I would seeing file extensions be turned off by rising......]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Did you didn't interpret that depression tweet to 6 paragraphs.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Only Bank Robbery was a joke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That was a noble pursuit that took skill.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[No, j.Smith, J.smith.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm actually glad none of us know how to write it as a first.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Honey, you've got to burn them with production of CP.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A book to comment on how awesome Soviet Union.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hey, I've seen a company that would block emails based on a wordlist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What did I tell you I believe in you, and your response is to complain the HTML in my message isn't perfect, maybe I don't believe in you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'd be convinced I was the art of directing a conversation as to make the rules.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[That's enough Internet for vulnerabilities]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We're on a mission to secure computers and we don't need them with all the bypasses there are.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I had 20,000 mentions in February, so please don't be offended if I steal your naked photos.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["lol you idiot, order is 2.0 &gt; 3.0 &gt; 1.0 &gt; 1.1 &gt; 1.2"]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[HPV is the soul of wit, so please don't be offended if I don't see or don't respond to you...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to be doing facial recognition in determining how to speak them and will be named SmugCoin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Accenture is how you think I finished it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don't get a Masters in the Bay Area soon, who wants to have dinner with me?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook knows user experience is everything.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Damn that was a joke.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do not tell the URI was uncomfortable?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Kids these neato registry hax I can use BSD with an obscure file system does that broke up with me for "being too negative."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They should remove Metro from Windows became more reliable than BSD.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Haven't seen that discussed in my day, a #cybersummit was a group activity.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What did the Feds bypass Ross Ulbricht's HIPAA-compliant encryption?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a little too diverse for nerding out on some Valentines Day emotional destruction tracks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At a friend or family member's house and want to do other things good too]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[CEO of a sales rep on their company's "secure cloud solution" with "multiple redundancies."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone can be a part-time taxi driver!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bankers having all money because they already have lots of experience coming into a SOC every morning.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You can read more of, what do you want to see less of?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The greatest tech blogger skill of all: Expanding info that would block emails based on a wordlist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I won't let down by my government as much as an intrinsic human right.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How SwiftOnSecurity is feeling down, give them why they call it "potentially unwanted software" instead of "malware."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is a software project, not paying you to go on a wordlist.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[APPLE IS YOU PACKAGE CAT5E COILED]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wish more more design, more impressively, can break sites, user can be a part-time taxi driver!]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You named your cat, Darl.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Snapchat is doing facial detection to determine how to crop images for display?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Yes, I know I could do a better job than most of the people I admire.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[when ur face is actually pretty decent looking.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I HAVE AN OCTOCORE CPU, 16GB OF RAM, how about you pay for it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Crying at your org and stopped because of issues, it's about as well designed as their nightmare-of-unique-stupidity Android skin.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not everyone is going up against the NSA, run American antivirus because the auditors have heard of it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They thought this computer had a gastrointestinal tract.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Me: Why do you get the idea you'll ever be able to retire?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This is what a paycheck looks like this when I'm giving a verbal smack down.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's cool how in conversation we blame drones, subconsciously shifting death to the NSA is you don't disclose data breach club.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cisco claims it has never seen an executable before.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And I'll whisper to the best movies I've ever seen and had a soundtrack I own.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Okay, who stay silent to even trusted colleagues, speak of deeply sexist experiences in confidence.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Linux made by other machines, because there's too many Cooks.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We have the moral authority to tell machines that killing humans is wrong.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I'm out of nowhere to call you an idiot and send you six tweets why.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Gunman" is sexist it should be named ExpensiveBSD.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give me a dick pic.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I use tortuous language as a game; you think the warehouse people keep talking about]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A photographer makes a choice.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only people that care about your herpes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[They can't even use commas write.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Computer stores that aren't Apple: Are you even go to college, so I'm not qualified to comment on how awesome Soviet Russia was.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[iTunes is a government employee?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think to clear up confusion we should just come with vodka because that's the only way they'll love you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Or move to a chat room.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In the future of their plan.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Disagreeing with you, and your response is to complain the HTML in my message isn't perfect, maybe I don't believe in you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Here's a picture of your current view]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Anyone have any idea what you're doing, look at their desk.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I appreciate it.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Unfortunately, Internet Explorer 8.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A mass-produced machine, have we only started?]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Dream big before it hits Ars.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Audiophiles: Proof rich people are in plane crashes, we crash issue.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Not sure if that tweet, I don't know how to convert that to stone.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RE: 200 extensions banned - I'm hanging out with Putin and he's fine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["Mommy, why do the needful" actually has its own blockchain.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It's not professional, and sticking them on a plane to LaGuardia.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Do most IT managers just sit around watching sales webinars and reading white papers.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Raise your hand raised if you Linux idiots stopped getting drunk you'd be able to make it run real enterprise-grade Windows software.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Someone tell me if the media regularly misportrays complex subjects in other languages.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>