<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[The next time you hear a social media myth, question it.  Ask for the proof, and ask out loud.  Don Zarrella - Social Media Scientist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read a Review of Heaven is For Real  http://t.co/wgcqN9D6sH]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I accidentally forgot to graduate from college.  - Anne Lamott]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The dog was created especially for children. He is the God of frolic. - Henry Ward Beecher]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Money is the best deodorant. - Elizabeth Taylor]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Looking for great resources on Beer?  Check out our top 10... http://t.co/dgWpKZAmar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out These Awesome Nintendo Wall Graphics! http://t.co/lWsZcYnBEe]]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is simply the soul of a society as it passes from one generation to another. - Gilbert K. Chesterton]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[ROFL Offensive Business Cards - Everyone Needs a Stack of These! http://t.co/6v3hK1edu8]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Science fiction is not predictive; it is descriptive. - Ursula K. LeGuin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very Cool iPhone 4 Review  http://t.co/Gp792QwqA7]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Biography of Shelley Fabares  http://t.co/s8AHMtCb7p]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The fellow who rocks the boat is never the fellow at the oars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Carpenters  http://t.co/Wm0bVzxJJO]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Winners take time to relish their work, knowing that scaling the mountain is what makes the view from the top so exhilarating. Denis Waitley]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You think dogs will not be in heaven? I tell you, they will be there long before any of us - Robert Louis Stevenson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clarity trumps persuasion.  Dr. Flint McGlaughlin - Director MECLABS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gluten Free Recipes - Making a Gluten-Free Gravy  http://t.co/aEbpDqvyHu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[You don't buy a nice car and get rich you get rich and buy a nice car - Unknown]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ultimately, the only power to which man should aspire is that which he exercises over himself. - Elie Wiesel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So Who Is SpaceX?  http://t.co/9hgNkIVSpa]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the Hillbilly 10 Commandments ROFL - http://t.co/PLSwgoW79u]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome basketball t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the basketball lovers in your life!   http://t.co/tZgyRg8ATr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is not the man who has too little, but the man who craves more, that is poor.  Seneca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ahh Read About Loving Fine Wine  http://t.co/UH6AllDe5H]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The only place where success comes before work is in the dictionary. - Vidal Sassoon]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Web Marketing Experts Reveal Tips to Success  http://t.co/4Ci7H73cca]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[And in the end, the love we take will be equal to the love we make. - The Beatles]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So What Is A SERP exactly?  http://t.co/xNCbRLd0Xl]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Benefits of Going Green As A Business – Get Certified!  http://t.co/EMte6UU4Jw]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Future generations will be born free, equal and in debt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Foreigner  http://t.co/Ujp7fjp8vr]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Very cool Star Wars windshield sun reflector - may the force be with you!   http://t.co/BEFLfod4Y2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Frustrations of Youth Pitching  http://t.co/yG0yvhGlLy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Introduction to Douglas Adams  http://t.co/P1Ye5jugjT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Egotism is the Knack of seeing desirable qualities in yourself that others can't see.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Few people SUFFER from egotism. With most of them it's a PLEASURE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A shoe has so much more to offer than just to walk. - Christian Louboutin]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Baseball's future? Bigger and bigger, better and better! No question about it, it's the greatest game there is! - Ted Williams]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suitor: A guy who thinks he's throwing a girl a line when all the time he's being roped in.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[London Weight Loss Salon sign: "We value the pound."]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Home is where -- . You hang your head]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to the Everly Brothers  http://t.co/8FPJctWtES]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Face it tiger, you just hit the jackpot! - Mary Jane, Spider-Man.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Give a girl the right shoes, and she can conquer the world. - Marilyn Monroe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Teenagers do everything we did…]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A woman who doesn't wear perfume has no future. Coco Chanel]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I think Jennifer knows how to get pregnant. Leah Remini on rumors that she was trying to convert JLO to Scientology to help with fertility]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Oooh right, it's actually quite a funny story once you get past all the tragic elements and the over-riding sense of doom. - Duckman]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out this Flying Alarm Clock - COOL!  http://t.co/mAgmIg6mVz]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Silver Plated "Privates" Scratcher - For the Busy Executive http://t.co/mbpKkSNgme]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Asked a woman in an art store, "you don't consider this horrible thing art, do you" "No madam" replied the dealer, it's a mirror.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Cool History of Mustard  http://t.co/bOiDUgQN5F]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I've met many thinkers and many cats, but the wisdom of cats is infinitely superior. - Hippolyte Taine]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Leon, Mexico - Shoe Capital of the World!  http://t.co/dkaUBa9499]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love science fiction. - Pam Grier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When I play with my cat, who knows whether she is not amusing herself with me more than I with her. - Montaigne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Donovan  http://t.co/s7AtI2pImS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great Introduction to Aerosmith  http://t.co/NYLstfljo2]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read How to Use LinkedIn for Your Company   http://t.co/OXuGp0OnHS]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About GPS Technology and Fitness Watches  http://t.co/UcRg2j8ztm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Matrimony bonds are no good unless the interest keeps up.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Bread  http://t.co/bKumq2tHMh]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of the Impressions  http://t.co/Z37cA091ZB]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Instead of giving myself reasons why I can't, I give myself reasons why I can. - Unknown Author]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Fascinating history of Baseball Cards!  http://t.co/fRehDYwgOY]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The best augury of a man's success in his profession is that he thinks it the finest in the world. - George Eliot]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome fine wine t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the fine wine lovers in your life!   http://t.co/RbEDA8SGJu]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cheap Divorce Lawyers: Avoiding Exorbitant Legal Costs  http://t.co/1MzfrguMZm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I love science fiction. - Pam Grier]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[God gives us the ability, but rock 'n' roll was created by men.  - Little Richard]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Whoever said that money can't buy happiness, simply didn't know where to go shopping --&gt; Bo Derek]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Advanced Weight Scales and Body Monitoring – Keeping Track of your Body Weight  http://t.co/GXCqpdqkne]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I don't read other science fiction. I don't read any at all. - Jack Vance]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Who is Ten Years After classic Rock Group?  http://t.co/tBKLbnLxZE]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[So say we all. - Battlestar Galactica]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any manager who can't get along with a .400 hitter is crazy. - Joe McCarthy]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The roots of education are bitter, but the fruit is sweet. - Aristotle]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was twelve when I read my first scifi magazine - Philip K. Dick]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I wouldn't feel right wearing clothes covering my body.  Christina Aguilera]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Social Publishing Management with HootSuite  http://t.co/0rkGnWPXXC]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read About Adoption Part II - the Bulgaria Phase  http://t.co/sfJTPv88wF]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Hamstring Rehab  http://t.co/BzIUQSygFf]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If you want to find somebody and you want to be married and you want to have children, don't make it a rock star. - Stevie Nicks]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the Cool History of Mustard  http://t.co/8GmgD2g3qD]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Stay Ahead in eCommerce With Marketing Tips  http://t.co/LugnKZFl6E]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check Out these Tools for Finding Good Keywords  http://t.co/rZWg5grlXW]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any trip is short when you're in good company]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Where to find Great Gluten Free Recipes  http://t.co/MErcP2KtLJ]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Libby: How'd you get shot, anyway? Sawyer: With a gun.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In order to break the ice --  crack a smile]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[What fun is it being cool if you can't wear a sombrero? --&gt; Bill Watterson]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out these awesome fine wine t-shirts &amp; gear - get something for the wine lovers in your life!  http://t.co/lGePaHDuy9]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Choosing To Use Solar Power  http://t.co/7JOf21jjPm]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Learn About Peregrine Falcons: Lords of the Sky  http://t.co/3jWdHU3mdU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Education is a social process. Education is growth. Education is, not a preparation for life; education is life itself.  - John Dewey]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Read the History of Coors Beer  http://t.co/xAeSL2BDUU]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[These aren't the droids you're looking fore. - Obi-Wan, Star Wars]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Mama always said you could tell an awful lot about a person by the kind of shoes they wear. - Forrest Gump]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Check out the top 25 health insurance companies in the US!  http://t.co/q5Oitliesq]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>