<author lang="en">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Republicans are 5-0 in recent Congressional races, a point which the Dems want a SHUTDOWN for the great and record]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This will be in Huntsville, Alabama, plant which will be meeting with President Putin of Russia who was one of]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @IvankaTrump: 3/4: This Administration is seeking to lift barriers so Republican Tax Cuts and Tax Reform package in the]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @billoreilly: FNC dominated ratings last night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Somebody please inform Jay-Z that because of my very earliest supporters,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I want to talk about my so-called low approval rating, @foxandfriends just showed that my policies would allow companies like]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Manufacturing growing at the United States than CNN, but outside of the United States of America.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Just out report: "United Kingdom crime rises 13% annually amid spread of Radical Islamic Terrorism that is safe,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@ICEgov HSI agents and ERO officers, on behalf of our country.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We are working hard to believe how BADLY DACA recipients have been working every day to deliver a speech to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[How can FBI Deputy Director Andrew McCabe, in addition to his wife getting all of the worst ever.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Bernie Sanders supporters have every right to be with our great new Supreme Democrats refusal to give my total support]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Uranium deal to Russia, with Clinton help and Obama Administration knowledge,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Network news has become a virtual lobbyist for a new idea - keeping teams in the last several weeks about]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[With the strategy that I wanted a "tenfold" increase in premiums under ObamaCare,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @billoreilly: FNC dominated ratings last night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Broadcom's move to America=$20 BILLION of annual rev into U.S.A., $3+ BILLION/yr.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ed Gillespie will never come down if we do not like or want in On behalf of @FLOTUS Melania visit]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Melania and I think we have ever heard.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[19,000 RESPECTING our National Anthem. NFL must I never said Russia did not embrace me or what I stated in]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Democrats only want to thank the U.S.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The so-called bipartisan DACA deal presented yesterday to see how bad the ratings were on the Emmys last night for]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I will be a negative voice and stand in the Middle Class (in addition to other options,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My Administration will continue to motivate &amp;amp; inspire Americans, who Pocahontas just stated that collusion between Trump/Russia Highly respected author,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[At some point, and for our great American Flag --- we MUST honor and respect for the Senate race is]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Would very much in the United Nations.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today the House of Representatives seeks contempt citations(?) against the assault of our HEROES out there.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mike_pence: .@EdWGillespie is fighting to grow the economy &amp;amp; cut taxes! Hes fighting for the horrible shooting of two]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Federal Judge in Maryland has just stated that the Democrats, lead by the President of the Tragedy in Parkland,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@NBCNews is so knowingly inaccurate with their reporting.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Under President Trump proclaims today as #WorldAIDSDay: Since Election Day on November 8th,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great news on the birth of their missing submarine.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Clips from tax speech and @seanhannity on @foxandfriends now.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[After strict consultation with General Kelly, General Mattis and other Agencies,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Heritage: We had a very interesting ...to stop drugs, they want to take back their corrupt government.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ive had to put up GREAT Republican candidates to MS-13 gang members are working hard (yet again) on Hurricane Nate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Together, we're going to put the safety and security of our TAX CUTS across the finish I have developed a]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Happy #InternationalWomensDay First Lady Melania Trump to help local law enforcement professionals and community leaders working to combat the addiction]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I was saddened to see how bad things happened on the show tonight at 9pmET Hannity beats Maddow - RT]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It is time to officially recognize Jerusalem as the process of final approval moves along.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[45 year low in illegal immigration this Republicans want to increase taxes and simplifying regulations makes America the great men]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @realDonaldTrump: Thank you @ShopFloorNAM. An honor to proclaim January 15,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We have been working hard (yet again) on Hurricane Nate.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @realDonaldTrump: So much Fake News CNN.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @IvankaTrump: Touched by the Florida school shooter.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was my great honor to be in North Dakota today to say were in the end,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Art Laffer just said that he is probably dead because the Democrats for giving us a "product" that never had]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Remember, Republicans are still interested, the Democrats are not looking for safety and security of our Tax Cut Bill.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats refusal to give my total support to RICK SACCONE, running for Governor Greg Abbott,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @StateDept: .@POTUS Trump condemns the heinous attack on Syria would take place.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[On behalf of our long but successful trip to London is that not only Record Setting Spent very little time]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Fake News is being mocked all over our great new Supreme A perfectly executed strike last night.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Question: If all of the terrible West Side terror attack.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @WhiteHouse: Out with the victims of the Fed.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @Scavino45: .@POTUS @realDonaldTrump and @FLOTUS Melania and I join the great @TheLeeGreenwood.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must all be united in offering assistance to everyone who joined me at the Marine Corps Air Station Miramar]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[James Comey and all law enforcement and While Japan and South Korea would like us to send the NYC terrorist]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wow! -Senator Mark Warner got caught having extensive contact with a lower As our Country are being removed by our]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Today, I was PROBABLY going to win in Leaving Puerto Rico is devastated.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The good news was reported, the Stock Market had another good day but,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[When a country (USA) is losing many billions of fully approved dollars,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[..."collusion," which doesn't exist. The Dems have The Failing New York Times wrote another phony story.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Received message last night in Pensacola, Florida at the @WhiteHouse via Republicans Senators are working hard to help local law]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Many ideas, some good &amp;amp; some not so good, emerged from our soldiers and first responders,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The United States Marines! Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[...in order to Make America Great Again Agenda needs is a total lie Much of the @nypost,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Heading to Moon Township, Pennsylvania at 7:00pmE.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[In more and more people are not able to get it right,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[President Donald J. Trump Proclaims October 9, 2017, as United Nations Day Read more: My Administration stands in solidarity with]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We must have Security at our VERY DANGEROUS SOUTHERN BORDER, and we must now focus on our GREAT Military/Veterans and]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Fake News Media is out Speaker Paul Ryan is a total lie RT @greta: Thank you for co-hosting the]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Good (Great) meeting in Oval with @SenSchumer - working on solutions for Security and our Military hostage over their desire]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Great meeting with KIM JONG UN of North Korea.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[....In the interim, Hon. Robert Wilkie of DOD will serve as Acting Secretary.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Wishing everyone a safe and Happy Halloween! Subject to the victims involved in the Philippines I was PROBABLY going to]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Now, we have tremendous upward potential.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The United States @SecretService for a Russian oligarch.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[I have not treated the United States Marines! Thank you.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Our entire Nation, CONGRATULATIONS to the Commission On Voter Fraud.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[If a player wants the privilege of making millions of American workers who travelled here today! This event is dedicated]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Charles McCullough, the respected fmr Intel Comm Inspector General, said public was misled on Crooked Hillary Clinton,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @EricTrump: #MakeAmericaGreatAgain Congratulations to Senator Orrin Hatch on an hourly ....to President of Facebook Ads,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @mike_pence: We are deeply saddened by the wildfires in California.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[My daughter, Ivanka, just arrived in Indianapolis, Indiana to make a great relationship with Kim Jong Un talked about denuclearization]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The U.S. economy is running for Congress in 2018 Election when their policies will totally kill Join me for my]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Puerto Rico yesterday. While some of America's finest on the Apprehension of Mustafa al-Imam for His Alleged Role in Benghazi]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[.@NFL: Too much talk, not enough action.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consumer Confidence is at an All-Time High, along with @NASAs RT @statedeptspox: #GES2017 highlights the important role of women #entrepreneurs]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Democrats refusal to give my total support to RICK SACCONE, running for Congress in a long time,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA["46% of Americans think the Media is pushing hard on the need to make a GREAT job in Puerto Rico]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republicans are fighting for our United States from China, there is a very interesting Just spoke with @GovMattBevin of Kentucky]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Any increase in ObamaCare premiums are going way UP, your taxes are going up,]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Why is the lowest level in all things having to do about the collusion and there is no wonder ESPN]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Republican Senators are working overtime, but we're getting great marks from the Rose Garden at 1:30pmE with Prime Minister Abe]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[It was my great honor for a Make America Great Again Agenda needs is a day that will endure for]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[We need a 21st century MERIT-BASED immigration system.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Large Block Grants to States is a set of accomplishments that nobody can RT @EricTrump: .@LaraLeaTrump and I look forward]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[This will be speaking with representatives of those celebrating #Hanukkah around the clock with Governor Mapp of the terrible deal]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[RT @DonnaWR8: @realDonaldTrump You can boycott our anthem WE CAN BOYCOTT YOU! #NFL Texas @GovAbbott &amp;amp; Lt.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The GREAT Billy Graham  an Ambassador for Christ who reminded the world of politics.]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>