<author lang="es">
	<documents>
		<document><![CDATA[Pensando vivir en pareja…Haz este test para saber si estás preparado:  Dejar atrás tu casa para iniciar una nueva etapa de tu vida al...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Nueva York aumenta a 21 años la edad para comprar cigarrillos: Foto: Archivo “¿Me puede mostrar su documento?”: el vendedor de cigarr...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Medieval Kitchens Used a Specially Bred Dog to Turn Roasting Spits:  Before the era of "set it and forget it" countertop rotisserie o...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[La oposición hace exigencias a Nicolás Maduro para retornar al diálogo en Venezuela]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solicitan resolver caso local de la UDESA: SANTIAGO,- El presidente de la federación dominicana de uniones deportivas, inc., (Fedude)...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Hometown Heroes award aims to honor educators: Together with the Department of Education, the United Federation of Teachers and the C...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chirlane McCray discusses personal and political life in candid interview: In a candid new interview, First Lady Chirlane McCray admi...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cinq morts dans un attentat-suicide au nord du Nigeria: L'attentat survient au lendemain de la mise en place par le Nigeria et ses vo...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tech giant tells U.S. to quit secretly bugging its products: Cisco Systems Inc's chief executive officer has written a letter to U.S....]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boko Haram blame likely after car bomb on crowded Nigeria street: A suicide car bomber kills five people on a street of popular bars ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Irak: Atentados llevana la muerte a 16 personas, y secuestran candidato: Al menos 16 personas murieron en diversos atentados en Irak,...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[El Nikkei sube 0,36%, hasta 14.147,71 puntos: El índice Nikkei de la Bolsa de Tokio subió hoy en la apertura 51,12 puntos, un 0,36 po...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[MINUSMA condenó las muertes cauzadas por el Movimiento Nacional de Liberación: El jefe de la Misión de Estabilización de Naciones Uni...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[David Blatt felicitó al Maccabi Electra por haber ganado el título: El entrenador del Maccabi Electra Tel Aviv, David Blatt, se mostr...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Prisa recompra la Ser al fondo 3i por 42 millones y les pagará en cinco años: El fondo3i prepara su salida del capital de la Cadena S...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The Best Of The Dish This Weekend: 
First up, a little cavil at Ross today. The notion that Barack Obama’s foreign policy “stinks of ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA['Try to fear less': Cancer survivor chronicles year of treatment in video diary: Jennifer Glass can be defined in many ways: wife, st...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[La oposición hace exigencias a Nicolás Maduro para retornar al diálogo en Venezuela: Los representantes de la opositora Mesa de la Un...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Muere el piloto Jack Brabham: El anciano campeón del mundo de Fórmula 1 Jack Brabham ha fallecido a primera hora de este lunes en Aus...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Watch this 'Human Transformer' cause a happy frenzy: This street performer's costume definitely has more than meets the eye, and a gr...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Facebook reportedly building Snapchat rival called Slingshot: Mark Zuckerberg is personally supervising development of an "ephemeral ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Una 'fosa común' en los sótanos de la Complutense: 250 cadáveres donados a la ciencia se hacinan sin control ni higiene en la Faculta...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Romney: Commissioner should resign: He calls for the resignation of a police commissioner who used a racial slur to describe Obama.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[5 myths about China: Opinion: Is it the next great power or a political antique or an economic powder keg? Yes.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[The NSA, Cisco, And The Issue Of Interdiction: It’s been a hectic week of NSA news in light of Glenn Greenwald’s recently published b...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chinese Stocks Are Tumbling: After opening higher, Hong Kong's Hang Sent is now off 0.05%. The Shanghai composite is down 0.40%. Most...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Christie calls for more forceful foreign policy: (CNN) - New Jersey Gov. Chris Christie painted a bleak picture of America's standing...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Westeros vs Planet Earth: Who Has The Biggest Walls (And Animals)?:  This probably isn't the most important comparison you're going t...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[A Michael Jackson Hologram Performed at the Billboard Music Awards And It Was Uncomfortable:  Just when you might've started to enjoy...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Entre música, baile, alcohol y disparos sepultan restos de Monkey Black: Música, baile, alcohol y disparos salpicaron el cortejo fúne...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Professional Surfer Arrested for Attempted Murder:  A professional surfer and model is being held on a million dollar bail after she ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lance Armstrong Gets 'Cards Against Humanity' Card About His Testicle:  AWKWARD. Lance Armstrong tweeted this photo of a card he got ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cannes, verrückt wie nie: Nicht nur Schwarzenegger &amp; Hollandes Ex-Geliebte geben Gas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warum  denn nur  Fremdschämen?:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[La oposición hace exigencias a Nicolás Maduro para retornar al diálogo en Venezuela: Los representantes de la opositora Mesa de la Un...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Muere el piloto Jack Brabham: El anciano campeón del mundo de Fórmula 1 Jack Brabham ha fallecido a primera hora de este lunes en Aus...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Los secretos del rompecabezas que nos propone Google: El cubo de Rubik está de aniversario y Google lo celebra dedicándole un diverti...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boko Haram Strikes Chinese Company in Cameroon: Late Friday, Boko Haram Islamist insurgents reportedly attacked a Chinese-owned camp ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pro-Russian Forces Seize Police Headquarters in Luhansk, Ukraine: Pro-Russian forces are now in control of all major government build...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boko Haram: West Wakes Up, Media Still Asleep: For weeks, I have been wrestling with the question: Should America and the West take o...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Obama "Madder than Hell" Over VA, But Who Actually Has The Scars?: It seems fair to suggest Barack Obama's chief of staff Dennis McDo...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tigers Catcher Alex Avila Takes Foul Ball To The Junk:  Detroit Tigers catcher Alex Avila was probably, hopefully wearing a cup, but ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[7 Tips For Getting Your Foot in the Door at a Hot Tech Startup: Research shows that the top 25 highest paying companies for interns a...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Deadline’s Best Film Stories Of The Week: If you missed this week’s top film stories from Hollywood and Cannes, catch up now:
‘Godzil...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Media Update: `New Yorker’ Backs Off Pay-Gap Charge In Firing of `Times’ Editor Abramson: UPDATE, 5:57 PM: In round three of his cove...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[DealBook: AT&amp;T to Buy DirecTV for $48.5 Billion in Move to Expand Clout: Under the terms of the deal, AT&amp;T will pay about $95 a share...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South Korean President Vows to Disband Coast Guard Over Ferry Sinking: President Park Geun-hye of South Korea vowed on Monday to disb...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Pacers 107, Heat 96: Composed Pacers Muscle Past the Heat: The Pacers were the deeper, more composed and cohesive team, spreading out...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Killings Surge in North Bronx, Testing New Police Tactics: For the New York Police Department, the surge in violence presents an earl...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Day 1: Laredo, Tex.: Damien Cave and Todd Heisler will be blogging as they travel up an American highway. Their first post focuses on...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[La presidenta surcoreana pide perdón por la gestión del rescate del Sewol: "Me disculpo de todo corazón por el dolor de los que han s...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Envíe su pregunta al torero Javier Jiménez Fortes: El malagueño, una de las más firmes promesas del toreo, regresa mañana a Las Venta...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Una cita clave arruinada por el desafecto: Cañete es el tercer líder mejor valorado y Valenciano queda en penúltima posición. Leer]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[«Ocho apellidos vascos» y otras comedias que se reían «de lo que no debían»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Las diez citas más esperadas de la festivalitis veraniega]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Consejos para evitar caer en el fraude de los SMS Premium]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[«¿Cómo esconder un cadáver?»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Shriver, Kuehl spar over Westside subway route during debate: Candidates Bobby Shriver and Sheila Kuehl sparred Sunday over Kuehl's r...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Solicitan resolver caso local de la UDESA: SANTIAGO,- El presidente de la federación dominicana de uniones deportivas, inc., (Fedude)...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Voleibol Femenino RD al Mundial por séptima vez: LA ROMANA.- ¡Guión cumplido! República Dominicana avanzó invicto, sin perder un set,...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[El 76,3% de los suizos rechazan en referéndum elevar el salario mínimo: El 76,3 por ciento de los votantes suizos han rechazado este ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[El líder del PASOK muestra su satisfacción con los resultados en las elecciones locales: El líder del Movimiento Socialista Panheléni...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Park promete desmantelar la Guardia Costera por su mala respuesta al desastre del 'Sweol': La presidenta de Corea del Sur, Park Geun ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[River Plate vuelve a conquistar la liga argentina seis años después: River Plate se coronó campeón del fútbol argentino este domingo ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Don Meyer, among college basketball coaches with most wins, dies at 69:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Forgotten Congressional Cemetery seeks residents:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Gov. Christie gets do-over after stumble on Israel:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Flooding triggers more than 3,000 landslides across the Balkans:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Twisted up-skirt photo game prompts teacher lawsuit:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Boko Haram blame likely after car bomb on crowded Nigeria street: A suicide car bomber kills five people on a street of popular bars ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[South Korea's president apologizes for Sewol ferry disaster: South Korean President Park Geun-hye formally apologised on Monday for a...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Canciller García-Margallo conversó con su par de Trinidad y Tobago: El ministro español de Asuntos Exteriores y Cooperación, José Man...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Presidenta de Corea del Sur se disculpó por la mala gestión: La presidenta surcoreana, Park Geun-hye, pidió disculpas al país por la ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Suiza: Rechazaron aumento de salario mínimo: El 76,3 por ciento de los votantes suizos han rechazado  en referéndum elevar el salario...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lider de PASOK, satisfecho con elecciones locales: El líder del Movimiento Socialista Panhelénico (PASOK), Evangelos Venizelos, ha ex...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Tragedia en Colombia: al menos 30 niños mueren calcinados en un autobús: Al menos 30 niños y un adulto murieron calcinados al incendi...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Maduro: junio, mes de la "ofensiva revolucionaria": El presidente venezolano prefiere ocultar el fracaso del diálogo y vuelve con su ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AT&amp;T to buy DirecTV for $48.5bn: Analysts expect the companies to face a prolonged battle to convince regulators to allow further con...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[AstraZeneca set to reject ‘final’ Pfizer offer: US drugmaker says it will not make a hostile bid and would only proceed with the offe...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[“Quien diga que las europeas no influirán en autonómicas, miente”: El candidato de Compromís elegido en primarias afirma que sí hay a...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Una gasolinera que salva vidas]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ocho rutas en Valladolid de la mano de National Geographic]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Antonio Castillo-Olivares nos abre «Las puertas de Toledo»]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lista para el primer plano]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Las hijas de Estefanía, las nuevas estrellas del Principado]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Una gasolinera que salva vidas: Pacientemente, espera la llegada del autobús urbano. De repente, comienza a sentirse indispuesto. Una...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Ocho rutas en Valladolid de la mano de National Geographic: Carlos González ha elaborado unas guías con las mejores zonas verdes...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Antonio Castillo-Olivares nos abre «Las puertas de Toledo»: El escritor madrileño Antonio Castillo-Olivares Reixa ambienta la tercera...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Lista para el primer plano: Hay un lugar común repetido hasta el agotamiento que dice que a determinada edad una mujer debe elegir en...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Las hijas de Estefanía, las nuevas estrellas del Principado: Este fin de semana, el palacio del Principado de Mónaco ha sido el escen...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Cannes, verrückt wie nie: Nicht nur Schwarzenegger &amp; Hollandes Ex-Geliebte geben Gas.]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Warum  denn nur  Fremdschämen?:]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[OLIMPIADA NACIONAL- GIMNASIA FEMENIL-NIVEL FIG Y FIG MODIFICADO (18/05/14): DESCARGA + FOTOS GRATIS OLIMPIADA NACIONAL 2014 GIMNASIA ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Jornada para el olvido: Veracruz, Veracruz.- Una competencia marcada por los errores y las caídas, marcó la pérdida de medallas para ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Superan 400 registros en carrera del IPN: Ensenada, Baja California.- Gabriel Martínez ganó la carrera atlética “Once K” del Institut...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Karl Rove's attack on Hillary Clinton is crazy: Karl Rove is still regarded as some sort of genius of the Republican Party, except th...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Michael Jackson hologram performs at Billboard Music Awards: The King of Pop slayed them at the Billboard Music Awards Sunday night. ...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Chris Hadfield’s ‘Space Oddity’ copyright license expires: The out-of-this-world music video of Commander Chris Hadfield performing “...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[Citi Bike workers gear up to join TWU Local 100: Citi Bike might not be an option during the next bus and subway strike. TWU Local 10...]]></document>
		<document><![CDATA[‘Too Much Sun,’ theater review: Stage animals don’t come more magnetic than Linda Lavin. She’s a fierce star with the gift of grab. B...]]></document>
	</documents>
</author>